Hold on a second.
Nice. Nice.
Something for you.
What's this?
81 2 bucks.
Didn't Big Leon tell you? It's a thousand if you want me for the night.
What is this for?
Well, I'm making money now.
I'm paying you back for headshots, electric bills, pizza-- Love you, man.
Well, thanks, man. Now I can get my pony.
This is a little extra something for always being there for me.
Wow! I don't know what to say.
What do you say?
I don't know.
It's a bracelet.
Isn't it? It's engraved too. Check it out.
''To my best bud.''
Thanks, best bud.
Put it on!
Now?
It should be saved for a special occasion.
That's the beauty part. It goes with everything.
You put this on, you're good to go.
I've never been ''good to go,'' so why not try some jewelry, huh?
Oh, man!
You are so wearing that bracelet.
I so am.
Any idea what this will do for your sex life?
It might slow down at first but once I'm used to the weight, I'll be back on track.
This all looks good.
Great.
If I want to call for a job reference?
That's right there. The manager, Chandler Bing.
All right.
Let's see if you're as good in person. Make me a salad.
A salad? I could do something more complicated.
No, just the salad will be fine.
You got it.
Now, I want you to tell me what you're doing while you're doing it.
All right. Well, I'm tearing the lettuce.
Is it dirty?
Don't worry, I'll wash it.
Don't. I like it dirty.
It's your call.
So, what are you going to do next?
I thought I'd cut up the tomatoes.
Are they firm?
They're okay.
You sure they're not bad?
You sure they're not very, very bad?
No, they're okay.
You gonna slice them real nice?
I was gonna do them julienne.
I'm out of here.
Hello?
Rachel's not here. Can I take a message?
How do we spell Casey?
Is it like ''at the Bat'' or ''and the Sunshine Band''?
Hey, who's this Casey?
A guy she met at a movie.
What does he want with her?
Probably ''do a little dance.''
You know, ''make a little love.''
Well, pretty much ''get down tonight.''
I don't know. I don't--
I don't get it. Two months ago, Rachel and I were close.
Now I take messages from guys she meets at movies?
This Casey should be taking down my messages, you know?
Or Rachel and I should be together and we should get a message service.
Hang in there, it'll happen.
How do you know that?
Because she's your lobster.
She's going somewhere.
It's a known fact that lobsters fall in love and mate for life.
You know what? You can actually see old lobster couples walking around their tank holding claws, like....
You have to picture lobsters.
You feeling better?
I think the fifth shower got the interview off me.
Do you have other possibilities?
There is the possibility that I won't make rent.
I can lend you some money.
If I couldn't pay you back right away, I'd feel guilty and tense around you.
Why not borrow it from Mom and Dad?
You feel guilty and tense around them.
Might as well make money off of them.
The man's got a point.
What is that sparkly thing?
That thing?
Yeah, it's a little flashy.
No, no.
No, no. It's not flashy. Not for a Goodfella.
That is sharp! That must've cost you a few doubloons.
It's fun. It's like knowing one of the Gabor sisters.
Hi.
Hi, darling.
What's this?
Some of your old stuff.
Well, sweetie, we have a surprise for you.
We're turning your room into a gym.
Wow, that is a surprise!
Just one question. Why not Ross' room?
We talked about that but he had so many science trophies, plaques, merit badges.
We didn't wanna disturb them.
God forbid.
What's new? What can you tell us? How's your job?
My job? Well....
Did I mention I still don't have a boyfriend?
Oh well. I just assumed.
Oh, hi, Rachel!
Hi.
We're sorry to hear about your parents splitting up.
Well, they're just separated. You never know. We'll see.
I can't say we were surprised.
They've been unhappy since we've known them.
Especially after the incident in Hawaii.
What? What incident?
No, no. I must be thinking of someone else.
Maybe me.
Don't you have folding to do?
Fold, dear. You fold.
Want a refill?
I'm all right, thanks.
Give me a second. I want to get this right.
Eleven o'clock, totally hot babe checking you out.
That was really good. I think I'm ready for my penis now.
I know what you're thinking. Dave Thomas, founder of Wendy's.
I'm Gail.
Chandler.
I have to go. It was nice meeting you.
Excellent. He could have gotten me a VCR or golf clubs.
But he got me the ''woman repeller.''
The eyesore from the Liberace House of Crap.
It's not bad.
Easy for you to say.
You're not sporting a reject from the Mr. T Collection.
''I pity the fool that puts on my jewelry. I do.''
''I pity the fool that--'' Hi.
Hey, man. We were just doing some impressions.
Do your Marcel Marceau.
That's actually good.
Would you look at that guy?
How long have they been talking?
A couple minutes.
Try doubling that.
It's like, ''Back off, buddy. She's a waitress, not a geisha.''
I think she's okay.
Look at that. She pushes him away and he won't budge.
I'm gonna do something.
We'll get a condo on the mountain. Ski in, ski out. Great.
Excuse me? Are you Rachel?
What?
Ross Geller.
God, in your ad you said you were pretty, but wow!
What are you doing?
Oh, my God, is this the wrong day?
I don't believe it. If it works out, we'll have something to tell the kids.
You sure will.
I've gotta go.
Take care.
See you later. Nice meeting you.
You're welcome.
What?
I was saving you.
Saving me from a pleasant conversation with a man?
From where I was--
Ross, listen to me.
I am not yours to save.
But you are.
What?
You're my lobster.
Are you being the blind-date guy again?
No, you're my lobster.
Lobsters....
In the tank, when they're old...they get with the-- They walk around holding the claws.
In the tank!
With the holding and....
Pheebs, wanna help with the lobster thing?
Do the claws again.
Forget the lobsters, okay?
Let's talk-- What about us?
Ross, there is no ''us.'' Okay?
No, but--
No. Listen to me!
I fell for you and get clobbered.
You fall for me and I again get clobbered.
I'm tired of being clobbered, you know?
It's just not worth it.
Well, but--
No ''but,'' Ross.
We are never gonna happen, okay? Accept that.
''Except that'' what?
No. No.
Accept that.
Oh.
I gotta go.
Hey, man. Look, it's my best bud! How you doing?
You're getting good at that Marcel Marceau thing.
What do you say we play some ball? You and me?
Okay, that's my bad.
If you hated the bracelet, you should have just said so.
Doesn't the fact that I wore it say how much our friendship means to me?
But you insulted the bracelet and you made fun of me.
Well, that's the part where I'm a wank.
I hoped we wouldn't focus on that.
Oh, yeah? Well, focus on this.
Hard to argue with that.
Come on! I said I was sorry a hundred times.
I promise to never take it off my wrist.
If you want to stay in there and be mad you just stay in there.
You know what the--
I am here, on my knees...holding up these couch cushions as a symbol of my sorrow and regret.
Much like they did in biblical times.
You may haveth anger now....
You're gonna grab yourself again, aren't you?
You know, that Steffi Graf has quite a tush.
I'm just saying! Right there.
Hey, guys.
Hi, darling.
You didn't bring my grandson?
He's at Carol's and Susan's today.
A woman in my office is a lesbian.
I'm just saying.
Jack, look. There's that house paint commercial that cracks you up.
Where have you been?
Emotional hell.
Did they lend you the money?
I haven't asked them yet.
Come on, Monica, do it.
Hey, you guys.
Monica has some news.
Listen, I'm sorry I didn't tell you this before but I'm no longer at my job. I had to leave it.
Why?
Because they made me.
You were fired? What are you gonna do?
Judy, relax. This is our little ''har-Monica'' we're talking about.
We taught her well.
10 percent of your paycheck goes...?
In the bank.
So she dips into her savings. That's why it's there.
She's gonna be fine. Aren't you, sweetie?
In the bank.
If you need a little extra, you know where to find it.
Anything larger back there?
I can't believe it.
Would you stop already?
Get out of the bitter barn and play in the hay.
You're right. I should play in the hay.
I just dropped $400 to replace a bracelet I hated to begin with.
Bring on the hay.
Hey!
I've got something that'll make you happy.
Guess what Gunther found?
Now you have two!
Oh, you have two.
What am I gonna do?
Hey.
How come you have two?
This one's for you.
Get out!
No, I can't.
I know how much this means to you and it's about more than jewelry.
It's about you and me and that we're ''best buds.''
Is this friendship? I think so.
Check it out. We're bracelet buddies!
That's what they'll call us.
Here you go. Pay me back whenever you like.
You have dinosaur checks?
You get your money and you learn something.
What's wrong with that?
Nothing.
Hey, you're a cheap-osaurus!
I'm kidding. Thank you, I'm very grateful.
Hey, Mon, what is this?
My bathing suit from high school. I was a little bigger then.
That's what they use to cover Connecticut when it rains.
What's on this videotape?
I don't know. Put it in.
Over here, Jack. Okay.
Rachel's coming up the path.
Doesn't she look pretty? Jack? Can you get this?
Oh, my God.
What is with your nose?
They had to reduce it because of my deviated septum.
I was wrong. That's what they use to cover Connecticut.
This is us getting ready for prom.
We don't have to watch.
Yeah, we do.
Come on.
It's fun!
Get a shot of Monica.
-Where's Monica?
-Over here, Dad.
Wait. How do you zoom out?
There she is.
Some girl ate Monica!
Shut up. The camera adds ten pounds.
How many cameras are actually on you?
Oh, you look so great!
So do you! You look beautiful.
-Oops.
-What?
I got mayonnaise on you.
It's just the shoulder, not my dress.
Everybody, smile.
-Oh, Dad, turn it off!
-It is off.
-It is not! What's with the red light?
-It's the off light.
Right, Ross?
Looking good, Mr. Kotter.
-You look pretty tonight.
-Oh, thanks.
-What are you doing this summer?
-I'm gonna hang out, work on my music.
Is my hook unhooked? These things keep falling down.
Let me see. I don't know.
What are you gonna do...
The guys are here!
...this summer?
Work on your music?
Oh, my God, Roy Gublik!
You know, Roy saw Star Wars 31 7 times.
He made the paper.
Where's Chip? Why isn't he here yet?
He'll be here, okay? Take a chill pill.
There.
I just told Rachel that Roy touched my boob.
I can't go to my prom without a date. I can't. It's too late.
If you're not going, I don't want to go.
Oh, I'm gonna kick Chip's ass!
I have a wonderful idea.
You should take Rachel to the prom.
Doubtful.
Jack, give me that. Talk to your son.
All right, go on. This is heavy.
Your mother's right. Take her. You can wear my tux.
She won't go with me.
Of course she would. You're a college man.
-I don't know.
-Well, come on.
Don't you wanna find out?
I can't believe I can't go to the prom.
This is so harsh!
-Okay. Hold my board.
-Attaboy. Attaboy.
I think we've seen enough. Let's turn it off.
Well, I'm not gonna watch.
Come on, kid. Let's go.
-My! Are you handsome!
-Let's show them.
Just a sec, Dad.
Okay, be cool. Just be cool.
Okay, Dad.
Rachel, ready or not, here comes your knight in shining--
Oh, no!
Bye! Don't wait up.
Chip!
Oh, dear.
How do I turn this off?
-Press the button.
-Which one? Which button? Jack!
The button. The button!
I can't believe you did that.
Yeah, well....
See? He's her lobster.
Dance with him.
Mom, I'm hungry!
Dance with your father.
I may not know any flashdances but I'm no slouch on the dance floor.
-Oh, Jack.
-Oh, Judy!