Hey.
What you guys doing?
Monica's making us watch Old Yeller.
Why are you guys upset? It's Old Yeller. It's a happy movie.
What are you talking about?
Happy family gets a dog. Frontier fun!
Pheebs, what about the end?
When Yeller saves the family and everyone's happy?
That's not the end.
That's when my mother would shut off the TV and say, ''The end.''
What about when he has rabies?
He doesn't have rabies. He has babies.
That's what my mom said.
I don't think she'd want you to see what's about to happen.
Why? What's about to happen? I've never seen this part.
Hey, Travis, what you doing with that gun?
Oh, no.
No, Travis, put down the gun.
No, he's your buddy. He's your Yeller.
No! The end! The end!
Okay, what kind of a sick doggy snuff film is this?
Have you eaten? Richard and I just finished, and we have leftovers.
Chicken and potatoes.
What am I wearing?
Actually, nothing but rubber gloves.
One day, you'll really be naked and we won't come over.
That'd teach me a lesson.
I've got a leg, three breasts and a wing.
How do you find clothes that fit?
Hey, Monica? We got a question.
Yes, I see other women in the shower at the gym.
And no, I don't look.
No, not that one.
We have an extra ticket to the Knicks game.
Ross can't go, so it's between my friend Eric, who has breath issues and Dan, with the poking. ''Did you see that play?''
''You want more beer? Is that Spike Lee?''
Why don't you ask Richard?
Richard, if you had an extra ticket to the Knicks...and you had to choose between a friend who smells and one who bruises you, who would you pick?
Wow.
Being a Knicks fan myself I think you should take someone who's a huge Knicks fan.
Okay.
That's Eric.
Glad to be of help. Matches.
I meant, why don't you take Richard to the game?
What?
I don't know.
Come on!
He keeps his fingers to himself, and he's always minty fresh.
Richard's really nice. We just don't know him really well.
Plus, he's old...er than some people.
But younger than some buildings.
So he's a little older. Big deal.
He's important to me.
If you ask him, he might take you in his Jag.
How do we say yes and make it seem like it's not just to ride in the cool car?
Okay, this could be tough.
Monica?
We'll bring him, but only if he takes the Jaguar.
You almost had it.
No, no, you're fine. You're fine.
Hi, honey.
You are not gonna believe what happened!
We were on the floor, and he grabs the table and he pulls himself up!
He pulled himself up!
Standing man!
Sorry you missed it, but I taped it if you wanna see.
He already did it last week.
You can watch our tape if you want.
See, I don't believe this. I miss the first time of everything.
The first time he rolled over, the first time he crawled.
Has he spoken? Is he driving? Does he have a favorite liqueur?
He is getting closer on the talking thing.
He can't quite say ''mama,'' but once he said, ''Yemen.''
See, I don't know. I'm so sick of missing stuff.
I want him for more than a day. I want a weekend.
Listen. I feel--
That would be great.
Really? I had a whole speech prepared.
Shoot, that would've been fun.
Did you just see that?
Did you see? He just waved! He just waved!
He's never waved before!
Yes, he has. Very good.
Hey, what you got there?
Love Story, Brian's Song and Terms of Endearment.
All you need now is The Killing Fields and guacamole, and you've got a party!
I talked to my grandma about Old Yeller and she said my mom didn't show us the ends of sad movies to shield us from the pain and sadness.
You know, before she killed herself.
Where's Richard? Did you ditch him?
After we stole his lunch money and gave him a wedgie.
What's with you? He's parking.
Did you guys have fun?
Your boyfriend is so cool.
He let us drive his Jaguar. Joey for 1 2 blocks. Me for 1 5.
He must like you best.
And when he tipped the guy who showed us to our seats?
You never saw the money. Like this:
Hey, Chandler, thanks for showing us to our seats.
You're welcome. Hey, thanks for parking the car.
No problem.
Hey, Chandler--
I think they get it.
There's the man!
You're getting better.
I'm gonna keep this, by the way.
He kept my dollar.
Your first weekend without Ben.
We're going to colonial Williamsburg.
A woman I went to college with is the first female blacksmith there.
They're a little behind the times in colonial Williamsburg.
I better go before Mommy starts weeping.
We love you.
Bye, Mommy.
Bye.
Have a good time.
Ross? Look.
Joey, do you know we can see you from here?
How come Richard looks cooler with these?
You may want to light it and lose the spatula.
It's cute, trying to be like Richard.
Not like him, per se. Just not unlike him.
It's the artist formerly known as Chandler.
I'm just trying something here, you know?
Why didn't you grow a mustache?
We flipped for it.
I got the cigar, he got the mustache.
If we both grew them, we'd look like dorks.
You really sidestepped that land mine.
We gotta meet Richard downstairs.
You're meeting Richard?
Hockey.
Didn't he tell you?
He said he'd be with the guys. I didn't know that's you.
You hear that?
We're the guys!
That mustache reminds me of Aunt Sylvia.
Thank you!
Hi. We're visiting.
It's Ben and his dada.
Can you say ''dada''? I'm gonna tell your mommies you said it anyway.
No luck, huh?
A while ago, I got a ''se'' out of him which I thought might turn into ''secondary caregiver,'' but....
Would you hold him for a sec? I gotta take this off.
Sure. Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm holding Ben.
He's a baby, not a bomb.
Hold him like you'd hold a football.
This is how I would hold a football.
Here. Here. There we go.
Sorry, I'm not very good with babies. I haven't been around them.
I mean, since I was one.
It's all right. No big deal.
Really?
You'll feel different when it's our baby.
What?
You think about stuff like that?
Yeah.
Actually, I kind of think that we'll have two babies.
Two babies?
You know, a boy and a girl.
Hopefully, the girl will come first, so Ben won't feel competitive.
Then what's gonna happen?
We won't wanna raise kids in the city, so we'll move to Scarsdale.
It's far enough from our parents not to see them but close enough for them to babysit.
And yes, I know the taxes are a little higher than Nassau County but the school system's great.
Wow, that's great! Great!
Okay, you know what? I'm off my break now.
Here. You take this.
I'm gonna go pour these very nice people some coffee.
Look at that. I don't have a pot. Maybe I've got one at home.
Or in Scarsdale. Hey, is that a door?
Hey.
Hey, Pheebs. What's happening?
Murder, cancer, soccer teams eating each other in the Andes.
I was really just making small talk.
Well, I was just venting.
So you watched the movies?
What is happening to the world?
I mean, because E.T. leaves and Rocky loses. Charlotte dies.
Charlotte who?
With the web. The spider. She has babies and dies.
It's like, ''Welcome home from the hospital.'' Thud!
You wanna feel better?
Yeah.
Here. Watch this.
It's a Wonderful Life. I've heard of this.
You can't lose. It's there in the title.
Wonderfulness is baked in.
I thought so with The Pride of the Yankees.
I thought it was about Yankee pride, and the guy gets Lou Gehrig's disease.
The guy was Lou Gehrig. Didn't you kind of see it coming?
Watch that. It'll restore all your faith in humanity.
Hey, big guy. Game time.
Hey! Be right there!
There's a game?
I just got my Pik-Up Stiks back from the shop.
Bring your nerves of steel.
It's the basketball playoffs.
I appreciate this, but you don't have to hang out with them for me.
They have each other.
Oh, no, honey. Don't worry.
I like hanging out with them. They're not like my other friends.
They don't start sentences with, ''Guess who just died shoveling snow?''
All right, that's great. Then just go.
Go Knicks!
It's the college playoffs.
Then, go Vassar!
They're not in it.
Okay, then just go.
Okay.
Why does this bother me?
I'm not one of those people who wants to spend 24 hours a day together.
Sure.
He just doesn't have much free time. What do I do?
Does it matter? You'll ultimately die, divorce or blow your pet's head off.
Me too!
I got a question. Richard made plans with the guys--
Ross made plans for the century.
I'm gonna go read Cosmo. Maybe there's something helpful in it.
If not, I can learn how to do a bikini wax with Christmas candles.
What happened back there?
You tell me. One minute I'm holding Ben.
Then I have two kids and live in Scarsdale, complaining about taxes!
Well, I'm sorry. I think about stuff.
You're at work, assembling bones. Your mind wanders.
You planned ahead 20 years. We've dated for six weeks!
You never think about our future?
I think about whose apartment we'll sleep at and where we'll have dinner!
I do not think about our children's names!
You know what our children's names are gonna be?
No. I mean, I read a book, and there was a girl named Emily.
And I thought that might be good.
What was the book?
The Big Book of Children's Names.
Okay, Ross. Listen.
What we have is amazing.
But I do not want everything decided for me!
I spent my whole life like that. That's the reason I left Barry.
I like not knowing right now.
Sorry if that scares you, but if you want me, deal with that!
Okay, fine!
Thank you!
We're not done!
I didn't know that.
You're with a guy who won't stop planning his future with you.
He knows we'll be together.
If that scares you, tough! Deal with that.
I will!
Good, because I love you!
Oh, yeah? I love you too!
That's the first time we said it!
I'm gonna kiss you!
You better!
Thanks for the movie.
Did you like it?
Oh, yeah.
Was I happier when George destroyed the business or Donna Reed cried or when the pharmacist made his ear bleed?
I'll give you that, but wasn't the ending great?
I was too depressed to watch it. It should've been called:
It's a Sucky Life, and Just When You Think It Can't Suck Anymore, It Does!
Kick, save! And denied!
He gets it back. Pass to the middle, lines it up....
Yes! Could that shot be any prettier?
Man, you are incredible.
We had a table in college.
I didn't know they had foosball in the 1800s.
Nice mustache. When puberty hits, that thing will really kick in.
Not to sound too Florence Henderson, but dinner's ready.
One more point.
Score!
Now can we go?
That's why we don't let her play.
Is everything all right?
Don't be mad at him. It's our fault.
Sorry we're hogging his time.
He's just great to hang out with.
We were just talking about this.
He is so much cooler than our dads.
Our dads are okay and all, but Richard is just--
What are you kicking me for?
I'm trying to talk here.
You guys see me as a dad?
Oh, yeah!
No!
No.
You're clearly not familiar with our young persons' vernacular.
When we say ''dad,'' we mean ''buddy.''
We mean ''pal.''
No, seriously. Joey's my dad.
Monica's my dad.
I've even got some dads down at work.
That's fine.
Well, your other dad and I are gonna go have a romantic evening.
I'll just see you kids around.
Nighty-night.
You're not a dad!
I can't believe you got us into trouble.
So are you okay?
Yeah.
Just I feel like I'm about 100.
I thought I was just one of the guys.
Come here.
I'll make you feel like one of the guys.
For a really cool guy, you suck at foosball.
What? I was killing them.
Yeah, well they suck too.
Take the poopy diaper and put it in the poopy diaper pail.
Calling it a poopy diaper doesn't make this process any cuter.
-Hello?
-It's us.
Come on up. I'll get his stuff together.
Okay, we can do this now, can't we, Ben?
Yes, we can. Yes, we can.
There! I did it!
I did it!
Look at that!
It stays on and everything.
Hi!
Hi.
I'm sorry. What did you just say? Did you just say hi?
Oh, my God! Ross? Ben just said hi!
Ben just said hi!
The word ''hi''?
No, my Uncle Hi.
Great, I missed that too! I miss everything!
Oh, I'm sorry. I guess I just bring it out in him.
Hello! Where is he?
We missed you.
We missed you so much! Come here, Ben.
Guess what? Ben just said his first word.
What did he say?
Something about, ''Hi.''
That's so exciting!
Mommy's so proud of you!
Hi! Hi?
You know, actually, it's more like, ''Hi!''
This could go on for a while.
Yeah, we've got a cab waiting.
Well, this was fun.
We should do it again sometime, Ben. What do you say?
All right, so I've got him...?
Tuesday.
Bye, you guys.
Take care.
Bye, Ben.
Bye.
Did he just say bye? He said bye!
You said bye! He said bye to me!
Yes, he did!
Suddenly I'm seeing him go off to college!
We've gotta go. We've got that cab downstairs.
See you later.
Bye!
Bye.
Look at this nice deep hole I dug.
Hey, Bert, isn't this a nice hole?
This is the part where Ernie buries Bert in the sand and can't find him.
I've looked ahead on the tape, and he does find him again.
But before that happens, there's some rough going.
But I think we can handle it.
And there's just the alphabet, but we know that ends well, so....
Here we go.
Bert? Bert?
What happened to Bert? He was here a moment ago.
Oh, no! My old friend Bert is lost.
I'm so glad you're here.