How was Joan?
Broke up with her.
Oh, why?
Don't tell me.
Because of the big nostril thing?
They were huge.
When she sneezed, bats flew out.
They were not that huge.
She leaned back,
I could see her brain.
How many women will you reject
over superficial, insignificant--?
Hold it. I gotta side with Chandler.
When I first moved here, I went out
with this girl. Hot, great kisser but she had the biggest
Adam's apple.
Drove me nuts.
You or me?
I got it.
Joey, women don't have Adam's apples.
You guys are messing with me, right?
Yeah. We are.
That's a good one.
For a second there, I was like, whoa!
Name one woman you broke up with
for an actual real reason.
Maureen Rasillo.
Because she doesn't hate Yanni
is not a real reason.
Hello, Mr. Heckles.
You're doing it again.
We're not doing anything.
You're stomping.
It's disturbing my birds.
You don't have birds.
I could have birds.
We'll try to keep it down.
Thank you.
I'm going to rejoin my dinner party.
All right, bye-bye.
Okay, Janice.
Give me Janice.
That wasn't being picky.
We'll give you Janice.
I miss Janice, though.
Hello, Chandler Bing.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Chandler.
Now. Now.
That's it. There. Faster.
Stop with the broom.
We're not making noise.
We won.
We did it.
Mr. Heckles.
How did this happen?
He was sweeping.
They found a broom in his hand.
That's terrible.
I know.
I was sweeping yesterday.
It could've been me.
Sweeping. You never know.
Never know.
It's very faint, but I can
still sense him in the building.
Go into the light, Mr. Heckles.
Okay, Phoebe.
I'm sorry,
sometimes they need help.
Here we go.
That's fine, go ahead and scoff.
There are things I don't believe in.
It doesn't mean they're not true.
Such as?
Like crop circles
or the Bermuda Triangle or evolution.
You don't believe in evolution?
Not really.
I don't know. It's just, you know....
Monkeys, Darwin, it's a nice story.
I think it's a little too easy.
''Too easy''? Too--
The process of living things
on the planet evolving over years from single-celled
organisms is ''too easy''?
Yeah, I just don't buy it.
Excuse me. Evolution is not
for you to buy, Phoebe.
Evolution is scientific fact,
like the air we breathe like gravity.
Don't get me started on gravity.
You don't believe in gravity?
Well, it's not so much that,
you know, I don't believe in it.
I get the feeling that I'm not being pulled down
so much as I am being pushed.
Pushed.
It's Isaac Newton and he's pissed.
Quick, Pheebs, hop on the ceiling.
There she is.
And there, that's the other one.
Mr. Buddy Doyle, Heckles' attorney.
He'd like to talk.
What can we do for you?
All right, here's the deal.
According to my client's will he wants to leave
all his earthly possessions to ''the noisy girls
in the apartment above mine.''
What about his family?
He didn't have any.
Okay, so let's talk money.
There was none.
Now, let's talk signing.
You be noisy girl number one.
And number two.
I can't believe
that we thought he hated us.
It's amazing how much
you can touch someone's life without even knowing it.
Look at this dump!
He hated us. It's his final revenge.
I've never seen so much crap.
I think this apartment
sullies the good name of crap.
Check this out.
Can I have this?
How can you not believe in evolution?
I don't know, just don't.
Look at this funky shirt.
I've studied evolution
my entire adult life.
We've collected fossils
from all over the world that show the evolution
of different species.
I mean, you can literally see them evolving through time.
Really? You can actually see it?
You bet. In the U.S.,
China, Africa, all over.
See, I didn't know that.
Well, there you go.
So now the real question is,
who put those fossils there and why?
Look at this.
My Big Book of Grievances.
Hey, there's me.
''April 1 7th, excessive noise Italian guy comes home with a date.''
You're in here too.
''April 18th, excessive noise Italian guy's gay roommate
brings home dry cleaning.''
Well, that's excellent.
Look at this lamp. Is it tacky
or what? We have to have it.
I think we have enough regular lamps.
What? Come on, it's not like I'm asking
for this girlie clock or anything.
Which, by the way,
I also think is really cool.
It doesn't go with any of my stuff.
What about my stuff?
You don't have any.
It will be the start of my stuff.
No.
You still think of it
as your apartment, don't you?
No.
Yes, you do.
You think of it as your apartment,
and I just rent a room.
While you ''mmm'' on that,
I'll find a place for my new lamp.
Okay. See how I'm making
these little toys move?
Opposable thumbs.
Without evolution, how do you
explain opposable thumbs?
Maybe the Overlords needed them
to steer their spacecrafts.
Tell me you're joking.
Can't we say that you believe
in something and I don't?
No, Pheebs, we can't. Because it's
like math. One plus one equals two.
I can't let you think that it might
equal three or four or yellow.
Why not?
No, what is that all about?
What is this obsessive need
to make everybody agree with you?
You know what? I think maybe it's time
you put Ross under the microscope.
Is there blood coming out of my ears?
Check it out.
Heckles' high-school yearbook.
He looks so normal.
He's even kind of cute.
''You crack me up in science.
You're the funniest kid in school.''
Funniest? Heckles?
That's what it says.
Heckles was voted class clown,
and so was I.
He was right.
Would you listen to that?
I'd call that excessive.
Whoa.
What?
Heckles played clarinet in band.
I played clarinet.
He was in the scale
modeler's club and I was--
There was no club.
I thought they were cool.
So? You were both dorks.
Big deal.
I just think it's weird.
Heckles and me--
Heckles and me. Me--
Me and Heckles.
Hey, would you knock it off?!
Been here all night?
Look at this. Pictures of the women
Heckles went out with.
Look what he wrote on them.
''Vivian, too tall.''
''Madge, big gums.''
''Too loud.''
''Too smart.'' ''Makes noise
when she eats.'' This is me.
This is what I do.
I'll end up alone, just like him.
Heckles was a nutcase.
Our trains are on the same track.
I'm 30 years behind him,
but the stops are the same.
Bitter Town Aloneville, Hermit Junction.
We gotta get you out of here.
I'll buy you breakfast. Let's go.
What if I never find somebody?
What if I found her but dumped her
because she pronounces it, supposably?
Chandler, come on,
you'll find somebody.
How do you know that? How?
I don't. I'm just trying to help you.
You guys will all get married
and I'll end up alone.
Will you promise me something?
When you're married,
invite me over for holidays?
I don't know what we're doing.
What if we're over at her folks' place?
Yeah, I understand.
You can come watch the Super Bowl.
Every year, all right?
You know what?
I'm not gonna end up like this.
I'll see you, man.
Supposably.
Did they go to the zoo?
Hi. It's me.
Oh, my God.
Janice? You called Janice?
Yes. Janice.
Why is that difficult to comprehend?
You remember Janice, right?
Yes. She was smart, she was pretty
and she honestly cared about me.
Janice is my last chance
to have somebody.
Hello.
Oh, my God.
Look how fat she got.
Hey, it's everybody.
Hi, Janice.
Janice, you're....
Yes, I am.
Is it--?
Is it yours?
You wish, Chandler Bing.
You are looking at a married lady now.
Congratulations.
Sweetie, I'm sorry.
I couldn't wait for you forever.
You couldn't tell me on the phone?
And miss the expression on your face?
Oh, no. Janice likes to have her fun.
Know what we haven't done in a while?
What?
Hide the lamp.
Monica, let it go.
You know I'm allergic to shellfish?
Then you'll just have
to eat the other lamps.
It's scary scientist man.
Okay, Phoebe, this is it.
In this briefcase I carry
actual scientific facts.
A briefcase of facts, if you will.
Some of these fossils are
over 200 million years old.
Before you even start,
I'm not denying evolution.
It's one of the possibilities.
It's the only possibility.
Ross, could you open your mind,
like, this much?
Didn't the brightest minds in
the world believe the Earth was flat?
Up until 50 years ago, you thought
the atom was the smallest thing until you split it open
and a mess of crap came out.
Are you telling me that you are so
unbelievably arrogant that you can't admit
there's a teeny, tiny possibility that you could be wrong about this?
There might be...a teeny...tiny...possibility.
I can't believe you caved.
You just abandoned
your whole belief system.
Before, I didn't agree with you,
but I respected you.
But--
How are you going into work tomorrow?
How will you face
the other science guys?
How are you going to face yourself?
That was fun.
So who's hungry?
I am.
Me too.
Let me just get my coat.
It was an accident, I swear.
I was putting on my jacket...
and the Iamp...and it broke.
Oh, please, Monica.
You've always hated my lamp.
And all of a sudden,
it's just magically, it's just broken?
Phoebe, tell her?
I didn't see it,
I was putting on my jacket.
I want to believe you.
Hey, Chandler.
Monica just broke my seashell lamp.
Neat.
I'm gonna die alone.
Okay, you win.
Chandler, you're not gonna die alone.
Janice was my safety net.
And now I have to get a snake.
Why is that?
If I'm gonna be an old, lonely man,
I'll need a thing. You know, a hook?
Like that guy who eats his own face.
So I'll be ''Crazy Man With A Snake.''
''Crazy Snake Man.''
I'll get more snakes, call them my
babies. Kids will run past my place.
''Run away from Crazy Snake Man,''
they'll shout.
You've got to get over this.
You won't end up alone.
Of course I will.
I reject anyone who's crazy enough
to go out with me then I bitch that there
are no great women out there.
You have just described almost every
man that we've ever gone out with.
You are not a freak.
You're a guy.
She's right. You all do it.
This one guy stopped seeing me
because his cat didn't like me.
Or because I fell asleep
during Spinal Tap.
You fell asleep during Spinal Tap?
Teddy, who stopped seeing you
because you were too fat.
He said he didn't have time
for me because of the play.
That's what I said.
My point being,
you are no different than the rest.
Wait a minute. Yes, he is.
You are totally different.
In a bad way?
No, in a wonderful way.
You know what you want now.
Most guys don't know.
You're ready to take risks,
be vulnerable and intimate.
You won't end up alone.
You called Janice. That's how much
you wanted to be with someone.
You've made it.
You're there.
You are ready to make a commitment.
Don't know about that.
What you got there?
Something else that's not yours
you can break?
I know you like this.
I want you to have it.
It'll look good in our apartment.
Thank you.
That's fine.
You'll be pleased to know
that I have a date tomorrow night.
Allison from work. She is great.
She's pretty, she's smart.
I've been holding off asking her out,
because she has...an unusually large head.
But I won't let
that stuff hang me up anymore.
Look at me, I'm growing.
You can't recycle yearbooks, can you?
I'll take that.
You want his yearbook?
Yeah.
People said nice things.
Somebody should have it.
Gosh, this is so weird.
His whole life was in
this apartment and now it's gone.
It would be nice if we just
took a few moments for Mr. Heckles.
He was kind of a pain.
He was, but he was a person.
You're all going to hell.
It's really not that big.
Taking that with you?
Oh, yeah.
Hey, you coming?
Yeah, in a second.
Goodbye, Mr. Heckles.
We'll try to keep it down.
My major was useless.
How often do the classifieds
say ''Philosopher Wanted''?
Sure.
My God, that's a big head.
It didn't look this big in the office.
Maybe it's the lighting.
My head must look like
a golf ball at work.
Don't get hung up on it.
List five things you like about her.
Nice smile, good dresser.
Big head, big head, big head.