He's got it on tap!
Dad, did you talk about me?
I do.
So where did you get the hat?
I don't know.
You're wearing the tie I got you!
Yeah.
Look, you're a big girl. I just hope
you know what you're doing.
Oh, right. Well, actually,
we never got to you.
In his apartment. The thing is built
into his bar. It's unbelievable!
But he offered me a beer. Know what?
What?
At halftime,
I was gonna give him what for.
But he had the game on,
so we started watching.
And?
I was gonna punch him in the nose.
Hey, Dad. What are you doing here?
I just stopped by your boyfriend's.
So, what do you think?
Casa de Joey.
I decorated it myself.
Get out!
Wow, Joey, this is....
Art.
Art it is.
Check this out.
Is it a coffee table?
Is it a panther?
There's no need to decide.
Hey, nice pillow.
So now tell me,
is this genuine Muppet skin?
Hey, excellent water table thing.
Thanks. I love this. But you
know what? It makes me want to pee.
Yeah, me too.
I think that's the challenge.
How come Chandler didn't come?
It's because he had
a thing with the thing.
Right. I got it.
So why don't you show us
the rest of your casa?
The best part! Come on.
Nice toilet.
No. Behind it.
You have a phone in here?
That's right. I have a phone in here.
Promise me something.
Yeah?
Never call me from that phone.
Okay, here we go.
Sorry, they were all out of apple pie.
Someone just got the last piece.
Oh, my God!
You won't believe this!
I have just been discovered.
Now wait a minute. I claimed you
in the name of France four years ago.
Anyway.
Don't freak out and say how
great this is until I'm done.
I met this producer
of this record company who said I have
a fresh, offbeat sound and she wants to do
a demo of ''Smelly Cat.''
I told you not to do that yet.
And she wants to do a video.
I'm not done yet, okay?
God!
If that goes well, they may
even want to make an album.
I'm done now.
If you care for me,
get the pie out of the man's hood.
Get the what?
There's a pie in the hood. Go!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry. My pie was in your hood.
I have to get the coffee out of that guy's pants and I'll
be back in the hospital by 7.
Damn it, Ross!
Get your butt out of the bathroom!
Calm down. I'm blow-drying.
Blow-drying what?
You have no hair.
What's going on?
He's been in there for an hour.
It's like I live with him again.
He's here when I sleep, wake up
and when I want to shower.
It's like I'm 1 6 again.
Well, you're not 1 6.
You're both adults now.
Get out, you doofus!
Or, you know,
he's rubber and you're glue.
All yours.
I hope you cleaned your hair
out of the drain.
Shut up!
Shut up.
Cut it out!
I've never wanted you more.
Hello?
Louie? Where's Howard?
He went home.
He said he might stop up.
He said to tell you
he wasn't feeling so good.
Hey, what time do you get off?
I'm not feeling too good either.
So, what do you say, boys?
Should I call him?
You know what they say:
Ask your slippers a question you're going crazy.
Freaking art!
Hello.
Hey.
Hey!
Sorry I didn't make it over there.
That's okay.
You had a thing.
I hear the place looks great.
Forget about it. I'm having a ball!
How's the apartment doing?
It's terrific.
I mean, it's a regular space fest!
Well, great.
Yeah, I just wanted
to call and say hey.
Well, okay.
Was that the oven timer?
That's right, my friend.
-It's time for....
-Baywatch!
You believe Stephanie has skin cancer?
I can't believe she's lieutenant!
That's because you love
Yasmine Bleeth.
How could anyone not love
Yasmine Bleeth?
They're running!
See, this is the brilliance
of the show.
I say always keep them running.
All the time running!
Run!
Run, Yasmine! Run like the wind!
But you wanted to live by yourself.
I did. I thought it'd be great.
I figured I'd have time alone
with my thoughts.
It turns out I don't have
as many thoughts as you'd think.
Why don't you talk to Chandler
and move back?
You really think he'd take me?
We had a good talk last night but when I moved, I hurt him bad.
He would definitely want you back.
I'm telling you,
no way he's moving back.
But we had one of the greatest
talks we ever had last night.
I mean, it was--
It was like when we first
lived together.
I know you don't want
to hear this now but we've seen him
in his new place. And he's happy.
He's decorated.
Chandler, he has moved on, okay?
You have to, too.
You have to accept the fact
that you're just friends now.
You're not roommates anymore.
Okay, you ready to try one?
Okay.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
Smelly, smelly
Really bad smelling smelly cat
Whoa! Oh, my God!
I mean, like, who was that?
They're your backup singers.
Behind you, hon.
I thought they were just watching me.
Like at an aquarium, you know?
They're so good. You're so good!
Alrighty!
Okay, now that everyone knows
everyone, let's try it again.
From the top.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
Smelly, smelly, smelly, really bad
Smelling smelly cat. It's not your--
Okay, sorry.
I'm just not getting that everyone gets how smelly
this cat actually is.
If we could talk about this. I need
to feel that you care about the cat.
We can talk, but this costs
$100 a minute to be in here.
Okay, so the cat stinks,
but you love it. Let's go.
No, there is no way
he was a velociraptor.
Look at the cranial ridge.
If Dino was a velociraptor,
he would have eaten the Flintstones.
Were you taking a nap?
I was.
Can you hold on?
That's the other line.
Hello?
Yeah, she's here,
but can she call you back?
Okay, thanks.
Call Joanna.
She leave a number?
Did you see me write one down?
I don't have her number, butt-munch.
She'll call back. Don't be a baby.
You're the baby.
Off my back.
Get out of my face.
Wait, hold on, Tony. Hold on.
Hello?
Hi.
Yeah, No. she's right here. Hold on.
Tony, can I call you back?
That's my sister's boyfriend.
Give me that.
Okay.
Sweetie, before I forget, did I
leave my diaphragm at your place?
Hi, Mom.
So how's the palace?
Funny you should mention that,
because I was thinking--
What's with the boxes?
Actually, I have some news.
Is Joey gonna pick up
his moose hat or should I toss it?
Why don't you ask him yourself?
This is my roommate, Eddie.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
I'll take that.
It's what I came for.
So this is new.
Where did you two meet?
At the supermarket
in the ethnic food section.
I helped him pick a chorizo.
We got to talking. He needed
a place and I had a spare room.
Oh, now it's a spare room?
Well, yeah.
In that it's not being used and I have it to spare.
Well, I got what I came for.
I'll see you guys.
Hey, Joe.
When'd you start using
moose in your hair?
Is this guy great or what?
Yeah, yeah, he is.
He has a new roommate? Who is he?
Eddie. He just met him.
It'll never last.
He's just a rebound roommate.
Check it out! Check it out!
It's ''Smelly Cat,'' the video!
Now, I haven't seen it yet,
so if you don't like it so what?
None of you ever made a video.
Get out of here, cat! You stink!
Smoking!
Look at me!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
It's not your fault
Smelly, smelly, really bad smelling
Smelly cat, it's not your fault
Smelly cat, smelly cat
Oh, my God!
I know.
I sound amazing!
They won't take you to the vet
You're obviously not their favorite pet
Smelly cat, smelly cat
It's not your fault
Oh, no
I've never heard myself sing before.
I mean, except in my own head.
This is so cool!
Now I can hear what you hear!
Pretty different, huh?
I am sorry,
but I'm incredibly talented!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
It's not your fault
Joey, what's going on, man?
Eddie.
Morning.
I just came by to pick up my mail.
Where's the mail?
Over on the table.
It's not on this table anymore?
No. Eddie likes to keep it over there.
All right, here you go, my friend.
Eggs à Ia Eddie.
That's great.
What?
I thought you liked eggs with bread
with the hole in the middle à Ia me!
I do, but Eddie makes them this way.
They're darn good.
Wanna try some?
No, thanks.
All right. Well, you guys,
I'm out of here.
See you, pals.
See you.
How are you two getting along?
I couldn't be happier.
Great. I'm happy for you.
All right, that's it!
He just comes in here,
Mr. Johnny New Eggs, with his--
His moving the mail
and his, ''See you, pals.''
There's no juice!
There's no juice for the people
who need the juice. I need the juice!
There's another carton
right over there.
This isn't about juice anymore,
all right?
All right. What's it about?
Eggs!
Whose eggs do you like better,
his or mine?
I like both eggs equally!
Come on!
Nobody likes two eggs equally!
Which one do you like better?
What's the difference?
Your eggs aren't here anymore!
You took your eggs and you left!
Did you expect me
to never find new eggs?
Maybe this isn't about the eggs.
Maybe this is about
the chicken that laid them.
What chicken?
There's no chicken.
I can't talk to you!
I want Entertainment Tonight.
We're watching Predators of the Serengeti.
Would you guys stop?!
It's my TV!
Quit it!
Bite me!
Oh, my God!
Monica keeps changing the channel.
Great. Why don't you tell Mommy on me?
Now I'm Mommy in this little play?
Look, I refuse to get sucked into this
weird little Geller dimension thing!
I'm gonna take a nice long,
hot bubble bath because you kids
are driving me crazy!
What do we do about this?
Tape Entertainment Tonight.
Not that! This! Us!
Oh, my God, Ross....
You're just....
Since you've been here,
you drive....
Mon, you've gone ultrasonic
again, all right?
I just can't stand you being here all the time!
Why? Why can't you stand me
being here? We're just having fun.
Fun? You think this is fun?
We were fooling around,
like when we were kids.
I hated you when we were kids!
You hated me when we were kids?
I hated you. I loved you in a you're-my-brother-so-I-have-to
way, but basically I hated your guts.
Why did you hate me?
Because you were mean to me and you teased me
and you always got your way.
And that wasn't fun for you?
I can't believe you hated me.
But now I love you.
And not just because I have to.
Really?
Yeah.
You're just gonna have to stop
pissing me off.
I can do that.
Then I won't have to kill you.
So you wanna watch
Entertainment Tonight?
Thanks.
Tonight, America's sport's
magazine moves to--
You know what?
What?
If you really wanna watch
that Serengeti thing, we can.
Okay.
Listen, you are not going
to believe this but that is not me
singing on the video.
How did you find out?
The record company sent a paper
for me to sign saying it's okay for someone else to sing for me.
That was a clue.
What will you do?
I can't work with people who do this.
Sure.
I mean, this poor woman.
What woman?
The voice woman.
She has a great voice,
but she doesn't have a video.
Okay, Pheebs, what about you?
I have a video. Pay attention.
This voice woman, she's so talented.
But according to the producer people,
she doesn't have the right look.
She's like one of those
animals at the pound who nobody wants
because they're not pretty enough.
Or some old dog
who's kind of stinky and--
Oh, my God! She's ''Smelly Cat''!
That song has so many levels.
Hey, Eddie.
You wanna play some foosball?
No, thanks, man.
I'm not really into sports.
Yeah, okay. All right.
Doesn't matter.
Time for Baywatch!
You like that show?
You don't like that show?
It's just pretty people
running around on the beach.
That's the brilliance of it.
The pretty people.
And the running.
I'm gonna go read in my room
for a little while.
Okay, man.
I'm gonna start off with a little
song called ''Smelly Cat.''
Oh, for those of you who are
wondering, this is my real voice.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
Everybody!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
It's not your fault
Monica!
-They won't take you to the vet
Chandler!
You're obviously not
their favorite pet
Joey!
-You may not be a bed of roses
Rachel!
You're no friend to those with noses
Ross, those are
the only lines we have. Sorry.
Back to the chorus everybody!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you
It's not your fault
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you
It's not your fault