It's not fair! It's my money.
I know. But it's what Brad wanted.
Which one is she?
That's Brad's widow.
Why is she so upset?
She was cut out of the will.
Doesn't she know you can't
define yourself by money?
It's about values and morals and
your ability to give and receive love.
No.
-Oh, Drake.
-I'm sorry, Amber.
It's just like Brad to have
to have the last word.
Sorry I'm late. What happened?
We wanna see the end.
-I want you, Drake.
-I know you do.
But we can never
be together that way.
What?
There's something I never told you.
I'm actually your half-brother.
So, what happens next?
I get a medical award
for separating Siamese twins.
Then Amber and I go to Venezuela to
meet our other half-brother, Ramon where I find the world's
biggest emerald. It's really big.
But it's cursed.
So cool!
God, that is good TV!
Come on, Pheebs. Play with me!
No! This game is grotesque!
Twenty armless guys joined
at the waist by a steel bar forced to play soccer forever?
Hello? Human rights violation!
Don't feel bad. After playing I break out the plastic women
and everybody has a good time.
Why don't you play with your roommate?
He's not a big fan of foosball.
Are we not getting along
with the new boy?
No, he's all right. He spends
most of his time in his room.
Because you haven't gotten
to know him. Let's remedy that.
We don't need to remedy that.
Yeah, it'll be fun!
What was that?
Hi! I just thought it'd be fun if we
had beers and got to know each other.
All right.
Oh, good! Okay.
Oh, no! I have to go
because I'm late for my Green Eggs and Ham
discussion group.
Tonight, it's, ''Why he would not
eat them on a train.''
Have fun! Bye!
That was so lame.
I know.
Okay, talk to him.
So you think that Speed Racer guy
gets a lot of tickets or...?
That's good.
Who broke up with who?
I broke up with her. She thought Sean
Penn was the capital of Cambodia.
That's good! When everybody knows
the capital of Cambodia is....
Well, it's not Sean Penn.
All right, I got a funny one.
My last girlfriend, Tilly, we're
eating breakfast. I made 50 pancakes.
All of a sudden, she turns to me and
says, ''I don't wanna see you anymore.''
It was like she had reached
into my chest, ripped out my heart and smeared it all over my life!
There was this incredible abyss
and I'm falling and I don't think
I'm ever gonna stop!
That wasn't such
a funny story, was it?
A crusty old man
Said I'll do what I can
And the rest of the rats
Played maracas
That's it! Thanks! Good night.
Phoebe's got another job, right?
Great set tonight, Pheebs.
I know.
We should get going.
We should go too.
I got patients in the morning.
You know how we always
stay at your place?
I thought we'd stay at my place.
I don't know. I don't have my jammies.
You don't need them.
My baby sister, ladies and gentlemen.
Shut up. I'm happy.
Oh, this is so nice!
I have to make a speech.
I want to say, of all the guys Monica
has been with, and that is a lot...I like you the best.
Thank you, Pheebs.
That's very sweet.
You hear that?
She likes me best. And apparently,
there have been a lot.
Not a lot. Phoebe's kidding.
Phoebe's crazy.
Phoebe's dead.
I'm looking for Eddie Manoick.
He's not here now. I'm Chandler.
Can I take a message or a fish-tank?
Thanks.
Come on in.
I'm Tilly.
I gather by that ''Oh,''
he told you about me.
Yeah, your name came up in a conversation that
terrified me to my very soul.
He's kind of intense.
Yes! Can I ask you,
is Eddie a little--?
A little what?
Bit country?
Or, you know, a little rock 'n' roll?
Come on in here, you roomie!
Hello, Tilly.
I just came by to drop off your tank.
That was very thoughtful of you.
It's very thoughtful.
Well, okay then.
I'm gonna go. Bye.
Bye!
So we getting a fish?
You had sex with her, didn't you?
Pheebs! Check it out,
check it out, check it out!
Soap Opera Digest!
That's one of my favorite digests!
Page 42! Page 42! Page 42!
''New Doc on the Block,
Days of our Lives Joey Tribbiani.''
Cool picture!
Oh, I look good.
Is this true? That you write
a lot of your lines?
Well, kind of, yeah.
Remember last week
when Alex was in the accident?
The script said, ''If we don't get this
woman to a hospital she'll die.''
But I made it, ''If this woman doesn't
get to a hospital she won't live.''
Oh, okay.
I see what you did there.
Aren't you afraid the writers
will be mad when they read this?
I never thought about the writers.
The scripts just come to my house.
But you know what?
This makes me look good, which makes
the show and the writers look good.
How could they be mad?
Makes up most of his lines.
Son of a....
Write this,jerk-weed.
I fall down an elevator shaft?
What the hell does this mean?
I don't know.
I just bring the scripts.
They can't kill me!
I'm Francesca's long lost son!
Right. Could you sign this?
No! No way! I'm not signing that!
I don't think that's gonna affect
the plot of the show.
How can they do this to me?
I'm just gonna go.
Sorry.
Well, it wasn't that many guys.
If you consider
how many guys there are it's a very small percentage.
It's not a big a deal.
I was just curious.
Good night.
Good luck, Mon.
Before I tell you, you tell me
how many women you've been with.
Two.
Two? Two?
How is that possible?
I mean, have you seen you?
Well, what can I say?
I was married to Barbara for 30 years,
my high school sweetheart.
Now you. That's two.
Two it is.
Time for bed.
I'm gonna brush my teeth.
No, wait a minute now!
Come on, it's your turn.
Oh, come on!
You know, I don't need the
actual number. Just a ballpark.
Okay, it is definitely
less than a ballpark.
I am so glad
I'm not Monica right now.
Tell me about it.
So what's your magic number?
Come on, you know everyone
I've been with. All both of them.
Well, there's you.
Better not be doing these in order.
Billy Dreskin, Pete Carny,
Barry and oh, Paolo.
Oh, yes, the weenie from Turinie.
Honey, are you jealous of Paolo?
I'm so much happier with you
than I ever was with him.
Really?
Oh, please!
That Paolo thing was
barely a relationship.
All it really was just
meaningless, animal sex.
Okay, you know, that sounded
so much better in my head.
Eddie, I didn't sleep with her!
That's what someone
who slept with her would say.
This is nuts!
She was over for two minutes dropped off a fish tank and left!
Where's Buddy?
Buddy?
My fish, Buddy.
There was no fish
when she dropped it off.
This is unbelievable! First you sleep
with my ex-girlfriend insult me by lying,
then you kill my fish, my Buddy?
I didn't kill your fish!
Look, Eddie--
Would you look at what I'm doing here?
Now that can't be smart.
So we're gonna take this guy right off
you and put him here in Mr. Pocket.
Tangelo?
That's it? That's the number
you were afraid to say?
Well, yeah.
That's not bad at all.
You had me thinking
it was, like, a fleet.
You're really okay with it?
Oh, honey, I'm fine.
Okay, about that two.
What?
All right, what about my two?
It just seems like
a really small number.
Right. And...?
And, well, don't you have
a lot of wild oats to sow?
Or is that what you're doing with me?
Oh, my God! Am I an oat?
Honey, you are not an oat.
I don't know, I guess
I'm just not an oat guy.
I've only slept with women I love.
But you've only slept with two people.
Right.
You know I love you too, right?
Now I do.
Ross! Ross, please listen to me!
Ross!
You are so much better
for me than Paolo ever was!
You care for me, you're loving,
you make me laugh.
If I make you laugh, here's an idea.
Invite Paolo for a romp in the sack and I'll stand in the corner
and tell knock-knock jokes!
What we have is special!
All Paolo and I had was--
Animal sex? Animal sex?
So, what are you saying? There's
nothing between us ''animal'' at all?
There's not even, like,
a little animal? Not even, like chipmunk sex?
Try to hear me, okay?
I'm not gonna lie to you.
It was good with Paolo.
Knock-knock.
But!
What you and I have
is so much better.
We have tenderness,
we have intimacy, we connect.
You know? I swear this is the best I have ever had.
Until now.
Richard said he loved me.
Oh, my God!
I know!
Honey, that's great!
I can't find--
Top drawer. Hurry.
Why? You need one too?
Oh, yeah.
Found them!
There's only one.
We'll be right there.
We're trying to decide something.
They're trying to decide something.
Good. Good, good.
So was your mustache,
did it used to be different?
No.
How do you, you know,
keep it so neat?
I have a little comb.
And what do you call that?
A mustache comb.
Okay, I will do your laundry
for one month.
No!
I will, I will.... I will clean
the apartment for two months.
I'll give this to you now, if you
tell me where we keep the dustpan.
So were you in Nam?
We are both adults here. Right? There
has to be a mature way to handle this.
Rock, paper, scissors?
Gotcha.
One, two, three.
Yes!
Fine. Go have sex.
Thank you.
No! You have got it completely wrong!
John Savage was Deer Hunter, no legs.
Jon Voight was Coming Home,
couldn't feel his legs.
You've got it the other way
around, my friend. Jon Voight--
Honey?
What?
Shall we?
It's not gonna happen.
They're doing it tonight.
We can do it tomorrow.
In the future, if I could see
the schedule beforehand....
When I woke up this morning, he'd
stolen all the insoles out of my shoes!
Why?
He thinks I slept with his
ex-girlfriend and killed his fish.
Why would you kill his fish?
Because sometimes, after you sleep
with someone, you have to kill a fish.
Chandler, honey, I'm sorry.
Can we watch Joey's show now, please?
Wait. He's not here yet.
So? He's on the show.
He knows what happens.
I'm fine about my problem now,
by the way.
Amber I'll always be there for you,
as a friend and as your brother.
Oh, Drake.
Hard day, huh?
First the medical award, now this?
Yeah. Some guys are
just lucky, I guess.
Dr. Ramoray, report to
first floor Emergency stat.
Well, then, I guess that's me.
Anyone else need to go on
the elevator? Dr. Horton? Dr. Wall?
They only said you.
Oh, okay. All right.
I love you, Drake.
Yeah, whatever.
Oh, no!
Drake, look out!
Did they just kill off Joey?
No!
Now maybe.
Come on! Open up!
We want to talk to you!
I don't feel like talking!
We care about you.
We're worried about you.
And some of us really have to pee!
I'm sorry, Joey.
Listen, sorry about your death.
That really sucks.
We came when we saw.
Why didn't you tell us?
I don't know. I was kind of hoping
no one would find out.
Well, maybe they could find
a way to bring you back.
They said when they found my body,
my brain was so smashed in that the only doctor who
could have saved me was me.
It's supposed to be
some kind of irony.
You're gonna be fine. You don't need
that show. It was a dumb soap opera.
It was the greatest thing
that ever happened to me.
Yes! I was going to incorporate that.
Here's Monica.
She'll say something nice.
I straightened out your shower curtain
so you won't get mildew.
What? To me, that's nice.
It'll be okay. You know that.
No, I don't.
It's like you work
your whole life for something and you think when you get it,
it'll never be as good as you thought.
But this so was.
It changed everything.
The other day, I got
a credit card application and I was pre-approved!
I've never been pre-approved
for anything in my life!
I'm sorry, man.
I don't know if this'll mean
anything to you but you'll always be
pre-approved with us.
No, that means nothing to me.
Pecan sandy? Just made them.
Yeah, all right.
What are these, raisins?
Sure, why not?
Listen, Eddie.
I've been thinking about our living
situation. Why are you smiling?
I got a little surprise.
Look. There's a new fishy.
I named him Chandler,
you know, after you.
Well, that's not even a real fish.
No, that's a Goldfish cracker.
So what's your point, man?
Okay, good night.
You big freak of nature!
Brisk tonight.
Oh, man.
Let's never speak of this.
You got it.