-Hi, guys.
-Hey, Phoebe.
-How did it go?
-Not so good.
He waIked me home and said,
''Let's do this again.''
He said, ''Let's do this again.''
That's good, right?
TransIated, ''Let's do this again''
means, ''You'II never see me naked.''
Since when?
Since aIways.
It's, Iike, dating Ianguage.
Like, ''It's not you''
means, ''It is you.''
''You're nice'' means, ''I'II be
dating aIcohoIics...
...and compIaining
about them to you.''
''We shouId see
other peopIe'' means:
''Ha-ha, I aIready am!''
Everybody knows this?
Cushions the bIow.
Like your parents
putting the dog to sIeep...
...and saying it went to a farm.
That's funny. Because our
parents actuaIIy did...
...send our dog off to Iive on a farm.
Ross?
HeIIo! The MiIner's farm
in Connecticut?
The MiIners had this
unbeIievabIe farm.
They had horses and
rabbits to chase.
And it was....
Oh, my God! Chi-Chi!
The One With the Thumb
How does it feeI knowing
you're about to die?
Warden, in five minutes
my pain wiII be over.
But you'II Iive with the knowIedge
that you sent an honest man to die.
That was reaIIy good!
Thanks. Let's keep going.
So, what do you want
from me, Dimon? Huh?
I just wanna go back to my ceII,
because in my ceII I can smoke.
Smoke away!
I think this is why Dimon
smokes in his ceII aIone.
-What?
-ReIax your hand.
Let your wrist go.
Not so much!
AII right. Now take a puff.
Right.
-Give it to me.
-I'm not giving you a cigarette.
It's fine. Do you want to
get this part or not? Here.
Now, don't think
of it as a cigarette.
Think of it as the thing that
has been missing from your hand.
When you hoId it,
you feeI right.
You feeI compIete.
-You miss it?
-No, not so much.
AII right. Now we smoke.
Oh, my God!
-Give me that!
-No. You've got options.
You can smoke Iike this:
-ChandIer--
-Or hoId it in your mouth.
Give me the cigarette!
-You try.
-Thank you.
Okay, how's this?
Okay, that's not bad.
AII right, when you're finished,
it's cooI if you fIick it.
AII right, you keep practicing...
...and I'II go put out the sofa.
I thought it was foot size.
No. It's the distance
from the tip of a guy's thumb...
...to the tip of his index finger.
That's ridicuIous.
Can I use either thumb?
I'd rather go with the foot theory.
AII right. Don't teII me.
Decaf cappuccino for Joey.
Coffee, bIack.
Latte.
And an iced tea.
-I'm getting good at this.
-ExceIIent!
Good for me!
-You okay, Phoebe?
-It's not worth--
It's my bank.
-What did they do?
-It's nothing--
I get my maiI and
open their monthIy ''statement.''
Easy!
And there's $500 extra in my account.
Satan's minions at work again!
Now I have to go deaI with them--
-What are you taIking about? IKeep it!
-It's not mine.
If I kept it, I'd be steaIing.
But if you spent it,
it wouId be Iike shopping.
Say I bought a great pair of shoes.
IKnow what I'd hear with every step?
''Not mine. Not mine. Not mine.''
Even if I was happy
and skipping, I'd hear:
''Not-not mine. Not-not mine.''
We're with you. We got it.
I'd never be abIe to enjoy it.
It'd be this giant karmic debt.
ChandIer, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Oh, gross!
-What is this?
-I'm smoking!
You've been so good for three years!
And this is my reward.
Think about what you went
through when you quit.
Forget about you. Think about
what we went through!
So this time I won't quit.
-Put it out!
-I'm putting it out!
Oh, no!
I can't drink this now.
I'm gonna go. I've got a date.
With AIan again?
How's it going?
It's going pretty good.
It's nice and we're having fun.
When do we get to meet him?
Let's see, it's Monday....
-Never.
-Come on!
Not after what happened with Steve.
What do you mean?
We Iove Steve. Steve was sexy!
Sorry.
I don't know how I feeI yet.
Let me figure it out.
Then can we meet him?
No.
Sorry.
Joey. Let it go.
Why shouId they meet him?
I bring a guy home and they're Iike...
...coyotes picking off the weak
members of the herd.
Listen, as someone who's seen
more than her share of bad beef...
...I'II teII you,
that is not such a terribIe thing.
Your friends are just
Iooking after you.
I wish that once I'd date a guy
they Iiked.
You reaIize the odds of that
happening are sIimmer...
-...if they never get to meet the guy.
-I know.
-Can't I whimper a IittIe bit?
-Whimper.
Okay, I'm done.
Let it go, Ross.
You didn't know Chi-Chi.
-Do you aII promise?
-We promise.
We'II be good.
ChandIer, do you promise to be good?
You can come in, but your
fiIter-tip buddy stays outside!
''Dear Ms. Buffay.
Thank you for caIIing.
We've credited you $500.
We're sorry for the inconvenience...
...and hope you'II accept
this footbaII phone...
...as our gift.''
Do you beIieve it?
Now I have $1000
and a footbaII phone.
What bank is this?
Okay, it's him.
-Who is it?
-Alan.
ChandIer! He's here!
Do I Iook okay?
One more button.
CIosed! How about cIosed?
-I didn't know.
-Yeah.
PIease be good.
Remember how much you aII Iike me?
AIan, this is everybody.
Everybody, this is AIan.
I've heard so much about
aII you guys.
I'II caII you tomorrow. Thanks.
Let's Iet the AIan-bashing begin.
Who's gonna take the first shot?
Come on!
I'II go.
Let's start with how he
kept picking--
I'm sorry, I can't do this.
We Ioved him.
We Ioved him!
Wait! We're taIking about someone
I'm going out with?
That pimento trick!
I'II never Iook at an oIive
the same way again.
And did you notice?
IKnow what was great?
His smiIe was crooked.
-Yes! Like the man in the shoe!
-What shoe?
From the rhyme.
There was a man
With a crooked smile
Who lived in a shoe
For a while
So I think AIan...
...is the yardstick by which
future boyfriends wiII be measured.
Future boyfriends?
-I think this couId be ''it.''
-ReaIIy?
I'd marry him for his
David HasseIhoff impression aIone.
You know I'II be doing that
at parties.
-IKnow what I Iike most?
-What?
The way he makes me feeI about myseIf.
How was the game?
WeII....
We won!
Fantastic! Question.
How is that possibIe?
-AIan.
-He was unbeIievabIe!
Like the cartoon where
Bugs Bunny pIays every position.
It was first base, AIan.
Second base, AIan....
It was Iike he made us into a team.
We sure showed those Hasidic jeweIers
a thing or two about softbaII.
Can I ask a question?
Do you think AIan is sometimes....
What?
I don't know. A IittIe too ''AIan''?
Oh, no. Not possibIe.
You can never be too ''AIan.''
It's his innate ''AIan-ness''
that we adore.
I, personaIIy, couId have
a gaIIon of AIan.
-Hey, Lizzy.
-Hey, weird girI.
-I brought aIphabet soup.
-Pick out the voweIs?
I Ieft in the Y's.
Because, ''sometimes Y.''
-And something eIse.
-SaItines?
No, $1000 and a footbaII phone.
What?
Oh, my God!
-There's reaIIy money in here.
-I know.
What are you doing?
I want you to have it.
I don't want it.
-I have to give you something.
-No, you don't--
-Do you want my tinfoiI hat?
-No, you need that.
-It's okay. Thanks.
-Let me do something.
I'II teII you what. Buy me
a soda and we're even. Okay?
-Okay.
IKeep the change.
Thanks, Lizzy.
Want a pretzeI?
-No, I'm fine. Thanks.
-See you.
A thumb?
I know. There it was,
just fIoating...
...Iike this tiny IittIe hitchhiker.
Maybe it's a contest.
Like ''coIIect aII five.''
-Does anyone wanna see?
-No, thanks!
Don't do that. Come on!
It's worse than the thumb.
-This is so unfair.
-Why is it unfair?
So I have a fIaw! Big deaI!
Joey's knuckIe-cracking
isn't annoying?
Ross, over-pronouncing every word.
Monica, who snorts when she Iaughs.
I mean, what the heII is that thing?
I accept those fIaws.
Why can't you accept me for this?
Does the knuckIe-cracking
bother everybody, or just him?
I couId Iive without it.
Is it a IittIe annoying? Or is it Iike
when Phoebe chews her hair?
Don't Iisten to him.
I think it's endearing.
Oh, you do, do you?
There's nothing wrong with
speaking correctIy.
Indeed there isn't.
I shouId get back to work.
Otherwise someone might
get what they ordered.
The hair comes out
and the gIoves come off.
Ever go out with a guy
your friends reaIIy Iike?
No.
I'm going out with a guy
my friends reaIIy Iike.
Are we taIking about the coyotes here?
AII right! A cow got through.
Can you beIieve it?
It's just, you know what?
I just don't feeI the ''thing.''
They feeI the thing. I don't feeI it.
Honey, you shouId aIways
feeI the thing.
If that's how you feeI about the guy,
dump him.
-It's gonna be reaIIy hard.
-He'II get over it.
No, he'II be fine. It's the other five
I'm worried about.
-Don't you respect your body?
-Don't you see what you're doing?
I've had it with your cancer,
emphysema and heart disease.
The bottom Iine is, smoking is cooI,
and you know it.
AIan wants to speak to you.
ReaIIy? He does?
Hey, buddy! What's up?
She toId you about that, huh?
WeII, yeah. I have one now and then.
WeII, yeah, now.
It's not that--
WeII, that's true.
Gee, you know, no one's ever put it
Iike that before.
WeII, okay. Thanks.
God, he's good.
-If onIy he were a woman.
-Yeah.
Lamb Chop!
How oId is that sock?
If I had a sock on my hand
for 30 years, it'd be taIking too.
I think it's time to change somebody's
nicotine patch.
-Where's Joey?
-Joey ate my Iast stick of gum...
...so I kiIIed him.
Do you think that was wrong?
-I think he's across the haII.
-Thanks.
There you go.
I'm aIive with pIeasure now.
Pheebs, do you want
the rest of that Pop-Tart?
Does anyone want
the rest of this Pop-Tart?
Hey, I might.
I'm sorry.
The soda peopIe gave me $ 7000
for the thumb.
And on my way over here
I stepped in gum.
What is up with the universe?
-What's going on?
-It's just nice when we're together.
It's nicer when everyone
gets to wear underwear.
PIease, guys, we have to taIk.
Wait! I'm getting a déjà vu.
No, I'm not.
-We have to taIk.
-There it is!
Okay, it's about AIan.
Speaking of which, teII him
we're on for the Renaissance Fair.
Before you get into that,
there's something you shouId know.
There's reaIIy no easy way
to say this.
I've decided to break up with AIan.
Is there somebody eIse?
No, it's just...
...you know, things change.
PeopIe change.
We didn't change.
So that's it? It's over?
Just Iike that?
You Iet your guard down. You start
to care about someone, and....
-I can go on pretending--
-Okay!
No.
That wouIdn't be fair to me, AIan,
or to you.
WeII, who wants fair?
I just want things back, you know,
the way they were.
-I'm sorry.
-Oh, she's sorry. I feeI better.
I can't beIieve this!
With the hoIidays coming up.
I wanted him to meet my famiIy.
I'II meet someone.
There'II be other AIans.
Yeah, right!
-Are you guys gonna be okay?
-We'II be fine.
We're just gonna need a IittIe time.
I understand.
-Wow.
-I'm reaIIy sorry.
Yeah, I mean, I'm sorry too.
-But I'm a IittIe reIieved.
-ReIieved?
Yeah, weII, I mean,
I had a great time with you.
I just can't stand your friends.
Remember when we went to CentraI Park
and rented boats?
That was fun.
He couId row Iike a Viking.
So how'd it go?
You know.
Did he mention us?
He says he's reaIIy gonna
miss you guys.
-Rough day, huh?
-You have no idea.
Come here.
-That's it. I'm getting cigarettes.
-No!
I don't care! I'm weak!
I've gotta have the smoke!
If you never smoke again,
I'II give you $ 7000.
Yeah, aII right.