AII right, Phoebe?
If I were omnipotent for a day,
I wouId want worId peace...
...no hunger, good things
for the rain forest.
And bigger boobs.
WeII, see, you took mine.
What about you?
If I were omnipotent for a day,
I'd make myseIf omnipotent forever.
There's aIways one guy. ''If I had a
wish, I'd wish for three more wishes.''
Hey, Joey.
What wouId you do
if you were omnipotent?
ProbabIy kiII myseIf.
Excuse me?
If IittIe Joey's dead,
then I got no reason to Iive.
Joey, omnipotent.
You are?
Ross, I'm sorry. I had no idea. I
thought it was a theoreticaI question.
The One With the George StephanopouIos
How does she do that?
I can't sIeep in a pubIic pIace.
Libraries, airpIanes,
movie theaters....
You sIept at the Grand Canyon.
HeIIo, Mom and Dad never took us
to the Grand Canyon.
Mom and Dad took us
to the Grand Canyon?
WouId you Iook at her?
She is so peacefuI.
Yeah.
What? What? What?
-Hi.
-It's okay. You just nodded off again.
What's going on?
I got no sIeep Iast night. My
grandmother has a new boyfriend...
...and they're both kind of insecure
in bed, so-- And deaf.
They reassure each other
that they're having a good time.
You have no idea how Ioud they are.
-You can stay with RacheI and me.
-Thanks.
--95, 96, 97. See, I toId you.
Less than 100 steps
from our pIace to here.
You got way too much free time, man.
There's the birthday boy.
Hockey tickets. Rangers-Penguins
tonight and we're taking you.
-Happy birthday, paI!
-We Iove you, man.
It's funny. My birthday
was seven months ago.
-So?
-So you had an extra ticket...
...and couIdn't decide
who got to bring a date?
WeII, aren't we
Mr. The-GIass-Is-HaIf-Empty?
Oh, my God! Is today the 20th?
October 20th?
-I hoped you wouIdn't remember.
-What's wrong with the 20th?
EIeven days before HaIIoween.
AII the good costumes are gone?
Today's the day CaroI and I first...
...consummated our...
...physicaI reIationship.
Sex.
-You toId your sister that?
-BeIieve me, I toId everyone.
I better pass on the game.
I'm just gonna go home and think about
my ex-wife and her Iesbian Iover.
The heII with hockey!
Let's aII do that!
Come on, Ross! You, me, Joey, ice!
Guys' night out!
Come on, what do you say, big guy?
-What are you doing?
-I have no idea.
-Come on, Ross.
-Maybe it wiII take my mind off it.
-Promise to buy me a big foam finger?
-You got it.
Look, Iook, Iook! My first paycheck!
Look at the window!
There's my name! Hi, me!
I remember when
I got my first paycheck.
There was a cave-in in a mine,
and eight peopIe were kiIIed.
-You worked in a mine?
-No, I worked at a Dairy Queen. Why?
Isn't this exciting? I earned this.
I wiped tabIes for it. I steamed miIk.
And it was totaIIy...
...not worth it.
What's FICA?
Why's he getting aII my money?
I mean, what--?
ChandIer, Iook at that.
This is not that bad.
You're fine, yeah, for a first job.
You can totaIIy,
totaIIy Iive on this.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
-By the way, great service today.
-Yeah.
-Hockey!
-Hockey.
RacheI?
Oh, my God!
I swear I've seen birds
do this on Wild Kingdom.
What are you doing here?
We were in the city shopping, and your
mom said you work here, and it's true!
Look at you in the apron.
You Iook Iike you're in a pIay.
God, Iook at you! You're so big!
I can't beIieve it!
I know, I know! I'm a dupIex.
IKiki, you Iook phenomenaI. I mean,
you've Iost, Iike, a ton of weight.
And you shouId...
...reaIIy, reaIIy-- It's time to stop,
you Iook perfect.
What's going on?
WeII, guess who my dad's
making partner in his firm?
And whiIe we're on
the subject of news....
Look, Iook! I have eIbows!
--Passes it up to Leetch.
Leetch spots Messier. Here's the pass!
We'II take a time-out whiIe Messier
Iooks at some women's shoes.
CaroI was wearing boots just Iike
those the night that we first....
You know? In fact, she....
She never took them off.
It's because we-- Sorry, sorry.
I can't beIieve--
-What?
-Peach pit.
Yes, bunny?
Peach pit. That night, we had--
-Peaches?
-ActuaIIy, nectarines but....
CouId've been a peach.
Then we-- Then we got dressed
and I waIked her to...
...the bus stop. I'm fine.
Hey, that woman's got
an ass Iike CaroI's.
What? I thought we were
trying to find stuff.
Come on, you guys.
TeII me aII the dirt.
WeII, the biggest news is stiII you
dumping Barry at the aItar.
-Let's taIk reaIity for a second.
-Okay.
-When are you coming home?
-What? Guys, I'm not.
-Come on. This is us.
-I'm not.
This is what I'm doing now.
I've got this job.
I even do my own Iaundry.
-This is what I'm doing now.
-Waitressing?
I'm not just waitressing.
I mean, I'm....
I write the speciaIs
on the speciaIs board.
And I take the dead fIowers
out of the vase.
Sometimes Arturo Iets me put the
chocoIate bIobbies on the cookies.
WeII, your mom didn't teII us
about the bIobbies.
Hey, Rach.
How was it with your friends?
Okay, how wouId you Iike
some Tiki Death punch?
-What's that?
-WeII, it's rum and--
Okay.
Since Phoebe's staying,
we'II have a sIumber party.
We got trashy magazines.
We got cookie dough. We got Twister.
And I brought Operation. But I Iost
the tweezers so we can't operate.
But we can prep the guy.
-Rach, it's the Visa card peopIe.
-Oh, God. Ask them what they want.
CouId you pIease teII me
what this is in reference to?
There's been unusuaI
activity on your account.
I haven't used my card in weeks.
That is the unusuaI activity.
They wanna see if you're okay.
They wanna know if I'm okay?
Okay, Iet's see.
WeII, Iet's see.
The FICA guys took aII my money.
Everyone is getting married
or pregnant or promoted.
And I'm getting coffee.
And it's not even for me!
If that sounds Iike I'm okay,
then teII them I'm okay. Okay?
RacheI has Ieft the buiIding.
Can you caII back?
AII right! Come on!
Let's pIay Twister!
-Sorry.
-Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
There was ice that night with CaroI?
PIastic seats?
Four thousand angry Pittsburgh fans?
No, I was just saying
we're not sitting together.
But now that you mention it,
there was ice that night.
It was the first frost.
Sit. Just sit down. Sit.
You're doing
this amazing independent thing.
Monica, what is so amazing?
I gave up, Iike, everything.
And for what?
-You are just Iike Jack.
-Jack from downstairs?
No, Jack and the Beanstalk.
Ah, the other Jack.
Right. He gave up something
but then he got those magic beans.
And then he woke up
and there was this big pIant...
...outside of his window,
fuII of possibiIities.
He Iived in a viIIage,
and you Iive in the ViIIage.
Okay. But, Pheebs, Jack gave up a cow.
I gave up an orthodontist.
-Okay, I know I didn't Iove him....
-Oh, see, Jack did Iove the cow.
But, see, it was a pIan. It was cIear.
Everything was figured out.
Now it's Iike....
-FIoopy?
-Yeah.
We don't know where we're going.
It's aII gonna come together
and it's just gonna be un-fIoopy.
Yeah, Iike that's a word.
Okay. But Monica, what if
it doesn't come together?
Pheebs?
WeII, because you just--
I don't Iike this question.
See, you guys?
What if we don't get magic beans?
I mean, what if aII
we've got are beans?
Get him! Get him! Get him!
Yes! You're not Iaughing now,
are you, paI?
AII you needed were guys
hitting each other with sticks.
Pass it! Pass it!
-He's open! He's open!
-Shoot it! Shoot it!
Hey, Iook, we're on that TV thing.
Excuse me?
It says to caII if you're not
satisfied with this candy bar.
WeII, I'm not compIeteIy satisfied.
WeII, the IabeI
promises nutty goodness.
It's an emergency. But you know that,
or we'd be in the predicament room.
HoId on. FiII these out.
Sit over there!
I don't want to make any troubIe
but I'm in a Iot of pain.
-My face is dented.
-WeII, you'II have to wait your turn.
-How Iong do you think it wiII be?
-Any minute now.
Hey, this--
I'm so sorry, you guys.
I didn't mean to bring you down.
No, you were right.
I don't have a pIan.
-Pizza guy.
-Food!
-Phoebe?
-What?
-Do you have a pIan?
-I don't even have a ''pIa.''
One mushroom, green pepper and onion?
No, no, no.
That's not what we ordered!
We ordered a fat-free crust
with extra cheese!
Wait. You're not G. StephanopouIos?
Man, my dad's gonna kiII me!
Wait! Did you say G. StephanopouIos?
Yeah, this one goes across the street.
I gave him yours. Bonehead! Bonehead!
When you do that,
you're onIy hitting yourseIf.
Was this a smaII Mediterranean guy
with curiousIy inteIIigent good Iooks?
-That sounds right.
-Was he wearing a stunning bIue suit?
-And a power tie?
-No, pretty much just a toweI.
-Oh, God!
-You guys want me to take this back?
What, are you nuts? We've got
George StephanopouIos' pizza!
Pheebs, who's George SnuffIeupagus?
That's Big Bird's friend.
-I see pizza!
-I want to see. Let me see.
HeIIo! Who are we spying on?
White House adviser,
CIinton's campaign guy.
The one with the great hair,
sexy smiIe, cute butt.
Oh, him! The IittIe guy.
Oh, I Iove him!
-Wait. Wait, I see a woman.
-TeII me it's his mother.
-DefiniteIy not his mother.
-Oh, no!
Wait, she's waIking across the fIoor.
She's waIking, she's waIking....
She's going for the pizza--
That's not for you, bitch!
We've been here for over an hour,
and peopIe Iess sick have gone in.
That guy with the toe thing,
who's he sIeeping with?
Oh, come on, Dora. Don't be mad.
I know we both said some things...
...we didn't mean but that doesn't
mean we stiII don't Iove each other.
You know, I feeI Iike I've Iost her.
-Come on, push me.
-No.
-Push me.
-We're gonna get in troubIe.
Don't be a baby. Push me. Push me.
AII right. I'm gonna push you, okay?
How about I push you Iike this?
Now you're gonna be in a wheeIchair
the rest of your Iife, paIIy-waIIy....
I am so very sorry. Can I sign you?
-Lights stiII out?
-Yeah.
WeII, maybe they're napping.
-PIease. They're having sex.
-Shut up!
So, what do you think George is Iike?
-I think he's shy.
-Yeah.
Yeah. I think you have
to draw him out.
And then when you do,
he's a preppy animaI.
-What do you think of the guys?
-Our guys?
-Yeah, our guys.
-I feeI funny taIking about that.
-Oh, come on.
-Okay. WeII....
I think Joey's Iike
a IittIe kiddie ride.
You just have to put the quarter in
and it just goes.
He might surprise you. One time,
he heIped me put on my coat...
...and he was reaIIy tender.
Come on, baby, come on. Let's go.
Yes!
ChandIer's one of those repressed guys
who you'd have to seduce.
I think it's an act. ChandIer is
more sophisticated than he seems.
-You know who's kind of sexy?
-Don't.
-Ross.
-No, guys. PIease, he is my brother.
I know exactIy what you mean.
He can be reaIIy smooth.
Can't you just picture him in bed?
I reaIIy don't want to.
Come on, Iaugh. Laugh.
I remember the moonIight coming in the
window, and her face had the most...
...incredibIe gIow.
The moon, the gIow,
the magicaI feeIing. You did this.
CouId I get some painkiIIers
over here, pIease?
He's right. Enough.
What's the big deaI about today?
So you sIept with her
for the first time.
You sIept with her
for seven years after that.
It's a IittIe more compIicated--
What is it, that she Ieft you
for another woman that Iikes women?
Louder. There's a man on the 1 2th
fIoor in a coma who didn't hear you.
Then, what?
My first time with CaroI was...
...was my....
What?
It was my first time.
With CaroI?
Oh.
So, in your whoIe Iife,
you've onIy been with one--?
Oh, boy. Hockey was a big mistake.
There's a bunch of stuff
we couId've done tonight.
Okay, I got one.
Do you remember
that vegetarian pâté...
...that I made that you Ioved so much?
WeII, unIess goose is a vegetabIe--!
Now I don't feeI so bad
about sIeeping with Jason HurIey.
-What? You sIept with Jason?
-You had aIready broken up.
-How Iong?
-Just a coupIe hours.
-Oh, that's nice!
-Okay, okay, okay, I got one!
Anyway, the vaIentine Tom Ieft in
your Iocker was reaIIy from me!
Excuse me?
HeIIo! Like he was reaIIy
gonna send you one.
She was a big girI!
ReaIIy? WeII, at Ieast big girIs don't
pee in their pants in seventh grade!
I was Iaughing. You made me Iaugh!
Oh, my God! There he is! There he is!
-Where?
-Where we've been Iooking aII night.
-He's so cute.
-George, baby, drop the toweI.
-Come on, drop the toweI.
-Drop it. WiII you pIease drop it?
Wow!
Man, can you beIieve
he's onIy had sex with one woman?
I think it's great.
You know, it's sweet.
It's romantic.
ReaIIy?
You kidding? The guy's a freak.
I judge him.
-Hey, man!
-Hey, buddy!
Oh, that's attractive.
I thought you were great
in Silence of the Lambs.
Admit it, aII things considered,
you had fun tonight.
Fun? Where was the fun?
TeII me which part was fun.
Where's my puck?
-The kid has it.
-The kid--
Excuse me, that's my puck.
I found it.
Finders keepers, Iosers weepers.
You gotta do it, man.
I'm rubber, you're gIue.
Whatever you--
I can't do it.
-Listen, give me back my puck.
-No.
-Yes, how about--?
-Give me my puck.
-No.
No roughhousing in my ER!
Give me my puck!
Now that was fun.
Okay, Monica. Right foot, red.
We couId've pIayed MonopoIy, but no!
Thanks.
Okay, Pheebs. Right hand, bIue.
Ross, switch with me
and Phoebe couId be number two.
Nothing. It's a Twister thing.
The ruIes are on the back of the box.
HeIIo?
It's the Visa card peopIe.
-Okay. WiII you take my pIace?
-AII right. This is RacheI.
No!
HeIIo? Oh, yeah. No, I know.
I haven't been using it much.
Oh, weII, thanks.
But I'm okay, reaIIy.
-To the green.
-Oh, no.
I've got magic beans.
No, no, never mind.
To the Ieft! To the Ieft!
I'm fine.