Terry, I know I haven't worked here very long but would it be possible if I got a $100 advance on my salary?
An advance?
So I can spend Thanksgiving with my family.
Every year we ski in Vail, and my father pays for my ticket.
But I've started this independent thing which is actually why I took this ''job.''
Rachel, Rachel, sweetheart!
You're a terrible, terrible waitress.
Really, really awful.
I hear what you're saying. I'm with you.
But I'm trying really hard, and I think I'm doing better.
I really do.
Does anybody need coffee?
Yeah, over here.
Look at that.
Excuse me, sir? Hi. You come in here all the time.
Do you think there's a possibility that you could advance me my tips?
Okay, okay. That's fine. Fine. Sorry about that spill before!
Only 98.50 to go!
Did you know Mom and Dad are going to Puerto Rico for Thanksgiving?
What? No, they're not.
Yes, the Blymans invited them.
You're wrong.
I am not wrong.
No, I just talked to them.
I'm calling Mom.
Hey, hey.
Hey!
And this from the Cry for Help Department: Are you wearing makeup?
Yes, I am. As of today, I'm officially Joey Tribbiani, actor/model.
That's funny. I was thinking you look more like, Joey Tribbiani, man/woman.
What were you modeling for?
Posters for the free clinic.
So you're gonna be one of those healthy guys?
The asthma guy's really cute.
Know which one you'll be?
No, but I hear Lyme disease is open, so you know....
Good luck, man. I hope you get it.
Thanks.
You were right. How can they do this? It's Thanksgiving!
What if I cook dinner at my place? I'll make it just like Mom's.
Will you make mashed potatoes with the lumps?
They're not actually supposed to-- I'll work on the lumps.
Joey, you're going home?
Yeah.
Chandler, you're still boycotting all the pilgrim holidays?
Every single one of them.
Phoebe, you'll be with your grandma?
And her boyfriend.
We're celebrating Thanksgiving in December because he's lunar.
So you're free Thursday then?
Yeah. Oh, can I come?
Yeah.
Rach, are you gonna make it to Vail?
Absolutely. Shoop, shoop, shoop.
Only $102 to go.
I thought it was 98.50?
Yeah, well, it was, but I-- I broke a cup, so....
Well, I'm off to Carol's.
Ooh, ooh, why don't we invite her?
Ooh, ooh, because she's my ex-wife and will want to bring her ooh, ooh, lesbian life partner.
Hi. Is Carol here?
No, she's at a faculty meeting.
I just came by to pick up my skull.
Well, not mine, but....
Come in.
Thanks.
Carol borrowed it, and I have to get it back to the museum.
What's it look like?
Kind of like a big face without skin.
Yes. I'm familiar with the concept.
We can just look for it.
Okay.
Wow, you guys sure have a lot of books about being a lesbian.
Well, you know, you have to take a course.
Otherwise they don't let you do it.
Hey, Yertle the Turtle! A classic.
Actually, I'm reading it to the baby.
The baby that hasn't been born yet?
Wouldn't that mean you're crazy?
You don't think they can hear sounds in there?
You're not serious? I mean, you really talk to it?
Yeah, all the time. I want the baby to know my voice.
Well, that's just-- Do you talk about me?
Yeah. All the time.
Really?
But, we just refer to you as ''Bobo the Sperm Guy.''
If she's talking to it, I just think I should get some belly time too.
Not that I believe this.
I believe it. I think the baby can hear everything.
Really?
I'll show you. This'll seem weird.
But you put your head inside this turkey and we'll all talk and you'll hear everything we say.
I'd just like to say I'm totally behind this experiment.
In fact, I'd very much like to butter your head.
Hey.
Rach, did you make your money?
No, not even close. Forget Vail. Forget seeing my family.
Forget shoop, shoop, shoop.
Rach, here's your mail.
Thanks. You can put it on the table.
No. Here's your mail!
Thanks. You can put it on the table!
Would you just open it!
Oh, my God! You guys are great!
We all chipped in.
We did?
You owe me $20.
Thank you. Thank you so much!
Chandler, got your traditional holiday feast. Tomato soup grilled-cheese fixings and a family-size bag of Funyuns.
This is your Thanksgiving dinner? What is it with you and this holiday?
I'm 9 years old.
I hate this story!
We've finished this magnificent Thanksgiving dinner. I have a mouthful of pumpkin pie.
And then my parents tell me they're getting divorced.
Oh, my God!
Very difficult to enjoy Thanksgiving dinner once you've seen it in reverse.
What's this? I never saw this at Mom's.
It's a yam.
Hello....
This isn't a yam. Yam comes in purple cans.
They don't-- They don't come in these.
Ross, don't take this the wrong way or anything, but back off.
Hi.
We used to work together.
We did?
Yeah, at Macy's. You're the Obsession girl, right?
Yes.
I was the Aramis guy.
Aramis. Aramis. Aramis.
Yeah, right!
You're the best in the business.
Get out.
You're amazing! You know when to spritz. You know when to lay back.
Really? You don't know what that means to me.
You smell great tonight. What are you wearing?
Nothing.
Listen, do you wanna go get a drink?
Yeah, that would be--
What's wrong?
I have to do something.
What?
Leave.
Wait, wait, wait!
So I guess you all saw it.
What?
Saw what?
No, we're just laughing. You know how laughter can be infectious.
Set another place for Thanksgiving. My entire family thinks I have VD.
''Tonight, on a very special Blossom. ''
Looking good! Okay!
Cider's mulling, turkey's turkeying, yams are yamming....
What?
I don't know. It's just not the same without Mom in the kitchen.
Get out and stop annoying me!
Oh, that's closer.
I got the tickets!
Five hours from now, shoop, shoop, shoop!
Oh, you must stop shooping.
Okay, I'm gonna get my stuff.
Will you come in?
I prefer to keep a safe distance from all this merriment.
Look out! Incoming pumpkin pie!
We laughed when you did it with the stuffing, but that's not funny.
Hey, Monica, I got a question. I don't see any Tator Tots.
That's not a question.
My mom makes them. It's a tradition.
You get a piece of turkey on your fork, a little cranberry sauce and a Tot!
I mean, it's bad enough I can't be with my family because of my disease.
All right. Fine.
Tonight's potatoes will be mashed, with lumps and in the form of Tots.
All right, I'm off to talk to my unborn child.
Okay, Mom never hit.
Okay, all done.
Phoebe, did you whip the pota--? Ross needs lumps!
Oh, I'm sorry! I just--
I thought we could have them whipped and then add some peas and onions.
Why do that?
Because then they'd be just like my mom used to make it, before she died.
Okay. Three kinds of potatoes coming up.
Okay. Goodbye, you guys! Thanks for everything!
Oh, God, look at-- Sorry! I'm so sorry.
An unbelievable thing happened! Underdog got away!
The balloon?
No, no, the actual cartoon character.
Of course the balloon!
He broke free and was spotted flying over Washington Square Park.
I'm going to the roof. Who's with me?
I can't!
An 80-foot dog over the city? How often does that happen?
Almost never.
Got the keys?
Okay.
Anytime you're ready.
Okay. Okay, here we go.
Okay. Where am I talking to here?
There is one way that offers a certain acoustical advantage, but....
Just aim for the bump.
Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay, here goes.
You know, I can't do this. This is--
It's too weird. I feel stupid.
It's fine. You don't have to do it just because Susan does it.
Hello, baby. Hello. Hello.
--the moment we first saw the dog shadow fall over the park!
But did they have to shoot him down? That was just mean.
Right now the turkey should be crispy on the outside and juicy on the inside.
Why are we standing here?
We're waiting for you to open the door. You have the keys.
No, I don't.
Yes, you do. When we left, you said, ''Got the keys.''
No, I didn't. I asked, ''Got the keys?''
No, no, no. You said, ''Got the keys!''
Do either of you have the keys?
The oven is on!
I've gotta get my ticket!
Wait! We have a copy of your key.
Get it!
That tone won't make me go any faster.
Joey.
That one will.
And everyone's telling me, ''You gotta pick a major.''
So on a dare, I picked paleontology.
And you have no idea what I'm saying, because, face it, you're a fetus.
You're happy you don't have gills anymore.
You don't have to talk to it. You can sing--
Please. I am not singing to your stomach, okay?
How's it going?
Here we come
Walking down the street
Get the funniest looks from Everyone we meet
Hey, hey--
Hey, did you just feel that?
I did.
Does it always--?
That was the first.
Keep singing! Keep singing!
Hey, hey, you're my baby And I can't wait to meet you
When you come out I'll buy you a bagel Then we'll go to the zoo
It did it again!
I felt it that time!
Hey, hey, I'm your daddy I'm the one without any breasts
This is great. It's 5:00. My plane is pulling away from the gate.
Maybe you can take a later flight.
There is none.
You can go tomorrow.
Tomorrow is not Thanksgiving!
If I'm gonna cheer you up, you have to meet me halfway.
Can you go any faster?
I got one keyhole and a zillion keys! You do the math.
Why do you guys have so many keys in there anyway?
For an emergency just like this.
All right. Listen, smirky!
If not for your stupid balloon, I'd be on a plane watching a woman do this...right now. But I'm not!
You said you had the keys!
No, I didn't! I wouldn't say I had the keys unless I had the keys!
That's it! Enough with the keys. No one say keys!
Why would I have the keys?!
Aside from the fact you said you did?
I didn't!
You should've.
Why?
Because!
Everything's my responsibility? Isn't it enough that I'm making dinner?
Everyone wants a different kind of potato, so I'm making them.
Does anybody care what kind of potatoes I want? No!
No! No!
Just as long as Phoebe gets her peas and onions, and Mario gets his Tots--
It's my first Thanksgiving, and I--
It's all burnt, and I can't....
Monica, only dogs can hear you now. Look, the door's open. Here we go.
All right, Chandler, don't lose this.
No--
Well, the turkey's burnt!
Potatoes are ruined! Potatoes are ruined! Potatoes are ruined!
Here we come
Walking down the--
This doesn't smell like Mom's.
It doesn't, does it? You wanted lumps? Here you go, buddy. You got one!
Don't yell at me. You burned dinner!
Hey, don't make her squeak again!
God, this is great! The plane is gone. I guess I'm stuck here with you guys.
We all had better plans. This was nobody's first choice!
Oh, really? So why was I busting my ass to make this delicious dinner?
You call that delicious?
You be quiet!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Now this feels like Thanksgiving.
Skiing.
Shoop, shoop, shoop....
Shoop.
Eww.
What?
Ugly Naked Guy's taking his turkey out of the oven.
Who cares?
He just sat in gravy.
Oh, my God! He's not alone.
Ugly Naked Guy is having Thanksgiving dinner with Ugly Naked Gal.
I gotta see this!
All right, Ugly Naked Guy!
Ugly naked dancing!
It's nice that he has someone.
Shall I carve?
By all means.
All right.
Who wants light cheese, and who wants dark cheese?
I don't even want to know about the dark cheese.
Does anybody wanna split this?
I will.
You guys have to make a wish.
Make a wish?
Come on, you know, Thanksgiving.
You got the bigger half! What did you wish for?
The bigger half.
All right, I'd like to propose a toast.
A little toast here. Ding, ding!
This isn't the Thanksgiving you planned but for me, this has been really great.
I think because it didn't involve divorce or projectile vomiting.
If you'd gone to Vail or if you had been with your family or if you didn't have syphilis and stuff...we wouldn't be together.
I guess what I'm trying to say is that I'm very thankful that all of your Thanksgivings sucked.
That's so sweet!
Thank you.
Here's to a lousy Christmas!
And a crappy New Year!
Hear, hear!
All right! You guys, it's starting to snow.
And look, Ugly Naked Guy is hanging candy canes.
Where?
Oh. Well.
That's festive.
Guys, there's somebody I'd like you to meet.
Wait, wait. What is that?
That's Marcel. Wanna say hi?
No, I don't.
He's cute! Where'd you get him?
My friend Bethel saved him from a lab.
That is so cruel.
Why would a parent name their child Bethel?
That monkey's got a Ross on his ass.
Is he gonna live with you in your apartment?
Yeah. It's been kind of quiet since Carol left.
Why not get a roommate?
You reach a certain age, having a roommate is just kind of pathet--
That's ''pathet.'' Sanskrit for ''really cool way to live.''
I'm doing new material tonight.
I have 1 2 songs about my mother's suicide and one about a snowman.
You might wanna open with the snowman.
Hi, Joey.
Hey, buddy.
So how'd it go?
I didn't get the job.
How could you not? You were Santa last year.
Some fat guy's sleeping with the store manager.
He's not even jolly. It's all political.
What are you gonna be?
One of his helpers.
It's just such a slap in the face, you know?
Do you know what you're doing for New Year's?
Hey, what? What is wrong with New Year's?
You have Paolo. You don't have to face the pressure of finding lips to kiss when the ball drops!
Man, I'm talking loud!
Paolo's gonna be in Rome this New Year's.
I'll be just as pathetic as you.
Yeah, you wish.
I've got an idea. Dinner.
It's perfect. We'll put it between lunch and breakfast.
I'm sick of being a victim of this Dick Clark holiday.
I say this year, we make a pact. Just the six of us. Dinner.
Sure.
Fine.
I was hoping for more enthusiasm.
Phoebe, you're on.
Oh, good.
Hi. Ladies and gentlemen, back by popular demand Miss Phoebe Buffay.
Hi. Thanks. Hi.
I wanna start with a song that means a lot to me.
I made a man with eyes of coal
And a smile so bewitching
How was I supposed to know
That my mom was dead in the kitchen?
My mother's ashes
Even her eyelashes
Are resting in a little yellow jar
And sometimes when it's freezing
I feel a little sneezy
And now I-- Excuse me? Excuse me? Yeah, noisy boys.
Is it something you'd like to share with the group?
No. No, that's okay.
If it's important enough while I'm playing it's important enough for everyone else.
That guy's going home with a note.
I was just saying--
Speak up.
Sorry, I--
I was saying you were the most beautiful woman I'd ever seen.
And he said that Daryl Hannah was the most beautiful woman he'd ever seen.
I said I liked her in Splash, but not Wall Street.
I thought she had a hard quality.
While Daryl is beautiful in a conventional way you are luminous with a kind of delicate grace.
Then that's when you started yelling.
We're gonna take a short break.
That guy's going home with more than a note.
Come here, Marcel. Sit here.
I can't believe he hasn't kissed you yet.
By my sixth date with Paolo, he'd already named both my breasts.
Did I just share too much?
Just a smidge.
David's, like, a scientist guy. He's very methodical.
I think it's romantic.
Me too!
Did you ever see An Officer and a Gentleman?
He's kind of like the guy I went to see that with.
Except he's smarter and gentler and sweeter.
I just wanna be with him all the time.
You know, day and night. And night and day.
And special occasions.
I see. You're gonna ask him to New Year's.
She's gonna break the pact.
No! No, no.
No. Yeah, could I just--?
Yeah. I already asked Janice.
What?
This was a pact! This was your pact!
I couldn't handle the pressure. I snapped!
But that was the worst breakup in history!
I'm not saying it was a good idea. I snapped!
Hi, sorry I'm late.
Too many jokes.
Must mock Joey.
Nice shoes, huh?
God, you're killing me!
Ross, he's playing with my spatulas again!
He's not gonna hurt them, right?
Do you always have to bring him?
I didn't wanna leave him alone. We had our first fight this morning.
It has to do with my working late. I said some things that I didn't mean.
He threw some feces.
If you're working late, I can look in on him.
That would be great!
But make sure it seems like you're there to see him.
You're not doing it for me.
Okay. But if he asks, I'm not going to lie.
But you can't actually test this theory.
Today's particle accelerators aren't powerful enough to simulate these conditions.
I have a question then.
Yeah?
Do you plan on kissing me ever?
That's definitely a valid question, and the answer would be yes. Yes, I was.
But I wanted it to be this phenomenal kiss at a phenomenal moment because it's you.
Sure.
The longer I waited, the more phenomenal the kiss had to be.
Now, it's just gotta be one of those things where I sweep everything off the table.
And I'm not really a sweeping sort of fella.
David, I think you are a sweeping sort of fella.
I mean, you're a sweeper trapped inside a physicist's body.
Really?
I'm sure.
You should just do it. Just throw me.
Now?
Yeah, right now. Just....
Okay. Okay. Okay.
You know what? This is really expensive.
And this was a gift.
Now you're just tidying up.
Okay.
You want me to throw you--?
I can hop.
Tell me something, what does ''no-date pact'' mean to you?
It's just that Chandler and Phoebe have somebody.
I thought I'd ask Fun Bobby.
Your ex-boyfriend?
Yeah.
You know more than one Fun Bobby?
I happen to know a Fun Bob.
Okay. Here we go.
There's no room for milk.
There. Now there is.
So on our no-date evening, three of you now have dates.
Four.
Five.
Sorry. Paolo's catching an earlier flight.
And I met this really hot single mom at the store.
What's an elf to do?
So I'll be the only one alone when the ball drops?
We'll have a big party, and no one will know who's with who.
I'll know. This is so not what I needed right now.
What's the matter?
Oh, it's Marcel.
He's angry with me. I have no idea why. He keeps shutting me out.
He's walking around all the time, dragging his hands.
That's weird. I had a blast with him.
Really?
We played, watched TV.
That juggling thing is amazing.
What juggling thing?
With the socks? I figured you taught him that.
No.
It wasn't that big a deal. Just socks. And a melon.
Phoebe!
Max. Do you know everybody?
No. Have you seen David?
He hasn't been around.
If you see him, tell him to pack. We are going to Minsk.
Minsk?
Minsk. It's in Russia.
I know where Minsk is.
We got the grant. Three years, all expenses paid.
And if you're gonna do Minsk, that's the way to go.
So when do you leave?
January 1st.
Hello?
What? Hey. Hi.
What are you doing here?
Max told me about Minsk.
Congratulations! This is so exciting!
It'd be even more exciting if we were going.
Oh, you're not going? Oh, why?
Tell her. ''I don't wanna go to work with Lipson, Yamaguchi and Flank.
I wanna stay and make out with my girlfriend!''
Okay, thank you, Max. Thank you.
So you're really not going?
I don't know what I'm gonna do. I just....
How can I leave you? I just found you.
Oh, David. But what are you gonna do?
I don't know. You decide.
Don't do that.
But I'm asking you.
I can't make a decision. Just--
Okay. Stay.
Stay.
Getting so good at that!
It was Max's stuff.
I love this artichoke thing.
Don't tell me what's in it. The diet starts tomorrow.
You remember Janice.
Vividly.
How are you?
I am fantastic.
Now.
It's amazing. We've been back together for what like 10 minutes, and--
Is that all?
It's like we were never apart.
Of course, we were, but-- Forgive and forget.
Well, forget.
Hi.
Hi, I'm Sandy.
Sandy, hi. Come on in.
You brought your kids.
Yeah. That's okay, right?
Party!
That thing is not coming in here!
This is how you greet guests?
If I showed up with my new girlfriend, she wouldn't be welcome?
Your new girlfriend wouldn't urinate on my coffee table.
He was more embarrassed about that than anyone.
And for him to have the courage to walk back in here like nothing happened--
All right. All right. Just keep him away from me.
Thank you. Come on, Marcel.
What do you say you and I mingle?
All right, I'll catch up with you later.
Oh, my gosh! Rachel, honey, are you okay?
Where's Paolo?
Rome. Jerk missed his flight.
And then your face exploded?
No.
Okay. I was at the airport getting into a cab when this woman, this blond planet with a pocketbook starts yelling. Something about how it was her cab first.
The next thing, she just starts pulling me out by my hair!
And I was blowing my attack whistle thingy and three more cabs show up.
So as I'm going to get into a cab, she tackles me!
And I hit my head on the curb and cut my lip on my whistle.
Everybody having fun at the party?
Are people eating my dip?
Yes.
There.
That looks okay, right?
You went a bit wide on the lipstick.
Oh, I did?
Yeah.
It's hard for me to tell. My eye's closing up.
Let me get it for you.
Ow!
Okay.
You know what? It looks fine.
Okay, here we go.
Screw Paolo, screw the psycho cab lady.
It's New Year's Eve. Let's have a good time.
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
All right, there you go. This way.
Here you go.
When I saw you at the store last week it was the first time I ever mentally undressed an elf.
Wow, that's dirty.
Yeah.
Hey, kids.
He doesn't have to spend the whole evening with me but at least check in.
There you are!
You got away from me.
But you found me.
Here, Ross, take our picture.
Smile. You're on Janice Camera.
IKill me. IKill me now.
Hi, I'm Rachel.
So whose friend are you?
Look at me, spilling everywhere.
Everybody, it's Fun Bobby!
Hey, sorry I'm late. But my grandfather died about two hours ago.
But I couldn't get a flight out till tomorrow, so here I am.
Hey, Fun Bobby! How's it going, man? Whoa! Who died?
It's gonna be an open casket, you know?
So at least I'll get to see him again.
Bobby? Fun Bobby?
Let me talk to you for just a sec.
I recently lost a grandparent myself so I really know exactly how you feel.
But you're really bringing the party down.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
There you go. There you go.
I'm gonna blow this one up and write ''Reunited'' in glitter.
All right, Janice, that's it!
Janice. Janice.
Hey, Janice, when I invited you, I didn't think it meant--
Oh, no!
I'm sorry you misunderstood.
You listen to me! You listen to me!
One of these times, it's just gonna be your last chance with me!
Will you give me the thing?
Hi, Max.
Yoko.
I've decided to go to Minsk without you.
Wow.
It won't be the same...but it will still be Minsk. Happy New Year.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Come on.
You're going to Minsk.
No, I'm not going to Minsk.
You are so going to Minsk.
You belong in Minsk. You can't stay here just for me.
If I go, I have to break up with you.
And I can't break up with you.
Yes, you can.
Just say, ''Phoebe, I love you, but my work is my life.
That's what I have to do.''
And I say, ''Your work? How can you say that?''
Then you say, ''I have no choice. Can't you understand that?''
And I say, ''No! No! I can't understand that!''
Ow.
Sorry.
And then you put your arms around me.
Then you put your arms around me.
Oh, sorry.
And then you tell me you love me and you'll never forget me.
I'll never forget you.
Then you say that you have to go because you don't wanna start the year with me if you can't finish it.
I'm gonna miss you, you scientist guy.
Hi, Dick Clark in Times Square.
We're in a virtual snowstorm of confetti here in Times Square.
It gets better every....
Here you go, kids.
And then the peacock bit me.
Please kiss me at midnight!
You seen Sandy?
I don't know how to tell you this but she's in the bedroom getting it on with Max.
Oh, I did know how to tell you.
Hey, everybody, the ball is dropping.
What?
The ball is dropping!
In 20 seconds, it'll be midnight.
And the moment of joy is upon us.
Looks like that no-date pact worked out.
Everybody looks so happy. I hate that!
Not everybody is happy. Hey, Bobby!
--four, three, two one! Happy New Year!
I thought I'd throw this out. I'm no math whiz but I do believe there are three girls and three guys right here.
I don't feel like kissing anyone tonight.
I can't kiss anyone.
So, I'm kissing everyone?
No, you can't kiss Ross. That's your brother.
So now everybody's getting kissed but me.
Somebody kiss me.
Somebody kiss me! It's midnight! Somebody kiss me!
All right! All right!
There!
I wanted this to work so much.
I'm still in there.
Changing his diapers. Picking his fleas.
But he's just phoning it in.
It's hard that something you love so much doesn't love you back.
I think that bitch cracked my tooth.
Do you think they have yesterday's Daily News?
I just wanna check my horoscope, see if it was right.
Oh, my God! Don't look now. Behind you there's a guy who can break our hearts and plunge us into depression.
Come to mama.
He's coming. Be cool. Be cool. Be cool.
Nice hat.
Thanks.
We should do something. Whistle.
I'm not whistling.
Come on, do it!
Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it.
I can't believe you did that.
It's all my fault.
No, it's mine.
Why did I whoo-hoo?
Was I hoping he'd turn around and say ''I love that sound. I must have you now''?
I wish there was something we could do.
Hello, coma guy.
Get up, you Girl Scout! Up, up, up!
What are you doing?
Maybe nobody's tried this.
I wish we at least knew his name.
I hate that they're calling him John Doe.
It's so sad. It's like he's a deer, a female deer.
Oh, I was gonna stop.
Look at that face.
Even sleeping he looks smart.
Yeah, but the dents in his knuckles mean he's artistic.
Okay. He's a lawyer who teaches sculpting on the side.
And he can dance.
And he's the kind of guy who, when you're talking, he's listening not saying, ''I understand'' but really wondering what you look like naked.
I wish all guys could be like him.
I know.
You don't even know this guy.
Are there no conscious men in the city for you two?
He doesn't have anyone.
We feel kind of responsible.
I can't believe you said ''whoo-hoo.''
I don't even say ''whoo-hoo.''
Oh, she's coming up.
When we return, we'll talk with the always interesting Nora Tyler Bing.
Put the kids to bed for this one.
Don't watch this. Weekend at Bernie's is on Showtime and HBO.
No way.
She's your mom.
Exactly. Weekend at Bernie's.
Dead guy getting hit in the groin 20, 30 times.
I gotta tell you, I love your mom's books.
I can't get on a plane without one. This is so cool.
You wouldn't think so if you were 1 1  and your friends were passing around page 79 of Mistress Bitch.
I remember page 79.
The thing after the opera with the girl with the trick hip?
I love your mom. I think she's a blast.
That's because she's not your mom.
Oh, please. She's the--
Hi, sweetie.
When did ''Rigatoni'' get back from Rome?
Last night.
Really?
So, his plane didn't explode in a big ball of fire?
Just a dream I had.
But, phew!
Hey, she's on.
Nora Bing.
Back to the book. What is this about you being arrested in London?
Your mom was arrested?
I'm busy beaming with pride.
This is kind of embarrassing...but occasionally, after I've been intimate with a man...
Why would she say that's embarrassing?
...I just get this craving for kung pao chicken.
That's too much information.
Needless to say, he got a huge tip.
Oh, God, I love her!
I think I'm having a stroke.
So how is your book tour going?
Oh, fine. I'm leaving for New York tomorrow, which I hate.
But I get to see my son, who I love.
This is the way that I find out. Most moms use the phone.
Don't take this wrong, I just don't see you as a mom.
-I don't mean that bad.
-Oh, no. I'm a fabulous mom.
I bought my son his first condoms.
And then he burst into flames.
Let's see. Congress is debating a new deficit-reduction bill.
The mayor wants to raise subway fares. The high today was 45.
And teams played sports.
What about Glen?
He could be a Glen.
Not special enough.
How about Agamemnon?
Way too special.
I'm famished. What do I want?
Please, God, don't let it be kung pao chicken.
You watched the show. What did you think?
I think you need to come out of your shell.
What is this dive?
Only you could've picked this place.
Come on. Shut up. It's fun. Give me a hug.
I heard about the divorce. Lesbian, huh?
Well, you know what they say: Be careful what you wish for.
I think we're ready for some tequila.
I know I am.
Who's doing shots?
Hit me.
There you go. Ross?
I'm not really a shot-drinking kind of guy.
Hi. Sorry we're late.
We kind of just, you know, lost track of time.
But a man can change.
Anyone want me to appraise anything?
Well, I'm gonna go to tinker-town.
Mrs. Bing, I've read everything you've written.
When I read Euphoria at Midnight, I wanted to become a writer.
Oh, please. If I can do it, anybody can.
Start with half a dozen European cities throw in 30 euphemisms for male genitalia and you've got yourself a book.
My mother, ladies and gentlemen.
Yeah, any messages for room 226?
You okay, slugger?
Oh, yeah. I'm fine.
What is with you tonight?
Nothing. Nothing, nothing.
Okay, thank you.
It's the Italian hand-licker, isn't it?
No. It's the one he's licking.
She's supposed to be with you.
You're good.
I have sold 100 million copies of my books, and you know why?
The girl on the cover with her nipples showing?
No, because I know how to write men that women fall in love with.
I cannot sell a Paolo.
People will not turn 325 pages for a Paolo.
Come on. The guy's a secondary character.
He's just a complication you eventually kill off.
When?
He's not a hero.
You know who our hero is?
The guy on the cover with his nipples showing?
No, it's you.
Please.
No, really.
Come on. You're smart. You're sexy.
Right.
Yes, you are.
The fact that you don't think you are makes you sexier.
Come on, kiddo. You're gonna be fine, believe me.
I'll just pee in the street.
Is Chandler here?
Wait. Come here.
Okay, about last night you know Chandler, you didn't tell....
We don't need to tell Chandler. It was just a kiss. No big deal, right?
Right. No big deal.
In bizarro world.
You broke the code.
What code?
You don't kiss your friend's mom.
Sisters are okay. Maybe a hot-looking aunt.
But not a mom. Never a mom.
What are you guys doing out here?
Joey and I had discussed getting in an early morning racquetball game.
But apparently somebody overslept.
Well, you don't have your racquet.
No. No, I don't because it's being restrung.
Somebody was supposed to bring me one.
Well, you didn't call and leave your grip size.
You guys are spending way too much time together.
I'm scum. I'm scum.
How could you let this happen?
I don't know.
It's not like she's a regular mom.
She's sexy. She's....
You don't think my mom's sexy?
Well, not in the same way.
I'll have you know, Gloria Tribbiani was a handsome woman in her day.
You think it's easy giving birth to seven children?
Okay, I think we're getting into a weird area here.
What are you doing here?
Not playing racquetball.
He forgot to leave his grip size.
He didn't get the goggles.
Sounds like you two have issues.
Goodbye, baby.
Do they wait for me to do this?
Are you gonna tell him?
Why would I tell him?
If you don't, his mother might.
What are you guys doing here?
He's not even wearing a jock strap.
What did I ask?
What are you doing here?
Nothing. I just thought I'd stop by, you know, after that I, you know.
So, what are you doing here?
I'm not really here.
I just thought I'd drop these off on the way. My way.
Do you come here a lot without me?
No, no, no.
Do you think he's doing any better than he was this morning?
How would I know? I wasn't here.
Really? Not even to change his pajamas?
Oh, my God.
You're my friend. I had to tell you.
I can't believe it.
Paolo kissed my mom?
I don't know if you noticed, but he drank a lot.
I mean, you know how he gets--
I can't do this. I did it.
It was me. I'm sorry. I kissed your mom.
What?
I was upset about Rachel and I had too much tequila, and Nora Mrs. Mom, your Bing, was...being nice. But nothing happened.
Nothing. Ask Joey.
Joey came in--
You knew about this?
You know, knowledge is a tricky thing.
Why didn't you tell me?
You're lucky I caught them, or else who knows what would've happened?
Thanks, man. Big help.
What the hell were you thinking?
I wasn't. I don't know. I--
No one knows the crap I go through with my mom more than you.
I know.
I can't believe you did this.
Me neither.
I'm mad at you too.
Why are you mad at me--?
Let me slam the door.
I didn't kiss her. See what happens when you break the code?
''A Woman Undone, by Rachel Karen Greene.''
I thought I'd give it a shot. I'm on the first chapter.
Do you think his ''love stick'' can be ''liberated from its denim prison''?
Yeah, I'd say so.
And there's no ''J'' in ''engorged.''
You going to the hospital tonight?
No. You?
You just asked me.
Maybe it was a trick question.
Rachel, can we do this now?
I am so hot.
Here's my mom and dad on their wedding day.
Now, you tell me she's not a knockout.
I can't believe this conversation.
Just try to picture her not pregnant.
Central Perk is proud to present Miss Phoebe Buffay.
Thanks.
I'd like to start with a song about a man I recently met who's come to be very important to me.
You don't have to be awake To be my man
Long as you have brain waves I'll be there to hold your hand
Though we just met the other day
There's something I have got to say
Thank you very much. I'm gonna take a short break.
That was Phoebe Buffay, everybody.
What the hell was that?
Phoebe just started--
I was talking to Joey. All right, there, mother-kisser?
''Mother-kisser.''
I'll shut up.
I know you're still mad at me but there were two people there that night.
There were two sets of lips.
I expect this from her.
She's always been a Freudian nightmare.
Then why don't you say something?
Because it's complicated. It's complex.
You kissed my mom.
We're rehearsing a Greek play.
That's funny. Are we done now?
You mean you're not gonna tell her how you feel?
Just because you played tonsil tennis with my mom doesn't mean you know her. You can't talk to her.
Okay. ''You can't''? Or you can't?
Okay, that's my finger.
Okay, that's my knee.
Still doing the play.
What did you do with him?
You're awake.
Look at you.
How do you feel?
A little woozy, but basically okay.
Gosh, you look good.
I feel good.
Who are you?
Sorry.
I'm Phoebe.
I'm Monica. I've been caring for you.
We both have.
The Etch A Sketch is from you?
Actually, me.
I got you the foot massager.
I shaved you.
I read to you.
I sang.
Well, thanks.
Oh, my pleasure.
You're welcome.
So I guess I'll see you around.
What? That's it?
''See you around''?
What do you want me to say?
I don't know.
Maybe ''That was nice.''
''It meant something to me.''
''I'll call you.''
Okay. I'll call you.
I don't think you mean that.
This is so typical.
You know, we give and we give and we give.
And we just get nothing back.
And then one day, you wake up, and it's, ''See you around.''
Let's go, Phoebe.
You know what? We thought you were different.
But I guess it was just the coma.
The car's waiting. I just wanted to drop off my book for your friends.
Autographed. And give you a goodbye kiss.
Here's the kiss, here's the goodbye....
Anything you want from Lisbon?
Just knowing you're there is enough.
All right. Well, be good. I love you.
You kissed my best Ross.
Or something to that effect.
Look, it was stupid.
Really stupid.
I don't even know how it happened.
I'm sorry, honey. I promise it will never happen again.
Really, really stupid.
Are we okay now?
Yeah.
No.
The forbidden love of a man and his door.
He told her off. And not just about the kiss.
You're kidding?
He said, ''When are you gonna start being a mom?''
Then she said:
''The question is, when are you gonna realize I have a bomb?''
Are you sure she didn't say:
''When are you gonna grow up and realize I am your mom?''
That makes more sense.
You think?
What's going on now?
I don't know. I've been standing here spelling it out for you.
I don't hear anything. Wait.
What do you see?
It's hard to tell. They're tiny and upside down.
Wait, wait, wait.
They're walking away. They're walking away.
No, they're not. They're coming right at us. Run!
Are you okay, kiddo?
Yeah, I'm okay.
All right. You be good.
Drive safe.
Mrs. Bing.
Mr. Geller.
You mean that?
Yeah, why not?
So I told her.
How did it go?
Awful. Awful.
Couldn't have gone worse.
Well, how do you feel?
Pretty good.
I told her.
Well, see?
So maybe it wasn't such a bad idea, me kissing your mom, huh?
But we don't have to go down that road.
This is just the first chapter and I want your absolute honest opinion. Okay?
And on page two, he's not reaching for her ''heaving beasts.''
She could have heaving beasts.
Right, but in this case she doesn't.
What's a ''niffle''?
You can usually find them on the heaving beasts.
Okay, so I'm not a great typist.
Did you get to the part about his ''huge, throbbing pens''?
You don't wanna be around when he starts writing with those.
That's it. Give them back.
Wait, I just got to the part about her ''public hair.''
No, no, we're done!
Aunt Silv, stop yelling!
If you'd told me vegetarian lasagna l would've made vegetarian lasagna.
The meat's only every third layer. Maybe you could scrape.
Ross, did you really read all these baby books?
You could plunk me down in any woman's uterus, no compass and l could find my way out like that!
This is cool.
It says in some parts of the world people eat the placenta.
And we're done with the yogurt.
Sorry.
l did this as a favor. l am not a caterer.
What do you want me to do with a dozen lasagnas?
Nice talk, Aunt Silv.
You kiss Uncle Freddie with that mouth?
Ross, listen. Do you know that right now your baby is only this big?
This is your baby. ''Hi, Daddy.''
Hello.
''How come you don't live with Mommy?''
''How come Mommy lives with that other lady?''
''What's a lesbian?''
Honey, you can say it. Poconos.
Poconos. It's like ''poke a nose.''
Poke a nose.
So did l hear Poconos?
Yes.
My sister's giving us her place for the weekend.
First weekend together.
It's a big step.
l know.
It's just a weekend. Big deal.
Wasn't this supposed to be a fling?
Shouldn't it be flung by now?
We are way past a ''fling.''
I'm feeling things I've read about in Danielle Steel books.
When I'm with him, I'm just totally....
Nauseous. I'm physically nauseous.
What am l supposed to do? Call Immigration?
l could call Immigration.
What?
Ugly Naked Guy is making shadow puppets.
Look, it's Abraham Lincoln.
Oh, right!
Go. Go!
l love babies with their little baby shoes and their little baby toes and their little hands....
Okay, you're gonna have to stop that. Forever.
Need a new table.
You think?
Come on in.
Hello.
l brought the books and Monica sends her love along with this lasagna.
Great! ls it vegetarian? Because Susan doesn't eat meat.
I'm pretty sure that it is.
Nineteen weeks, the breasts are starting to swell.
According to the literature.
l got the results of the amnio.
Tell me. ls everything...?
Totally and completely healthy.
That is great!
When did you and Susan meet Huey Lewis?
That's our friend Tanya.
Of course, it's your friend Tanya.
Don't you wanna know about the sex?
The sex?
I'm having enough trouble with the image of you and Susan together.
But when you throw in Tanya....
The sex of the baby, Ross.
You know the sex of the baby?
Want to know?
No.
l don't want to. Absolutely not.
You shouldn't know until you look down there and see, ''Oh, there it is.''
Or isn't.
Hello, Ross.
Susan.
So?
So did you hear?
Yes, we did. Everything's A-Okay.
Oh, that's so cool!
It really is.
Do we know?
We certainly do. It's going to be a--
Hello?
A guy who doesn't wanna know is standing here.
Well, is it what we thought it would be?
What--?
What did we think it'd be?
l don't wanna know. Don't wanna know.
l should probably just go.
Well, thanks for the books.
No problem. Okay.
Susan.
Who should we call first? Your folks or Deb and Rhona?
Hello?
Never mind. I don't wanna know.
Because it was my table, l have to buy a new one?
That's the rule.
What rule? There's no rule.
You owe me a table.
How did you get there?
It was fine until your breakfast adventure with Angela Delvecio.
You knew about that?
The impressions in the butter left little to the imagination.
How about if we split it?
What do you mean, buy it together?
Yeah.
Do you think we're ready for that?
Why not?
It's a big commitment. What if one of us wants to move out?
You're moving out?
I'm not.
You'd tell me if you were, right?
Yes.
It's just, with my last roommate--
l know all about Kip.
We bought a hibachi, then he ran off and got married. Things got ugly.
Let me ask you something. Was Kip a better roommate than me?
Oh, don't do that.
There's changes in your schedule.
Your 4:00 herbal massage is at 4:0.
And Miss Summerfield canceled her 5:0 shiatsu.
Thanks.
Oh, here comes your :00.
l don't mean to sound unprofessional, but-- Yum!
Paolo! Hi! What are you doing here?
Rachella tell me you massage?
Well, Rachella's right.
Oh, okay.
l don't know what you just said, so let's start.
l am...being naked?
That's your decision. Some people prefer to take off--
Being naked!
l can't believe you don't wanna know. l couldn't not know.
If the doctor knows, Carol and Susan know--
And Monica knows.
How? l don't even know.
Carol called to thank me for the lasagna. She told me.
So what's it gonna be?
Oh, great! Now he knows.
I'm just excited about being an aunt.
Or an uncle.
Hey, Phoebe.
Hey, Pheebs.
Fine!
What's the matter?
Nothing. I'm just out of sorts.
Well, you can use some of my sorts. l rarely use them.
Can we get some cappuccino over here?
Oh, right! That's me!
That table place closes at 7. Come on.
Fine.
What is it?
All right. You know Paolo?
I'm familiar with his work.
He made a move on me.
The store will be open tomorrow.
More coffee, please.
Well, what happened?
He came in for a massage, and everything was fine until....
Oh, my God.
Are you sure?
Oh, yeah. I'm sure.
And all of a sudden, his hands weren't the problem anymore.
Was it...?
Boy Scouts could've camped under there.
Wow.
What did you do?
l dealt with it like a professional.
''Ooh,'' what?
--ma Thurman.
The actress!
Uma Thurman!
Thanks, Rach.
What'll you do?
You have to tell her.
It's your moral obligation as a friend, as a woman. It's a feminist issue.
Guys?
You have to.
Feminist issue? That's where l went.
She is gonna hate me!
Yeah, well....
Will you pick one? Just pick one.
Here, how about that one?
That's patio furniture.
So what? Like people will come in and think, ''Oh, I'm outside again.''
Fine.
What about the birds?
l don't know. They don't say, ''Hello, sit here. Eat something.''
You pick one.
Okay. How about the ladybugs?
Forget about the birds, but big red insects suggest fine dining.
Fine! Want the birds? Get the birds!
Not like that, l won't.
Kip would have liked the birds.
Hi, Pheebs.
What's going on?
Are you moving out?
I'm getting ready for the weekend.
Are your weekends longer than two days?
These aren't all my suitcases.
This one's Paolo's.
Rachel, can we talk for a sec?
Well, sure.
Just for a sec, Paolo's on his way.
We haven't known each other that long.
There are three things you should know:
One, my friends are the most important thing in my life.
Two, l never lie.
And three, l make the best oatmeal raisin cookies in the world.
Okay. Thanks, Pheebs.
Oh, my God!
l know.
Why have l never tasted these?
l don't make them a lot, because it's not fair to the other cookies.
These are the best oatmeal raisin cookies.
Which proves that l never lie.
l guess you don't.
Paolo made a pass at me.
What do you think?
It's the most beautiful table I've seen.
l know.
Will you balance plates on these heads?
Who cares? We'll eat at the sink. Come on!
Heads up, Ross.
Score! You suck!
Are you okay?
l need some milk.
Okay. I've got milk.
Here you go.
Better?
No.
l feel so stupid! l think about the other day with you guys.
And l was all, ''Oh, Paolo! He's so great!
He makes me feel so--''
God!
I'm so embarrassed!
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm the one he hit on.
l unleashed him on you.
If l had never met him--
I'm so sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Wait.
What are we sorry about?
l don't know.
Right. He's the pig.
Such a pig!
Oh, God, he's such a pig!
He's like a big disgusting pig....
Pig man!
Yes, good!
But he was my pig man!
How did l not see this?
Oh, l know!
Because he's gorgeous.
And he's charming.
And when he looks--
Okay, Pheebs.
The end.
God.
Should l not have told you?
Trust me, it's much better that l know.
But l just liked it better before. It was better.
She took it pretty well. Paolo's over there now, so....
We should go and see if she's okay. Just one second.
Score!
Game! Nice!
Come on, Pheebs.
Well, it looks like we kicked your butts.
She did. You could be on the Olympic ''Standing There'' team.
Come on. Two on one.
Why are you here? She just broke up with him.
It's time for you to swoop in.
What, now?
Yes. Now is when you swoop.
When Paolo walks out, you gotta be the first guy she sees.
She's gotta know you're everything he's not. You're the anti-Paolo.
My Catholic friend is right.
She's distraught. You're there for her.
You pick up the pieces and then you usher in ''The Age of Ross.''
See this? See?
Hold it! Ascolta!
How's it going?
Don't stare.
She threw his clothes off the balcony. Now there's gesturing and arm-waving.
That is, ''How could you?'' or ''Enormous breasts!''
Here he comes.
l am to say goodbye.
Okay, bye-bye.
Paolo, l really hate you for what you did, but l still have five of these so heat it at 75 until the cheese bubbles.
l just wanna tell you, and l think I'd speak for everyone when l say....
Oh, just look at her.
Guys, l think only one of us should go so she's not overwhelmed.
Right.
And l really think it should be me.
You all right?
I've been better.
l don't believe this.
l wasn't supposed to care about this guy.
It was just supposed to be this big, fun, ltalian thing.
Someday l could look back and say, ''That was a big, fun, ltalian thing.''
It wasn't supposed to feel like this when it was over.
Come here.
Listen you deserve so much better than him.
l mean, you should be with a guy who knows what he has when he has you.
What?
I'm so sick of guys!
l don't want to look at or think about another guy.
l don't even want to be near another guy.
Ross, you're so great.
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Medium. Any cookies left?
Yeah.
See, Rach l don't think swearing off guys altogether is the answer.
What you need is to develop a more sophisticated screening process.
l just need to be by myself for a while.
l just gotta figure out what l want.
No, no.
See, because not all guys out there are gonna be a Paolo.
No, l know. l know.
And I'm sure your little boy's not gonna grow up to be one.
What?
I'm having a boy?
No.
No. In fact, you're not having a boy.
I'm having a boy.
Huh? Am l having a boy?
You're having a boy!
I'm having a boy!
What is it?
I'm having a boy! I'm having a boy!
We already knew that!
I'm having a son.
Yes! And that would be a shutdown!
Shutout!
Where you going? One more game!
It's 2:0 in the morning.
Yeah, get out!
You guys always hang out in my apartment.
l'll only use my left hand.
Come on, wussies!
All right! Okay! l gotta go!
I'm going.
And I'm gone.
One more game?
Oh, yeah.