HoId on a second.
Nice. Nice.
-Something for you.
-What's this?
81 2 bucks.
Didn't Big Leon teII you? It's a
thousand if you want me for the night.
-What is this for?
-WeII, I'm making money now.
I'm paying you back for headshots,
eIectric biIIs, pizza-- Love you, man.
WeII, thanks, man.
Now I can get my pony.
This is a IittIe extra something
for aIways being there for me.
Wow! I don't know what to say.
-What do you say?
-I don't know.
It's a braceIet.
Isn't it? It's engraved too.
Check it out.
''To my best bud.''
Thanks, best bud.
-Put it on!
-Now?
It shouId be saved
for a speciaI occasion.
That's the beauty part.
It goes with everything.
You put this on,
you're good to go.
I've never been ''good to go,''
so why not try some jeweIry, huh?
Oh, man!
You are so wearing that braceIet.
I so am.
Any idea what this wiII
do for your sex Iife?
It might sIow down at first...
...but once I'm used to the weight,
I'II be back on track.
The One With the Prom Video
-This aII Iooks good.
-Great.
If I want to caII for a job reference?
That's right there.
The manager, ChandIer Bing.
AII right.
Let's see if you're as good in person.
Make me a saIad.
A saIad? I couId do
something more compIicated.
No, just the saIad wiII be fine.
You got it.
Now, I want you to teII me what
you're doing whiIe you're doing it.
AII right.
WeII, I'm tearing the Iettuce.
-Is it dirty?
-Don't worry, I'II wash it.
Don't. I Iike it dirty.
It's your caII.
So, what are you going to do next?
I thought I'd cut up the tomatoes.
Are they firm?
They're okay.
You sure they're not bad?
You sure they're not very, very bad?
No, they're okay.
You gonna sIice them reaI nice?
I was gonna do them juIienne.
I'm out of here.
HeIIo?
RacheI's not here.
Can I take a message?
How do we speII Casey?
Is it Iike ''at the Bat''
or ''and the Sunshine Band''?
Hey, who's this Casey?
A guy she met at a movie.
What does he want with her?
ProbabIy ''do a IittIe dance.''
You know, ''make a IittIe Iove.''
WeII, pretty much ''get down tonight.''
I don't know. I don't--
I don't get it. Two months ago,
RacheI and I were cIose.
Now I take messages from guys
she meets at movies?
This Casey shouId be
taking down my messages, you know?
Or RacheI and I shouId be together...
...and we shouId get
a message service.
Hang in there, it'II happen.
How do you know that?
Because she's your Iobster.
She's going somewhere.
It's a known fact that Iobsters
faII in Iove and mate for Iife.
You know what? You can actuaIIy
see oId Iobster coupIes...
...waIking around their tank
hoIding cIaws, Iike....
You have to picture Iobsters.
You feeIing better?
I think the fifth shower
got the interview off me.
Do you have other possibiIities?
There is the possibiIity
that I won't make rent.
I can Iend you some money.
If I couIdn't pay you back right away,
I'd feeI guiIty and tense around you.
Why not borrow it from Mom and Dad?
You feeI guiIty and tense around them.
Might as weII make money off of them.
The man's got a point.
What is that sparkIy thing?
That thing?
Yeah, it's a IittIe fIashy.
No, no.
No, no. It's not fIashy.
Not for a GoodfeIIa.
That is sharp! That must've
cost you a few doubIoons.
It's fun. It's Iike knowing
one of the Gabor sisters.
-Hi.
-Hi, darIing.
What's this?
Some of your oId stuff.
WeII, sweetie,
we have a surprise for you.
We're turning your room into a gym.
Wow, that is a surprise!
Just one question.
Why not Ross' room?
We taIked about that...
...but he had so many science
trophies, pIaques, merit badges.
We didn't wanna disturb them.
God forbid.
What's new? What can you teII us?
How's your job?
My job? WeII....
Did I mention I stiII
don't have a boyfriend?
Oh weII. I just assumed.
-Oh, hi, RacheI!
-Hi.
We're sorry to hear
about your parents spIitting up.
WeII, they're just separated.
You never know. We'II see.
I can't say we were surprised.
They've been unhappy
since we've known them.
EspeciaIIy after
the incident in Hawaii.
What? What incident?
No, no. I must be
thinking of someone eIse.
Maybe me.
Don't you have foIding to do?
FoId, dear. You foId.
-Want a refiII?
-I'm aII right, thanks.
Give me a second.
I want to get this right.
EIeven o'cIock,
totaIIy hot babe checking you out.
That was reaIIy good.
I think I'm ready for my penis now.
I know what you're thinking.
Dave Thomas, founder of Wendy's.
-I'm GaiI.
-ChandIer.
I have to go.
It was nice meeting you.
ExceIIent. He couId have
gotten me a VCR or goIf cIubs.
But he got me the ''woman repeIIer.''
The eyesore from
the Liberace House of Crap.
-It's not bad.
-Easy for you to say.
You're not sporting a reject
from the Mr. T CoIIection.
''I pity the fooI that puts on
my jeweIry. I do.''
''I pity the fooI that--''
Hi.
Hey, man. We were just
doing some impressions.
Do your MarceI Marceau.
That's actuaIIy good.
WouId you Iook at that guy?
-How Iong have they been taIking?
-A coupIe minutes.
Try doubIing that.
It's Iike, ''Back off, buddy.
She's a waitress, not a geisha.''
I think she's okay.
Look at that. She pushes him away
and he won't budge.
I'm gonna do something.
We'II get a condo on the
mountain. Ski in, ski out. Great.
Excuse me? Are you RacheI?
What?
Ross GeIIer.
God, in your ad you said
you were pretty, but wow!
What are you doing?
Oh, my God, is this the wrong day?
I don't beIieve it. If it works out,
we'II have something to teII the kids.
You sure wiII.
I've gotta go.
Take care.
See you Iater.
Nice meeting you.
You're weIcome.
-What?
-I was saving you.
Saving me from a pIeasant
conversation with a man?
From where I was--
Ross, Iisten to me.
I am not yours to save.
But you are.
What?
You're my Iobster.
Are you being
the bIind-date guy again?
No, you're my Iobster.
Lobsters....
In the tank, when they're oId...
...they get with the--
They waIk around hoIding the cIaws.
In the tank!
With the hoIding and....
Pheebs, wanna heIp
with the Iobster thing?
Do the cIaws again.
Forget the Iobsters, okay?
Let's taIk--
What about us?
Ross, there is no ''us.'' Okay?
-No, but--
-No. Listen to me!
I feII for you and get cIobbered.
You faII for me
and I again get cIobbered.
I'm tired of being cIobbered,
you know?
It's just not worth it.
-WeII, but--
-No ''but,'' Ross.
We are never gonna happen, okay?
Accept that.
''Except that'' what?
No. No.
Accept that.
Oh.
I gotta go.
Hey, man. Look, it's my best bud!
How you doing?
You're getting good at that
MarceI Marceau thing.
What do you say we pIay some baII?
You and me?
Okay, that's my bad.
If you hated the braceIet,
you shouId have just said so.
Doesn't the fact that I wore it say
how much our friendship means to me?
But you insuIted the braceIet
and you made fun of me.
WeII, that's the part
where I'm a wank.
I hoped we wouIdn't focus on that.
Oh, yeah? WeII, focus on this.
Hard to argue with that.
Come on! I said I was
sorry a hundred times.
I promise to never take it off my...
...wrist.
If you want to stay in there
and be mad...
...you just stay in there.
You know what the--
I am here, on my knees...
...hoIding up these couch cushions...
...as a symboI
of my sorrow and regret.
Much Iike they did in bibIicaI times.
You may haveth anger now....
You're gonna grab yourseIf again,
aren't you?
You know, that Steffi Graf
has quite a tush.
I'm just saying!
Right there.
-Hey, guys.
-Hi, darIing.
You didn't bring my grandson?
-He's at CaroI's and Susan's today.
-A woman in my office is a Iesbian.
I'm just saying.
Jack, Iook. There's that house
paint commerciaI that cracks you up.
-Where have you been?
-EmotionaI heII.
-Did they Iend you the money?
-I haven't asked them yet.
Come on, Monica, do it.
Hey, you guys.
Monica has some news.
Listen, I'm sorry I didn't
teII you this before but...
...I'm no Ionger at my job.
I had to Ieave it.
-Why?
-Because they made me.
You were fired?
What are you gonna do?
Judy, reIax. This is our IittIe
''har-Monica'' we're taIking about.
We taught her weII.
-10 percent of your paycheck goes...?
-In the bank.
So she dips into her savings.
That's why it's there.
She's gonna be fine.
Aren't you, sweetie?
In the bank.
If you need a IittIe extra,
you know where to find it.
Anything Iarger back there?
I can't beIieve it.
WouId you stop aIready?
Get out of the bitter barn
and pIay in the hay.
You're right.
I shouId pIay in the hay.
I just dropped $400 to repIace
a braceIet I hated to begin with.
Bring on the hay.
Hey!
I've got something
that'II make you happy.
Guess what Gunther found?
Now you have two!
Oh, you have two.
What am I gonna do?
Hey.
How come you have two?
This one's for you.
Get out!
No, I can't.
I know how much this means to you
and it's about more than jeweIry.
It's about you and me
and that we're ''best buds.''
Is this friendship?
I think so.
Check it out.
We're braceIet buddies!
That's what they'II caII us.
Here you go.
Pay me back whenever you Iike.
You have dinosaur checks?
You get your money
and you Iearn something.
What's wrong with that?
Nothing.
Hey, you're a cheap-osaurus!
I'm kidding.
Thank you, I'm very gratefuI.
Hey, Mon, what is this?
My bathing suit from high schooI.
I was a IittIe bigger then.
That's what they use to cover
Connecticut when it rains.
What's on this videotape?
I don't know. Put it in.
Over here, Jack. Okay.
Rachel's coming up the path.
Doesn't she look pretty?
Jack? Can you get this?
Oh, my God.
What is with your nose?
They had to reduce it
because of my deviated septum.
I was wrong. That's what they use
to cover Connecticut.
This is us getting ready for prom.
-We don't have to watch.
-Yeah, we do.
-Come on.
-It's fun!
Get a shot of Monica.
-Where's Monica?
-Over here, Dad.
Wait. How do you zoom out?
There she is.
Some girI ate Monica!
Shut up.
The camera adds ten pounds.
How many cameras are actuaIIy on you?
Oh, you look so great!
So do you! You look beautiful.
-Oops.
-What?
I got mayonnaise on you.
It's just the shoulder,
not my dress.
Everybody, smile.
-Oh, Dad, turn it off!
-It is off.
-It is not! What's with the red light?
-It's the off light.
Right, Ross?
Looking good, Mr. Kotter.
-You look pretty tonight.
-Oh, thanks.
-What are you doing this summer?
-I'm gonna hang out, work on my music.
Is my hook unhooked?
These things keep falling down.
Let me see. I don't know.
What are you gonna do...
The guys are here!
...this summer?
Work on your music?
Oh, my God, Roy GubIik!
You know,
Roy saw Star Wars 31 7 times.
He made the paper.
Where's Chip?
Why isn't he here yet?
He'll be here, okay?
Take a chill pill.
There.
I just toId RacheI
that Roy touched my boob.
I can't go to my prom without a date.
I can't. It's too late.
If you're not going,
I don't want to go.
Oh, I'm gonna kick Chip's ass!
I have a wonderful idea.
You should take Rachel to the prom.
Doubtful.
Jack, give me that.
Talk to your son.
All right, go on.
This is heavy.
Your mother's right.
Take her. You can wear my tux.
She won't go with me.
Of course she would.
You're a college man.
-I don't know.
-Well, come on.
Don't you wanna find out?
I can't believe
I can't go to the prom.
This is so harsh!
-Okay. Hold my board.
-Attaboy. Attaboy.
I think we've seen enough.
Let's turn it off.
WeII, I'm not gonna watch.
Come on, kid. Let's go.
-My! Are you handsome!
-Let's show them.
Just a sec, Dad.
Okay, be cool. Just be cool.
Okay, Dad.
Rachel, ready or not,
here comes your knight in shining--
Oh, no!
Bye! Don't wait up.
Chip!
Oh, dear.
How do I turn this off?
-Press the button.
-Which one? Which button? Jack!
The button. The button!
I can't beIieve you did that.
Yeah, weII....
See? He's her Iobster.
Dance with him.
Mom, I'm hungry!
Dance with your father.
I may not know any flashdances...
...but I'm no slouch
on the dance floor.
-Oh, Jack.
-Oh, Judy!