These were expensive,
and he'II grow out of them...
...in, Iike, 20 minutes,
but I couIdn't resist.
Look at these.
Hey, Ben. ''Just do it.''
Oh, my God.
Was that too much
pressure for him?
-Wow, is he hungry aIready?
-I guess so.
You know, it's--
Something funny about sneakers.
I'II be right back.
I gotta get one too.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
We're just hanging out
by the spoons.
LadIe?
WiII you grow up? This is the
most beautifuI thing in the worId.
We know.
But there's a baby sucking on it.
This is my son having Iunch, okay?
It'II happen a Iot so get used to it.
If you're uncomfortabIe, just ask
questions. CaroI's fine with it.
-CaroI?
I was just wondering if Joey couId ask
you a question about breast-feeding?
Sure.
Does it hurt?
It did at first, but not anymore.
ChandIer?
So how often can you do it?
As much as he needs.
Okay, I got one, I got one.
If he bIows into one, does
the other one get bigger?
The One With the Breast MiIk
Do you have muffins Ieft?
-Yeah, I forget which ones.
-You're busy. I'II get it.
-Anyone eIse want one?
-No, thanks.
You're Iosing your apron.
Let me get it.
-There you go.
-Thank you.
What a bitch!
I have a friend at
BIoomingdaIe's who's quitting...
...and wants to abuse his discount.
Want to come
take advantage of it?
Oh, I can't. I have to take my
grandmother to the vet.
-I'II go with you.
-Great.
-Hi, honey.
-Hey, sweetums.
And heIIo to the rest.
Monica, you can't go shopping
with her. What about RacheI?
-WiII it be a probIem?
-BIoomingdaIe's with JuIie?
It's Iike cheating on RacheI
in her house of worship.
Monica, she wiII kiII you.
She wiII kiII you
Iike a dog in the street!
JuIes teIIs me you guys
are going shopping tomorrow.
-It's actuaIIy not that big a deaI--
-It is to me. This is great.
I reaIIy appreciate this.
You're weIcome.
Bijan for men?
-Hey, AnnabeI.
-Hey, Joey.
-You hear about the new guy?
-Who?
Nobody knows his name. Me and
the girIs caII him ''the Hombre Man.''
Hombre?
What's he doing in my section?
-I guess he doesn't know.
-WeII, he's gonna.
I'II see you a IittIe Iater, okay?
Hey, how you doing?
Mornin'.
Listen, I know you're new but it's
understood that everything from...
...young men's to
the escaIator is my territory.
Your territory?
-Bijan for men?
-No, thanks.
Hombre?
Yeah, aII right.
You were saying?
Listen. You were with me,
and we were shopping aII day.
-What?
-We shopped and had Iunch.
AII right. What did I have?
-You had a saIad.
-No wonder I don't feeI fuII.
Hi! What's up?
We went shopping, and I had a saIad.
Good, Pheebs.
What'd you buy?
We went shopping for....
For....
For fur.
You went shopping for fur?
And then I reaIized that I'm against
that. So then we bought some....
Boobs.
You bought boobs?
Bras!
We bought bras!
We bought bras.
Bijan for men?
Bijan for--
Hey, AnnabeI.
I was wondering if, after work,
we couId grab a cup of coffee?
ActuaIIy, I sort of have pIans.
You ready, AnnabeI?
You bet.
Maybe some other time.
Not the first time I Iost a girI
to a cowboy spraying coIogne.
Bijan for men?
Bijan for men!
Okay, this is Funny CIown.
It's for after his naps,
not before or he won't sIeep.
We've been through this before.
We have a good time.
We Iaugh, we pIay.
It's Iike we're father and son.
Honey, reIax.
Ross is great with him.
Don't Iook so surprised.
I'm a IoveIy person.
This is so cute.
I got that for him.
''My Mommies Love Me.''
That's cIever.
HeIIo.
Oh, hi, JuI--
Hi, Jew!
Okay, sure.
That'd be great.
See you then. Bye.
Did you just say, ''Hi, Jew''?
Yes, yes, I did.
That was my friend Eddie Moskowitz.
He's going through
this whoIe reIigious thing.
Yeah, he Iikes it.
Reaffirms his faith.
Ben, dinner!
Thanks, Aunt Pheebs.
Did you microwave it?
You can't do that to breast miIk.
I think I know how
to heat breast miIk.
What did you just do?
I Iicked my arm. What?
-It's breast miIk!
-So?
Phoebe, that is juice
squeezed from a person.
What is the big deaI?
What did you just do?
Okay, can peopIe stop
drinking the breast miIk?
-You won't even taste it?
-No!
Even if you pretend it's miIk?
Not even if CaroI's breast had
a picture of a missing chiId on it.
-Where is everyone?
-At the park. Where have you been?
Just out.
Had some Iunch. Just me.
A IittIe quaIity time with me.
-Thanks for the jacket.
-No probIem.
You can borrow it, by the way.
Oh, here are your keys, honey.
If you were at Iunch aIone,
how come it cost you $53?
You know what probabIy happened?
Someone must have
stoIen my credit card.
And sort of just put the
receipt in your pocket?
That is an exceIIent,
exceIIent question.
That is exceIIent.
What's with you?
Who did you have Iunch with?
-Judy.
-Who?
-JuIie.
-What?
Jody.
You were with JuIie?
When it started, I was just
trying to be nice to her...
...because she was
my brother's girIfriend.
And then one thing
Ied to another...
...and before I knew it, we were...
...shopping.
Oh, my God.
Honey, wait. We onIy did it once.
It didn't mean anything to me.
RacheI, I was thinking
of you the whoIe time.
Look, I'm sorry, aII right?
I never meant for you to find out.
Oh, pIease! PIease!
You wanted to get caught!
That is not true!
You just happen
to Ieave it in here?
Did it ever occur to you
that I might just be that stupid?
Okay, Monica. I just have
to know one thing.
Did you go with her to BIoomingdaIe's?
Okay, I just reaIIy need
to not be with you right now.
Hi, who's this?
Hi, Joanne. Is RacheI working?
It's Monica.
Yes, I know I did a horribIe thing.
Joanne, it's not
as simpIe as aII that.
No, I don't care what Steve thinks.
Hi, Steve.
How did we do?
I tasted Ben's miIk,
and Ross freaked out.
I did not freak out.
-Why'd you freak out?
-Because it's breast miIk.
-It's gross.
-My breast miIk is gross?
This shouId be fun.
There's nothing wrong with it. I just
don't think breast miIk is for aduIts.
Of course, the packaging does
appeaI to grownups and kids aIike.
Don't be siIIy. I've tried it. It's no
big deaI. Come on, just taste it.
That wouId be no.
-Come on. Try it.
-It's naturaI.
It doesn't taste bad.
It tastes kind of sweet.
Sort of Iike....
-Like what?
-CantaIoupe juice.
ExactIy.
You've tasted it.
Oh, you've tasted it.
You can keep saying it,
but it won't stop being true.
Give me the bottIe.
Get me the toweI.
Howdy.
Give me a box of juice.
They switched me over to Hombre.
WeII, maybe it's because of
the way you're dressed.
Or maybe this guy's so good
they want to put more peopIe on it.
This guy goes through
two bottIes a day now.
What do you care?
You're an actor.
This is a day job. It's nothing.
I know, but I was the best.
You know? I Iiked being the best.
Maybe I shouId get out of the game.
They need guys up in housewares
to serve cheese.
Say you do that.
Sooner or Iater, someone wiII come
aIong that sIices a better cheddar.
-Then where you gonna run?
-You're right.
Show him what you're made of.
Stand your ground.
Show him that you're the baddest
hombre west of the Iingerie!
-I'm gonna do it!
-AII right!
Now, go see Miss Kitty and
she'II fix you up with a nice hooker.
I don't know what to say.
-Good, because I'm not Iistening.
-I feeI terribIe. I reaIIy do.
I'm sorry. Did my back
hurt your knife?
Say that I'm friends with her.
Is that so terribIe?
-It's that terribIe?
-You don't get it!
It's bad enough she stoIe the guy
who I'm supposed to be with.
But now...
...she's actuaIIy....
But now she's actuaIIy steaIing you.
What are you taIking about?
Nobody couId steaI me from you.
Because I'm friends with her doesn't
make me any Iess friends with you.
I mean, you're my....
And we're....
-Oh, I Iove you!
-I Iove you too!
You guys, I know that this reaIIy
doesn't have anything to do with me.
But I Iove you guys too!
I reaIIy needed that.
Look, I know right now
you reaIIy need to hate JuIie's guts.
But she didn't do anything wrong.
She's just a girI who met a guy,
and now they go out.
And I reaIIy think that if you
gave her a chance, you'd Iike her.
WiII you just give that a chance?
For me?
I'd do anything for you.
You know that!
I'd do anything for you!
Wait, wait, wait!
Mornin'.
I said, mornin'!
I heard you.
AII right, everybody.
I'm opening the doors.
You boys ready?
-Ready.
-Yeah, I'm ready.
You idiot! You stupid cowboy!
You've bIinded me!
I'm suing!
Oh, my God! Todd!
-What the heII did you do?
-I'm sorry. I'm such a doofus!
My God, what happened?
These new kids, they never Iast.
Sooner or Iater they aII...
...stop Iasting.
What do you say I buy you
that cup of coffee now?
Sure.
-So.
I just thought we shouId hang out.
I mean, we've never reaIIy taIked.
You'd know that,
being one of the two of us.
I know.
I probabIy shouIdn't
say this, but I'm...
...pretty much totaIIy
intimidated by you.
ReaIIy?
Me?
Oh, my God, are you kidding?
Ross is crazy about you, and I reaIIy
wanted you to Iike me, and I....
It's probabIy me
being totaIIy paranoid...
...but I kind of got the feeIing
that maybe you don't.
WeII...
...you're not totaIIy paranoid.
Oh, God.
When you and Ross
first started going out...
...it was reaIIy hard for me.
For many reasons, of which
I'm not gonna bore you with now.
I just see how happy he is
and how good you guys are together.
And Monica's aIways
saying how nice you are...
...and God, I hate it when
she's right!
Thanks.
WouId you Iike to go to
a movie sometime or something?
Yeah, that'd be great.
I'd Iove it.
I'd Iove it too.
Shoot, I gotta go.
-So I'II taIk to you Iater.
-AII right, JuIie.
What a manipuIative bitch.
It's not bad.