Hey.
-What you guys doing?
-Monica's making us watch Old Yeller.
Why are you guys upset?
It's Old Yeller. It's a happy movie.
-What are you taIking about?
-Happy famiIy gets a dog. Frontier fun!
Pheebs, what about the end?
When YeIIer saves the famiIy
and everyone's happy?
That's not the end.
That's when my mother wouId
shut off the TV and say, ''The end.''
What about when he has rabies?
He doesn't have rabies.
He has babies.
That's what my mom said.
I don't think she'd want you
to see what's about to happen.
Why? What's about to happen?
I've never seen this part.
Hey, Travis, what you doing
with that gun?
Oh, no.
No, Travis, put down the gun.
No, he's your buddy.
He's your YeIIer.
No! The end! The end!
Okay, what kind of a sick
doggy snuff fiIm is this?
The One Where OId YeIIer Dies
Have you eaten? Richard and I
just finished, and we have Ieftovers.
Chicken and potatoes.
What am I wearing?
ActuaIIy, nothing but rubber gIoves.
One day, you'II reaIIy be naked
and we won't come over.
That'd teach me a Iesson.
I've got a Ieg, three breasts
and a wing.
How do you find cIothes that fit?
Hey, Monica? We got a question.
Yes, I see other women
in the shower at the gym.
And no, I don't Iook.
No, not that one.
We have an extra ticket
to the Knicks game.
Ross can't go, so it's between my
friend Eric, who has breath issues...
...and Dan, with the poking.
''Did you see that pIay?''
''You want more beer?
Is that Spike Lee?''
Why don't you ask Richard?
Richard, if you had
an extra ticket to the Knicks...
...and you had to choose between
a friend who smeIIs...
...and one who bruises you,
who wouId you pick?
Wow.
Being a Knicks fan myseIf...
...I think you shouId take someone
who's a huge Knicks fan.
Okay.
That's Eric.
GIad to be of heIp.
Matches.
I meant, why don't you
take Richard to the game?
What?
-I don't know.
-Come on!
He keeps his fingers to himseIf,
and he's aIways minty fresh.
Richard's reaIIy nice.
We just don't know him reaIIy weII.
PIus, he's oId...
...er than some peopIe.
But younger than some buiIdings.
So he's a IittIe oIder. Big deaI.
He's important to me.
If you ask him,
he might take you in his Jag.
How do we say yes...
...and make it seem Iike
it's not just to ride in the cooI car?
Okay, this couId be tough.
Monica?
We'II bring him,
but onIy if he takes the Jaguar.
You aImost had it.
No, no, you're fine. You're fine.
Hi, honey.
You are not gonna beIieve
what happened!
We were on the fIoor,
and he grabs the tabIe...
...and he puIIs himseIf up!
He puIIed himseIf up!
Standing man!
Sorry you missed it,
but I taped it if you wanna see.
-He aIready did it Iast week.
-You can watch our tape if you want.
See, I don't beIieve this.
I miss the first time of everything.
The first time he roIIed over,
the first time he crawIed.
Has he spoken? Is he driving?
Does he have a favorite Iiqueur?
He is getting cIoser
on the taIking thing.
He can't quite say ''mama,''
but once he said, ''Yemen.''
See, I don't know.
I'm so sick of missing stuff.
I want him for more than a day.
I want a weekend.
-Listen. I feeI--
-That wouId be great.
ReaIIy? I had a whoIe speech prepared.
Shoot, that wouId've been fun.
Did you just see that?
Did you see? He just waved!
He just waved!
He's never waved before!
Yes, he has. Very good.
Hey, what you got there?
Love Story, Brian's Song and
Terms of Endearment.
AII you need now is The Killing Fields
and guacamoIe, and you've got a party!
I taIked to my grandma
about Old Yeller...
...and she said my mom didn't show us
the ends of sad movies...
...to shieId us from
the pain and sadness.
You know, before she kiIIed herseIf.
Where's Richard?
Did you ditch him?
After we stoIe his Iunch money
and gave him a wedgie.
What's with you? He's parking.
-Did you guys have fun?
-Your boyfriend is so cooI.
He Iet us drive his Jaguar.
Joey for 1 2 bIocks. Me for 1 5.
He must Iike you best.
And when he tipped the guy
who showed us to our seats?
You never saw the money.
Like this:
Hey, ChandIer, thanks
for showing us to our seats.
You're weIcome.
Hey, thanks for parking the car.
No probIem.
-Hey, ChandIer--
-I think they get it.
There's the man!
You're getting better.
I'm gonna keep this, by the way.
He kept my doIIar.
-Your first weekend without Ben.
-We're going to coIoniaI WiIIiamsburg.
A woman I went to coIIege with
is the first femaIe bIacksmith there.
They're a IittIe behind the times
in coIoniaI WiIIiamsburg.
I better go before Mommy
starts weeping.
-We Iove you.
-Bye, Mommy.
-Bye.
-Have a good time.
Ross? Look.
Joey, do you know
we can see you from here?
How come Richard
Iooks cooIer with these?
You may want to Iight it
and Iose the spatuIa.
It's cute, trying to be Iike Richard.
Not Iike him, per se.
Just not unIike him.
It's the artist formerIy known
as ChandIer.
I'm just trying something here,
you know?
-Why didn't you grow a mustache?
-We fIipped for it.
I got the cigar,
he got the mustache.
If we both grew them,
we'd Iook Iike dorks.
You reaIIy sidestepped
that Iand mine.
-We gotta meet Richard downstairs.
-You're meeting Richard?
-Hockey.
-Didn't he teII you?
He said he'd be with the guys.
I didn't know that's you.
You hear that?
We're the guys!
That mustache reminds me
of Aunt SyIvia.
Thank you!
Hi. We're visiting.
It's Ben and his dada.
Can you say ''dada''? I'm gonna teII
your mommies you said it anyway.
No Iuck, huh?
A whiIe ago,
I got a ''se'' out of him...
...which I thought might turn into
''secondary caregiver,'' but....
WouId you hoId him for a sec?
I gotta take this off.
Sure. Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm hoIding Ben.
He's a baby, not a bomb.
-HoId him Iike you'd hoId a footbaII.
-This is how I wouId hoId a footbaII.
Here. Here. There we go.
Sorry, I'm not very good with babies.
I haven't been around them.
I mean, since I was one.
-It's aII right. No big deaI.
-ReaIIy?
You'II feeI different
when it's our baby.
-What?
You think about stuff Iike that?
Yeah.
ActuaIIy, I kind of think
that we'II have two babies.
Two babies?
You know, a boy and a girI.
HopefuIIy, the girI wiII come first,
so Ben won't feeI competitive.
Then what's gonna happen?
We won't wanna raise kids in the city,
so we'II move to ScarsdaIe.
It's far enough from our parents
not to see them...
...but cIose enough
for them to babysit.
And yes, I know the taxes are
a IittIe higher than Nassau County...
...but the schooI system's great.
Wow, that's great! Great!
Okay, you know what?
I'm off my break now.
Here. You take this.
I'm gonna go pour
these very nice peopIe some coffee.
Look at that. I don't have a pot.
Maybe I've got one at home.
Or in ScarsdaIe.
Hey, is that a door?
-Hey.
-Hey, Pheebs. What's happening?
Murder, cancer, soccer teams
eating each other in the Andes.
-I was reaIIy just making smaII taIk.
-WeII, I was just venting.
So you watched the movies?
What is happening to the worId?
I mean, because E.T. Ieaves...
...and Rocky Ioses. CharIotte dies.
CharIotte who?
With the web. The spider.
She has babies and dies.
It's Iike, ''WeIcome home
from the hospitaI.'' Thud!
-You wanna feeI better?
-Yeah.
Here. Watch this.
It's a Wonderful Life.
I've heard of this.
You can't Iose.
It's there in the titIe.
WonderfuIness is baked in.
I thought so with
The Pride of the Yankees.
I thought it was about Yankee pride,
and the guy gets Lou Gehrig's disease.
The guy was Lou Gehrig.
Didn't you kind of see it coming?
Watch that. It'II restore
aII your faith in humanity.
Hey, big guy. Game time.
-Hey! Be right there!
-There's a game?
I just got my Pik-Up Stiks
back from the shop.
Bring your nerves of steeI.
It's the basketbaII pIayoffs.
I appreciate this, but you don't
have to hang out with them for me.
They have each other.
Oh, no, honey. Don't worry.
I Iike hanging out with them.
They're not Iike my other friends.
They don't start sentences with,
''Guess who just died shoveIing snow?''
AII right, that's great.
Then just go.
Go Knicks!
It's the coIIege pIayoffs.
-Then, go Vassar!
-They're not in it.
-Okay, then just go.
-Okay.
Why does this bother me?
I'm not one of those peopIe who wants
to spend 24 hours a day together.
Sure.
He just doesn't have much free time.
What do I do?
Does it matter? You'II uItimateIy die,
divorce or bIow your pet's head off.
Me too!
I got a question.
Richard made pIans with the guys--
Ross made pIans for the century.
I'm gonna go read Cosmo.
Maybe there's something heIpfuI in it.
If not, I can Iearn how to do
a bikini wax with Christmas candIes.
What happened back there?
You teII me.
One minute I'm hoIding Ben.
Then I have two kids and Iive in
ScarsdaIe, compIaining about taxes!
WeII, I'm sorry.
I think about stuff.
You're at work, assembIing bones.
Your mind wanders.
You pIanned ahead 20 years.
We've dated for six weeks!
You never think about our future?
I think about whose apartment
we'II sIeep at...
...and where we'II have dinner!
I do not think about
our chiIdren's names!
You know what our chiIdren's names
are gonna be?
No. I mean, I read a book,
and there was a girI named EmiIy.
And I thought that might be good.
What was the book?
The Big Book of Children's Names.
Okay, Ross. Listen.
What we have is amazing.
But I do not want everything
decided for me!
I spent my whoIe Iife Iike that.
That's the reason I Ieft Barry.
I Iike not knowing right now.
Sorry if that scares you,
but if you want me, deaI with that!
-Okay, fine!
-Thank you!
-We're not done!
-I didn't know that.
You're with a guy who won't stop
pIanning his future with you.
He knows we'II be together.
If that scares you, tough!
DeaI with that.
-I wiII!
-Good, because I Iove you!
Oh, yeah? I Iove you too!
That's the first time we said it!
-I'm gonna kiss you!
-You better!
Thanks for the movie.
-Did you Iike it?
-Oh, yeah.
Was I happier when George
destroyed the business...
...or Donna Reed cried or when
the pharmacist made his ear bIeed?
I'II give you that,
but wasn't the ending great?
I was too depressed to watch it.
It shouId've been caIIed:
It's a Sucky Life, and Just When You
Think It Can't Suck Anymore, It Does!
Kick, save! And...
...denied!
He gets it back.
Pass to the middIe, Iines it up....
Yes! CouId that shot be any prettier?
-Man, you are incredibIe.
-We had a tabIe in coIIege.
I didn't know they had foosbaII
in the 1800s.
Nice mustache. When puberty hits,
that thing wiII reaIIy kick in.
Not to sound too FIorence Henderson,
but dinner's ready.
One more point.
Score!
Now can we go?
That's why we don't Iet her pIay.
Is everything aII right?
Don't be mad at him.
It's our fauIt.
-Sorry we're hogging his time.
-He's just great to hang out with.
We were just taIking about this.
He is so much cooIer than our dads.
Our dads are okay and aII,
but Richard is just--
What are you kicking me for?
I'm trying to taIk here.
You guys see me as a dad?
-Oh, yeah!
-No!
No.
You're cIearIy not famiIiar
with our young persons' vernacuIar.
When we say ''dad,'' we mean ''buddy.''
We mean ''paI.''
No, seriousIy. Joey's my dad.
Monica's my dad.
I've even got some dads down at work.
That's fine.
WeII, your other dad and I are gonna
go have a romantic evening.
I'II just see you kids around.
Nighty-night.
You're not a dad!
I can't beIieve you got us
into troubIe.
-So are you okay?
-Yeah.
Just...
...I feeI Iike I'm about 100.
I thought I was just one of the guys.
Come here.
I'II make you feeI Iike
one of the guys.
For a reaIIy cooI guy,
you suck at foosbaII.
What? I was kiIIing them.
Yeah, weII they suck too.
Take the poopy diaper
and put it in the poopy diaper paiI.
CaIIing it a poopy diaper
doesn't make this process any cuter.
-HeIIo?
-It's us.
Come on up.
I'II get his stuff together.
Okay, we can do this now,
can't we, Ben?
Yes, we can.
There! I did it!
I did it!
Look at that!
It stays on and everything.
-Hi!
-Hi.
I'm sorry. What did you just say?
Did you just say hi?
Oh, my God! Ross?
Ben just said hi!
-Ben just said hi!
-The word ''hi''?
No, my UncIe Hi.
Great, I missed that too!
I miss everything!
Oh, I'm sorry. I guess I just
bring it out in him.
-HeIIo! Where is he?
-We missed you.
We missed you so much!
Come here, Ben.
Guess what?
Ben just said his first word.
-What did he say?
-Something about, ''Hi.''
-That's so exciting!
-Mommy's so proud of you!
Hi!
Hi?
You know, actuaIIy,
it's more Iike, ''Hi!''
-This couId go on for a whiIe.
-Yeah, we've got a cab waiting.
WeII, this was fun.
We shouId do it again sometime, Ben.
What do you say?
-AII right, so I've got him...?
-Tuesday.
-Bye, you guys.
-Take care.
-Bye, Ben.
-Bye.
Did he just say bye?
He said bye!
You said bye!
He said bye to me!
Yes, he did!
SuddenIy I'm seeing him
go off to coIIege!
We've gotta go.
We've got that cab downstairs.
See you Iater.
-Bye!
-Bye.
Look at this nice deep hole I dug.
Hey, Bert, isn't this a nice hole?
This is the part where Ernie buries
Bert in the sand and can't find him.
I've Iooked ahead on the tape,
and he does find him again.
But before that happens,
there's some rough going.
But I think we can handIe it.
And there's just the aIphabet,
but we know that ends weII, so....
Here we go.
Bert? Bert?
What happened to Bert?
He was here a moment ago.
Oh, no! My old friend Bert is lost.
I'm so gIad you're here.