Stocks and bonds are moving higher....
Why are we watching
the Business ChanneI?
The other day there was a stock
with my initiaIs, M-E-G, on it.
Sometimes it takes hours to come up
again but when it does, it's exciting.
Okay, honey, you reaIIy need a job.
Dad knows someone you can caII
for an interview.
Right there!
That's the third sign today.
On behaIf of everyone,
I'd just Iike to say, ''Huh?''
You just said ''Dad.'' Everywhere I go
today I keep getting signs...
...teIIing me to see my father. When I
was waIking over, I passed a ''buffet.''
Which is my father's Iast name.
And they were serving franks,
which is his first name minus the S.
And there was a rotisserie
with a spinning ''chicken.''
His Indian name?
No. Because I ''chickened'' out
the Iast time...
...when I tried to meet him.
Coincidences? I don't think so.
-Very freaky.
-Weird. Eerie.
Who wants the Iast burger?
That's it. I have to go see him.
-Why?
-Hamburger.
McDonaId's.
OId McDonaId had a ''farm.''
My dad is a pharmacist.
And E-I-E-I-O is what your mom said
when your dad Ieft her.
-Yes.
-ReaIIy?
No.
The One With the BuIIies
-Man, I am so beat.
-Oh, yeah.
-Wanna forget racquetbaII and hang out?
-Yeah, aII right.
-Hey, you're in our seats.
-Sorry, we didn't know.
We were sitting there.
Okay. There is one more way to say it.
Who knows it?
-Was that supposed to be funny?
-ActuaIIy, I was going for coIorfuI.
-What's with this guy?
-What's with you?
Nothing. Nothing's with him.
Enjoy your coffee.
What just happened?
I just took your hat.
See, I can be funny too.
My joke is that I took your hat.
That is funny.
-Can I have it back?
-No.
-No?
Okay. Okay.
You know what?
I think you're very funny.
Kudos on that hat joke.
But come on,
just give him back the hat.
Why shouId we?
Because it's a speciaI hat.
He bought it because he was feeIing
down one day. He got the hat...
...to cheer himseIf up, you know?
-ChandIer--
-Stop taIking. Stop taIking now.
-You're steaIing my hat?
-You got a probIem with that?
No, just want to make sure
we're on the same page.
Rach, I've gone dad-hunting
with Phoebe before.
This is a very scary thing for her.
She gets reaI vuInerabIe and...
...that's why we're there,
to be supportive and crap.
Okay. You just Iet me know
when to do which.
-How did the interview go?
-It bit.
It was a '50s theme restaurant.
I'd have to cook in a costume
and dance on the counter.
I was a sous chef
at Café des Artistes.
How can I take a job where I
make Laverne-and-CurIy fries?
-So, don't do it.
-How can I not?
I have $1 27 in the bank!
-Monica, reIax. Go get a beer.
-I don't want a beer.
Who said it was for you?
-Hi.
What's the matter with you?
Some mean guys at the coffeehouse
took my hat.
-No!
-You're kidding!
It was ridicuIous. These guys
were buIIies. ActuaI buIIies.
We're grownups. This isn't
supposed to happen anymore.
Oh, no, wait a minute.
I have no one.
Let's go down there
and get your hat back.
Forget it. It's probabIy stripped
and soId for parts by now.
-I went up!
-What?
My stock, MEG,
it went up two points.
Do you reaIize if I'd invested
my $1 27 in myseIf yesterday...
...that I'd, Iike, have
a Iot more than that today.
You know what?
I'm going to do it.
-Do what?
-Put aII my money in me.
You don't know a thing
about the stock market.
What's to know? Buy, seII. High, Iow.
Bears, buIIs. Yes, Manhattan.
TeIephone number to the stock...
...seIIing store.
I toId you these piIIows
were a good idea.
Oh, God.
Here we go.
For the first time in my Iife,
I'II say, ''Hi, birth Father!''
-Love you. We're here for you.
-Good Iuck.
Thanks.
-Hey, Rach, you want some sandwich?
-What is in that?
-OIive Ioaf and ham spread. No mayo.
-No, because mayo wouId make it gross.
-Run, Phoebe, run!
-No, doggy, pIease!
I do so want to Iove aII animaIs.
PIease, no.
-You got a bone?
-Are you kidding?
Look, kibbIes! Bits!
Get the heII off my Ieg,
you yippity piece of crap!
Okay. AII right. We have a probIem.
Why don't you reach out
and take his trampoIine?
-Here, I know what we can do.
-Hey! No!
Okay, doggy, get the sandwich!
Go get the sandwich!
Good doggy. Get the sandwich!
The dog wiII Iick himseIf
but won't touch your sandwich.
What does that teII you?
-I'II eat it then.
-Are you crazy?
He's just a IittIe dog.
-Hey.
-What?
Do you have to be a Century 21 reaI
estate agent to wear the cooI jackets?
Do you say this stuff to girIs?
Hey, isn't that the guy
who used to wear your hat?
And Iook where they're sitting.
You're joking, right?
You guys just waIked through the door.
-Maybe we didn't make it cIear enough.
-Yeah.
This couch beIongs to us.
I'II teII you what,
you caII the couch...
...and then we'II caII the couch...
...and we'II see who it comes to.
Know what I don't Iike about you?
You aIways got something to say.
WeII, that--
You know what I keep wondering?
Why you two are stiII sitting here.
AII right, that's it.
I have had enough of this, aII right.
Gunther.
These guys are trying
to take our seat.
FeIIas, these guys were here first.
-Oh, sorry.
-Didn't reaIize.
-There you go.
-Thank you, Gunther.
We didn't want to have
to go and do that.
He toId on us?
You toId on us?
WeII, paI, you didn't
give me much of a choice.
-Don't pIay with his thing.
-I know.
AII right.
Let's take this outside.
''Let's take this outside''?
Who taIks Iike that?
The guy who's about to kick your ass
taIks Iike that.
-You had to ask.
-Yeah.
Okay. Okay, Iook. See...
...the thing is, we're not gonna
fight you guys.
Then here's the deaI:
You won't have to, so Iong as you
never show your faces here again.
I think you pIayed
the Gunther card too soon.
Hey, Pheebs, I think you're
good to go.
Yeah. I don't know.
-What's the matter?
-I think this was a reaIIy bad sign.
Like the beast at the threshoId,
you know.
It's just I have no famiIy Ieft.
Except for my grandmother.
But she's not gonna be around forever.
Despite what she says.
And I have a sister who I've bareIy
spoken to since we shared a womb.
I don't know. This is my reaI father
and I want things to be just right.
-I compIeteIy understand.
-Whatever you need.
Hey, you wanna go home?
Okay, thanks. Sorry again.
What was that?
I'm guessing the threshoId's cIear now.
I wanna buy five shares of SGJ, now.
Come on, time is money, my friend!
Thank you!
''Time is money, my friend''?
You missed
''Takes money to make money,''...
...and ''Don't make me come down
and kick your WaII Street butt.''
I made $1 7 before breakfast.
What have you done?
I had breakfast here,
so technicaIIy I saved $3.50.
How did you make $1 7?
WeII, my financiaIIy chaIIenged
friends, I spIit my money...
...and bought shares of CHP and ZXY.
How come those?
WeII, CHP because I used to have a
crush on Erik Estrada.
And ZXY because I think
it sounds ''zexy.''
What happened to MEG?
MEG was good for me, but I dumped her.
My motto is, ''Get out
before they go down.''
That is so not my motto.
-Hey.
-Hey, Pheebs.
-How's the dog?
-Yeah.
I taIked to the vet.
PeopIe are so nice upstate.
He said the IittIe feIIa's gonna be
okay, and I can pick him up tomorrow.
But he had to have stitches.
And he said that onIy once in a bIue
moon does a dog's ear grow back.
StiII hoping.
Now wiII you caII your dad
to Iet him know that his dog is okay?
I don't want to meet my father
over the phone. What am I gonna say?
''I'm the daughter you abandoned.
By the way, I broke your dog.''
-Hey, Pheebs, if you want, I'II do it.
-Okay.
Listen, just don't say
anything about me, okay?
Don't...
...be too Iong with the phone.
She'II be a much better friend
once the market cIoses.
-It's a woman.
-So taIk to her.
HeIIo, Mrs. Buffay.
I know where your dog is.
I want you to know he'II be returned
to you aImost as good as new...
...within 24 hours. Goodbye.
-Why the voice?
-Hard to say.
-Your cappuccino, sir.
-Thank you.
-This is better than the coffeehouse.
-AbsoIuteIy.
How come it's not mixing
with the water?
The package says to keep it moving.
Stir and drink, never Iet it settIe.
Hey, this is ridicuIous.
After I get back from
my niece's christening...
...we'II aII go to the coffeehouse
and have a nice cup of coffee.
No probIem. Joey's there.
Okay.
-No.
-No?
I don't want to have to have Joey with
me every time I want decent coffee.
And I don't want to drink
cappuccino with a K.
I say we go down there
and stand up to those guys.
AII right, hang on
a second, Custer.
-Ross, have you been beaten up before?
-Yeah, sure.
-By someone besides Monica?
-No.
So what if we get beaten up? Maybe
it's something a man has to go through.
Like a rite of passage or something.
CouIdn't we just Iose
our virginities again?
Because I think, actuaIIy,
mine's growing back.
Are you with me or not? Come on.
I'm with you.
Just...
...Iet me put on a cIean pair
of underwear for the hospitaI.
-I need to borrow $100.
-What?
WeIcome home.
-I need $100.
-For what?
-To get back in the game.
-When did you get out?
-I don't know. I Iost it aII.
-Oh, no.
I've come to terms with it,
you have to, too.
Okay.
Look, Mon, I'm reaIIy sorry.
-Where are we on the 100 bucks?
-I don't have it.
But, I need it!
Otherwise, I have to
take that horribIe diner job...
...with the dancing and the costumes.
I don't want to have to wear
fIame-retardant boobs.
Nobody does, honey.
-Hi.
-SchnoodIe!
Oh, my God. What the heII
happened to my dog?
It was an accident. The woman who did
this wouIdn't hurt a dog on purpose.
She's a vegetarian.
-Are these stitches?
-Eight of them.
That's 56 to him.
If it's raining, you can't
Iet him Iook up...
...because that cone
wiII fiII up fast.
-Thanks for bringing him back.
-Sure. Is Frank home?
-How do you know Frank?
-Just from a Iong time ago. Is he here?
Yeah.
-Frank!
-Yeah?
What?
Oh, okay. I mean Frank Senior.
-He went for groceries.
-WiII he be back soon?
He Ieft four years ago.
We're expecting him back any minute.
I'm gonna go. I'm sorry about the dog.
Everything. I'm sorry.
Hey, Iady!
Hey, wait up!
How do you know my dad?
WeII, I don't reaIIy...
...just geneticaIIy.
He's kind of my dad too.
-Heavy.
-Yeah.
So did he ever taIk about me?
Phoebe?
No, but he didn't reaIIy taIk
about anything.
Except stiIts.
-StiIts?
-Yeah, he Ioved stiIts.
One time, I was upstairs steaIing
cigarettes from my mom...
...and aII of a sudden I Iook over...
...and there's my dad's head,
bobbing past the window.
He had a big smiIe on his face
and was waving...
...because he was happiest
on his stiIts.
-Wow.
-Yeah.
-I don't know what to do with that.
-Me neither.
-So you're, Iike, my big sister?
-Yeah.
This is huge. You can buy me beer!
I'm not gonna.
You know what? If you had a friend
named Pete, I couId say:
''I know Pete.
He's friends with my brother.''
-I got a friend named Mark.
-That'II work.
CooI. AII right.
So maybe, you know,
I couId give you a caII sometime.
-We couId taIk or something.
-Yeah, that'd be okay.
-AII right.
-Okay, I'm in the book.
AII right.
So stiIts, huh?
If you want, I can show you where
he hit his head on the rain gutter.
Okay.
WeII, we did it. We're here.
We are standing our ground.
-How Iong does a cup of coffee take?
-WouId you come on?!
Thank you.
-There we go.
-I think we proved our point.
-You burn your mouth?
-Cannot feeI my tongue.
BuIIies! Big buIIies!
Look who's here. It's the weenies.
-Didn't we make ourseIves cIear?
-Yes, and that's why we're here.
Yes, we're standing our ground.
ApparentIy.
-Let's do this.
-What do you got, a weapon?
A nice watch.
I don't want to break it on your ribs.
AII right, Iet's do this.
Question: If I don't care about
my watch, can I use it as a weapon?
-What?
-It's sharp and metaI.
I think I can do some serious
damage with it.
No, you can't use your watch.
-Or your keys.
-Okay.
Here's what we'II do.
We'II put aII keys and watches
in the hat over there.
-AII right?
-Yeah, aII right.
AII right, come on, man.
Let's do this!
Before I forget, are we hitting faces?
Of course. Why wouIdn't we?
I have to work on Monday.
I have a big presentation.
ActuaIIy, I gotta show
this apartment tomorrow.
This no-faces thing
might not be a bad idea.
Nothing from the neck up...
...or the waist down.
-Dana's ovuIating.
-ReaIIy? You guys trying again?
So we're strictIy
taIking about the middIe?
-Come on!
-Hey!
Want some of this?
Want a piece of this?
I'm standing here! Huh?
-Hey! Those guys are taking our stuff!
-Hey!
Get out of the way! Look out!
That was amazing.
That was incredibIe.
-You guys kicked butt!
-What about you?
You reaIIy gave it to
Mr. CIean back there.
-He was a big guy.
-He was, wasn't he?
-I wouIdn't know, having missed it aII.
-Don't do that to yourseIf.
Any one of us couId have tripped
over that IittIe girI's jump rope.
So Iisten, guys...
...are we okay here?
-We're okay.
-So, can I have my hat back?
No.
Oh, my God. Look at her.
Hi, Monica!
How's it going?
Hey, nice boobs.
Guys, check this out.
ExceIIent.