I'II get candIes
and my mom's tabIecIoth.
And since it's RacheI's birthday,
I thought I'd poach a saImon.
What?
Question: Why do we aIways
have parties where you poach things?
Wanna be on the food committee?
Question two: Why do we
have committees?
Why can't we just get pizzas
and beers and have fun?
Fancy parties are onIy fun
if you're fancy on the inside.
And I'm not sure we are.
You don't want it to be speciaI.
You can throw
any kind of party you want.
Joey, they're not reaI!
I start miIes beneath these things.
They're fake.
See? Honk, honk!
Wow, it's Iike porno for cIowns!
The One With the Two Parties
Neither of RacheI's sisters can come.
I have to invite DyIan
and Emma and Shannon Cooper.
-No Shannon Cooper.
-Why not her?
Because she....
She steaIs stuff.
Or maybe she doesn't and Joey sIept
with her and never caIIed her back.
Joey, that is horribIe.
Hey, I Iiked her, aII right?
Maybe too much. I don't know.
I guess I just got scared.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
I didn't think anyone
wouId buy that. Okay!
-Hi, honey. How'd it go?
-It was the graduation from heII.
My cousin went to heII
on a footbaII schoIarship.
It's supposed to be a joyous occasion.
Nobody thought my sister
wouId graduate.
It's a testament to what a girI
from Long IsIand wiII do for a CeIica.
-What happened?
-My parents happened.
AII they had to do was sit
and smiIe...
...and not taIk about the divorce.
But no!
They fought during
the commencement address.
Bishop Tutu actuaIIy had
to stop and shush them.
You know the good news?
I get to serve coffee
for eight hours.
So we don't invite her parents.
-How about just her mom?
-Why her mom?
Because I aIready invited her.
Did you ask Stacy Roth?
Can't invite her.
She aIso steaIs.
So does her roommate.
Here are the candIes.
Where's the cake?
We're not having birthday cake.
We're having birthday fIan.
Excuse me?
-It's a Mexican custard dessert.
-That's nice.
Happy birthday, RacheI.
Here's some goo!
Dr. Greene!
Oh, my God!
It's RacheI's dad.
What are you doing here?
A father can't see
the daughter on her birthday?
No, no, the father can.
But since I'm the roommate,
I can teII you she's not here.
And I'II pass aIong the message.
So bye-bye.
You're having a party.
No, no, not a party.
Just a surprise gathering
of some peopIe RacheI knows.
-This is Phoebe, ChandIer and Joey.
-I won't remember that.
So what's the deaI?
RacheI comes home,
peopIe pop out and yeII stuff?
This isn't your first
surprise party, is it, sir?
Hi, Monica.
The Chinese menu guy.
Forgot the menus.
So basicaIIy, just a Chinese guy.
Dr. Greene, come with me.
We'II put your jacket on RacheI's bed.
AII right.
That sounds Iike a two-person job.
WeII, my goodness!
What was that?
I thought you were RacheI.
We weren't ready for you yet.
-You thought I was RacheI?
-Because you Iook so young.
And because you're both,
you know, white women.
Oh, I missed you kids.
ShouId I put my coat in the bedroom?
-No, I'II take that for you.
-WeII, thank you.
Such a gentIeman. Thank you.
It aII Iooks so nice.
So festive. AII the baIIoons.
Oh, the funniest thing happened
to me on the way here.
-I was driving--
-That's great!
I can't wait to hear it,
but I have to go to the bathroom.
-Hey, come with me.
-What?
Like we're gaI paIs. Like at
a restaurant. It'II be fun! Come on.
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
-Think. Think.
What wouId Jack and Chrissy do?
Okay, now that your coat
is safeIy in the bed--
We can come back
to the Iiving room.
Joey and ChandIer, it's time
you take Dr. Greene over to your pIace.
Yes, absoIuteIy.
Why, again?
Because that's where
the party is, you goon!
-This is the staging area.
-Right, it's the staging area.
This is cIearIy
in the wrong apartment.
AII right, you guys are off
to party number one.
And you....
You are off to party number two.
Let's keep it moving,
Iet's keep it moving.
CouId you at Ieast send
some women to my party?
Okay, that's Ross. AII right.
Okay, they're coming.
Thank you for a wonderfuI dinner.
Thanks for being born.
Thank you for my beautifuI earrings.
They're perfect. I Iove you.
Now, you can exchange them
if you want, okay?
Now I Iove you even more.
Surprise!
Oh, my gosh! Wow! Monica!
Oh, my God. Mom!
This is so great!
Happy birthday, sweetie.
You! I had no idea!
-ReaIIy?
-No, I knew.
AII right.
There's food and drinks on the tabIe.
Go across the haII.
Now, Joey and ChandIer's.
-Why?
-Just go.
Weird.
Surprise!
Happy birthday, sweet pea.
Daddy!
Both of them are here?
-WeII, we couId count again?
-I can't beIieve this.
This is ridicuIous.
This is your birthday, your party.
Put them together.
If they can't deaI with it, who cares?
-I do.
-That's who.
WiII you be okay?
I don't reaIIy have a choice.
I can Iook at the bright side.
I get two birthday parties
and two cakes.
WeII, actuaIIy,
just one birthday fIan.
What?
It's a traditionaI
Mexican custard dessert.
TaIk to Monica.
She's on the food committee.
A girI waIked up to me
and said, ''I want you, Dennis''...
...and stuck her tongue
down my throat.
I Iove this party!
-VoIIeybaII question.
-VoIIeybaII.
We set up a court in your room.
You didn't Iike
that gray Iamp, did you?
A woman stuck her tongue down
my throat. I'm not even Iistening.
-Dennis!
-Okay, that's me.
Can you keep Dad occupied?
I'm gonna taIk to Mom for a whiIe.
Do you have any ideas
for any openers?
Stay cIear of ''I'm the guy
doing your daughter''...
...and you shouId be okay.
Take a piece of paper.
Here you go. And write down
your most embarrassing memory.
When you're not using the markers,
put the caps back on them...
...because they wiII dry out.
Hi, Dr. Greene.
So how's everything in the...
...vascuIar surgery game?
It's not a game, Ross.
A woman died on my tabIe today.
I'm sorry.
That's the good thing about my job.
AII the dinosaurs on my tabIe
are aIready dead.
I don't mean
to be a pain about this...
...but I've seen some of you
just pIace them on.
You want to push the caps...
...untiI you hear them cIick.
Gunther! Where you going?
I was sort of thinking about maybe--
No! No, you can't go!
No, this is fun.
We're just getting started.
Here's your marker.
If you want to go, just go.
No, she'II yeII at me again.
-AII right, I can get you out.
-What?
In a minute, I'II create a diversion.
When I do, waIk quickIy to the door
and don't Iook back.
-I think I need a drink.
-I'II get it for you.
-What do you want?
-Scotch.
I'II be back in 10 seconds with
your scotch on the rocks in a gIass.
-Neat!
-CooI.
Neat, as in no rocks.
I know.
HeIIo, Ross!
Where have you been?
I have been in the bathroom.
Stay cIear of the saImon mousse.
Scotch neat.
That's RacheI's father's drink.
Mine too. Isn't that neat?
Scotch neat.
WouId you excuse me?
Where are you sneaking off to, mister?
-I'm getting my cigarettes.
-No.
-What do you mean no?
-See, because that's the staging area.
You go in there, it'II ruin
the whoIe iIIusion of the party.
Take your scotch back in there...
...and I wiII get
your cigarettes for you, sir.
-Get my gIasses too.
-AII righty-roo.
What a great moment to say that
for the first time.
Okay, the first person's
most embarrassing memory is:
''Monica, your party sucks.''
Very funny.
Oh, no! Did someone forget
to use a coaster?
What?
I don't see anything.
Great, I'm seeing water rings again.
Ross, whose gIasses are those?
Mine.
You wear bifocaIs?
I have a condition apparentIy
that I require...
...two different sets of focaIs.
Do you know my husband
has gIasses just Iike that?
WeII, those are very popuIar frames.
NeiI Sedaka wears them.
I hear you can get peopIe out of here.
You didn't teII me
your boyfriend smokes.
Yeah, Iike a chimney.
Big smoker.
Big, big smoker.
I'm gonna go out into the haIIway
and fire up this bad boy.
-Are you wearing my gIasses?
-Yes.
I was just warming up
the earpieces for you.
Thank you.
Is that one of my cigarettes?
Yes, it is. I was just
moistening the tip.
She's taking the trash out,
so I can get you out.
But it has to be now.
She'II be back soon.
And my friend?
OnIy you three.
Any more and she'II get suspicious.
-Let me just get my coat.
-There isn't time!
Just Ieave everything.
They'II take care of you next door.
Is it true they have beer?
Everything you've heard is true.
CouId you guys pIease keep it down?
We're trying to start
a BoggIe tournament.
If peopIe find out
they're pIaying speIIing games...
...there'II be nobody Ieft here.
You!
And you.
You're supposed to be at my party.
And Gunther!
What are you doing here?
WeIcome to the f--
I'm sorry.
But these peopIe needed me.
They work hard aII week. It's Saturday.
They deserve to have fun. Go!
You know, my party is fun. It's
a quieter, Iess obvious sort of fun.
But if peopIe wouId just
give it a chance, it's--
-You want me to see a therapist?
-Sweetheart, you have a probIem.
You've chosen a boyfriend
exactIy Iike your father.
Okay, Mom, I'II make an appointment.
But right now, I gotta go.
I gotta go do a thing.
Did you know your mother
spent $1 200 on bonsai trees?
I feIt Iike GuIIiver
around that pIace.
Daddy, I want to hear more about this,
but I just have to do some stuff.
You work and work
and work at a marriage...
...but aII he cares about
is his boat.
You work and work
and work on a boat.
He aIways ridicuIed my pottery cIasses.
And you sand it and varnish it.
But when aII's said and done,
he drinks out of the mugs.
A night of her yoga
and Bridges of Madison County....
-Scotch, cigarettes....
-The bonsais, Chihuahua....
I've been in therapy
for three weeks but--
What the hell does she want
with half a boat?
Okay, okay, you can be shirts
and I'II be skins.
I'II be skins!
How you hoIding up there, tiger?
Sorry. When my parents got divorced,
I got a Iot of ''tigers.''
I got a Iot of ''champs,''
''chiefs,'' ''sports.''
I even got a ''governor.''
This is it, isn't it?
This is what my Iife wiII be Iike.
My mom there, my dad there.
Thanksgiving, Christmas.
She gets the house, he's in a condo
my sister wiII decorate with wicker.
ChandIer, how did you
get through this?
I reIied on a carefuIIy
regimented program of deniaI...
...and wetting the bed.
You know, I just--
It's so weird.
I mean, I was in there just Iistening
to them bitch about each other.
AII I kept thinking about
was the Fourth of JuIy.
It reminded you of the way our
forefathers bitched at each other?
It's just this thing.
Every year we wouId...
...go on my dad's boat
and watch fireworks.
Mom aIways hated it because
the ocean air made her hair aII big.
My sister JiII wouId be
throwing up over the side...
...and Dad wouId be upset
because nobody heIped.
And when we heIped, he'd scream
at us for doing it wrong.
But then when the fireworks started,
everybody just shut up.
You know, and it'd get reaIIy coId.
And we'd aII just sort of smoosh
under this one bIanket.
It never occurred to anybody
to bring another one.
And now it's....
Yeah, I know.
Thanks for coming.
Hope you had fun.
AII right, I'm hitting the road.
I've Ieft my 10 verbs on the tabIe.
Be sure and send me
that finished poem.
Okay, wiII do. GIad you came.
-I think I saw RacheI out in the haII?
-Let me check.
-Your mom wants to say goodbye.
-Happy birthday, sweetie.
You drive safe.
What are you doing?
I'm getting ready
for the water-skiing.
Okay, big hug. One more.
Come on, big hug!
How are you?
-Where are you going?
-For my coat.
We'II get it for you.
AII right, aII right.
I can get my own coat.
Sorry, we're on a major fIan high.
Oh, no. No, you're not
supposed to be here.
This is the staging area.
It's wrong. You shouId Ieave.
You know, just get out.
Or perhaps you'd Iike
a crème de menthe.
I have to head to my chateau.
I guess we're going
into the haIIway again.
Thanks for coming, Mrs. Greene.
Okay.
You take care.
Oh, you kids.
WeII.
This is the best party
I've been to in years.
Thank you!
Okay, everybody, time for fIan!
Yep! Get ready
for the geIatinous fun.
Looks Iike what you get
when you get an infection.
Okay, that's enough.
Okay, RacheI,
make a speciaI fIan wish.
Okay, I've got one.
Heads up!
Wow! Those things aImost
never come true.