ChandIer, Mon, there's onIy
one muffin Ieft.
-I ordered mine first.
-Yeah, but I'm so much faster.
-Give it to me.
-No.
Give it to me!
Okay, you can have it.
There you go. Enjoy your coffee.
That was there when I got here.
Hey, you'II never guess
who's coming to New York.
TeII us before he can swaIIow.
Ryan, that guy I dated
who's in the Navy.
You dated a guy in the Navy?
I met him whiIe pIaying guitar.
Ryan threw in saItwater taffy.
He had no change.
Is that when you wrote
''SaItwater Taffy Man''?
He's my submarine guy.
He resurfaces every coupIe years...
...and we have an amazing
three days together.
OnIy, he's coming for two weeks.
Two whoIe weeks, which means yea!
So, wait, this guy goes down
for, Iike, two years at a time?
That'II teach you to Iick my muffin.
Hi.
-Oh, no. What happened?
-Ben's got the chickenpox.
So if you haven't had it,
chances are you wiII.
-I've had it.
Had it.
I've never had it. I feeI so Ieft out.
Oh, Iook!
The One With the Chicken Pox
Honey, you made the bed again.
You don't have to do that.
This isn't camp.
I guess the panty raid Iast night
was totaIIy uncaIIed for.
Okay, I'm taking a shower. Today
I'II sing Jim Croce's ''Leroy Brown.''
Hey, Mon, I have a question.
Is Leroy the baddest man
in the whoIe damn town...
...or the fattest man?
The baddest. Or the song
wouId be ''Fat, Fat Leroy Brown.''
What are you doing?
I'm just waiting for you, sweetie.
Are you remaking the bed?
I'm sorry. The way you did it,
it was just fine.
Then you're redoing it because...?
You'II think I'm crazy.
You're pretty much
running that risk either way.
Okay. You see...
...the duvet tag shouIdn't be
at the top Ieft corner...
...it shouId be
at the bottom right corner.
-It's not crazy.
-I'm easing you in.
AII right.
You see these fIower bIossoms?
They shouId be facing up, not down...
...because the head of the bed
is where the sun wouId be.
You don't Iove me anymore, do you?
ActuaIIy, if it's possibIe,
I Iove you more.
ReaIIy?
Wow. WeII, then, come on!
I wanna show you how to foId
the toiIet paper into a point.
Look, if you need something...
...I can get you a job here
as a processor.
-Don't you need experience?
-It's not hard to Iearn.
As far as not knowing
what you're doing, you're an actor.
Act Iike a processor,
peopIe wiII think you're a processor.
Here's this morning's projections.
Thanks.
Scott AIexander, Joey Tribbiani.
Joey is a feIIow processor.
No kidding?
Yeah.
I process. PeopIe want the processing,
I'm the one they caII.
-Where do you work?
-WeII, I'm in between things.
You know, one day
you're processing, the next day...
...not so much processing anymore.
I toId Joey about FIeischman's group.
FIeischman's group?
Whatever you do,
don't touch his sandwiches.
Are aII you processors dorks?
This Iipstick Iooks just great on you.
You Iook fabuIous, reaIIy.
Yeah, are you sure? ReaIIy?
See, you Iook beautifuI.
For God's sakes, dim the Iights.
I'm hideous!
It's gonna be okay.
Ryan's been underwater.
He's just gonna be so gIad
you don't have barnacIes on your butt.
Come in.
Hey, baby, I'm back--
Hey, Ryan. What's up?
-What's going on?
-No, no. You have to stay back.
I have the pox!
Chicken or smaII?
Chicken, which is so ironic
considering I'm a vegetarian.
-Why aren't you at home?
-My grandma's never had it.
PIease teII me you have, because
oh, my God, I forgot how cute you are.
I'm sorry, I never had them.
If I had one wish,
I'd go back to when I was 7...
...when Jimmy Hauser had chickenpox,
and I'd rub him aII over my face.
Yeah, or you couId wish
that I didn't have them now.
Can I see your face?
You don't wanna see a face
covered with pox.
It couId be covered with Iox,
I wouIdn't care.
And you hate fish.
So sweet. AII right.
Okay, aII right. You can see.
This is me.
Sorry!
I am scary!
Sorry, the Iightning was
an unfortunate coincidence.
-You Iook IoveIy! LoveIy!
-I hate this.
I had the most amazing
two weeks pIanned for us.
And everything I had in mind,
we had to be cIoser than this.
Phoebe, I've spent the Iast eight
months in a steeI tube with men...
...thinking about this moment.
I am not gonna Iet a bunch...
...of itchy spots stand between us.
Okay. This is the most
romantic disease I've ever had.
-How's the first day?
-It's Iike you said.
It's mostIy just putting numbers
from one coIumn into another.
Everybody's so nice. I just had
a good taIk with that Iady, Jeannie.
Jeannie? The head
of East Coast operations?
Turns out our kids
go to the same schooI.
Yeah. SmaII worId, huh?
Weird worId.
-Your kids?
-I figure my character has kids.
There isn't a part of that sentence
I don't need expIained.
In acting, you need
to think about that stuff.
My character, Joseph,
the processing guy...
...has two IittIe girIs,
AshIey and Brittany.
AshIey copies everything
Brittany does.
WeII, invisibIe kids
can be that way sometimes.
You know, Joseph and his wife, Karen,
are thinking of having a third kid.
You know what?
Just did.
Wow, that's some pretty powerfuI
imaginary sperm you must have there.
-Know what makes the itching worse?
-That you don't stop taIking about it?
-Fine.
-Let's just pIay, okay?
Good, okay. Here we go, doubIe sixes.
Here we go....
Here we go. Come to Mama. Just getting
ready to roII the dice....
-What're you doing? Are you scratching?
-No. This is what I do for Iuck, okay?
-You're scratching. Give me the dice.
-No.
-Give me the dice.
-No! Here. There!
Look, doubIe sixes!
We can't scratch. We'II scar.
I can't stop thinking about it.
It's just so hard.
I wanna grab these houses
and rub them on my body.
-No!
-Give it! Yeah, come on!
You know you want it too.
Come on.
Let's just be bad.
It'II feeI so good.
Come on.
Oh, God heIp me.
-Oh, yeah.
-Good. Now do me.
Do my back.
Oh, come on. Harder!
-There you go. Don't move.
-Why?
-Don't move.
-What are you...?
Stop that! Stop that right now.
I might've expected this of Phoebe.
But, Ryan, you're a miIitary man.
She made me do it.
That's a nice coIor on you.
Yeah, weII, it comes in pink
and bIotchy, baby.
I hope you get a weenie pock.
You and MiIton have to join us
on the boat.
-We'II make a day of it.
-That sounds IoveIy. We'II set it up.
I better get back.
Hope the baby feeIs better.
-Thanks. Bye-bye, Jeannie.
-Bye-bye, Joseph.
What a phony.
You'II teach her a Iesson when she
steps off the dock onto nothing.
-Hey, Mr. DougIas.
-Sir.
Bing, I got your memo. We won't
see the report tiII next Friday?
-My group wants the weekend for famiIy.
-I have a famiIy. I'm gonna be here.
Yeah, Bing. What's that about?
It's about cutting peopIe
sIack for moraIe.
I can get some rough numbers
by Wednesday.
Rough numbers?
This company wasn't buiIt
on rough numbers. Right, Mr. DougIas?
Have the finaI numbers
on my desk by Tuesday.
If you say so, sir.
Joseph's good, isn't he?
I'm going to kiII you.
Hey, I figure Joseph's the kind of guy
who Iikes to mix it up.
You know, get in there,
ruffIe some feathers.
Why?
Look, I'm sorry,
but that's what Joseph does.
Okay? If you try to puII something,
he'II caII you on it.
''What're you trying to puII?''
he'II say.
Duct tape.
Was I supposed to bring something too?
This is for the scratchy twins.
I taped oven mitts to their hands.
-You're strict.
-WeII, it's for their own good.
You know, I Iike the way you have
efficientIy foIded this tab under.
See, in a tape emergency you couId
shave vaIuabIe seconds off your time.
ExactIy!
God, I Iove that I can be
totaIIy neurotic around you now.
Don't you Iike it better with
everything on your desk perpendicuIar?
If it's not a right angIe,
it is a wrong angIe.
-Very good.
-Thank you.
Tomorrow I'm gonna do your cIocks.
-You're gonna do what to them?
-Set them to my time.
I'm confused.
I thought we shared time.
No. See, in my bedroom, I set my cIock
six minutes fast. Know why?
Because it's in a sIightIy different
time zone than the kitchen?
-Forget it.
-No, come on, teII me.
You don't understand. You don't
have any of these obsessions.
No, that's not true.
Oh, yeah? TeII me one of yours.
Okay.
One of my things is,
I aIways separate my sweat socks...
...from my dress socks.
-What if they get mixed up?
-Boy, I wouId just....
I wouId freak out.
You wouId not.
I can't beIieve this.
I hate this. You're too normaI.
I can't beIieve you don't have a thing.
My boyfriend doesn't have a thing.
See, if anyone overheard that,
I didn't come off weII there.
Hey!
-Mr. DougIas is Iooking for you.
-Why is Mr. DougIas Iooking for me?
He has a suspicion you dropped
the baII on the Lender project.
Why? Why does he suspect that?
At first, he thought it was Joseph.
But after he asked Joseph about it....
Turns out it was you.
-I thought you shouId know.
-AII right. That's it!
Look, Joey, I reaIize this
is the roIe of a Iifetime for you...
...and if I couId just fire Joseph,
I wouId. But that's not possibIe.
So I'm gonna have to Iet
both of you go.
-What? Everybody Ioves Joseph.
-I don't. I hate Joseph.
I think he's a brownnosing suck-up.
Oh, yeah? WeII, you can't fire Joseph.
He's not in your department.
AII right, okay.
So I can't fire Joseph...
...but I can sIeep with his wife.
Not Karen!
Yeah, I'm thinking about
having an affair with her.
You know what?
I just did.
-What the heII are you doing?
-Oh, it's not me.
It's my character!
Chandie.
The rogue processor who seduces
his coworkers' wives...
...and then Iaughs about it.
I have her panties
right there in my drawer!
-ReaIIy?
-No, freak! She's fictionaI!
AII right. Hey, take it easy.
If it means that much to you,
I'II go find something eIse.
Thank you.
It's just that I'm gonna miss Joseph.
I Iiked him. His wife?
She was hot.
And the kids. You know he was gonna
put in a pooI next summer.
Take these off.
I swear I won't scratch.
No, sorry, hon. Monica's orders.
WeII, that wasn't easy.
Okay, dinner's on.
There's a peach cobbIer
in the oven.
So the pIate's gonna be hot, but that
shouIdn't be a probIem for you.
AII right, you kids. Bye, now.
-Bye.
-Oh, Iook.
A Iow-budget puppet show.
It's a shame you can't see
what finger I'm hoIding up.
-Wine?
-PIease.
-SpiIIed some.
-I got it.
I must say,
you Iook beautifuI tonight.
What?
Sorry.
You Iook beautifuI.
Okay. You know what? That's it.
Oh, yes.
Good.
You guys, did you--?
Monica, wake up.
-What's up?
-I thought of a thing.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
I have to sIeep, have to,
on this side of the bed.
No. You have to sIeep
on this side of the bed...
...because I have to sIeep
on this side of the bed.
Or so I wouId have you beIieve.
So you have a side of the bed.
Everybody has a side of the bed.
Come on. You haven't
heard my reason yet.
-AII right, go on.
-Okay.
I have to sIeep on the west side...
...because I grew up in CaIifornia,
and otherwise...
...the ocean wouId be
on the wrong side.
Oh, my God.
-You're a freak!
-Yeah.
How about that?
-Where are you shipping off to?
-I can't say.
-Do you have nucIear weapons onboard?
Do you get to Iook
through a periscope?
I'm sorry, but I can't say.
Wow, it's neat Iearning
about submarines.
-I better get out of here.
-I'II waIk you out.
-Bye, Ryan.
-A pIeasure. Take care.
So do you think we couId get you
one of those uniform things?
-You Iike that, do you?
-Oh, yeah.
-I'II make some caIIs.
-Okay.
-Can you beIieve how we spent our time?
-We didn't do anything I pIanned...
...Iike having a picnic in CentraI Park
and coffee at CentraI Perk.
Oh, I just got that!
Taxi!
Bye, you.
I'm sorry, we're cIo--
-Hey, saiIor.
-Is this what you had in mind?
I'II say.
I'm shipping out tomorrow.
WeII, then...
...we better make this night count.
Wait, I forgot to turn off
the cappuccino machine.
Anchors aweigh.
Oh, wait, wait!
My purse, my purse!
Oh, I forgot to turn off the Iight.
Why don't I just meet you upstairs?
Honey!