Who the winny-binny boy?
You the winny-winny-binny-binny boy!
Yes.
Now, don't cry.
Don't cry.
Why is he stiII crying?
Don't worry. It's nothing that can't
be soIved by ''happy keys.''
I feeI better when someone
shakes jagged metaI in my face.
AII right, here.
Let me hoId him for a sec.
Here we go.
There we are.
Maybe it's me.
Don't be siIIy. Ben Ioves you.
He's being Mr. Cranky Pants.
You know, I once dated
a Miss Cranky Pants.
LoveIy girI. Kind of moody.
There we go. AII better.
There's my IittIe boy.
Can I see something?
-CooI!
-He hates me. My nephew hates me!
-I'm unempIoyed and he hates me.
-Don't do this.
You're just unempIoyed.
What if my own baby hates me?
What do I do?
Monica, this is nuts!
You know how Iong it'II be
before you have to deaI with this?
You don't even have a boyfriend yet.
Joey, she does not Iook fat.
The One With the Baby on the Bus
-Here you go.
-Hey, Mon.
Goo, goo, goo!
That is so funny!
Let me see that a sec.
-You okay, Ross?
-I don't know.
What's in this pie?
I don't know. Butter and eggs,
fIour and Iime and kiwi--
Kiwi? Kiwi?!
You said it was key Iime.
No, I said kiwi Iime.
That's what makes it speciaI.
That's what's gonna kiII me.
I'm aIIergic to kiwi.
No, you're not. You're aIIergic
to Iobster, peanuts and--
Oh, my God!
-It's definiteIy getting worse.
-Is your tongue sweIIing up?
Either that or my mouth
is getting smaIIer!
We're going to the hospitaI.
-Is he okay?
-He's gotta get a shot.
You know, actuaIIy
it's getting better. It is.
Let's not go.
Anyone for ScrabbIe?
Jacket, now!
What about Ben? We can't
bring a baby to the hospitaI.
We'II watch him.
I don't think so.
I have seven CathoIic sisters.
I take care of hundreds of kids.
-We wanna do it. Don't we?
-I was gonna pIay basketbaII but...
...I guess that's out the window.
If you take him for a waIk,
remember his hat.
There's miIk in the fridge
and extra diapers.
Hat, miIk....
-Got it!
-Let's go.
Consider it done!
-You understood that?
-My uncIe SaI has a reaIIy big tongue.
Is he the one
with the beautifuI wife?
Want to hear the song
I'm singing this afternoon?
-I wrote it this morning in the shower.
-Okay.
I'm in the shower
And I'm writing a song
Stop me if you've heard it
My skin is soapy and my hair is wet
And Tegrin spelled backward is Nirget
RacheI, sweetheart,
couId I see you for a minute?
What's up?
FYI:
I've decided to pay a professionaI
musician to pIay on Sundays.
Her name's Stephanie something.
She's supposed to be very good.
-But what about Phoebe?
-RacheI...
...it's not that your friend is bad.
It's that she's so bad...
...she makes me want to put my finger
through my eye into my brain...
...and swirI it around.
Okay, so you're not a fan.
But, I mean, come on.
You cannot do this to her.
Oh, no.
I have to do this?
Lather, rinse, repeat
And lather, rinse, repeat
As needed
We didn't bring enough.
Did you forget to pack
the baby's anviI?
It'II be worth it.
It's a fact that women Iove babies.
Women Iove guys who Iove babies.
It's the sensitive thing.
Aim him at that pack of babes.
Maybe one wiII break away.
Wait, forget them.
We got one. Hard Ieft.
-Give me the baby.
-I got him.
-Come on, seriousIy.
-Oh, seriousIy you want him?
HeIIo.
Who is this cutie-pie?
WeII, don't think me immodest, but...
...me.
-Want to smeII him?
-We're taIking about the baby?
He's got that great baby smeII.
Get a whiff of his head.
My uterus just skipped a beat.
What'd I teII you?
-It's great you're doing this.
-WeII, we are great guys.
My brother and his boyfriend
are trying to adopt.
What agency did you two go through?
But this is my gig.
This is where I pIay.
My name is written out there in chaIk.
You know, you can't just erase chaIk.
Honey, I'm sorry.
And he's going to
be pay this woman?
Why doesn't he give her a throne
and a crown?
And, Iike, a goId stick
with a baII on top?
Terry is a jerk! That's why we say,
''Terry's a jerk!''
That's where that came from.
Yeah, okay. You probabIy did
everything you couId.
Okay, you know what? Let me just see
what eIse I can do.
AII right. Let her go on after
Stephanie whatever-her-name-is.
You won't be here. Don't pay her.
-I don't know.
-I'II cIean the cappuccino machine!
You don't cIean
the cappuccino machine?
Of course I cIean it.
I mean, I wiII cIean it.
-I mean, I wiII cIean it.
-AII right, fine!
-Done.
-ReaIIy?
Who's working for you, babe?
Oh, my God! This is so exciting!
How much am I gonna get?
What?
You said he's paying
the peopIe who pIay.
I meant, he's paying that other woman
because she's a professionaI.
I'm not gonna be the onIy one
not getting paid.
-But Pheebs--
-No, I'm sorry, no!
No, I'm not some sIoppy second,
you know, charity band.
There are thousands of pIaces...
...where peopIe wouId pay
to hear me pIay.
When I play, I play for me
I don't need your charity
Thank you!
I'm not getting a shot.
They can take the needIe...
...and squirt it in my mouth.
Like a squirt gun.
See what the doctor says.
They've got to do something.
These are the '90s.
HeIIo, there. I'm Dr. CarIin.
I see someone's having
a IittIe aIIergic reaction.
Doctor, can I see you
for just a moment?
My brother has a sIight phobia
about needIes.
Did you teII him
about my squirt gun idea?
My brother wouId Iike to know...
...if there's a way
to treat this oraIIy?
Under these circumstances, it has to
be an injection and it has to be now.
So?
Have a seat. The doctor says
it's gotta be a needIe.
You're just gonna have to be brave.
Can you do that for me?
-Okay.
-Okay. Oh, boy!
You are doing so good.
You want to squeeze my hand?
Ross, don't squeeze it so hard.
Honey, reaIIy.
Don't squeeze it so hard!
Ross, Iet go of my hand!
Good. Next time we pick up women...
...we shouId go to the park
and make out.
Taxi! Taxi!
Hey, Iook at that taIent.
Just practicing. You're good.
Carry on.
Wait, wait, wait!
Hey, you. He is just adorabIe.
Can you teII him that?
Because he thinks he Iooks too pink.
-What are you guys out doing today?
-We're not out.
We're two hetero guys
hanging with the son...
...of our other heterosexuaI friend,
doing the usuaI straight-guy stuff.
-You done?
-Yeah.
There's our stop.
Get out of here! This is our stop.
You guys Iive here too?
We Iive in the buiIding
by the sidewaIk.
Do you know it?
Since we're neighbors, what do you say
we get together for a drink?
So you wanna go to MarqueI's?
Sure, they Iove us.
Where's your baby?
Ben! Ben!
That's good. Maybe he'II
hear you and puII the cord!
-Stop the bus! Hey!
-No!
-We need the baby!
-Wait!
You sure it didn't break?
It hurts.
No, it's just a good bone bruise.
And right here is the puncture wound
from your ring.
-I'm reaIIy sorry.
-It's okay.
Sorry.
Sorry! Hey! I got my ''S''s back!
Which we can ceIebrate Iater.
CeIebrate. CeIebrate....
He was a double, double
Double-jointed boy
Hey, so are you the professionaI
guitar pIayer?
Yeah, I'm Stephanie.
Right. My name was on there.
Now it just says carrot cake.
-Okay.
-So how many chords do you know?
-AII of them.
-So you know D?
-Yeah.
-Okay. Do you know A-minor?
Okay, do you know
how to go from D to A-minor?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
So does your guitar have a strap?
-No.
-Mine does.
Stephanie knows all the chords
Come on! Pick up, pick up! HeIIo.
Transit Authority? Yes. HeIIo.
I'm doing research for a book.
I was wondering what somebody might do
if they Ieft a baby on a city bus.
Yes, I reaIize that wouId be stupid.
We Iost a car seat on a bus today.
It's white pIastic
and it fits onto a stroIIer.
And there was a baby in it.
He wants to taIk to you again.
Everybody, Iet's give a warm
CentraI Perk weIcome to--
Terry's a jerk
And he won't let me work
And I hate Central Perk
To Stephanie Schiffer!
I'd Iike to start with a song I wrote
for the first man I ever Ioved.
Zachary--
Are all invited to bite me
We're the guys that caIIed
about the baby! Is he here?
He's here.
Is one of you the father?
-That's me.
-I'm him.
ActuaIIy, we're both the father.
-Oh, Ben!
-Hey, buddy.
TeII me you know
which one is our baby.
One has ducks on his shirt
and one has cIowns.
And Ben was definiteIy wearing ducks.
Or cIowns.
That one's Ben! Remember, he had
that IittIe moIe by his mouth!
Hey, Ben! Remember us?
Okay, the moIe came off.
What are we gonna do?
FIip for it.
Ducks or cIowns.
We're gonna fIip for the baby?
AII right, caII it in the air.
-Heads.
-Heads, it is.
We have to assign heads to something!
Right! Okay.
Ducks is heads
because ducks have heads.
What kind of scary-ass cIowns
came to your birthday?
-Hey.
-Oh, hi.
Here. I thought you might be coId.
Thank you.
Look at you!
You did weII.
8 doIIars and 27 cents.
But not reaIIy
because I put in the first two.
Just to get the baII roIIing
and to make myseIf feeI better.
-Do you?
-No.
This whoIe pIaying for money thing
is so not good for me.
I don't know, when I sang
''Su-Su-Suicide''...
...I got, Iike, $1 .75.
But then ''SmeIIy Cat''?
I got 25 cents and a condom.
So, you know, now I just feeI
reaIIy bad for ''SmeIIy Cat.''
Honey, I don't think
everybody gets ''SmeIIy Cat.''
I mean, if aII you've ever actuaIIy
had are heaIthy pets, then whoosh!
But it's not even that, you know?
I pIayed my songs
because it made me happy.
Now it's just aII
about the money, you know?
PeopIe missed you in there.
In fact, there was a request
for ''SmeIIy Cat.''
ReaIIy? From who?
WeII, me.
I know it's not your big money song,
but it's my favorite.
Hi. Did I accidentaIIy drop a condom
in your case?
-It's kind of an emergency.
-Yeah.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Hey, Christine! I got it!
I want to thank you
for being there for me.
Sorry I aImost broke your hand.
That's okay.
I'm sorry I poisoned you.
Remember when I jammed
a penciI into your hand?
Remember it? What do you
think this is, a freckIe?
What about the time I hit you
in the face with a pumpkin?
Remember, I stuck a broom
in your spokes...
-...and you hit your head on a curb?
-No.
But I remember
peopIe teIIing me about it.
-I hope Ben has a IittIe sister.
-Yeah.
And I hope she can kick his ass.
I'm gonna get a new Band-Aid.
How about when I cut the Iegs
off your MaIibu Ken?
That was you?
They were infected.
He wouIdn't have made it.
My IittIe nephew.
Come here, IittIe one!
There's my IittIe baby Ben!
Hey, my IittIe boy.
Hey, he's not crying!
Yes!
There's stiII pie!
I'm here. I'm here.
How's my IittIe boy?
You want Daddy to change
your diaper? I know, I know.
Did you have fun with UncIe Joey
and UncIe ChandIer today?
Yeah. He rode the bus today.
Big boy riding the bus--
Hey, I have a question.
How come it says ''Property
of Human Services'' on his butt?
You....
You are gonna Iove this.
Can you hoId Ben for a sec?
Come here.
Stay back! I've got kiwi!
Run, Joey, run!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
No, no. I'm sorry, it's:
Smelly cat, smelly cat
-Better!
-Yeah?
Much better. Good.
Don't feeI bad
because it's a hard song.
-You want to try it again?
-From the top?
There is no ''top,'' aII right?
That's the beauty of ''SmeIIy Cat.''
-Why don't you just foIIow me?
-Okay.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
It's not your fault
That's too much. Sorry.