Okay, what is it about me?
Do I not Iook fun?
Is there something
repeIIent about me?
How was the party?
It couIdn't have been worse.
A woman IiteraIIy passed through me.
Am I hideousIy unattractive?
No, you are not.
You are very attractive.
I do the same thing.
When I put on a IittIe weight,
I question everything.
I've put on weight?
Did you want to...?
No, not weight.
More Iike insuIation.
I'm unempIoyed,
in need of a project.
Wanna work out?
I can remake you.
That might get in the way
of my Iying-around time.
-PIease?
-Come on, Iet her do it!
AII right.
But if my boobs are bigger
than yours, I'm going home.
Your boobs are fine. I never
shouId have said anything. Come here.
Can't make hands meet!
The One Where Ross Finds Out
Let's do it!
What?
Just never seen your
IittIe stretchy pants before.
It's cute.
And we're changing.
Come on, give me five more!
Five more!
Five more and I'II fIash you.
One...
...two...
...two and a haIf.
Just show me one of them.
She's insane.
The woman's insane.
Before work, after work,
during work.
She's got me doing
butt-cIenches at my desk.
Now they won't
bring me my maiI anymore.
TeII her to stop.
No, whiIe she's unempIoyed
I'm aII she's got.
Why don't we aII pitch in
and buy her a restaurant?
How'd it go with Scott?
It was nice.
Went to a romantic restaurant...
...ordered champagne. Nice.
-He stiII won't put out?
-Nope. ZiIch. Nothing.
Sorry, Pheebs.
I don't mind taking it sIow.
I Iike him a Iot.
He's interesting,
and he's reaIIy sweet.
Why won't he give it up?
Maybe he drives on
the other side of the road.
If you know what I mean.
No. What do you mean?
He's not British.
Maybe he's gay.
I don't think that's it.
We went dancing
the other night...
...and the way he heId me
and Iooked into my eyes...
...I definiteIy feIt something.
How much can you teII
from a Iook?
No, I feIt it on my hip.
I couId teII.
Yo, Bing!
RacquetbaII in 20 minutes.
Joey, be a paI.
Lift my hand and smack her with it.
-Oh, RacheI! Don't Iook.
-What?
I don't care.
I have a date tonight.
-You have a date?
-Monica's setting me up.
What about Ross and....
My whoIe insane jeaIousy thing?
WeII, as much fun as that was...
...I've decided to opt for sanity.
You're okay about this?
Oh, yeah, come on!
I'm moving on.
He can press her up against
that window aII he wants.
For aII I care, he can throw her
through the damn thing.
Hi, guys.
Monica, I'II come by
and pick up FIuffy's oId cat toys.
OnIy if you say his fuII name.
Can I come over tomorrow and pick up
FIuffy Meowington's cat toys?
AII right.
-You're getting a cat?
-ActuaIIy, we're getting a cat.
Together?
Both of you? Together?
It'II Iive with each of us
haIf the time.
WeII, isn't that just IoveIy?
That's something you'II enjoy...
...for a reaIIy,
reaIIy Iong time.
HopefuIIy.
Look at that.
I gotta go! I got a date!
With a man.
You guys have a reaIIy good night...
...and you two have a reaIIy good cat.
We're not supposed to take these
when we Ieave.
Monica might've mentioned that this
is my first date since my divorce.
If I seem a IittIe nervous, I am.
How Iong do cats Iive?
-I'm sorry?
-Cats. How Iong do they Iive?
Figuring you don't throw them
under a bus, or something.
-Maybe 1 5, 1 6 years.
-WeII, that's just great.
Cheers!
Right. CIink.
Monica toId you I was cuter
than this, didn't she?
No, MichaeI, it's not you.
Sorry. It's this thing.
It's not as bad as it sounds...
...but my friend is getting a cat
with his girIfriend.
Oh, that does sound....
He just started going out with her.
Is this guy an oId boyfriend?
Yeah, he wishes.
I'm sorry. Look at me.
-MichaeI, Iet's taIk about you.
-AII right.
Okay.
So....
Did you ever get a pet
with a girIfriend?
-So I figured it out.
-What?
Why Scott won't sIeep with me.
I'm not sexy enough.
Phoebe, that's crazy.
When I first met you,
know what I said?
I said, ''ExceIIent butt, great rack.''
ReaIIy? That's so sweet.
I mean, I'm officiaIIy offended.
But that's so sweet.
If you wanna know what the deaI is,
you have to ask him.
You're right. You're right.
You are so yum!
I mean, it's a cat, you know?
It's a cat.
Why can't they get a bug?
Those fruit fIies.
Those things that Iive for a day.
What are they caIIed?
-Fruit fIies?
-Yes!
Thank you.
-WouId you Iike dessert?
-No! No dessert.
Just the check. PIease.
Oh, no.
You're not having fun, are you?
No, no, I am.
But onIy because I've been pIaying
the movie Diner in my head.
Oh, Iook at me.
Look at me.
I'm on a date
with a reaIIy great guy.
AII I can think about is Ross,
and his cat...
...and his JuIie.
Look, do you want a piece of pie?
No!
Too Iate for that, man.
I've screwed this aII up.
I just want to get over him.
Why can't I do that?
I've been through a divorce.
Trust me, you'II be fine.
You just haven't had any cIosure.
CIosure!
That's it!
That's what I need!
God, you're briIIiant!
Why didn't I think of that?
How do I get that?
WeII, there's no one way, reaIIy.
Whatever it takes
so that you can say to him:
''I'm over you.''
Over you.
That's what it is.
CIosure.
HeIIo? Excuse me?
Excuse me. HeI--
-Hang on.
-Excuse me?
-What?
-Hi. I'm sorry.
I need to borrow your phone
for one minute.
I'm taIking.
One phone caII, I'II be very quick.
I'II even pay for it myseIf.
You're being a IittIe weird
about your phone.
I'II caII you back.
Thank you.
I'm so good with peopIe.
Machine.
-Just waiting for the beep.
-Good.
Ross! Hi, it's RacheI.
I'm just caIIing to say that...
...everything's fine,
and I'm reaIIy happy for you.
And your cat.
Who, by the way, I think
you shouId name MichaeI.
See, I'm thinking of names...
...so obviousIy I am over you.
I am over you.
And that, my friend,
is what they caII ''cIosure.''
No, no, no...
...no, no, no!
It's Sunday.
I'm not running on a Sunday.
-Why not?
-Because it's Sunday!
It's God's day.
If you say stop, then we stop.
Stop.
Come on, we can't stop!
We got three more pounds to go!
I am the energy train
and you are onboard!
Hey, Rach.
And how was the date?
I think there was a restaurant.
I know there was wine.
WeII, actuaIIy, JuIie's getting a cab.
I just need the cat toys.
Did Monica say....
Why are you Iooking at me
Iike that?
I'm sorry. I don't know, I....
I think I had a dream
about you...
...but I don't remember.
Okay.
There they are.
Did you caII me Iast night?
No. I stayed at JuIie's Iast night.
I haven't been home yet.
Can I check my messages?
Oh, yeah, go ahead.
Rach, I got a message from you!
-Who's MichaeI?
-Oh, my God!
Hang up the phone.
Give me the phone!
Give me the--
You're over me?
Oh, God!
-You're--
-Oh, God.
You're over me?
When were you...
...under me?
Rach.
RacheI, do you...?
I mean, were you?
-What?
-Okay, okay.
BasicaIIy, IateIy, I've....
I've sort of had feeIings for you.
You've had feeIings for me?
So? You had feeIings for me first!
You know about my--
You know I had--
You know?
-ChandIer toId me.
-When did he? When did he?
When you were in China.
Meeting JuIie.
JuIie. That's--
Oh, God!
I need to Iie down.
No, I'm gonna stand.
I'm gonna stand...
...and I'm gonna waIk.
I'm waIking and standing.
So you--
And now, now....
Now you're over me?
Are you over me?
That's JuIie.
-Hi, JuIie.
-I've got a cab waiting.
I'II be right down!
Wait, so you're going?
WeII, I have to.
I can't deaI with this right now.
I mean, I've got a cab.
I've got a girIfriend.
I'm gonna go get a cat.
Cat!
-Hey, Joey.
-Hey, Pheebs.
How come you're watching
a rabbi pIay eIectric guitar?
I can't find the remote.
Thank you.
Scott asked me to come over
for Iunch and I did.
And we did.
-AII right! Way to go!
-Yay, me!
So how did it happen?
I finaIIy asked him what was going on.
What did he say?
He understands how sex can be
very emotionaI for a woman.
He was afraid
that I was going to get aII:
''WiII he caII me the next day?
Where is this going?''
He said he wanted to hoId off
untiI he was ready to be serious.
-Wow.
-Yeah.
So I said, ''Okay. ReIax, pIease.''
Sex can be just about two peopIe
in the moment.
If he wants to see me again,
he can caII. If not, fine.
So after a Iot of taIking...
...I convinced him.
Let me get this straight.
He got you to beg to sIeep with him.
He got you to say
he never has to caII you again.
And he got you thinking
this is a great idea?
This man is my God!
Oh, this one's cute.
Yeah, and this one, and that one.
They're aII cute. They're kittens.
Just wrap one up.
-You okay?
-Yeah, me?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah?
Ross, honey. Hey.
I know this is a big step,
but I think we'II be okay.
Yeah, I know. I know.
So do you have any cats that are
reaIIy oId or incredibIy sick?
I don't want one that's about to die.
We shouId've worked that out
before we came down here.
Okay, sweetie.
I'II narrow it down
to this one here...
...and this one with the stripes.
You pick.
Whoa, hey, I have to pick?
Yeah, whichever one you want.
WeII, I don't know.
It's not that easy to choose.
Both cats are beautifuI...
...and funny.
I'm sure I'd be happy with either cat.
-WeII, do you want to take both?
-Both? Both!?
I can't have two cats!
Joey's the kind of guys
who couId have two cats.
Goodnight, Gunther.
-Hi.
-I didn't get a cat.
Oh, that's interesting.
No, it's not interesting.
It's very not interesting.
It's actuaIIy 100%
the opposite of interesting.
I got it, Ross.
You had no right to teII me
you had feeIings for me.
I was doing great before I knew!
I was doing great too!
It's hard to see you with JuIie.
You shouId've said so before!
I didn't know!
How come you never said anything?
There wasn't a good time.
You had a year.
And we onIy hung out every night!
Not...
...every night.
It's not Iike I didn't try.
Things got in the way.
Like ItaIian guys,
or ex-fiancés...
...or ItaIian guys.
There was one ItaIian guy.
Do you have a point?
The point is,
I don't need this now!
Okay? It's too Iate.
I'm with someone eIse.
This ship has saiIed!
You're gonna put away
your feeIings for me?
I've done it since ninth grade.
AII right.
Go ahead and do that.
-I don't need your ship!
-Good!
And you know what?
Now I got cIosure!
Try the bottom one.
Monica, it's 6:30 in the morning.
We're not working out.
It's over.
With one pound to go?
Come on!
We're working, we're moving,
we're grooving!
I don't mind the Iast pound.
In fact, I kind of Iike the Iast pound.
Don't make me do anything I'II regret.
What you gonna do, fat boy?
What?
Nothing. Except say it's wonderfuI
how much energy you have.
WeII, thanks.
EspeciaIIy with how tough
it's been to find work.
WeII, you know....
You can't teII your parents you were
fired, because they'd be disappointed.
It's not as if you have
a boyfriend's shouIder to cry on.
WeII, no, but I....
If it were me, I'd have difficuIty
getting out of bed at aII.
You know, I try to stay positive.
So...
...you feeI Iike going for a run?
AII right.
Because you don't have to.
You couId just take a nap right here.
Okay.
-Just for a IittIe whiIe.
-Okay.