Okay, what is it about me?
Do I not look fun?
Is there something
repellent about me?
How was the party?
It couldn't have been worse.
A woman literally passed through me.
Am I hideously unattractive?
No, you are not.
You are very attractive.
I do the same thing.
When I put on a little weight,
I question everything.
I've put on weight?
Did you want to...?
No, not weight.
More like insulation.
I'm unemployed,
in need of a project.
Wanna work out?
I can remake you.
That might get in the way
of my lying-around time.
Please?
Come on, let her do it!
All right.
But if my boobs are bigger
than yours, I'm going home.
Your boobs are fine. I never
should have said anything. Come here.
Can't make hands meet!
Let's do it!
What?
Just never seen your
little stretchy pants before.
It's cute.
And we're changing.
Come on, give me five more!
Five more!
Five more and I'll flash you.
One...two...two and a half.
Just show me one of them.
She's insane.
The woman's insane.
Before work, after work,
during work.
She's got me doing
butt-clenches at my desk.
Now they won't
bring me my mail anymore.
Tell her to stop.
No, while she's unemployed
I'm all she's got.
Why don't we all pitch in
and buy her a restaurant?
How'd it go with Scott?
It was nice.
Went to a romantic restaurant ordered champagne. Nice.
He still won't put out?
Nope. Zilch. Nothing.
Sorry, Pheebs.
I don't mind taking it slow.
I like him a lot.
He's interesting,
and he's really sweet.
Why won't he give it up?
Maybe he drives on
the other side of the road.
If you know what I mean.
No. What do you mean?
He's not British.
Maybe he's gay.
I don't think that's it.
We went dancing
the other night and the way he held me
and looked into my eyes I definitely felt something.
How much can you tell
from a look?
No, I felt it on my hip.
I could tell.
Yo, Bing!
Racquetball in 20 minutes.
Joey, be a pal.
Lift my hand and smack her with it.
Oh, Rachel! Don't look.
What?
I don't care.
I have a date tonight.
You have a date?
Monica's setting me up.
What about Ross and....
My whole insane jealousy thing?
Well, as much fun as that was I've decided to opt for sanity.
You're okay about this?
Oh, yeah, come on!
I'm moving on.
He can press her up against
that window all he wants.
For all I care, he can throw her
through the damn thing.
Hi, guys.
Monica, I'll come by
and pick up Fluffy's old cat toys.
Only if you say his full name.
Can I come over tomorrow and pick up
Fluffy Meowington's cat toys?
All right.
You're getting a cat?
Actually, we're getting a cat.
Together?
Both of you? Together?
It'll live with each of us
half the time.
Well, isn't that just lovely?
That's something you'll enjoy for a really,
really long time.
Hopefully.
Look at that.
I gotta go! I got a date!
With a man.
You guys have a really good night and you two have a really good cat.
We're not supposed to take these
when we leave.
Monica might've mentioned that this
is my first date since my divorce.
If I seem a little nervous, I am.
How long do cats live?
I'm sorry?
Cats. How long do they live?
Figuring you don't throw them
under a bus, or something.
Maybe 1 5, 1 6 years.
Well, that's just great.
Cheers!
Right. Clink.
Monica told you I was cuter
than this, didn't she?
No, Michael, it's not you.
Sorry. It's this thing.
It's not as bad as it sounds but my friend is getting a cat
with his girlfriend.
Oh, that does sound....
He just started going out with her.
Is this guy an old boyfriend?
Yeah, he wishes.
I'm sorry. Look at me.
Michael, let's talk about you.
All right.
Okay.
So....
Did you ever get a pet
with a girlfriend?
So I figured it out.
What?
Why Scott won't sleep with me.
I'm not sexy enough.
Phoebe, that's crazy.
When I first met you,
know what I said?
I said, ''Excellent butt, great rack.''
Really? That's so sweet.
I mean, I'm officially offended.
But that's so sweet.
If you wanna know what the deal is,
you have to ask him.
You're right. You're right.
You are so yum!
I mean, it's a cat, you know?
It's a cat.
Why can't they get a bug?
Those fruit flies.
Those things that live for a day.
What are they called?
Fruit flies?
Yes!
Thank you.
Would you like dessert?
No! No dessert.
Just the check. Please.
Oh, no.
You're not having fun, are you?
No, no, I am.
But only because I've been playing
the movie Diner in my head.
Oh, look at me.
Look at me.
I'm on a date
with a really great guy.
All I can think about is Ross,
and his cat and his Julie.
Look, do you want a piece of pie?
No!
Too late for that, man.
I've screwed this all up.
I just want to get over him.
Why can't I do that?
I've been through a divorce.
Trust me, you'll be fine.
You just haven't had any closure.
Closure!
That's it!
That's what I need!
God, you're brilliant!
Why didn't I think of that?
How do I get that?
Well, there's no one way, really.
Whatever it takes
so that you can say to him:
''I'm over you.''
Over you.
That's what it is.
Closure.
Hello? Excuse me?
Excuse me. Hel--
Hang on.
Excuse me?
What?
Hi. I'm sorry.
I need to borrow your phone
for one minute.
I'm talking.
One phone call, I'll be very quick.
I'll even pay for it myself.
You're being a little weird
about your phone.
I'll call you back.
Thank you.
I'm so good with people.
Machine.
Just waiting for the beep.
Good.
Ross! Hi, it's Rachel.
I'm just calling to say that everything's fine,
and I'm really happy for you.
And your cat.
Who, by the way, I think
you should name Michael.
See, I'm thinking of names so obviously I am over you.
I am over you.
And that, my friend,
is what they call ''closure.''
No, no, no no, no, no!
It's Sunday.
I'm not running on a Sunday.
Why not?
Because it's Sunday!
It's God's day.
If you say stop, then we stop.
Stop.
Come on, we can't stop!
We got three more pounds to go!
I am the energy train
and you are onboard!
Hey, Rach.
And how was the date?
I think there was a restaurant.
I know there was wine.
Well, actually, Julie's getting a cab.
I just need the cat toys.
Did Monica say....
Why are you looking at me
like that?
I'm sorry. I don't know, I....
I think I had a dream
about you but I don't remember.
Okay.
There they are.
Did you call me last night?
No. I stayed at Julie's last night.
I haven't been home yet.
Can I check my messages?
Oh, yeah, go ahead.
Rach, I got a message from you!
Who's Michael?
Oh, my God!
Hang up the phone.
Give me the phone!
Give me the--
You're over me?
Oh, God!
You're--
Oh, God.
You're over me?
When were you under me?
Rach.
Rachel, do you...?
I mean, were you?
What?
Okay, okay.
Basically, lately, I've....
I've sort of had feelings for you.
You've had feelings for me?
So? You had feelings for me first!
You know about my--
You know I had--
You know?
Chandler told me.
When did he? When did he?
When you were in China.
Meeting Julie.
Julie. That's--
Oh, God!
I need to lie down.
No, I'm gonna stand.
I'm gonna stand and I'm gonna walk.
I'm walking and standing.
So you--
And now, now....
Now you're over me?
Are you over me?
That's Julie.
Hi, Julie.
-I've got a cab waiting.
I'll be right down!
Wait, so you're going?
Well, I have to.
I can't deal with this right now.
I mean, I've got a cab.
I've got a girlfriend.
I'm gonna go get a cat.
Cat!
Hey, Joey.
Hey, Pheebs.
How come you're watching
a rabbi play electric guitar?
I can't find the remote.
Thank you.
Scott asked me to come over
for lunch and I did.
And we did.
All right! Way to go!
Yay, me!
So how did it happen?
I finally asked him what was going on.
What did he say?
He understands how sex can be
very emotional for a woman.
He was afraid
that I was going to get all:
''Will he call me the next day?
Where is this going?''
He said he wanted to hold off
until he was ready to be serious.
Wow.
Yeah.
So I said, ''Okay. Relax, please.''
Sex can be just about two people
in the moment.
If he wants to see me again,
he can call. If not, fine.
So after a lot of talking I convinced him.
Let me get this straight.
He got you to beg to sleep with him.
He got you to say
he never has to call you again.
And he got you thinking
this is a great idea?
This man is my God!
Oh, this one's cute.
Yeah, and this one, and that one.
They're all cute. They're kittens.
Just wrap one up.
You okay?
Yeah, me?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah?
Ross, honey. Hey.
I know this is a big step,
but I think we'll be okay.
Yeah, I know. I know.
So do you have any cats that are
really old or incredibly sick?
I don't want one that's about to die.
We should've worked that out
before we came down here.
Okay, sweetie.
I'll narrow it down
to this one here and this one with the stripes.
You pick.
Whoa, hey, I have to pick?
Yeah, whichever one you want.
Well, I don't know.
It's not that easy to choose.
Both cats are beautiful...and funny.
I'm sure I'd be happy with either cat.
Well, do you want to take both?
Both? Both!?
I can't have two cats!
Joey's the kind of guys
who could have two cats.
Goodnight, Gunther.
Hi.
I didn't get a cat.
Oh, that's interesting.
No, it's not interesting.
It's very not interesting.
It's actually 100%
the opposite of interesting.
I got it, Ross.
You had no right to tell me
you had feelings for me.
I was doing great before I knew!
I was doing great too!
It's hard to see you with Julie.
You should've said so before!
I didn't know!
How come you never said anything?
There wasn't a good time.
You had a year.
And we only hung out every night!
Not every night.
It's not like I didn't try.
Things got in the way.
Like Italian guys,
or ex-fiancés or Italian guys.
There was one Italian guy.
Do you have a point?
The point is,
I don't need this now!
Okay? It's too late.
I'm with someone else.
This ship has sailed!
You're gonna put away
your feelings for me?
I've done it since ninth grade.
All right.
Go ahead and do that.
I don't need your ship!
Good!
And you know what?
Now I got closure!
Try the bottom one.
Monica, it's 6:30 in the morning.
We're not working out.
It's over.
With one pound to go?
Come on!
We're working, we're moving,
we're grooving!
I don't mind the last pound.
In fact, I kind of like the last pound.
Don't make me do anything I'll regret.
What you gonna do, fat boy?
What?
Nothing. Except say it's wonderful
how much energy you have.
Well, thanks.
Especially with how tough
it's been to find work.
Well, you know....
You can't tell your parents you were
fired, because they'd be disappointed.
It's not as if you have
a boyfriend's shoulder to cry on.
Well, no, but I....
If it were me, I'd have difficulty
getting out of bed at all.
You know, I try to stay positive.
So you feel like going for a run?
All right.
Because you don't have to.
You could just take a nap right here.
Okay.
Just for a little while.