Can't get the monkey off your back?
Then put it in your mouth  with Monkeyshine Beer.
Get it, monkey
Get it, get it, monkey
Monkey, monkey
Monkeyshine Beer.
'Cause it's a jungle out there.
That commercial always makes me sad.
But the guy opens his beer,
the girls run at him so everything works out okay.
I meant,
the monkey reminds me of Marcel.
I can see that.
Because they both have those big
brown eyes and the little pouty chin.
And the fact that
they're both monkeys?
Did I do the right thing,
giving him away?
Ross, you had to.
He was humping everything in sight.
My Malibu Barbie won't
be wearing white to her wedding.
Remember when he'd borrow your hat and when you got it back,
there'd be monkey raisins in it?
He loved that joke.
When he did it, it was funny.
When I did it to my boss...suddenly I had this big
attitude problem.
Hey, check it out.
Guess what I got?
Rhythm?
No. My first fan mail.
''Dear Dr. Ramoray:
I love you and would do
anything to have you.''
My gosh. ''Your not-so-secret
admirer, Erika Ford.''
Oh, wait.
''P.S. Enclosed, please find
1 4 of my eyelashes.''
In Crazy World, that means
you're married.
It's not addressed to Days of our
Lives. It came to your apartment.
She was in our building.
Oh, my God.
I got my very own stalker.
You're so lucky.
I have to share with guys at work.
Remember we talked about ''good thing,
bad thing''? This is a bad thing.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Where are you off to?
There's a paleontology
conference in L.A.
I figured I'd go, drive down
to the zoo and surprise Marcel.
He will be surprised.
Till he realizes he's a monkey and isn't capable of that emotion.
Phoebe?
That cute guy is here again.
Okay, so everyone pretend I'm telling a story.
It's really funny.
So everyone just laugh.
Now!
I know, I know.
Hello.
Hi.
I'm Rob Donnen.
Hi, Rob Donnen.
I don't know a thing about music
but I think you're great.
Oh! Wow.
Anyway, I schedule performers
for children's libraries.
I was thinking, have you thought
about playing your songs for kids?
I would love to have kids...hear me play the songs
that I will write for them.
What'll we do for dinner?
We could cook for ourselves.
Hello.
-It's Erika.
My God. The stalker!
It's open.
Hit her with a frying pan.
Good idea.
But we want a backup plan,
in case she isn't a cartoon.
Let's get out of here.
The one time they're not home.
We'll leave. When we pass her, she
won't know it's me. We've never met.
That's how radio stars
escape stalkers.
She's coming.
It's me.
This is it.
This is how we're gonna die.
You ready?
Wait, wait, wait.
Erika!
Mr. Geller?
Yes, hi.
Dean Lipson, zoo administrator.
You had a question?
I can't find the monkey
I donated last year.
He's a capuchin,
answers to the name Marcel?
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
Marcel has passed on.
Oh, my God! What happened?
He got sick,
and then he got sicker then he got a little better.
But then he died.
I can't believe this.
I'm sorry, Mr. Geller.
But you know, there's an old saying:
''Sometimes monkeys die.''
It's not a great saying but it certainly is fitting today.
Someone should've called me.
I'm sorry.
Look, I know this can't bring him
back, but here. It's just a gesture.
Zoo dollars?
Yes, and come see the bird show at 4.
The macaws wear hats.
It's cuter if your monkey
hasn't just died.
I know.
I can't believe Joey's having lunch
with his stalker. What is she like?
Remember Kathy Bates in Misery?
Well, she looks
the exact opposite of that.
And she's not crazy?
Oh, no.
She's a total whack-job.
She thinks that Joey is
actually Dr. Drake Ramoray.
Oh, my God.
And he's going out with her?
He cannot pursue this.
Just because she thinks she can truly
see Joey through her magic box doesn't mean she's not a person.
Does she not deserve happiness
or love?
Why are you looking at me?
He wants to boff the maniac.
Are you okay?
No, I'm nervous.
Maybe if I picture them
in their underwear....
That's not a good idea.
That's why the last guy got fired.
I'm used to playing for grownups.
Grownups drink coffee,
do their grownup thing.
And kids listen.
It's just a huge responsibility.
What?
Are you gonna kiss me?
I was thinking about it.
Okay.
Alrighty. Let's play some tunes.
Let's go find our seats.
Chandler?
Hold on a second.
He thinks he can.
Oh, what the hell?
He can.
Hi, everybody. I'm Phoebe.
Hi, Phoebe!
I'm gonna play some songs
about grandparents, okay?
Now Grandma's a person
Who everyone likes
She bought you a train
And a bright shiny bike
But lately she hasn't
Been coming to dinner
And last time you saw her
She looked so much thinner
Now, your mom and your dad said
She moved to Peru
But the truth is she died
And someday you will too
I'll have the grilled salmon.
And the doctor will have the risotto.
Oh, Drake, isn't it amazing?
Yeah, it is.
What?
Well, here we sit, devil-may-care and a while ago you were
re-attaching Simone's spinal cord.
That was a tricky one.
In reality, that operation takes 10
hours. They only showed two minutes.
Who's ''they''?
No one.
Drake, you are so talented.
Let me see those hands.
These hands, these beautiful hands.
I could just eat them.
But I won't.
Otherwise my watch would fall off.
No, seriously.
These hands, these miracle,
magical, life-giving hands.
Just to be near them, touch them,
maybe even lick one?
All right. Just one.
You're good at that.
Oh, my God! Someone, he's choking.
Is anyone here a doctor?
Yes, the best doctor in Salem.
Dr. Drake Ramoray.
Meet me in the nocturnal
house in 1 5 minutes.
Hey, look. I don't really enjoy
being with other men that way.
But...zoo dollars?
It's about your monkey.
It's alive.
I don't understand.
Why didn't you help that man?
Because I'm a neurosurgeon and that was clearly a case of ''foodal chokage.''
I gotta tell you something--
No.
You don't have to tell me anything.
You don't have to explain yourself.
Who am I to question
the great Dr. Ramoray?
I should be happy to be near you.
Hey, I--
Hey what?
That's it. Just hey.
Like at the end of a dance. ''Hey!''
There'll be times when you get older
When you'll want to sleep with people
Just to make them like you
But don't!
'Cause that's another thing that you don't wanna do
Everybody!
That's another thing
That you don't wanna do
Excellent!
Very informative.
Not at all inappropriate.
Thank you for coming.
There are cookies in the back.
That was great.
The kids loved you.
I rock.
You know why?
Because you told the truth.
Nobody tells kids the truth.
You were incredible.
But...?
How'd you know there was a ''but''?
I sense things.
It was either ''but'' or ''butter.''
I think some of the parents....
They were hoping that you'd play songs
about barnyard animals.
I can do that.
Really?
Because that would be fantastic.
What? You wanna kiss me?
I'm thinking about it.
If I get a library card,
can I take you out some time?
What?
I'm unemployed.
The bat.
Ambassador of darkness.
Flitting out of his cave
like a winged messenger.
Sightless specter of the macabre.
Buddy, my monkey?
Oh, yeah, right.
There was a break-in
a few months back. Inside job.
Your monkey was taken.
Along with a snowy egret,
a two-toed sloth and three sweatshirts
from the zoo gift shop.
But the zoo told me
that my monkey was dead.
The zoo.
You believe everything
the zoo tells you?
That's the only thing
the zoo's ever told me.
Of course they say that.
They don't want bad publicity.
It's a big cover-up.
Do you have any idea
how high up this thing goes?
That guy Lipson?
Lipson knows?
Who else knows?
I only know Lipson.
Lipson knows, huh?
Hello, Mr. Possum.
Enigma of the trees,
upside-down denizen of the night.
Taunting gravity--
Buddy, my monkey?
Word on the street--
When I say ''street,''
I mean those pretend streets here.
Of course.
Your monkey found a new career in the entertainment field.
That's all I know.
This is unbelievable!
So, what is this information
worth to you, my friend?
Are you trying
to get me to bribe you?
Maybe.
But you already told me everything.
Check it out.
He actually is the Monkeyshine monkey.
What'll you do?
I'll call the beer company
and try to find him.
That's what I did
when I lost my Clydesdales.
Okay, hi again.
Hi, Phoebe.
Today we're gonna start with
some songs about barnyard animals.
The cow in the meadow goes moo
The farmer hits him and grinds him up
And that's how we get hamburgers
Now chickens!
-You're the only one who can save her.
-Damn it. I'm a doctor. I'm not God.
There goes my belief system.
It's Erika.
Quick. Shut off the TV.
I wanna see what happens.
I get Leslie out of the coma.
We kiss.
You were just kissing Sabrina.
Rachel, it's a world
where Joey is a neurosurgeon.
Hey, Erika. Come in.
How'd you get here so fast?
I just saw you in Salem.
Right, they choppered me in.
What's up?
You're having a party too.
Is she here?
Who?
Sabrina. I know about you two.
I saw you
kissing in the doctor's lounge.
It's not what you think--
You told me I was the only one.
All right, look.
That's it.
We shouldn't see each other.
I should have told you before but I am not Drake Ramoray.
I'm not a doctor. I'm an actor.
I pretend to be a doctor.
Oh, my God.
Do the people at the hospital know?
Somebody wanna help me out here?
Oh, I know. I know.
Where am I?
University Hospital  where you've been for 18 years.
How can you be here and there?
Because it's a TV show.
What are you getting at?
Nice girl. Not great with concepts.
I'm not Drake.
That's right.
He's not Drake. He's Hans Ramoray, Drake's evil twin.
Is this true?
Yes. Yes, it is true.
And I know this because he pretended
to be Drake to sleep with me.
And he told me
he would run away with me.
And he didn't.
And you left the toilet seat up,
you bastard!
Is all this true?
Yes, I'm afraid it is.
You deserve much better than me.
You deserve to be with the real Drake,
who you fell in love with.
Go to Salem. Find him.
He's the guy for you.
Oh, Hans.
Hans?
Hans.
Yo, evil twin!
Right. Goodbye, Erika.
Good luck in Salem.
Take care.
I'll never forget you, Hans.
Okay, the people who threw the water!
Helping you out.
Fired?
Why?
The library board got complaints
from parents about your songs.
I can't believe it. The library?
Books. Free speech.
Newspapers on sticks.
I know.
And the kids? Did you tell your board
that the kids want to hear the truth?
No.
I see.
Maybe if you just played
some regular kiddie songs....
No. What do you want me to be?
Like some stupid, big, like, purple dinosaur?
You don't have to be Barney.
Who's Barney?
You'll never believe it.
Let me guess.
What?
Some Weebles actually do fall down?
A stitch in time now only saves seven?
What do you got?
Well never mind.
What? What?
I tracked down Marcel.
He's healthy, he's happy and he's in New York filming
Outbreak 2: The Virus Takes Manhattan.
You're kidding!
This is amazing.
I know.
I finally get on TV and
the monkey's making movies.
Rachel, I'm ready.
Excuse me. Is this where the
singing lady is, who tells the truth?
I guess that's me.
She's here!
Sometimes men love women
Sometimes men love men
Then there are bisexuals
Though some just say
They're kidding themselves
I haven't seen my monkey in a year.
You never look down in the shower?
I'm not allowed one joke
in the ''monkey is penis'' genre?
Back up, please.
Back up. Come on.
Excuse me.
Where can we find the monkey?
It's a closed set.
You don't understand.
I'm a friend of his.
We used to live together.
I have a timeshare
in the Poconos with Flipper.
There he is!
Hey! Buddy!
Marcel. Marcel!
In the jungle
The mighty jungle
The lion sleeps tonight
In the jungle
The mighty jungle
The lion sleeps tonight
Excuse me, this is a--
Closed set. We know.
We're friends with the monkey.
Good morning.
Look who I brought!
Your friend, Harry Elefante.
Whoa, dude. Burn.
I don't get it. He seemed
so happy to see me yesterday.
Don't take it personal. He's under
pressure, starring in a movie.
How big of a star is Marcel?
In human terms? I'd say Cybill Shepherd.
So you guys in the movie
or you just really paranoid?
Hey, Sal?
Jerry's asking if the monkey's ready.
Excuse me?
Jerry is the director?
Which one's he?
The one in the director's chair.
Gotcha.
Pheebs, walk with me.
Okay.
Why am I walking with you?
We're going over here
so we can get away from the horrible flesh-eating virus!
For the love of God,
listen to me!
Is he looking? Is he looking?
We've got a problem.
Tell me.
Can't do Chris' makeup.
She won't acknowledge her mustache.
Is it bad?
It looks like her eyebrow fell down.
Unless we convince her to bleach it,
Van Damme will be kissing Gabe Kaplan.
I'll talk to her.
I hate actors.
Nice camouflage. For a minute,
I almost didn't see you.
Excuse me.
Is your name Chandler?
Yes, it is.
Chandler Bing?
Do you know me
or are you just good at this game?
I'm Susie Moss.
Fourth grade? Glasses?
I carried a box of
animal crackers like a purse?
Susie Moss.
Right. Yeah. Wow.
You look....
Great job growing up.
It's nice to see you don't still
wear the cap with the mirrors.
I graduated fourth grade
and realized I wasn't a pimp.
Remember the class play?
You pulled up my skirt and the
entire auditorium saw my underpants?
Yes. Back then,
I used humor as a defense mechanism.
Thank God I don't do that anymore.
So? What have you
been doing since childhood?
Well, I got a new belt.
I wondered.
Oh, my God.
What? What?
It's Jean-Claude Van Damme.
I didn't know he was in this.
He is so hot.
You think?
The Muscles from Brussels?
Wham-Bam Van Damme?
Did you see Timecop?
No. Was he any good in it?
Rachel, he totally changed time.
So why don't you go talk to him?
Go tell him he's cute.
What could happen?
He could hear me.
I'm doing it for you.
Don't you dare. Don't.
Don't!
Tell him I cook.
Excuse me. Hi.
Hi.
This is gonna sound kind of goofy...but my friend over there who cooks, by the way....
She thinks you're cute.
You don't think I'm cute?
I don't know.
Do you think you're cute?
We're getting off the track.
I was supposed to tell you my friend thinks you're cute.
What should I tell her?
You can tell her
I think her friend is cute.
Stephen Hurs would
eat things for money.
David Stein had no elbows.
Who got caught masturbating?
That's not what he was doing.
He was looking for his bus money.
Makeup!
That's me. I gotta go.
Oh. Okay.
How many times must I touch you on
the arm before you ask me on a date?
Well, let's try one more.
There you go. Ernie's, 8:00?
I'll be there.
And if things go well, maybe this time
I'll get to see your underwear.
No one was around to hear that?
So, what did he say?
What a jerk!
I kept talking about you
and he kept asking me out.
Naturally, you know, I said no.
Thanks anyway.
He just kept asking and asking, asking, asking....
If you want to go out with him,
you can.
Sounds like a jerk to me, but--
Jean-Claude, she said yes.
I'll see you tonight.
Thank you.
Then Jean-Claude took me
to Crossroads where we hung out
with Drew Barrymore.
Oh, man. She's so smoking.
She has the greatest set--
No guys around, huh?
Anybody need anything?
I'll have espresso.
I'll get it. If I ask you,
you'll end up drinking it yourself.
That is so unfair.
I know.
Like you'd drink her coffee after
what you did with Van Damme?
I have to cancel racquetball tonight.
Marcel's trainer will let me
have him for a while.
You're blowing me off?
We can reschedule for Saturday.
Unless you hook up
with a bunch of pigeons.
Stick a fork in me...I am done.
Stick a fork what?
Like when you're cooking a steak.
I don't eat meat.
How do you know
when vegetables are done?
You don't.
You eat them and you can tell.
Then eat me, I'm done.
I've met the perfect woman.
We're on her couch, fooling around and then she turns to me and says:
''Ever want to do it in an elevator?''
What did you say?
I believe my exact words were:
How do you know if you wanna do that?
You just know.
We gotta go.
Got a reservation in 30 minutes.
No. What I had planned shouldn't take
more than two, three minutes, tops.
Two hundred seconds of passion!
We gotta go.
But here's an idea.
Have you ever worn
women's underwear?
Well, yes, actually but they were my Aunt Edna's.
And there were three of us in there.
I was thinking
it would be kind of sexy if you wore mine tonight at dinner.
You want me to wear your panties?
Could you?
If I wear your underwear,
then what would you be wearing?
You're swell.
Got the music. Got the dinner.
I made Marcel's favorite dish,
banana cake with mealworm.
Candle.
What do you think's
gonna happen here tonight?
Hello.
Hi, are you on your way over--?
No, I understand.
A monkey's gotta work.
It's no big deal. It's not like
I had anything special planned.
Yeah. Okay.
Okay. Bye.
I'm sorry, man.
Feel that?
What?
The moment we should have
stopped holding hands?
Rachel, why don't you
start talking first?
All right.
This is totally unjustified.
She gave me the green light.
I did nothing--
Do you think I can't
see you in the TV set?
If there is something
you'd like to share--
You had no right.
That's the most ridiculous--
You sold me out.
I did not.
You absolutely--
Would you let me talk?
Did you just flick me?
You wouldn't let me finish and I was--
That hurt.
Quit flicking.
Stop flicking!
You flicked me first!
Let's not do this.
Happy thoughts. Happy thoughts.
Now I'm gonna kick some ass.
All right.
Now, I will let go if you both stop.
You want me to stop seeing him?
You want me to tell him
you're seeing him instead?
Is that what you want?
Okay.
That's what you want?
Yes.
Fine.
There we go.
If we were in prison,
you guys would be my bitches.
Thanks for letting me tag along.
Forget about it.
How you doing there, squirmy?
I'm hanging in.
And a little out.
So, assistant to the director?
That's an exciting job.
You must have responsibilities--
I don't do the casting.
What are you guys gonna eat?
How come all I can think about is
putting that ice in my mouth and licking you all over?
'Cause I went to an all-boys high
school and God is making up for it?
I want you right here right now.
Right now, right here?
Don't you think
we're in a public place?
They do have the shrimp.
Meet me in the bathroom.
I'm going to the bathroom now.
He likes to keep us in the loop.
Come on.
I can't believe we're doing this.
All right, mister.
Let's see those panties.
Alrighty.
But you know what
would be even sexier?
What?
If you didn't have
your shirt tucked into them.
All right. Now, I would like
to see you wearing nothing but them.
Take your clothes off.
I hope you realize we'll miss
hearing about the specials.
Come on, hurry.
Do you want this done quick
or done right?
All right, turn around.
I wanna see you from behind.
Somebody's been doing
his Buns of Steel video.
So you want me
to clench anything or...?
Susie?
This is for the 4th grade.
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
I mean underpants, mister.
That's what.
What? What do you mean?
My skirt you lifted. Kids laughing.
I was Susie Underpants till I was 18.
That was 4th grade.
How could you still be upset?
Call me in 20 years and tell me
if you're still upset about this.
I hope you realize you're not
getting these underpants back.
I can't believe this.
Just two weeks ago,
I was watching Sudden Death and now I'm on a date
with Jean-Claude Van Damme.
Can you beat up that guy?
Sure.
This is so wild.
I gotta admit, I was surprised
that you agreed to go on a blind date.
Normally I would not do it.
What made you make
the exception for me?
Rachel told me you wanted a threesome
with me and Drew Barrymore.
By the way,
Drew has some ground rules and....
Say you're sorry.
No.
Say it!
No! I'm not gonna.
Say it. Say it.
Oh, great.
Say you're sorry
or your sweater gets it.
That is my favorite sweater.
My third-date sweater.
Say you're sorry.
You wanna play?
Okay, let's play.
Let's play.
What'll you do?
Give me my sweater
or it's handbag marinara.
You don't have the guts.
At least I wasn't too chicken
to tell a guy he was cute.
Stop! Stop the madness!
This is crazy.
Who can even remember
why you're fighting?
Yes, that's right.
But still....
Look at your purse.
Look at your sweater.
Look at yourselves.
I'll help you fix your sweater.
I'll help you throw out your purse.
I'm sorry I made you stop seeing him.
I'm sorry I went out with him
when I knew you liked him.
I'm sorry that I borrowed your gloves.
Joey?
Ma?
Joey.
Chandler?
You're still here?
I thought you guys took off.
She took off with my clothes.
Are you naked in there?
Well, not exactly.
I'm wearing panties.
You always wear panties?
No, no. This is the first time.
Wow! Talk about your bad luck.
The first time you try panties and
someone walks off with your clothes.
I was not trying them out.
Susie asked me to wear them.
Let me see.
No. I'm not letting you
or anybody else see, ever.
All right, all right.
Someone's flossing.
Joey, some people don't like that.
Chandler's wearing panties.
What? Let me see.
You don't have to see.
Hi, tushy.
One of you give me your underpants.
Can't help you. I'm not wearing any.
How can you not be wearing any?
I'm getting heat from the guy
in the hot pink thong.
Look, Ross. I'll give you
$50 for your underpants.
Can I have the milk?
I'm almost done.
Keep your panties on.
I'm in the movie!
What happened?
A victim called in sick.
Cathy recommended me and boom!
I'm dying on a gurney.
Marcel finished his last scene
if you want to say goodbye.
That's okay. He's probably
got parties to go to and stuff.
He's moved on.
That's the way it goes, right?
Oh, my God.
What?
Sorry it didn't work out between us.
Or us.
Drew was very disappointed.
Okay. Well, bye.
Goodbye.
Well, bye for me too.
Okay. Well, bye-bye again.
Okay.
Perhaps the three of us just could:
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Are you sure?
I can crush a walnut with my butt.
Oh, no, no, no. Impressive.
But no.
Maybe if I were baking.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Bye, Marcel.
See you on the big screen.
You keep people drinking
that beer, okay?
I'll miss you, buddy.
Bye.
I think I want to write
a song about all this.
Except one of the strings
on my guitar is broken.
Chandler, can I borrow your G-string?
How long you been waiting to say that?
About 20 minutes!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
Cut!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
Cut!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
Mommy!
Can't you see what's going on?
This man is dead!