All right, no peeking.
No peeking. No peeking. No peeking!
All right, but you better be
wearing clothes when I open my eyes.
All right. Open your eyes.
Sweet mother of all
that is good and pure!
Days of our Lives picked up my option!
Congratulations!
Now we can watch Green Acres
the way it was meant to be seen.
So which one is mine?
Whichever one you want, man.
Whichever one you want!
Not that one.
Oh, yes!
Oh, yeah! That's the stuff.
Do we dare?
We dare.
I can't believe two cows made a
sacrifice so you guys could watch TV with your feet up.
They were chair-shaped cows.
They never would have survived
in the wild.
This screen is amazing.
Dick Van Dyke is practically life-size.
Rose Marie really belongs
on a smaller screen.
Hi, you guys.
Hey, you.
How was your day?
You know, pretty much the usual.
Sun shining, birds chirping.
Really? Mine too.
Hey, cool. Mine too.
I gotta get to the museum.
I'll see you tonight?
Okay.
Bye, guys!
Tonight?
What's tonight?
Our first official date. First date.
Hello?
Hi.
You're waitressing
at my catering thing.
Any of those words trigger anything?
Monica, I forgot.
It's our first date.
My mom got me this job.
I can be a waitress!
Thank you, thank you.
See? Phoebe! Phoebe!
You'd have to be an actual waitress.
It can't be like your ''I can be a bear cub'' thing.
I can be a waitress. Watch this.
Give me two number ones, 86 the bacon.
One Adam and Eve on a raft
and wreck them!
It's James Bond.
Sorry we're late.
That's okay. Come on in.
Is Monica Geller coming?
I was told she was.
Dr. Burke, it's me.
Monica?
My God! You used to be so....
I mean, you've--
You must have lost like....
You look great.
Thank you. This is Phoebe.
She'll be helping me.
Nice to meet you.
How you been?
Great. How have you been?
You know Barbara and I split
or you wouldn't do the head tilt.
The head tilt?
Since the divorce everybody asks how I am with a
sympathetic head tilt. ''How you doing?''
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Believe me, I do it too.
I always answer with the
''I'm okay'' head bob. ''I'm okay.''
''You're sure?''
''Yeah, I'm fine.''
I gotta set up the music.
I got a new CD changer.
The divorce only left
me with four CDs to change.
That's too bad.
I'll survive.
Two larges, extra cheese on both.
But listen don't ring the buzzer for 1 9.
Ring 20. Geller/Greene.
They'll let you in, okay?
If you buzz our door,
there's no tip for you.
Okay, thanks.
Pizza's on the way.
I told you we wouldn't have to get up.
What if we have to pee?
I'll cancel the sodas.
Get out there.
It's your party!
They're so dull!
They're all ophthalmologists.
You're an ophthalmologist.
That's what my parents wanted.
I wanted to be a sheriff.
That's funny. Cadillac, cataract.
I get it.
No! You stay out there!
You see?
I tell you what.
I'll come get you in five minutes
with some sort of kebab emergency.
Better. Oh, God, here we go.
Want to see them go nuts?
Watch this.
Who needs glasses?
You are so smitten.
I am not!
Oh, you are so much
the smitten kitten.
Ask him out.
Dr. Burke?
I don't think so.
I mean, like, he's a grownup.
So? You two are totally
into each other.
He's a family friend.
He's 20 years older than me.
So you're never gonna see him again?
Not never.
I'm gonna see him tomorrow
at my eye appointment.
Didn't you just get your eyes checked?
Yeah, but you know 27 is a dangerous eye age.
They're picking teams to play
''Guess my prescription.'' Help me!
I'm not saying it was a bad movie.
I'm saying it was a little hard to follow.
I told you there would be subtitles.
I know.
I just didn't want to wear
my glasses on our first date.
Monica?
It would help when I'm kissing you
if you didn't shout my sister's name.
I'm just checking.
Monica?
Mon?
What?
I'm sorry.
When you moved your hands
down to my butt it was, like,
''Whoa! Ross's hands are on my butt!''
And that's funny. Why?
Well, it's not.
Sorry. I'm just nervous.
I mean, it's you. You know, it's us.
We're crossing that line.
It's sort of a big thing.
Well, I know it's big.
I just didn't know it was ha-ha big.
Okay, my hands were
nowhere near your butt.
I know! I know!
I was thinking about
the last time they were there.
I'm sorry. Look! I promise.
I won't laugh anymore.
Put your hands back.
No, see, now I can't.
I'm feeling too self-conscious.
Touch my butt.
Just one cheek.
The moment's gone.
I'll back up into your hands.
That's romantic.
-Touch it.
-No.
-Come on, squeeze it.
-No!
-Rub it?
-No.
Oh, come on!
Would you just grab my ass?
Wow! Look at that!
The car is on fire yet somehow
its expensive paint job is protected by the Miracle Wax.
You got a Chee-to on your face, man.
Aren't you supposed
to be out with Rachel?
That was 1 4 hours ago.
We gotta set the clock on this.
So how'd it go?
Have you ever been, you know,
fooling around with a girl and she started laughing?
Yeah.
But it was 1 982 and my Flock of
Seagulls haircut tickled her chin.
She laughed at you?
It could have been worse.
I could have been naked.
I've wanted this since 9th grade.
I want it to be perfect and right and....
Why isn't that laser
cutting through the paint?
It's the Miracle Wax!
It certainly is a miracle.
Hi, you guys.
Hey.
Listen, I was thinking about....
Can you guys speak up?
It's harder for us to hear you
when you lower your voice.
Hallway?
Yeah.
I'm sorry about last night.
I really want to make it up to you.
There's no need to make it--
How?
Well, I was thinking maybe
a romantic dinner with candles and wine.
And then maybe going
back to my place for dessert.
That sounds perfect.
What's this?
Would you get us a couple of beers?
I'm going to look into your eyes now.
Really?
Yeah, that's my job.
All right. Look up.
Look down.
No, open your eyes and look down.
That's right.
Look into the light.
Now look at me.
Okay!
Your eyes look good.
Those are good eyes.
Good. They feel good.
In my head.
It was great to see you.
You too.
Goodbye.
Drops!
What?
Here, they're free.
Thanks.
I better be going.
Yeah, I'll see you later.
Thanks again.
We have to get you lazy boys
out of these chairs.
You should go out and be with
the three-dimensional people.
No. Inside good.
Outside bad.
You guys are so pathetic.
Oh, Xanadu!
She's one of us now.
Hi, you guys.
Hey.
We wanted to stop by
and say good night.
Good night.
They won't even turn their heads.
All right. I'm taking off my shirt.
No. She's lying.
Stop sending food to our apartment!
Why are you dressed up?
You're not the only one with a date.
You have a date? Who with?
No one.
What's his name?
Nothing.
Come on, tell me.
All right, but I'm excited about this.
Promise you won't get
big-brothery and judgmental.
I promise.
Richard Burke.
Who's Richard Burke?
Dr. Burke?
You have a date with Dr. Burke?
Why? Why? Why should that bother me?
I love that man.
He's like a a brother to Dad.
Here we go.
No, I think it's great that he's 50.
He'll be an inspiration to men who are
almost retired all over the world.
He's the brightest, most sophisticated,
sexiest man I've ever been with.
He's sexy?
Oh, God! Absolutely!
Damn!
It's the museum again.
Can I--?
Dr. Burke kissed me once.
When?
When I was 7, I crashed my bike
out in front of his house and to stop me from crying,
he kissed me right here.
Oh, you are so lucky!
I know.
Australopithecus isn't supposed
to be in that display.
No, Homo habilis was erect.
Australopithecus was never fully erect.
Well, maybe he was nervous.
Oh, look!
I can't believe this!
Homo habilis can't use tools yet,
and he has clay pots?
Why don't they just
give him a microwave?
Clearly he'd have no place
to plug it in.
Sorry.
I'm sorry this is taking so long.
It's longer than I expected.
We will have dinner.
It's fine.
Karl!
Oh, God.
Wow! Is that Michelle?
Yep.
I've not seen her since graduation.
Oh, my God, that night
she got so dru--
Emotional.
You know, she's having another baby.
I thought she just had one.
No, no. Henry's almost 2.
And he's talking
and everything. Here.
He told me he liked me
better than his other grandpa.
In all fairness, his other
grandpa's a drunk, but still....
You're a grandpa.
Yeah.
Are we nuts here?
I don't know. Maybe.
I mean, I'm dating a man
whose pool I once peed in.
I didn't need to know that.
I guess 21 years is a lot.
Hell, I'm a whole ''person
who can drink'' older than you.
Yeah.
So....
So maybe we should just....
Yeah.
Maybe....
Wow.
This really sucks.
Yeah, it sure does.
We don't have to decide
anything now, do we?
No, there's no rush or anything.
Pizza delivery!
Oh, I'm gonna kill those guys!
Rach.
I'm done.
Yeah, well, you know what?
So is Sorrentino's.
I'm sorry.
Why don't we find someplace else?
It's late. Everything's closed.
We'll do it again.
No, no, we won't.
We won't?
Come on.
Okay, that's dead, right?
What are we doing?
Do you want Cran-Apple or Cran-Grape?
Grape.
Okay, now sit.
Oh, my God!
Billions of years ago,
Earth was only--
Sorry.
So what are we looking at?
See that little cluster
of stars next to the big one?
That is Ursa Major.
Really?
I have no idea. Could be.
I'm sorry I had to work tonight.
Oh, that's okay.
You were worth the wait.
And I don't just mean tonight.
You're not laughing.
This time it's not so funny.
Loosen the knot.
Oh, God!
Honey? That's okay.
What?
Oh, no. You just rolled
over the juice box.
Thank God!
Hey.
Hey, you.
I can't believe I'm waking up
next to you.
I know. It is pretty unbelieve--
What?
We're not alone.
Is that the fire alarm?
Yeah.
It's not warm yet.
We still have time.
Cool.
-Yeah, yeah. Cool!