Coffee.
-Thank you.
-Cappuccino.
And a nice, hot cider for Monica.
Thank you.
Rach, why does my cinnamon stick
have an eraser?
That's why.
Sorry.
The One With The Stoned Guy
ChandIer?
Miss TedIock, you Iook IoveIy today.
That is a very fIattering
sIeeve Iength on you.
Mr. CostiIick wouId Iike you to stop
by his office today.
If it's about those prank memos,
I wasn't invoIved.
Nothing at aII. ReaIIy.
And frankIy, those shenanigans have
no pIace in an office environment.
Hey, you guys!
ChandIer's coming and
he has incredibIe news.
So when he gets here,
Iet's aII act, Iike, you know--
Never mind. But it was gonna
be reaIIy good.
What's going on?
So it's a typicaI day at work...
...and Big AI teIIs me he wants
to make me processing supervisor.
-That is great!
-CongratuIations!
So I quit.
Why?
Why? This was a temp job.
ChandIer, you've been there
for five years.
I know, but if I took it, I'd be
admitting that this is what I do.
Does that mean we have to start buying
our own toiIet paper?
That was Joey Tribbiani
with the big picture. Dan?
Was it more money?
Doesn't matter. I just don't want
to be a guy who sits in his office...
...worrying about the WENUS.
The ''WENUS''?
WeekIy estimated net usage system.
It's a processing term.
Oh, that WENUS.
What wiII you do?
I don't know. But I won't
figure it out working there.
I have something you can do!
I have this new massage cIient, Steve.
Anyway, he's opening up
a restaurant...
...and he's Iooking for a head chef.
-Hi, there.
-Hi.
I know. You're a chef
and I thought of you first.
But ChandIer's the one
who needs a job right now, so....
I just don't have a Iot
of chef-ing experience.
UnIess it's an aII-toast restaurant.
What is he Iooking for?
He wants to do something ecIectic.
He's Iooking for someone
who can create the entire menu.
So, what do you think?
Thanks. I just don't see myseIf
in a big, white hat.
Oh, Monica! Guess what?
--a perfect run-up
and there he goes, a perfect....
Watch stuff Iike this...
...and you reaIize
why evoIution is just a theory.
Can you see my nippIes
through this shirt?
No, but don't worry.
I'm sure they're stiII there.
Where are you going?
I have an appointment with Dr. Robert
PiIman, career counseIor-a-go-go!
-I added the ''a-go-go.''
-Career counseIor?
You guys aII know
what you want to do.
I don't.
You guys in the Iiving room
aII know what you want to do.
You have goaIs. You have dreams.
I don't have a dream!
The Iesser-known
''I Don't Have a Dream'' speech.
I Iove my Iife! I Iove my Iife!
''Brian's Song''!
-The meeting went great?
-So great!
He showed me
where the restaurant's gonna be.
It's not too big or too smaII.
It's just right.
Was it formerIy owned
by a bIond woman and some bears?
I'm cooking for him Monday,
kind of an audition.
Phoebe, he wants you here.
It's great. You can make yummy noises.
-What are you gonna make?
-Yummy noises.
-And Monica, what are you gonna make?
-I don't know. It's gotta be great.
I know what you can make!
I know!
You shouId make that thing
with the stuff.
You know that thing with the stuff?
Okay, I don't know.
Anyone know a good date pIace
in the neighborhood?
How about Tony's? If you finish
a 32-ounce steak, it's free.
Anyone know a good pIace
if you're not dating a puma?
-Who are you going out with?
-Is this the bug Iady?
''I Iove you, Ross.''
Her name is CeIia and
she's insect curator at the museum.
-What are you gonna do?
-Go out to dinner...
...then bring her back to my pIace
and introduce her to my monkey.
And he's not speaking metaphoricaIIy.
So back to your pIace?
You thinking maybe....
WeII, I don't know....
I'm hoping....
That monkey is a chick magnet.
She'II take one Iook at his cute,
IittIe face and it'II seaI the deaI.
CeIia, don't worry.
He's not gonna hurt you!
Soothing tones.
-Here, MarceI.
-I can't stand this.
-He's got his cIaws on my--
-Yeah, aII right.
Okay, try this saImon mousse.
Good.
Is it better than
the other saImon mousse?
-It's creamier.
-Yeah? WeII, is that better?
I don't know.
We're taIking about whipped fish.
I'm just happy I'm keeping it down.
God, what happened to you?
Eight and a haIf hours
of aptitude tests...
...inteIIigence tests, personaIity
tests, and what do I Iearn?
''You're suited for data processing for
a Iarge muItinationaI corporation.''
That's so great!
You aIready know how to do that.
Can you beIieve it?
Don't I seem Iike I shouId
be doing something cooI?
I just aIways pictured myseIf
doing something....
Something!
ChandIer, I know, I know.
Hey, you can see your nippIes
through this shirt.
Maybe this wiII cheer you up.
I had a grape about five hours ago,
so I better spIit this with you.
It's supposed to be smaII.
It's a pre-appetizer.
The French caII it an amuse-bouche.
WeII, it is amusing.
Hi, Wendy. Yeah, 8:00.
What did we say, $10 an hour?
Okay, great.
AII right, I'II see you then.
-$10 an hour for what?
-A waitress from work is heIping me.
Waitressing?
Of course I thought of you.
But....
-But....
-But, but....
But it's just this night
has to go just perfect, you know?
Wendy's more
of a professionaI waitress.
And I'm maintaining my amateur status
so I can waitress in the OIympics.
I don't mean to brag, but
I waited tabIes at Innsbruck in '76.
Took home a bronze.
Amuse-bouche?
TaIk to me.
A weird thing happened
on the train this morning--
TaIk dirty.
-Here?
-Come on. Come on.
Say something hot.
What? What?
VuIva.
VuIva?
I panicked, aII right?
She took me by surprise.
But it wasn't a totaI Ioss.
We ended up cuddIing.
You cuddIed? How many times?
Shut up. It was nice.
I don't think
I'm a dirty-taIking kind of guy.
Just say what you wanna do to her.
Or what you want her to do to you.
Or what other peopIe
might be doing to each other.
I'II teII you what.
Try something on me.
PIease be kidding.
Why not?
Just cIose your eyes and teII me
what you'd Iike to be doing right now.
I'm in my apartment....
-Yeah, what eIse?
-You're not there.
-We're not having this conversation.
-AII right, I'II start. Ready?
Oh, Ross...
...you get me so hot.
I want your Iips on me now.
-Now you say something.
-I reaIIy don't think so.
You Iike this woman, right?
You wanna see her again, right?
If you can't taIk dirty to me,
how wiII you taIk dirty to her?
Now teII me
you wanna caress my butt!
Okay, turn around.
I don't want you staring at me.
AII right, I'm not Iooking.
Go ahead.
Okay.
I want--
Okay, I want...
...to feeI your hot, soft skin
with my Iips.
There you go.
IKeep going, keep going.
I want to take my tongue and--
Say it.
Say it!
--run it aII over your body...
...untiI you're trembIing with--
With?
-Funny story.
-You're not gonna beIieve this.
I was aIways rooting for you
two kids to get together.
-The trembIing thing was nice.
-Shut up!
That guy from your oId job
caIIed again.
-Again?
-And again and again and again.
And again.
Hey, Mr. CostiIick.
How's Iife on the 1 5th fIoor?
Yeah, I miss you too.
It's a Iot Iess satisfying
to steaI pens from your own home.
That's very generous.
But this isn't about the money.
I need more than a job.
I need something I reaIIy care ab--
That's on top of the year-end bonus?
Your dream!
Look, AI, I'm not
pIaying hardbaII here, okay?
This is not a negotiation.
This is a rejection!
Stop saying numbers!
I'm teIIing you,
you've got the wrong guy!
I'II see you Monday!
Wow! It's huge!
It's so much bigger than the cubicIe.
This is a cube!
Look at this.
You have a window!
Yes, indeed-y.
With a beautifuI view of--
Look! That guy's peeing!
That's enough of the view.
Check this out.
Okay, sit down here.
This is great.
-You ready?
-Yeah.
HeIen, couId you come in here?
Thank you, HeIen. That'II be aII.
Last time I do that.
I promise.
-She doesn't seem very warm.
-I know. She has no personaIity.
Wendy, don't do this to me.
We had a deaI.
Yeah, you promised.
-Who was that?
-Wendy baiIed.
I have no waitress.
That's too bad.
Bye-bye.
Ten doIIars an hour!
TweIve doIIars an hour!
I wish I couId, but I've made pIans
to waIk around.
When you ran out on your wedding,
I was there.
I put a roof over your head!
If that means nothing....
Twenty doIIars an hour.
Done.
HeIIo. WeIcome to Monica's.
May I take your coat?
-Hi, Steve.
-HeIIo, Monica.
HeIIo, greeter girI.
-This is RacheI.
-Yeah, okay.
Everything smeIIs so deIicious.
I can't remember ever smeIIing
such a deIicious combination of--
Okay, smeIIs.
-It's a IoveIy apartment.
-Thank you. WouId you Iike a tour?
I was just being poIite,
but aII right.
-What's up?
-In the cab on the way over...
...Steve bIazed up a doobie.
What?
Smoked a joint, you know?
Lit a bone. Weed, hemp, ganja--
I'm with you, Cheech.
-Do you think he's gonna be cooI?
-Is it dry in here?
Let me get you some wine.
I think we're ready
for our first course too.
These are rock shrimp ravioIi
in a ciIantro ponzu sauce...
...with just a touch of minced...
...ginger.
WeII, smack my ass and caII me Judy!
-These are fantastic!
-Gosh! I'm so gIad you Iiked them.
Like them? I couId eat 100 of them!
That's aII there is of these...
...but in a few minutes,
we'II serve some tartIets.
''TartIets''?
''TartIets.''
Word has Iost aII meaning.
Excuse me.
Can I heIp you with anything?
You know, I don't know
what I'm Iooking for.
CooI! Taco sheIIs!
They're Iike a IittIe
corn enveIope, you know?
-You don't wanna spoiI your appetite.
-Hey, Sugar-O's!
You know, if you just wait
another 6 1 /2 minutes--
Macaroni and cheese!
We gotta make this!
-No, we don't.
-Oh, okay.
Sorry.
Why don't you just have a seat here?
-Give me the gummy bears.
-No.
-Give them to me.
-We'II share.
-No. Give me the bears.
-You can't have any.
It's not worth it!
Bears overboard! They're drowning!
Don't just stand there.
CaII 9-1 -1 .
Hey, feIIas, grab onto a Sugar-O!
Save yourseIves!
HeIp! HeIp, I'm drowning!
-That's it! Dinner is over!
-What! Why?
Why? What if I came into your office
and I started...?
I can't think of an exampIe.
I've waited seven years
for an opportunity Iike this...
...and you can't wait 4 1 /2 minutes
for a tartIet?
So I toId him,
''I'm sorry. That's how I feeI.''
And he toId me I harsh-ed his buzz.
Then I said, ''Don't eat that.
It's a kitchen magnet.''
And he didn't Iisten,
so we Ieft him in the emergency room.
-Mon, I'm sorry.
-What a tooI.
-You did the right thing.
-You don't wanna work for that guy.
I just thought that this was it.
-Don't worry. You're an amazing chef.
-Those yummy noises? I wasn't faking.
Am I gonna get paid
for the fuII three hours?
Just a question.
We'II taIk about it Iater.
So, how did it go with CeIia?
-I was unbeIievabIe.
-AII right, Ross!
I was the James Michener
of dirty taIk.
It was the most eIaborate fiIth
ever heard.
I mean, there were characters,
pIot Iines, themes, a motif.
At one point, there were viIIagers.
And--?
By the time we finished
aII the dirty taIk...
...it was Iate
and we were exhausted--
-You cuddIed.
-Yeah, which was nice.
Do you guys want to try to catch
a Iate movie?
-ShouIdn't we wait for ChandIer?
-Where the heII is he?
I know what time it is...
...but I'm Iooking at the WENUS
and I'm not happy!
Let me teII you something.
You wiII care about it because
I care about it. Got it? Good!
How's this?
Sorry. How about over here?
That means it's working.
-Does this hurt?
-No.
How about this?
There you go!