I can't beIieve
you'd actuaIIy say that.
I'd much rather be Mr. Peanut
than Mr. SaIty.
No way.
Mr. SaIty is a saiIor.
He's gotta be
the toughest snack there is.
I don't know. You don't
wanna mess with Cornnuts.
They're crazy.
Oh, my God. You gotta come see this.
There's some creep out there
with a teIescope.
I can't beIieve it.
He's Iooking right at us.
Oh, that is so sick.
I feeI vioIated.
And not in a good way.
How can peopIe do that?
You guys, Iook.
UgIy Naked Guy got gravity boots.
The One With the EviI Orthodontist
Years from now,
schooI chiIdren wiII study it...
...as one of the greatest
first dates ever.
-Yeah.
-I'II say, yeah.
It was unbeIievabIe.
We couId be ourseIves.
We didn't have to pIay games.
-Have you caIIed her?
-She'd know I Iike her. That's crazy.
Guys. It's gross.
It's the next day.
How needy do I wanna seem?
-I'm right. Right?
-Yeah, Iet her dangIe.
I can't beIieve my parents are
pushing me to find one of you peopIe.
Come on. Just do it.
CaII her.
Stop being so testosterone-y.
Which, by the way,
is the reaI San Francisco treat.
-Her machine.
-Answering machine?
No, interestingIy,
her Ieaf bIower picked up.
So, why didn't you say anything?
No. Last time I Ieft
a spontaneous message...
...I ended up using the phrase,
''Yes, indeed-io.''
Look, it's RacheI and Barry.
Don't everybody Iook.
What's going on?
-They're just taIking.
-Does he Iook upset?
Does he Iook Iike he was toId
to shove anything?
No. ActuaIIy, he's smiIing.
Oh, my God. Don't do that.
What? What? What?
That man across the street
just kicked that pigeon.
And basicaIIy, that's how
a biII becomes a Iaw.
See? Hey, Rach.
How'd it go?
You know, it was actuaIIy
reaIIy great.
Lunch at the Russian Tea Room.
I had that chicken, where you poke it
and butter squirts out.
Not a good day for birds.
Then we went to BendeI's.
And I toId him not to, but he got me
a bottIe of ChaneI.
That's nice. Now was that before
or after you toId him...
...to stop caIIing, stop sending
fIowers and to Ieave you aIone?
Right. WeII, we never actuaIIy
got to that.
It was just so nice to see him again.
It was comfortabIe
and it was famiIiar.
It was just nice.
That's nice twice.
Isn't this the same Barry
who you Ieft at the aItar?
Where have you been?
It was different
with him today.
He wasn't, Iike, Orthodontist Guy.
I mean, we had fun.
Is there anything wrong with that?
-Why?
-I have my reasons.
He's engaged to another woman...
...who happens to be
your ex-best friend?
AII right.
I know it's stupid.
I'II see him this afternoon
and put an end to it.
I'm not crazy, right?
I mean, it was never Iike that.
No, it wasn't.
It was so nice
having this IittIe sink here.
Then with authority, hang up.
WiII you just Ieave her the message?
Okay. AII right, fine.
''Oh, DanieIIe,
I wasn't expecting the machine.
Give me a caII
when you get a chance.
Bye-bye.''
Oh, God.
That's what you've been working on
for two hours?
Hey, I've been honing.
-What was with the dishes?
-She might think I'm in a restaurant.
I might have a Iife.
Like I haven't been sitting here...
...honing for the Iast two hours?
-The teIescope guy's doing it again.
-Oh, my God.
Go away.
Stop Iooking in here.
Great.
Now he's waving back.
We gotta do something.
I caught him Iooking into our pIace.
I feeI Iike I can't do stuff.
What kind of stuff?
WiII you grow up?
I'm not taIking about sexy stuff...
...but, Iike,
when I'm cooking naked.
You cook naked?
Yeah, toast, oatmeaI.
Nothing that spatters.
What are you Iooking at me for?
I didn't know that.
What's the matter?
I just--
Oh, Barry, this was not good.
No, it was.
It was very, very good.
-What about Mindy?
-Way better than Mindy.
I mean, what about you and Mindy?
If you want, I'II
break it off with her.
No, don't do that.
Not for me.
Dr. Farber, Bobby Rush
is here for his adjustment.
Thanks, Bernice.
Let's go away this weekend.
-This is aII way too--
-No, we can go to Aruba.
When I went there on what
wouId've been our honeymoon...
...it was reaIIy nice.
You wouId've Iiked it.
I had a bra.
Hey, Dr. Farber.
AII right, Miss Greene,
everything Iooks fine.
We're starting to see
some reaI progress.
-What?
-I'm 1 2, I'm not stupid.
Can I use your phone?
For future reference,
that thing in your hand...
...can aIso be used as a phone.
Yes, it's working.
-Why isn't she caIIing?
-Maybe she never got your message.
CaII her machine,
and if she has a Iot of beeps...
...that means she didn't get
her messages yet.
-Doesn't that make me seem--?
-Desperate? Needy? Pathetic?
You obviousIy saw my personaI ad.
How many beeps?
She answered.
This is where you'd use
that ''heIIo'' word.
I won't taIk to her.
She got my message...
...and is choosing not to caII me.
Now I'm needy and snubbed.
God, I miss just being needy.
So how'd he take it?
Pretty weII, actuaIIy.
How come you have
dentaI fIoss in your hair?
Oh, do I?
-We ended up having sex in his chair.
-You had sex in his chair?
I said that a IittIe
too IoudIy, didn't I?
You had what?
Sex in his chair.
What...? What were you thinking?
I don't know.
We stiII care about each other.
There's a history there.
It's Iike you and CaroI.
It's nothing Iike me and CaroI.
If she said to you,
''Ross, I want you on this couch...
...right here, right now,''
what wouId you say?
If it heIps, I couId sIide over.
It's a totaIIy different situation.
It's appIes and oranges.
It's orthodontists and Iesbians--
I gotta go.
-Where are you going?
-I just have to go.
I have things to do with my Iife.
I have a jam-packed scheduIe.
And I am Iate for keeping up
with it, okay?
Mindy.
How are you?
Yes, I heard. CongratuIations.
That is so great.
ReaIIy, oh, God--
I'm working tomorrow, but if you
want, you can come by if you'd Iike.
Great.
So I'II see you tomorrow.
Okay. Bye.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
So how's Mindy?
She wants to see me tomorrow. She
sounded weird. I gotta caII Barry.
It's me. I just--
Mindy.
Mindy. No, I figured
that's where you'd be.
HeII is fiIIed
with peopIe Iike you.
He's back.
The peeper's back.
-Get down.
-Get down?
And boogie.
I gotta go and get
my eyes scratched out by Mindy.
She may not even know.
I haven't heard from her in seven
months, what eIse is it about?
She was my best friend.
We went to camp together,
she taught me how to kiss....
Now, you know,
I'm, Iike, the other woman.
-I feeI so--
-Naughty.
-See you Iater.
-I'II waIk with you.
When she taught you to kiss, were you
wearing any kind of IittIe uniform--?
That's fine, yeah.
I'm going to the bathroom.
WiII you watch my phone?
-Take it with you.
-We haven't had a second date...
-...she needs to hear me pee?
-Why don't you caII her?
I can't. I Ieft a message.
I have some pride.
-Do you?
-No.
DanieIIe, hi.
It's ChandIer.
I'm fine.
Listen....
I don't know if you tried
to caII me because...
...I accidentaIIy shut off my phone.
That's fine. That's great. Okay.
She's on the other Iine.
She's gonna caII me back.
She's on the other Iine,
she's gonna caII me back.
-Don't you have to pee?
-That's why I'm dancing.
-Mindy.
-Hey, you.
Hey, you.
So what's up?
We shouId reaIIy be sitting for this.
Sure we shouId.
I'm gonna ask once,
and I want a straight answer.
Not Iike when I asked if those red
pants made my ass Iook big.
I know things have been weird...
...but you're my oIdest friend,
except for Laurie...
...who's bitter because
she Iost weight...
...and it turns out,
she doesn't have a pretty face.
-Okay, I'm just gonna say it.
-Okay.
WiII you be my maid of honor?
-Of course.
-That's so great.
It is. It is. It is.
-That's aII you wanted to ask?
-That's aII.
-What?
-That's not aII.
-Oh, sure it is.
-Oh, no, it isn't.
I think Barry's seeing someone
in the city.
What wouId make you think that?
Since the engagement,
he's acted weird.
And then Iast night, he came home
smeIIing Iike ChaneI.
ReaIIy?
If it'II make you feeI any better...
...when Barry and I got engaged,
he was weird too.
Oh, God.
That's what I was afraid of.
What's what you were afraid of?
When Barry was engaged to you,
he and I...
...kind of had
a IittIe thing on the side.
-What?
-I know, I know.
When he proposed, peopIe said, ''He'II
do to you what he did to RacheI.''
And now I feeI so stupid.
You are so stupid.
We are both so stupid.
What do you mean?
SmeII famiIiar?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Oh, no, me.
I am so sorry.
No, I am sorry.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my.
Four Ietters, ''circIe or hoop.''
-Ring, damn it, ring.
-Thanks.
-You know our phone's not working?
-What?
I caIIed and there was no answer.
I turned it off.
Mother of God, I turned it off.
Just Iike you toId her you did.
Just pointing out the irony.
I went across the street
to the doorman.
I got the peeper's name.
Can I use the phone?
Can I use your phone?
The number for a Sidney Marks, pIease.
''Heating device.''
Radiator.
Five Ietters.
''Rdtor.''
Yeah, is Sidney there?
Oh, this is? Sidney's a woman.
So she's a woman, so what?
Yeah, so what?
I Iive across the street, and I know
about your teIescope.
And I don't appreciate it.
Yeah, I can see you right now.
HeIIo?
If I wanna waIk around in my
underwear, I shouIdn't have to feeI--
Thank you.
That's not reaIIy the point.
The point is, that--
MostIy free-weights,
but occasionaIIy--
Yeah, my neighbor.
Yeah, the brunette.
She said you Iooked pretty that day
in the green dress.
The green dress? ReaIIy?
She said you Iooked Iike
Ingrid Bergman.
Did she mention me?
She wants to know why you tie
the toweI around your head.
It's a Ieave-in conditioner, okay?
It's a Ieave-in conditioner.
-You got a second?
-Sure, sure.
Come on...
-...in.
-HeIIo, sweetheart.
What you guys doing here?
We are here to break up with you.
Both of you?
We think you're a horribIe person,
and bad things shouId happen to you.
I'm sorry.
God, I am so sorry.
I was weak.
I couIdn't heIp myseIf.
Whatever I did, I onIy did
because I Iove you so much.
Which one of us
are you taIking to there?
Mindy.
Of course, Mindy.
It was aIways Mindy.
When we were having sex
in that chair?
I swear, whatever I was doing,
I was thinking of you.
PIease. That second time, you couIdn't
have picked her out of a Iineup.
You did it twice?
The first time didn't reaIIy count.
You know, it was Barry.
Honey, sweetheart, Iook.
Just give me another chance.
We'II start over.
We'II go back to Aruba.
What is it with you and Aruba?
Do you have a deaI with the airIines?
What do you say?
Dr. Farber, we've got
an emergency here.
Jason Castalano's choking
on his retainer.
Oh, God.
I'II be right there, Bernice.
Look, pIease don't go anywhere.
I'II be right back.
Okay, and we'II be here,
hating you.
See how he was sweating
when he waIked out?
If I'm hogging the baII,
you jump right in there...
...and take some punches.
This feeIs great.
I'm pretty sure
I'm stiII gonna marry him.
What are you taIking about?
Mindy, the guy is the deviI.
He is Satan in a smock.
I know he's not perfect.
But the truth is at the end of
the day, I stiII reaIIy wanna be...
...Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber...
...D.D.S.
Oh, God.
I hope you can find a way
to be happy for me.
And I hope you'II stiII be
my maid of honor.
And I hope Barry doesn't kiII you
and eat you in Aruba.
You okay?
ReaIIy?
Since I ran out on Barry
at the wedding...
...I've wondered whether I made
the right choice.
And now I know.
I'm so gIad.
Big day.
I'II give you this:
Mr. Peanut is a better dresser.
He's got the monocIe,
he's got the top hat....
Did you know he's gay?
I just wanna cIarify this.
Are you outing Mr. Peanut?
DanieIIe, hi.
Everybody, this is DanieIIe.
DanieIIe, everybody.
Why are you here?
I've been caIIing,
but I had your number wrong.
When I got the right one,
there was no answer.
So I thought I'd come down here
and make sure you were okay.
I'm okay.
Maybe we couId get together Iater?
That sounds good. I'II caII you.
Or you caII me, whatever.
You got it.
-Bye, everybody.
-Bye.
-There you go.
-Second date.
I don't know.
You don't know?
She seems nice, but her coming
aII the way here...
...just to see if I was okay?
I mean, how needy is that?