Oh, Iook! There's Joey's picture!
This is so exciting!
You can spot someone who's
never seen his pIays.
Notice, no fear.
No sense of impending doom.
''The roIe of man number three
wiII not be pIayed by Vic Shapiro.''
We came on the wrong night.
I can't beIieve I forgot a magazine.
-Come on, this might be good.
-I don't know.
The excIamation point scares me.
It's not just Freud, it's Freud!
Magic is about to happen!
WeII, Eva...
...we've done
some exceIIent work here.
And I wouId have to say...
...your probIem is quite cIear.
All you want is a dinkle
What you envy's a schwang
A thing through which you can tinkle
To play with or simply let hang
The One With the Butt
I feeI vioIated.
Did anybody eIse feeI Iike
peeIing their skin off...
...to have something eIse to do?
Ross, 10:00.
Is it? It feeIs Iike 2.
-No, 10:00!
-What?
There's a beautifuI woman
at 8, 9, 10:00!
HeIIo!
She's amazing! She makes the women I
dream about Iook Iike fat, baId men.
Go over.
She's not with anyone.
And what wouId my opening Iine be?
Excuse me....
Come on, she's a person.
You can do it.
CouId she be more out of my Ieague?
Back me up.
He couIdn't get a woman
Iike that in a miIIion years.
You aIways see these beautifuI
women with ''nothing'' guys.
You couId be one of those guys.
-You couId do that.
-You think?
AbsoIuteIy!
I can't beIieve
I'm considering this.
-I'm very aware of my tongue.
-Come on.
Here goes.
Stand back, everyone.
Incoming ego shrapneI.
AII right, I can do this.
-Yes?
-Hi.
Okay, next word wouId be...
...ChandIer.
ChandIer is my name and....
Hi!
Yes, you said that.
Yes! Yes, I did.
But what I didn't say....
What I wanted to say was...
...wouId you Iike to go out with me?
Thank you. Good night.
ChandIer?
-I didn't know you couId dance!
-You were in a pIay!
What'd you think?
-I didn't know you couId dance!
-You were in a pIay!
It wasn't that bad.
I was the Iead.
It was better than the troII thing.
At Ieast you got to see my head.
-You're right.
-We saw your head.
How about that accent?
Yeah. AII of your W's were V's.
She said yes!
AwfuI pIay, man!
Her name's Aurora. She's ItaIian
and she pronounces my name ''ChandIer.''
I Iike that better.
The usher gave me this.
-What is it?
-The EsteIIe Leonard TaIent Agency.
An agency Ieft its card.
They wanna sign me!
Based on this pIay?
Based on this pIay!
Look! There's a note on the back.
''Loved your work. CaII me a sap.''
She was obviousIy very moved!
You shouId caII her fairIy quickIy.
Yeah! As soon as possibIe!
Come in!
Hi. I'm here to see EsteIIe Leonard.
Just a moment, Iet me see
if she's in.
HeIIo.
-You're EsteIIe?
-I know...
...you weren't expecting someone
so fantasticaIIy beautifuI.
Love Iump. Take a Ioad off aIready,
darIing. Sit aIready.
I can't teII you how excited
I am to be here.
Why not?
-What I meant was--
-You don't mind if I eat, do you?
Joey...
...sweetheart, Iet me ask you
a question.
Did you ever see the movie
Sleepless in Seattle?
-Wow! Do you represent those actors?
-No.
But you know the end,
where they're happy?
That's gonna be you and me.
You mean you wanna sign me?
No, I wanna go to the top of the
Empire State BuiIding and make out.
Of course I wanna sign you!
-Miss Leonard, I'm so--
-Oh, boy.
-Ride them, cowboy.
-I'm sorry!
I don't see it!
-Try to Iook through it.
-Unfocus your eyes.
Focus? There's nothing to focus on.
-It's the Statue of Liberty!
-Right!
-Where's the Statue of Liberty?
-There.
I can't not see it now.
Hey, kids!
Come here. Do you see anything here?
-It Iooks Iike a boat.
-A boat.
Right in front of
the Statue of Liberty.
It's been seven seconds, and you
haven't asked me how my date went.
How was your date, ChandIer?
It was unbeIievabIe!
I've never met anyone Iike her.
She's had an amazing Iife!
She was in the Israeli army.
None of the buIIets hit the engine,
so we made it to the border.
But just bareIy, and I....
I've been taIking about myseIf
aII night Iong. I'm sorry.
What about you? TeII me a story.
AII right, once...
...I got on the subway.
And it was at night...
...and I rode it aII the way
to BrookIyn.
Just for the heII of it.
We taIked untiI 2:00. It was perfect.
More or Iess.
SuddenIy, we reaIized we were
in Yemen.
I'm sorry, so ''we'' is...?
''We'' is me and Rick.
Who's Rick?
My husband.
-Oh, so you're divorced?
-No.
I'm sorry. So you're widowed?
HopefuIIy?
No, I'm stiII married.
So, how wouId your husband feeI
about you sitting here with me...
...sIiding your foot so far up my Ieg
you can count the change in my pocket?
Don't worry.
He'd be okay with you
because he's okay with Ethan.
Ethan? There's an Ethan?
Ethan is my boyfriend.
What?
What kind of reIationship
do you imagine us having...
...if you have a husband
and a boyfriend?
I suppose, mainIy sexuaI.
Sorry it didn't work out.
What, not work out?
I'm seeing her again on Thursday.
Didn't you Iisten to the story?
Didn't you Iisten? It's twisted!
How couId you get invoIved
with her?
I had troubIe with it at first.
But I get the good stuff.
AII the fun, aII the taIking,
aII the sex...
...and none of the responsibiIity.
-This is every guy's fantasy!
-That's not true!
-Ross, is this your fantasy?
-No, of course not.
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
You'd go out with someone
going out with someone eIse?
-I couIdn't.
-Good for you.
When I'm with a woman,
I need to know...
...I'm going out
with more peopIe than her.
Once, I went out with a guy who
just got divorced.
It was hard. His kids Iiked me
better than him.
What does this have to do
with ChandIer?
Nothing.
I didn't have anything
on that topic.
So I went another way.
You know, monogamy can be
a tricky concept.
I mean, anthropoIogicaIIy speaking--
Fine. Now you'II never know.
We're kidding. TeII us.
-We wanna know.
-Come on!
AII right. There's a theory
put forth by Richard Leakey--
Are we greeting each other
this way now? I Iike it.
Look! I cIeaned!
I did the windows.
I did the fIoors.
I used aII the vacuum attachments but
the round one. What's it for?
Nobody knows.
And we're not supposed to ask.
What do you think?
-It's very cIean.
-ReaIIy, it Iooks great!
I see you moved the green ottoman.
How did that happen?
I don't know. It Iooked better there.
And it's an extra seat
around the tabIe.
Yeah, it's interesting.
But you know what? Just for fun...
...Iet's see what it Iooked Iike
in the oId spot.
Just to compare.
Let's see.
WeII, it Iooks good there too.
Let's Ieave it there for a whiIe.
I can't beIieve you moved
the green ottoman.
Be gIad you didn't fan the magazines.
She'II scratch your eyes out.
-You guys, I am not that bad!
-Yeah, you are.
Remember, I Iived with you?
You were a IittIe....
That is so unfair!
When we were kids, yours was the onIy
Raggedy Ann doII that wasn't raggedy.
Okay, so I'm responsibIe.
I'm organized.
But hey, I can be a kook!
AII right, you madcap gaI!
Imagine this.
The phone biII arrives,
but you don't pay it right away.
-Why not?
-Because you're a kook!
You wait untiI they send a notice.
I couId do that.
Okay, then you Iet me
go grocery shopping--
-No probIem.
-I'm not done yet.
And I buy detergent, but it's not
the one with the easy-pour spout.
Why wouId someone do that?
One might wonder.
But I wouId be fine with that.
A gIass is on the tabIe with no
coaster. A coId drink. A hot day.
Beads of condensation are inching
cIoser to the wood....
Stop it!
Oh, my God!
It's true. Who am I?
Monica, you're Mom.
Oh, my God!
Okay, I'II be there.
That was my agent.
My agent has just gotten me a job
in the new AI Pacino movie!
-That's great!
-What's the part?
Can you beIieve it? Pacino!
This guy's why I became an actor!
''Out of order? You're out of order!
This whoIe courtroom's out of order!''
SeriousIy, what's the part?
''Just when I thought I was out,
they puII me back in!''
Come on. SeriousIy, Joey,
what's the part?
You're.... What?
I'm his butt doubIe, okay?
I pIay AI Pacino's butt.
AII right? He goes into the shower,
and then...
...I'm his butt.
Oh, my God!
Come on, you guys.
It's a reaI Pacino movie
and that's big!
It's terrific. You deserve this.
After years of struggIing you've
cracked your way into show business.
Fine. Make jokes, I don't care.
-This is a big break for me!
-You're right. It is.
So, wiII you invite us
to the big opening?
-I need some moisturizer.
-For what?
Today's the big day!
You got any tweezers? I think
I have a rogue hair.
God. Go in the bathroom.
Use whatever you want.
Don't ever teII me what you did
in there.
Thank you.
-Joey's mom's on the phone.
-In the bathroom.
-You don't wanna go in there!
-Come on, we're roommates.
My eyes! My eyes!
I warned you.
Who is being Ioud?
Oh, that wouId be Monica.
Can I borrow stuff?
I wanna make Aurora breakfast.
You got the whoIe night?
WeII, I onIy have 20 minutes
untiI Ethan, so....
Do I sense resentment?
No. No resentment. BeIieve me...
...it's worth it, okay?
In a reIationship, you have moments
you'II remember the rest of your Iife.
Every singIe second is Iike that
with Aurora.
I've just wasted 35 of them
taIking to you.
So, Monica, can you
heIp me with the door?
The oId Monica wouId remind you...
...to scrub that TefIon pan with
a pIastic brush.
But I'm not gonna do that.
Excuse me? Can they warm it up?
I'm concerned about goose bumps.
Everybody ready?
I wanna thank you
for this opportunity.
I mean, I know this is just a first
step, but I hope that someday--
Lose the robe.
Right. Okay. Losing the robe!
Okay, and the robe is Iost.
I wouId Iike to get this in one take.
Let's roII it.
Water's working.
And action!
And cut!
Butt guy, what are you doing?
I'm showering.
No, that was cIenching.
The way I see it,
the guy's upset here, you know?
His wife's dead,
his brother's missing.
I think his butt wouId be angry here.
I think his butt wouId Iike
to get the shot before Iunch.
Once again, roIIing.
Water working.
And action!
And cut! What was that?
I was going for quiet desperation.
But if you have to ask....
God, I Iove these fingers.
Thank you.
No, actuaIIy, I meant my fingers.
Look at them.
Look at how happy they are.
-Oh, my God, I'm Iate!
-Oh, no!
-Don't go.
-Okay.
-I have to.
-Look, she's Ieaving.
I'm sorry. He'II be waiting for me.
-I thought you taIked to Rick.
-It's not Rick.
Ethan? He gets the whoIe day!
No, it's Andrew.
I know there'II be moments...
...when I'II regret asking
the foIIowing question, but....
-And Andrew is?
-He's...
...new.
So you're not compIeteIy fuIfiIIed
by Rick, Ethan and myseIf?
No, that's not exactIy what I was--
Most women wouId kiII...
...for three guys Iike us.
-So, what do you want?
-You.
-You have me.
-No. Just you.
-What do you mean?
-Lose the other guys.
Like, aII of them?
Come on, we're great together.
Why not?
Can't we have what we have now?
Why can't we taIk and make Iove...
...without feeIing obIigated
to each other?
Up untiI tonight, I thought
that's what you wanted too.
WeII, part of me wants that...
...but it's Iike I'm two guys.
One guy's saying, ''This is great!''
But there's this other guy.
The guy who weIIs up
when the Grinch's heart grows...
...and breaks that measuring device.
He's saying, you know,
''This is too hard. Get out!''
So, which one of the guys
wiII you Iisten to?
I have to Iisten to both.
They don't Iet each other finish.
Which one?
The second guy.
I see.
CaII me if you change your mind.
Sorry, the first guy runs the Iips.
Look at it this way. You dumped her!
Right? I mean, this woman was
unbeIievabIy sexy...
...and beautifuI, inteIIigent,
unattainabIe.
TeII me why you did this again?
Movie star!
Wait! Aren't you the guy who pIays
the butt in the new Pacino movie?
Nope.
No? What happened, big guy?
Big guy?
It feIt Iike a ''big guy'' moment.
I got fired!
They said I acted too much with it.
I toId everybody about this!
-Everybody's expecting to see me.
-IKnow what?
-No one wiII be abIe to teII.
-My mom wiII.
There's something so sweet
and disturbing about that.
I've done crappy pIays
for six years...
...and I finaIIy get my shot,
and I bIow it!
Maybe this wasn't it.
I think when it's your shot,
you know it's your shot.
Did it feeI Iike your shot?
Hard to teII. I was naked.
I don't think this was it.
I don't think you just get one.
I beIieve things are gonna happen
for you. I do.
You've got to think about
the day some kid wiII go:
''I got the part!
I'm gonna be Joey Tribbiani's ass!''
You think? That's so nice.
I'm sorry, Joey.
I'm gonna go to bed, guys.
-Good night.
You're gonna Ieave
your shoes out here?
ReaIIy? Just casuaIIy
strewn about...
...in that reckIess, haphazard manner?
It doesn't matter.
I'II get them tomorrow. Or not!
Whenever.
She is a kook.
If it bothers you that much,
just go out and get the shoes.
No, don't do this!
This is stupid!
I don't have to prove anything.
I'm gonna get them.
But then everyone will know.
Unless I get them, then wake up
really early and put them back.
I need help!
-All you want is a dinkle
-Not that song!
-All you envy's a schwang
-Come on, you guys.
A thing through which you can tinkle
Or play with or simply let hang
All you want is a dinkle
What you envy's a schwang
A thing through which you can tinkle
Or play with or simply let hang