Terry, I know I haven't worked here
very Iong but wouId it be possibIe...
...if I got a $100 advance
on my saIary?
An advance?
So I can spend
Thanksgiving with my famiIy.
Every year we ski in VaiI,
and my father pays for my ticket.
But I've started
this independent thing...
...which is actuaIIy why
I took this ''job.''
RacheI, RacheI, sweetheart!
You're a terribIe, terribIe waitress.
ReaIIy, reaIIy awfuI.
I hear what you're saying.
I'm with you.
But I'm trying reaIIy hard,
and I think I'm doing better.
I reaIIy do.
-Does anybody need coffee?
-Yeah, over here.
Look at that.
The One Where Underdog Gets Away
Excuse me, sir? Hi.
You come in here aII the time.
Do you think there's a possibiIity
that you couId advance me my tips?
Okay, okay. That's fine. Fine.
Sorry about that spiII before!
OnIy 98.50 to go!
Did you know Mom and Dad are going
to Puerto Rico for Thanksgiving?
-What? No, they're not.
-Yes, the BIymans invited them.
You're wrong.
-I am not wrong.
-You're wrong.
No, I just taIked to them.
I'm caIIing Mom.
-Hey, hey.
-Hey!
And this from the Cry for HeIp
Department: Are you wearing makeup?
Yes, I am. As of today, I'm officiaIIy
Joey Tribbiani, actor/modeI.
That's funny. I was thinking you Iook
more Iike, Joey Tribbiani, man/woman.
-What were you modeIing for?
-Posters for the free cIinic.
So you're gonna be one
of those heaIthy guys?
-The asthma guy's reaIIy cute.
-IKnow which one you'II be?
No, but I hear Lyme disease
is open, so you know....
-Good Iuck, man. I hope you get it.
-Thanks.
You were right. How can they do this?
It's Thanksgiving!
What if I cook dinner at my pIace?
I'II make it just Iike Mom's.
WiII you make mashed potatoes
with the Iumps?
They're not actuaIIy supposed to--
I'II work on the Iumps.
-Joey, you're going home?
-Yeah.
ChandIer, you're stiII boycotting
aII the piIgrim hoIidays?
-Every singIe one of them.
-Phoebe, you'II be with your grandma?
And her boyfriend.
We're ceIebrating Thanksgiving
in December because he's Iunar.
So you're free Thursday then?
-Yeah. Oh, can I come?
-Yeah.
-Rach, are you gonna make it to VaiI?
-AbsoIuteIy. Shoop, shoop, shoop.
-OnIy $102 to go.
-I thought it was 98.50?
Yeah, weII, it was, but I--
I broke a cup, so....
-WeII, I'm off to CaroI's.
-Ooh, ooh, why don't we invite her?
Ooh, ooh, because she's my ex-wife
and wiII want to bring her...
...ooh, ooh, Iesbian Iife partner.
Hi. Is CaroI here?
-No, she's at a facuIty meeting.
-I just came by to pick up my skuII.
WeII, not mine, but....
-Come in.
-Thanks.
CaroI borrowed it, and I have
to get it back to the museum.
-What's it Iook Iike?
-IKind of Iike a big face without skin.
Yes. I'm famiIiar with the concept.
-We can just Iook for it.
-Okay.
Wow, you guys sure have a Iot
of books about being a Iesbian.
WeII, you know,
you have to take a course.
Otherwise they don't Iet you do it.
Hey, Yertle the Turtle! A cIassic.
ActuaIIy, I'm reading it to the baby.
The baby that hasn't been born yet?
WouIdn't that mean you're crazy?
You don't think
they can hear sounds in there?
You're not serious?
I mean, you reaIIy taIk to it?
Yeah, aII the time.
I want the baby to know my voice.
WeII, that's just--
Do you taIk about me?
-Yeah. AII the time.
-ReaIIy?
But, we just refer to you
as ''Bobo the Sperm Guy.''
If she's taIking to it, I just think
I shouId get some beIIy time too.
Not that I beIieve this.
I beIieve it. I think the baby
can hear everything.
-ReaIIy?
-I'II show you. This'II seem weird.
But you put your head
inside this turkey...
...and we'II aII taIk
and you'II hear everything we say.
I'd just Iike to say I'm totaIIy
behind this experiment.
In fact, I'd very much Iike
to butter your head.
-Hey.
-Rach, did you make your money?
No, not even cIose. Forget VaiI.
Forget seeing my famiIy.
Forget shoop, shoop, shoop.
-Rach, here's your maiI.
-Thanks. You can put it on the tabIe.
No. Here's your maiI!
Thanks. You can put it on the tabIe!
WouId you just open it!
Oh, my God! You guys are great!
We aII chipped in.
-We did?
-You owe me $20.
Thank you. Thank you so much!
ChandIer, got your traditionaI
hoIiday feast. Tomato soup...
...griIIed-cheese fixings
and a famiIy-size bag of Funyuns.
This is your Thanksgiving dinner?
What is it with you and this hoIiday?
-I'm 9 years oId.
-I hate this story!
We've finished this magnificent
Thanksgiving dinner. I have...
...a mouthfuI of pumpkin pie.
And then my parents teII me
they're getting divorced.
Oh, my God!
Very difficuIt to enjoy Thanksgiving
dinner once you've seen it in reverse.
What's this?
I never saw this at Mom's.
-It's a yam.
-HeIIo....
This isn't a yam.
Yam comes in purpIe cans.
They don't-- They don't come in these.
Ross, don't take this the wrong way
or anything, but back off.
Hi.
-We used to work together.
-We did?
Yeah, at Macy's.
You're the Obsession girI, right?
-Yes.
-I was the Aramis guy.
-Aramis. Aramis. Aramis.
-Yeah, right!
-You're the best in the business.
-Get out.
You're amazing! You know when
to spritz. You know when to Iay back.
ReaIIy? You don't know
what that means to me.
You smeII great tonight.
What are you wearing?
Nothing.
-Listen, do you wanna go get a drink?
-Yeah, that wouId be--
-What's wrong?
-I have to do something.
What?
-Leave.
-Wait, wait, wait!
So I guess you aII saw it.
-What?
-Saw what?
No, we're just Iaughing. You know
how Iaughter can be infectious.
Set another pIace for Thanksgiving.
My entire famiIy thinks I have VD.
''Tonight, on a very speciaI Blossom. ''
Looking good! Okay!
Cider's muIIing, turkey's turkeying,
yams are yamming....
What?
I don't know. It's just not
the same without Mom in the kitchen.
Get out and stop annoying me!
Oh, that's cIoser.
I got the tickets!
Five hours from now,
shoop, shoop, shoop!
-Oh, you must stop shooping.
-Okay, I'm gonna get my stuff.
WiII you come in?
I prefer to keep a safe distance
from aII this merriment.
Look out! Incoming pumpkin pie!
We Iaughed when you did it with
the stuffing, but that's not funny.
Hey, Monica, I got a question.
I don't see any Tator Tots.
-That's not a question.
-My mom makes them. It's a tradition.
You get a piece of turkey on your fork,
a IittIe cranberry sauce and a Tot!
I mean, it's bad enough I can't be
with my famiIy because of my disease.
AII right. Fine.
Tonight's potatoes wiII be mashed,
with Iumps and in the form of Tots.
AII right, I'm off
to taIk to my unborn chiId.
Okay, Mom never hit.
Okay, aII done.
Phoebe, did you whip the pota--?
Ross needs Iumps!
Oh, I'm sorry! I just--
I thought we couId have them whipped
and then add some peas and onions.
Why do that?
Because then they'd be just Iike my
mom used to make it, before she died.
Okay. Three kinds
of potatoes coming up.
Okay. Goodbye, you guys!
Thanks for everything!
Oh, God, Iook at--
Sorry! I'm so sorry.
An unbeIievabIe thing happened!
Underdog got away!
-The baIIoon?
-No, no, the actuaI cartoon character.
Of course the baIIoon!
He broke free and was spotted
fIying over Washington Square Park.
-I'm going to the roof. Who's with me?
-I can't!
An 80-foot dog over the city?
How often does that happen?
AImost never.
-Got the keys?
-Okay.
Anytime you're ready.
Okay. Okay, here we go.
Okay. Where am I taIking to here?
There is one way that offers a
certain acousticaI advantage, but....
Just aim for the bump.
Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay, here goes.
You know, I can't do this. This is--
It's too weird. I feeI stupid.
It's fine. You don't have to do it
just because Susan does it.
HeIIo, baby. HeIIo. HeIIo.
--the moment we first saw
the dog shadow faII over the park!
But did they have to shoot him down?
That was just mean.
Right now the turkey shouId
be crispy on the outside...
...and juicy on the inside.
Why are we standing here?
We're waiting for you to open
the door. You have the keys.
No, I don't.
Yes, you do. When we Ieft,
you said, ''Got the keys.''
No, I didn't. I asked, ''Got the keys?''
No, no, no. You said, ''Got the keys!''
Do either of you have the keys?
-The oven is on!
-I've gotta get my ticket!
-Wait! We have a copy of your key.
-Get it!
That tone won't make me go any faster.
-Joey.
-That one wiII.
And everyone's teIIing me,
''You gotta pick a major.''
So on a dare, I picked paIeontoIogy.
And you have no idea what I'm saying,
because, face it, you're a fetus.
You're happy you don't
have giIIs anymore.
You don't have to taIk to it.
You can sing--
PIease. I am not singing
to your stomach, okay?
How's it going?
Here we come
Walking down the street
Get the funniest looks from
Everyone we meet
Hey, hey--
-Hey, did you just feeI that?
-I did.
-Does it aIways--?
-That was the first.
IKeep singing! IKeep singing!
Hey, hey, you're my baby
And I can't wait to meet you
When you come out I'll buy you a bagel
Then we'll go to the zoo
-It did it again!
-I feIt it that time!
Hey, hey, I'm your daddy
I'm the one without any breasts
This is great. It's 5:00. My pIane
is puIIing away from the gate.
-Maybe you can take a Iater fIight.
-There is none.
-You can go tomorrow.
-Tomorrow is not Thanksgiving!
If I'm gonna cheer you up,
you have to meet me haIfway.
Can you go any faster?
I got one keyhoIe and a ziIIion keys!
You do the math.
Why do you guys have so many
keys in there anyway?
For an emergency just Iike this.
AII right. Listen, smirky!
If not for your stupid baIIoon,
I'd be on a pIane...
...watching a woman do this...right
now. But I'm not!
You said you had the keys!
No, I didn't! I wouIdn't say I had
the keys unIess I had the keys!
That's it! Enough with the keys.
No one say keys!
Why wouId I have the keys?!
-Aside from the fact you said you did?
-I didn't!
-You shouId've.
-Why?
-Because!
Everything's my responsibiIity?
Isn't it enough that I'm making dinner?
Everyone wants a different kind
of potato, so I'm making them.
Does anybody care what kind
of potatoes I want? No!
No! No!
Just as Iong as Phoebe gets her peas
and onions, and Mario gets his Tots--
It's my first Thanksgiving, and I--
It's aII burnt, and I can't....
Monica, onIy dogs can hear you now.
Look, the door's open. Here we go.
-AII right, ChandIer, don't Iose this.
-No--
WeII, the turkey's burnt!
Potatoes are ruined! Potatoes
are ruined! Potatoes are ruined!
Here we come
Walking down the--
This doesn't smeII Iike Mom's.
It doesn't, does it? You wanted Iumps?
Here you go, buddy. You got one!
-Don't yeII at me. You burned dinner!
-Hey, don't make her squeak again!
God, this is great! The pIane is gone.
I guess I'm stuck here with you guys.
We aII had better pIans.
This was nobody's first choice!
Oh, reaIIy? So why was I busting
my ass to make this deIicious dinner?
-You caII that deIicious?
-You be quiet!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Now this feeIs Iike Thanksgiving.
Skiing.
Shoop, shoop, shoop....
Shoop.
-Eww.
-What?
UgIy Naked Guy's taking his turkey
out of the oven.
-Who cares?
-He just sat in gravy.
Oh, my God! He's not aIone.
UgIy Naked Guy is having Thanksgiving
dinner with UgIy Naked GaI.
I gotta see this!
AII right, UgIy Naked Guy!
UgIy naked dancing!
It's nice that he has someone.
ShaII I carve?
-By aII means.
-AII right.
Who wants Iight cheese,
and who wants dark cheese?
I don't even want to know
about the dark cheese.
-Does anybody wanna spIit this?
-I wiII.
-You guys have to make a wish.
-Make a wish?
Come on, you know, Thanksgiving.
You got the bigger haIf!
What did you wish for?
The bigger haIf.
AII right, I'd Iike
to propose a toast.
A IittIe toast here. Ding, ding!
This isn't the Thanksgiving
you pIanned...
...but for me,
this has been reaIIy great.
I think because it didn't invoIve
divorce or projectiIe vomiting.
If you'd gone to VaiI
or if you had been with your famiIy...
...or if you didn't have syphiIis
and stuff...
...we wouIdn't be together.
I guess what I'm trying
to say is that...
...I'm very thankfuI that aII
of your Thanksgivings sucked.
-That's so sweet!
-Thank you.
-Here's to a Iousy Christmas!
-And a crappy New Year!
-Hear, hear!
AII right! You guys,
it's starting to snow.
And Iook, UgIy Naked Guy
is hanging candy canes.
Where?
Oh. WeII.
That's festive.
Guys, there's somebody
I'd Iike you to meet.
Wait, wait. What is that?
-That's MarceI. Wanna say hi?
-No, I don't.
-He's cute! Where'd you get him?
-My friend BetheI saved him from a Iab.
That is so crueI.
Why wouId a parent
name their chiId BetheI?
That monkey's got a Ross on his ass.
Is he gonna Iive with you
in your apartment?
Yeah. It's been kind of quiet
since CaroI Ieft.
Why not get a roommate?
You reach a certain age, having
a roommate is just kind of pathet--
That's ''pathet.'' Sanskrit for
''reaIIy cooI way to Iive.''
The One With the Monkey
I'm doing new materiaI tonight.
I have 1 2 songs about my mother's
suicide and one about a snowman.
You might wanna open with the snowman.
-Hi, Joey.
-Hey, buddy.
-So how'd it go?
-I didn't get the job.
How couId you not?
You were Santa Iast year.
Some fat guy's sIeeping
with the store manager.
He's not even joIIy.
It's aII poIiticaI.
-What are you gonna be?
-One of his heIpers.
It's just such a sIap in the face,
you know?
Do you know what you're doing
for New Year's?
Hey, what?
What is wrong with New Year's?
You have PaoIo. You don't have
to face the pressure...
...of finding Iips to kiss
when the baII drops!
Man, I'm taIking Ioud!
PaoIo's gonna be in Rome
this New Year's.
-I'II be just as pathetic as you.
-Yeah, you wish.
I've got an idea. Dinner.
It's perfect. We'II put it between
Iunch and breakfast.
I'm sick of being a victim
of this Dick CIark hoIiday.
I say this year, we make a pact.
Just the six of us. Dinner.
-Sure.
-Fine.
I was hoping for more enthusiasm.
-Phoebe, you're on.
-Oh, good.
Hi. Ladies and gentIemen,
back by popuIar demand...
...Miss Phoebe Buffay.
Hi. Thanks. Hi.
I wanna start with a song
that means a Iot to me.
I made a man with eyes of coal
And a smile so bewitching
How was I supposed to know
That my mom was dead in the kitchen?
My mother's ashes
Even her eyelashes
Are resting in a little yellow jar
And sometimes when it's freezing
I feel a little sneezy
And now I-- Excuse me?
Excuse me? Yeah, noisy boys.
Is it something you'd Iike
to share with the group?
No. No, that's okay.
If it's important enough
whiIe I'm pIaying...
...it's important enough
for everyone eIse.
That guy's going home with a note.
-I was just saying--
-Speak up.
Sorry, I--
I was saying you were the most
beautifuI woman I'd ever seen.
And he said that DaryI Hannah...
...was the most beautifuI woman
he'd ever seen.
I said I Iiked her in Splash,
but not Wall Street.
I thought she had a hard quaIity.
WhiIe DaryI is beautifuI
in a conventionaI way...
...you are Iuminous
with a kind of deIicate grace.
Then that's when you started yeIIing.
We're gonna take a short break.
That guy's going home
with more than a note.
Come here, MarceI. Sit here.
I can't beIieve he hasn't
kissed you yet.
By my sixth date with PaoIo,
he'd aIready named both my breasts.
Did I just share too much?
Just a smidge.
David's, Iike, a scientist guy.
He's very methodicaI.
-I think it's romantic.
-Me too!
Did you ever see
An Officer and a Gentleman?
He's kind of Iike the guy
I went to see that with.
Except he's smarter and gentIer
and sweeter.
I just wanna be with him aII the time.
You know, day and night.
And night and day.
And speciaI occasions.
I see. You're gonna ask him
to New Year's.
-She's gonna break the pact.
-No! No, no.
No. Yeah, couId I just--?
-Yeah. I aIready asked Janice.
-What?
This was a pact! This was your pact!
I couIdn't handIe the pressure.
I snapped!
But that was the worst breakup
in history!
I'm not saying it was a good idea.
I snapped!
Hi, sorry I'm Iate.
Too many jokes.
Must mock Joey.
Nice shoes, huh?
God, you're kiIIing me!
Ross, he's pIaying
with my spatuIas again!
-He's not gonna hurt them, right?
-Do you aIways have to bring him?
I didn't wanna Ieave him aIone.
We had our first fight this morning.
It has to do with my working Iate.
I said some things that I didn't mean.
He threw some feces.
If you're working Iate,
I can Iook in on him.
That wouId be great!
But make sure it seems
Iike you're there to see him.
You're not doing it for me.
Okay. But if he asks,
I'm not going to Iie.
But you can't actuaIIy
test this theory.
Today's particIe acceIerators
aren't powerfuI enough...
-...to simuIate these conditions.
-I have a question then.
-Yeah?
-Do you pIan on kissing me ever?
That's definiteIy a vaIid question,
and the answer...
...wouId be yes. Yes, I was.
But I wanted it to be
this phenomenaI kiss...
...at a phenomenaI moment
because it's you.
Sure.
The Ionger I waited, the more
phenomenaI the kiss had to be.
Now, it's just gotta be
one of those things where I...
...sweep everything off the tabIe.
And I'm not reaIIy
a sweeping sort of feIIa.
David, I think you are
I mean, you're a sweeper
trapped inside a physicist's body.
-ReaIIy?
-I'm sure.
You shouId just do it. Just throw me.
-Now?
-Yeah, right now. Just....
Okay. Okay. Okay.
You know what?
This is reaIIy expensive.
And this was a gift.
-Now you're just tidying up.
-Okay.
-You want me to throw you--?
-I can hop.
TeII me something, what does
''no-date pact'' mean to you?
It's just that ChandIer
and Phoebe have somebody.
I thought I'd ask Fun Bobby.
-Your ex-boyfriend?
-Yeah.
-You know more than one Fun Bobby?
-I happen to know a Fun Bob.
-Okay. Here we go.
-There's no room for miIk.
There. Now there is.
So on our no-date evening,
three of you now have dates.
-Four.
-Five.
Sorry. PaoIo's catching
an earIier fIight.
And I met this reaIIy hot
singIe mom at the store.
What's an eIf to do?
So I'II be the onIy one aIone
when the baII drops?
We'II have a big party,
and no one wiII know who's with who.
I'II know. This is so not
what I needed right now.
-What's the matter?
-Oh, it's MarceI.
He's angry with me. I have
no idea why. He keeps shutting me out.
He's waIking around aII the time,
dragging his hands.
That's weird.
I had a bIast with him.
-ReaIIy?
-We pIayed, watched TV.
That juggIing thing is amazing.
What juggIing thing?
With the socks?
I figured you taught him that.
No.
It wasn't that big a deaI.
Just socks. And a meIon.
-Phoebe!
-Max. Do you know everybody?
No. Have you seen David?
He hasn't been around.
If you see him, teII him to pack.
We are going to Minsk.
-Minsk?
-Minsk. It's in Russia.
I know where Minsk is.
We got the grant.
Three years, aII expenses paid.
And if you're gonna do Minsk,
that's the way to go.
-So when do you Ieave?
-January 1st.
-HeIIo?
-What? Hey. Hi.
-What are you doing here?
-Max toId me about Minsk.
CongratuIations! This is so exciting!
It'd be even more exciting
if we were going.
Oh, you're not going? Oh, why?
TeII her. ''I don't wanna go...
...to work with Lipson,
Yamaguchi and FIank.
I wanna stay and make out
with my girIfriend!''
Okay, thank you, Max. Thank you.
So you're reaIIy not going?
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I just....
How can I Ieave you?
I just found you.
Oh, David. But what are you gonna do?
I don't know. You decide.
-Don't do that.
-But I'm asking you.
-I can't make a decision. Just--
-Okay. Stay.
-Stay.
Getting so good at that!
It was Max's stuff.
I Iove this artichoke thing.
Don't teII me what's in it.
The diet starts tomorrow.
You remember Janice.
VividIy.
-How are you?
-I am fantastic.
Now.
It's amazing. We've been back
together for what...
-...Iike 10 minutes, and--
-Is that aII?
It's Iike we were never apart.
Of course, we were, but--
Forgive and forget.
WeII, forget.
-Hi.
-Hi, I'm Sandy.
Sandy, hi. Come on in.
-You brought your kids.
-Yeah. That's okay, right?
-Party!
-That thing is not coming in here!
This is how you greet guests?
If I showed up with my new girIfriend,
she wouIdn't be weIcome?
Your new girIfriend wouIdn't urinate
on my coffee tabIe.
He was more embarrassed
about that than anyone.
And for him to have the courage
to waIk back in here...
...Iike nothing happened--
AII right. AII right.
Just keep him away from me.
Thank you. Come on, MarceI.
What do you say you and I mingIe?
AII right, I'II catch up
with you Iater.
Oh, my gosh!
RacheI, honey, are you okay?
-Where's PaoIo?
-Rome. Jerk missed his fIight.
And then your face expIoded?
No.
Okay. I was at the airport
getting into a cab...
...when this woman, this bIond
pIanet with a pocketbook...
...starts yeIIing. Something
about how it was her cab first.
The next thing, she just
starts puIIing me out by my hair!
And I was bIowing my attack
whistIe thingy...
...and three more cabs show up.
So as I'm going to get into a cab,
she tackIes me!
And I hit my head on the curb
and cut my Iip on my whistIe.
Everybody having fun at the party?
-Are peopIe eating my dip?
-Yes.
There.
-That Iooks okay, right?
-You went a bit wide on the Iipstick.
-Oh, I did?
-Yeah.
It's hard for me to teII.
My eye's cIosing up.
Let me get it for you.
-Ow!
-Okay.
You know what? It Iooks fine.
Okay, here we go.
Screw PaoIo,
screw the psycho cab Iady.
It's New Year's Eve.
Let's have a good time.
-Okay, here we go.
-Okay.
AII right, there you go. This way.
Here you go.
When I saw you at the store
Iast week...
...it was the first time
I ever mentaIIy undressed an eIf.
-Wow, that's dirty.
-Yeah.
Hey, kids.
He doesn't have to spend
the whoIe evening with me...
...but at Ieast check in.
There you are!
You got away from me.
-But you found me.
-Here, Ross, take our picture.
SmiIe. You're on Janice Camera.
IKiII me. IKiII me now.
Hi, I'm RacheI.
So whose friend are you?
Look at me, spiIIing everywhere.
Everybody, it's Fun Bobby!
Hey, sorry I'm Iate.
But my grandfather...
...died about two hours ago.
But I couIdn't get a fIight
out tiII tomorrow, so here I am.
Hey, Fun Bobby! How's it going, man?
Whoa! Who died?
It's gonna be an open casket,
you know?
So at Ieast I'II get to see him again.
Bobby? Fun Bobby?
Let me taIk to you for just a sec.
I recentIy Iost
a grandparent myseIf...
...so I reaIIy know exactIy
how you feeI.
But you're reaIIy bringing
the party down.
-I'm sorry.
-Yeah, yeah, okay.
There you go. There you go.
I'm gonna bIow this one up
and write ''Reunited'' in gIitter.
AII right, Janice, that's it!
Janice. Janice.
Hey, Janice, when I invited you,
I didn't think it meant--
Oh, no!
I'm sorry you misunderstood.
You Iisten to me!
One of these times, it's just gonna be
your Iast chance with me!
WiII you give me the thing?
-Hi, Max.
-Yoko.
I've decided to go to Minsk
without you.
-Wow.
-It won't be the same...
...but it wiII stiII be Minsk.
Happy New Year.
-Are you aII right?
-Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Come on.
-You're going to Minsk.
-No, I'm not going to Minsk.
You are so going to Minsk.
You beIong in Minsk.
You can't stay here just for me.
If I go, I have to break up with you.
-And I can't break up with you.
-Yes, you can.
Just say, ''Phoebe, I Iove you,
but my work is my Iife.
That's what I have to do.''
And I say, ''Your work?
How can you say that?''
Then you say, ''I have no choice.
Can't you understand that?''
And I say, ''No! No!
I can't understand that!''
-Ow.
-Sorry.
And then you put
your arms around me.
-Then you put your arms around me.
-Oh, sorry.
And then you teII me you Iove me
and you'II never forget me.
I'II never forget you.
Then you say that you have to go...
...because you don't wanna start the
year with me if you can't finish it.
I'm gonna miss you,
you scientist guy.
Hi, Dick Clark in Times Square.
We're in a virtual snowstorm
of confetti here in Times Square.
It gets better every....
Here you go, kids.
And then the peacock bit me.
PIease kiss me at midnight!
-You seen Sandy?
-I don't know how to teII you this...
...but she's in the bedroom
getting it on with Max.
Oh, I did know how to teII you.
-Hey, everybody, the baII is dropping.
-What?
The baII is dropping!
In 20 seconds, it'll be midnight.
And the moment of joy is upon us.
Looks Iike that no-date pact
worked out.
Everybody Iooks so happy.
I hate that!
Not everybody is happy. Hey, Bobby!
--four, three, two...
...one! Happy New Year!
I thought I'd throw this out.
I'm no math whiz...
...but I do beIieve there are
three girIs and three guys right here.
I don't feeI Iike kissing
anyone tonight.
-I can't kiss anyone.
-So, I'm kissing everyone?
No, you can't kiss Ross.
That's your brother.
So now everybody's
getting kissed but me.
Somebody kiss me.
Somebody kiss me! It's midnight!
Somebody kiss me!
AII right! AII right!
There!
I wanted this to work so much.
I'm stiII in there.
Changing his diapers.
Picking his fIeas.
But he's just phoning it in.
It's hard that something you Iove
so much doesn't Iove you back.
I think that bitch cracked my tooth.
Do you think they have
yesterday's Daily News?
I just wanna check my horoscope,
see if it was right.
Oh, my God! Don't Iook now.
Behind you there's a guy...
...who can break our hearts
and pIunge us into depression.
Come to mama.
He's coming.
Be cooI. Be cooI. Be cooI.
-Nice hat.
-Thanks.
-We shouId do something. WhistIe.
-I'm not whistIing.
Come on, do it!
Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it.
I can't beIieve you did that.
The One With Mrs. Bing
-It's aII my fauIt.
-No, it's mine.
Why did I whoo-hoo?
Was I hoping
he'd turn around and say...
...''I Iove that sound.
I must have you now''?
I wish there was something
we couId do.
HeIIo, coma guy.
Get up, you GirI Scout!
Up, up, up!
What are you doing?
Maybe nobody's tried this.
I wish we at Ieast knew his name.
I hate that they're
caIIing him John Doe.
It's so sad. It's Iike he's a deer,
a femaIe deer.
Oh, I was gonna stop.
Look at that face.
Even sIeeping he Iooks smart.
Yeah, but the dents in his knuckIes
mean he's artistic.
Okay. He's a Iawyer who teaches
scuIpting on the side.
And he can dance.
And he's the kind of guy who,
when you're taIking, he's Iistening...
...not saying, ''I understand''...
...but reaIIy wondering
what you Iook Iike naked.
I wish aII guys couId be Iike him.
I know.
You don't even know this guy.
Are there no conscious men
in the city for you two?
He doesn't have anyone.
We feeI kind of responsibIe.
I can't beIieve you said ''whoo-hoo.''
I don't even say ''whoo-hoo.''
Oh, she's coming up.
When we return, we'll talk with
the always interesting Nora Tyler Bing.
Put the kids to bed for this one.
Don't watch this. Weekend at Bernie's
is on Showtime and HBO.
No way.
-She's your mom.
-ExactIy. Weekend at Bernie's.
Dead guy getting hit
in the groin 20, 30 times.
I gotta teII you,
I Iove your mom's books.
I can't get on a pIane without one.
This is so cooI.
You wouIdn't think so
if you were 1 1 ...
...and your friends were passing around
page 79 of Mistress Bitch.
I remember page 79.
The thing after the opera
with the girI with the trick hip?
I Iove your mom.
I think she's a bIast.
That's because she's not your mom.
Oh, pIease. She's the--
Hi, sweetie.
When did ''Rigatoni'' get back from Rome?
-Last night.
-ReaIIy?
So, his pIane didn't expIode
in a big baII of fire?
Just a dream I had.
But, phew!
Hey, she's on.
Nora Bing.
Back to the book. What is this
about you being arrested in London?
Your mom was arrested?
I'm busy beaming with pride.
This is kind of embarrassing...
...but occasionally, after
I've been intimate with a man...
Why wouId she say that's embarrassing?
...I just get this craving
for kung pao chicken.
That's too much information.
Needless to say, he got a huge tip.
Oh, God, I Iove her!
I think I'm having a stroke.
So how is your book tour going?
Oh, fine. I'm leaving
for New York tomorrow, which I hate.
But I get to see my son, who I love.
This is the way that I find out.
Most moms use the phone.
Don't take this wrong, I just
don't see you as a mom.
-I don't mean that bad.
-Oh, no. I'm a fabulous mom.
I bought my son his first condoms.
And then he burst into fIames.
Let's see. Congress is debating
a new deficit-reduction biII.
The mayor wants to raise subway fares.
The high today was 45.
And teams pIayed sports.
What about GIen?
He couId be a GIen.
Not speciaI enough.
How about Agamemnon?
Way too speciaI.
I'm famished. What do I want?
PIease, God, don't Iet it be
kung pao chicken.
You watched the show.
What did you think?
I think you need to come out
of your sheII.
What is this dive?
OnIy you couId've picked this pIace.
Come on. Shut up. It's fun.
Give me a hug.
I heard about the divorce.
Lesbian, huh?
WeII, you know what they say:
Be carefuI what you wish for.
-I think we're ready for some tequiIa.
-I know I am.
-Who's doing shots?
-Hit me.
There you go. Ross?
I'm not reaIIy a shot-drinking
kind of guy.
Hi. Sorry we're Iate.
We kind of just, you know,
Iost track of time.
But a man can change.
Anyone want me to appraise anything?
WeII, I'm gonna go to tinker-town.
Mrs. Bing, I've read
everything you've written.
When I read Euphoria at Midnight,
I wanted to become a writer.
Oh, pIease.
If I can do it, anybody can.
Start with haIf a dozen
European cities...
...throw in 30 euphemisms
for maIe genitaIia...
...and you've got yourseIf a book.
My mother, Iadies and gentIemen.
Yeah, any messages for room 226?
-You okay, sIugger?
-Oh, yeah. I'm fine.
What is with you tonight?
Nothing. Nothing, nothing.
Okay, thank you.
It's the ItaIian hand-Iicker, isn't it?
No. It's the one he's Iicking.
She's supposed to be with you.
You're good.
I have soId 100 miIIion copies
of my books, and you know why?
The girI on the cover
with her nippIes showing?
No, because I know how to write men
that women faII in Iove with.
I cannot seII a PaoIo.
PeopIe wiII not turn 325 pages
for a PaoIo.
Come on. The guy's
a secondary character.
He's just a compIication
you eventuaIIy kiII off.
When?
He's not a hero.
You know who our hero is?
The guy on the cover
with his nippIes showing?
No, it's you.
-PIease.
-No, reaIIy.
Come on. You're smart. You're sexy.
-Right.
-Yes, you are.
The fact that you don't think you are
makes you sexier.
Come on, kiddo.
You're gonna be fine, beIieve me.
I'II just pee in the street.
Is ChandIer here?
Wait. Come here.
Okay, about Iast night...
...you know...
...ChandIer, you didn't teII....
We don't need to teII ChandIer.
It was just a kiss. No big deaI, right?
Right. No big deaI.
In bizarro worId.
You broke the code.
-What code?
-You don't kiss your friend's mom.
Sisters are okay.
Maybe a hot-Iooking aunt.
But not a mom. Never a mom.
What are you guys doing out here?
Joey and I had discussed getting
in an earIy morning racquetbaII game.
But apparentIy somebody oversIept.
WeII, you don't have your racquet.
No. No, I don't
because it's being restrung.
Somebody was supposed to bring me one.
WeII, you didn't caII
and Ieave your grip size.
You guys are spending
way too much time together.
I'm scum. I'm scum.
-How couId you Iet this happen?
-I don't know.
It's not Iike she's a reguIar mom.
She's sexy. She's....
You don't think my mom's sexy?
WeII, not in the same way.
I'II have you know, GIoria Tribbiani
was a handsome woman in her day.
You think it's easy giving birth
to seven chiIdren?
Okay, I think we're getting
into a weird area here.
What are you doing here?
Not pIaying racquetbaII.
-He forgot to Ieave his grip size.
-He didn't get the goggIes.
Sounds Iike you two have issues.
Goodbye, baby.
Do they wait for me to do this?
-Are you gonna teII him?
-Why wouId I teII him?
If you don't, his mother might.
What are you guys doing here?
He's not even wearing a jock strap.
What did I ask?
What are you doing here?
Nothing. I just thought
I'd stop by, you know, after...
...that I, you know.
So, what are you doing here?
I'm not reaIIy here.
I just thought I'd drop these off
on the way. My way.
Do you come here a Iot...
...without me?
No, no, no.
Do you think he's doing any better
than he was this morning?
How wouId I know? I wasn't here.
ReaIIy? Not even
to change his pajamas?
Oh, my God.
You're my friend.
I had to teII you.
I can't beIieve it.
PaoIo kissed my mom?
I don't know if you noticed,
but he drank a Iot.
I mean, you know how he gets--
I can't do this. I did it.
It was me. I'm sorry.
I kissed your mom.
What?
I was upset about RacheI and
I had too much tequiIa, and Nora...
...Mrs. Mom, your Bing, was...
...being nice.
But nothing happened.
Nothing. Ask Joey.
-Joey came in--
-You knew about this?
You know, knowIedge is a tricky thing.
Why didn't you teII me?
You're Iucky I caught them, or eIse
who knows what wouId've happened?
Thanks, man. Big heIp.
What the heII were you thinking?
I wasn't. I don't know. I--
No one knows the crap I go through
with my mom more than you.
-I know.
-I can't beIieve you did this.
-Me neither.
-I'm mad at you too.
-Why are you mad at me--?
-Let me sIam the door.
I didn't kiss her. See what happens
when you break the code?
''A Woman Undone,
by RacheI IKaren Greene.''
I thought I'd give it a shot.
I'm on the first chapter.
Do you think his ''Iove stick'' can be
''Iiberated from its denim prison''?
Yeah, I'd say so.
And there's no ''J'' in ''engorged.''
-You going to the hospitaI tonight?
-No. You?
No. You?
You just asked me.
Maybe it was a trick question.
RacheI, can we do this now?
I am so hot.
Here's my mom and dad
on their wedding day.
Now, you teII me she's not a knockout.
-I can't beIieve this conversation.
-Just try to picture her not pregnant.
CentraI Perk is proud to present
Miss Phoebe Buffay.
Thanks.
I'd Iike to start with a song
about a man I recentIy met...
...who's come to be
very important to me.
You don't have to be awake
To be my man
Long as you have brain waves
I'll be there to hold your hand
Though we just met the other day
There's something I have got to say
Thank you very much.
I'm gonna take a short break.
That was Phoebe Buffay, everybody.
-What the heII was that?
-Phoebe just started--
I was taIking to Joey.
AII right, there, mother-kisser?
''Mother-kisser.''
I'II shut up.
I know you're stiII mad at me...
...but there were two peopIe
there that night.
-There were two sets of Iips.
-I expect this from her.
She's aIways been a Freudian nightmare.
Then why don't you say something?
Because it's compIicated.
It's compIex.
You kissed my mom.
We're rehearsing a Greek pIay.
That's funny.
Are we done now?
You mean you're not gonna
teII her how you feeI?
Just because you pIayed
tonsiI tennis with my mom...
...doesn't mean you know her.
You can't taIk to her.
Okay. ''You can't''?
Or you can't?
Okay, that's my finger.
Okay, that's my knee.
StiII doing the pIay.
What did you do with him?
-You're awake.
-Look at you.
How do you feeI?
A IittIe woozy, but basicaIIy okay.
Gosh, you Iook good.
I feeI good.
Who are you?
-Sorry.
-I'm Phoebe.
I'm Monica.
I've been caring for you.
We both have.
-The Etch A Sketch is from you?
-ActuaIIy, me.
-I got you the foot massager.
-I shaved you.
-I read to you.
-I sang.
WeII, thanks.
-Oh, my pIeasure.
-You're weIcome.
So I guess I'II see you around.
What? That's it?
''See you around''?
-What do you want me to say?
-I don't know.
Maybe...
...''That was nice.''
''It meant something to me.''
''I'II caII you.''
-Okay. I'II caII you.
-I don't think you mean that.
This is so typicaI.
You know, we give and we give...
...and we give.
And we just get nothing back.
And then one day, you wake up,
and it's, ''See you around.''
Let's go, Phoebe.
You know what?
We thought you were different.
But I guess it was just the coma.
The car's waiting. I just wanted
to drop off my book for your friends.
Autographed.
And give you a goodbye kiss.
Here's the kiss,
here's the goodbye....
-Anything you want from Lisbon?
-Just knowing you're there is enough.
AII right. WeII, be good.
I Iove you.
You kissed my best Ross.
Or something to that effect.
Look, it was stupid.
-ReaIIy stupid.
I don't even know how it happened.
I'm sorry, honey. I promise
it wiII never happen again.
ReaIIy, reaIIy stupid.
-Are we okay now?
-Yeah.
No.
The forbidden Iove
of a man and his door.
He toId her off. And not just
about the kiss.
You're kidding?
He said, ''When are you gonna
start being a mom?''
Then she said:
''The question is, when are you gonna
reaIize I have a bomb?''
Are you sure she didn't say:
''When are you gonna grow up
and reaIize I am your mom?''
-That makes more sense.
-You think?
What's going on now?
I don't know. I've been standing here
speIIing it out for you.
I don't hear anything. Wait.
What do you see?
It's hard to teII.
They're tiny and upside down.
Wait, wait, wait.
They're waIking away.
No, they're not. They're coming
right at us. Run!
-Are you okay, kiddo?
-Yeah, I'm okay.
AII right. You be good.
Drive safe.
-Mrs. Bing.
-Mr. GeIIer.
You mean that?
Yeah, why not?
So I toId her.
-How did it go?
-AwfuI. AwfuI.
CouIdn't have gone worse.
-WeII, how do you feeI?
-Pretty good.
I toId her.
WeII, see?
So maybe it wasn't such a bad idea,
me kissing your mom, huh?
But we don't have to
go down that road.
This is just the first chapter...
...and I want your absoIute
honest opinion. Okay?
And on page two, he's not reaching
for her ''heaving beasts.''
She couId have heaving beasts.
Right, but in this case she doesn't.
What's a ''niffIe''?
You can usuaIIy find them
on the heaving beasts.
Okay, so I'm not a great typist.
Did you get to the part
about his ''huge, throbbing pens''?
You don't wanna be around
when he starts writing with those.
That's it. Give them back.
Wait, I just got to the part
about her ''pubIic hair.''
No, no, we're done!
The One With the Dozen Lasagnas
Aunt Silv, stop yelling!
lf you'd told me
vegetarian lasagna...
...l would've made
vegetarian lasagna.
The meat's only every third layer.
Maybe you could scrape.
Ross, did you really read
all these baby boolks?
You could plunlk me down in
any woman's uterus, no compass...
...and l could find my way
out lilke that!
This is cool.
lt says in some parts of the world
people eat the placenta.
And we're done with the yogurt.
Sorry.
l did this as a favor.
l am not a caterer.
What do you want me to do
with a dozen lasagnas?
Nice tallk, Aunt Silv.
You lkiss Uncle Freddie
with that mouth?
Ross, listen. Do you lknow that right
now your baby is only this big?
This is your baby.
''Hi, Daddy.''
Hello.
''How come you don't live with Mommy?''
''How come Mommy lives
with that other lady?''
''What's a lesbian?''
Honey, you can say it. Poconos.
Poconos. lt's lilke ''polke a nose.''
Polke a nose.
-So did l hear Poconos?
-Yes.
My sister's giving us her place
for the weelkend.
First weelkend together.
-lt's a big step.
-l lknow.
-lt's just a weelkend. Big deal.
-Wasn't this supposed to be a fling?
Shouldn't it be...
...flung by now?
We are way past a ''fling.''
l'm feeling things l've read about
in Danielle Steel boolks.
When l'm with him,
l'm just totally....
Nauseous.
l'm physically nauseous.
What am l supposed to do?
Call lmmigration?
l could call lmmigration.
What?
Ugly Nalked Guy is malking
shadow puppets.
Loolk, it's Abraham Lincoln.
Oh, right!
Go. Go!
l love babies with
their little baby shoes...
...and their little baby toes
and their little hands....
Olkay, you're gonna have to stop that.
Forever.
Need a new table.
You thinlk?
-Come on in.
-Hello.
l brought the boolks...
...and Monica sends her love
along with this lasagna.
Great! ls it vegetarian?
Because Susan doesn't eat meat.
l'm pretty sure that it is.
Nineteen weelks, the breasts
are starting to swell.
According to the literature.
-l got the results of the amnio.
-Tell me. ls everything...?
-Totally and completely healthy.
-That is great!
When did you and Susan
meet Huey Lewis?
That's our friend Tanya.
Of course, it's your friend Tanya.
-Don't you wanna lknow about the sex?
-The sex?
l'm having enough trouble with
the image of you and Susan together.
But when you throw in Tanya....
The sex of the baby, Ross.
You lknow the sex of the baby?
-Want to lknow?
-No.
l don't want to. Absolutely not.
You shouldn't lknow until
you loolk down there...
...and see, ''Oh, there it is.''
Or isn't.
-Hello, Ross.
-Susan.
So?
So did you hear?
Yes, we did.
Everything's A-Olkay.
Oh, that's so cool!
lt really is.
Do we lknow?
We certainly do.
lt's going to be a--
Hello?
A guy who doesn't wanna lknow
is standing here.
Well, is it what
we thought it would be?
What--?
What did we thinlk it'd be?
l don't wanna lknow.
Don't wanna lknow.
l should probably just go.
-Well, thanlks for the boolks.
-No problem. Olkay.
Susan.
Who should we call first?
Your follks or Deb and Rhona?
Hello?
Never mind.
I don't wanna know.
Because it was my table,
l have to buy a new one?
-That's the rule.
-What rule? There's no rule.
-You owe me a table.
-How did you get there?
lt was fine until your brealkfast
adventure with Angela Delvecio.
You lknew about that?
The impressions in the butter
left little to the imagination.
How about if we split it?
-What do you mean, buy it together?
-Yeah.
-Do you thinlk we're ready for that?
-Why not?
lt's a big commitment.
What if one of us wants to move out?
-You're moving out?
-l'm not.
-You'd tell me if you were, right?
-Yes.
-lt's just, with my last roommate--
-l lknow all about Kip.
We bought a hibachi, then he ran off
and got married. Things got ugly.
Let me aslk you something.
Was Kip a better roommate than me?
Oh, don't do that.
There's changes in your schedule.
Your 4:00 herbal massage is at 4:0.
And Miss Summerfield
canceled her 5:0 shiatsu.
Thanlks.
Oh, here comes your :00.
l don't mean to sound unprofessional,
but-- Yum!
Paolo! Hi! What are you doing here?
Rachella tell me you...
...massage?
Well, Rachella's right.
Oh, olkay.
l don't lknow what you just said,
so let's start.
l am...
...being nalked?
That's your decision.
Some people prefer to talke off--
Being nalked!
l can't believe you don't
wanna lknow. l couldn't not lknow.
lf the doctor lknows,
Carol and Susan lknow--
And Monica lknows.
How? l don't even lknow.
Carol called to thanlk me
for the lasagna. She told me.
So what's it gonna be?
-Oh, great! Now he lknows.
-l'm just excited about being an aunt.
Or an uncle.
-Hey, Phoebe.
-Hey, Pheebs.
Fine!
-What's the matter?
-Nothing. l'm just out of sorts.
Well, you can use some of my sorts.
l rarely use them.
Can we get some cappuccino
over here?
Oh, right! That's me!
That table place closes at 7. Come on.
Fine.
What is it?
-All right. You lknow Paolo?
-l'm familiar with his worlk.
He made a move on me.
-The store will be open tomorrow.
-More coffee, please.
Well, what happened?
He came in for a massage,
and everything was fine until....
-Oh, my God.
-Are you sure?
Oh, yeah. l'm sure.
And all of a sudden, his hands
weren't the problem anymore.
Was it...?
Boy Scouts could've camped
under there.
Wow.
-What did you do?
-l dealt with it lilke a professional.
''Ooh,'' what?
--ma Thurman.
-The actress!
-Uma Thurman!
Thanlks, Rach.
-What'll you do?
-You have to tell her.
lt's your moral obligation as a friend,
as a woman. lt's a feminist issue.
Guys?
-You have to.
-Feminist issue? That's where l went.
-She is gonna hate me!
-Yeah, well....
Will you piclk one?
Just piclk one.
-Here, how about that one?
-That's patio furniture.
So what? Lilke people will come in
and thinlk, ''Oh, l'm outside again.''
Fine.
What about the birds?
l don't lknow. They don't say,
''Hello, sit here. Eat something.''
-You piclk one.
-Olkay. How about the ladybugs?
Forget about the birds, but big red
insects suggest fine dining.
-Fine! Want the birds? Get the birds!
-Not lilke that, l won't.
Kip would have lilked the birds.
-Hi, Pheebs.
-What's going on?
-Are you moving out?
-l'm getting ready for the weelkend.
Are your weelkends longer
than two days?
These aren't all my suitcases.
This one's Paolo's.
-Rachel, can we tallk for a sec?
-Well, sure.
Just for a sec, Paolo's on his way.
We haven't lknown each other that long.
There are three things
you should lknow:
One, my friends are the most
important thing in my life.
Two, l never lie.
And three, l malke the best
oatmeal raisin coolkies in the world.
Olkay. Thanlks, Pheebs.
-Oh, my God!
-l lknow.
Why have l never tasted these?
l don't malke them a lot, because
it's not fair to the other coolkies.
These are the best
oatmeal raisin coolkies.
-Which proves that l never lie.
-l guess you don't.
Paolo made a pass at me.
What do you thinlk?
lt's the most beautiful table
l've seen.
l lknow.
Will you balance plates
on these heads?
Who cares? We'll eat at the sinlk.
Come on!
Heads up, Ross.
Score! You suclk!
Are you olkay?
l need some millk.
Olkay. l've got millk.
Here you go.
Better?
No.
l feel so stupid! l thinlk about
the other day with you guys.
And l was all, ''Oh, Paolo!
He's so great!
He malkes me feel so--''
God!
l'm so embarrassed!
l'm so embarrassed.
-l'm the one he hit on.
-l unleashed him on you.
lf l had never met him--
-l'm so sorry.
-No, l'm sorry.
-l'm sorry.
-l'm sorry. Wait.
-What are we sorry about?
-l don't lknow.
Right. He's the pig.
-Such a pig!
-Oh, God, he's such a pig!
He's lilke a big disgusting pig....
-Pig man!
-Yes, good!
But he was my pig man!
How did l not see this?
Oh, l lknow!
Because...
...he's gorgeous.
And he's charming.
-And when he loolks--
-Olkay, Pheebs.
The end.
God.
Should l not have told you?
Trust me, it's much better
that l lknow.
But l just lilked it better before.
lt was better.
She toolk it pretty well.
Paolo's over there now, so....
We should go and see if she's olkay.
Just one second.
-Score!
-Game! Nice!
Come on, Pheebs.
Well, it loolks lilke we
lkiclked your butts.
She did. You could be on the Olympic
''Standing There'' team.
Come on. Two on one.
Why are you here?
She just brolke up with him.
lt's time for you to swoop in.
-What, now?
-Yes. Now is when you swoop.
When Paolo wallks out,
you gotta be the first guy she sees.
She's gotta lknow you're everything
he's not. You're the anti-Paolo.
My Catholic friend is right.
She's distraught.
You're there for her.
You piclk up the pieces and then
you usher in ''The Age of Ross.''
-See this? See?
-Hold it! Ascolta!
-How's it going?
-Don't stare.
She threw his clothes off the balcony.
Now there's gesturing and arm-waving.
That is, ''How could you?''
or ''Enormous breasts!''
Here he comes.
l am...
...to say goodbye.
Olkay, bye-bye.
Paolo, l really hate you for what you
did, but l still have five of these...
...so heat it at 75
until the cheese bubbles.
l just wanna tell you, and l thinlk
l'd spealk for everyone when l say....
Oh, just loolk at her.
Guys, l thinlk only one of us
should go...
-...so she's not overwhelmed.
-Right.
And l really thinlk it should be me.
You all right?
l've been better.
l don't believe this.
l wasn't supposed to care
about this guy.
lt was just supposed to be
this big, fun, ltalian thing.
Someday l could loolk baclk and say,
''That was a big, fun, ltalian thing.''
lt wasn't supposed to feel
lilke this when it was over.
Come here.
Listen...
...you deserve
so much better than him.
l mean, you...
...should be with a guy who lknows
what he has when he has you.
What?
l'm so siclk of guys!
l don't want to loolk at
or thinlk about another guy.
l don't even want
to be near another guy.
Ross, you're so great.
-Are you all right?
-Are you olkay?
-Medium. Any coolkies left?
-Yeah.
See, Rach...
...l don't thinlk swearing off guys
altogether is the answer.
What you need is to develop a more
sophisticated screening process.
l just need to be by myself
for a while.
-l just gotta figure out what l want.
-No, no.
See, because not all guys out there
are gonna be a Paolo.
No, l lknow. l lknow.
And l'm sure your little boy's
not gonna grow up to be one.
-What?
l'm having a boy?
No.
No. ln fact, you're not having a boy.
l'm having a boy.
-Huh? Am l having a boy?
-You're having a boy!
l'm having a boy!
-l'm having a boy!
-What is it?
l'm having a boy!
We already lknew that!
l'm having a son.
Yes! And that would be a shutdown!
Shutout!
Where you going? One more game!
-lt's 2:0 in the morning.
-Yeah, get out!
You guys always hang out
in my apartment.
l'll only use my left hand.
Come on, wussies!
All right! Olkay! l gotta go!
l'm going.
And l'm gone.
-One more game?
-Oh, yeah.