This is pretty much what's happened so far.
Ross was in love with Rachel forever.
When he tried to tell her, things got in the way. Like cats, Italian guys.
Finally, Chandler said, ''Forget about her. ''
When Ross was in China, Chandler let it slip that Ross loved Rachel.
She said, ''Oh, my God!''
So she went to the airport to meet him.
She didn't know Ross was with another woman.
That's everything you need to know.
Enough about us. How've you been?
Flight number 257 from Beijing now arriving.
Oh, my God.
Excuse me.
Move, move, move! Emergency, please!
There you are.
So, so....
How was China? You!
It was great. What happened?
You're bleeding.
I am?
Oh, look at that! Yes, I am.
Enough of me, Mr. Back-from-the-Orient.
Come on, I wanna hear everything! Everything!
Well, where do I start?
This is Julie. Julie, this is Rachel.
These are.... These are aren't for you.
These are for you.
Welcome to our country.
Thank you. I'm from New York!
No problem. We'll use them to stop the bleeding.
Baggage claim?
Okay.
She went to the airport. She's going for it with Ross.
Oh, my God! This is huge!
This is bigger than huge. This is....
All right, what's bigger than huge?
This?
Yes.
You got new haircuts.
Yes, we did. Thanks to Vidal Buffay.
Because, ''If you don't look good, we don't look good.''
I love that voice.
Here. And the winner is Ava Gardner.
You guys.
Airport. Airport. Ross. Not alone.
Julie. Arm around her.
Cramp! Cramp! Cramp!
I think she's trying to say something.
Quick, get the verbs.
You! You!
You said he liked me! You!
You slowpokes!
That's all right. We got the bags.
Hi. Hello.
Hi, honey.
This is my sister, Monica.
This is Chandler. Phoebe, hi.
Joey, what up?
Hello.
Everyone, this is Julie.
Julie.
I'm not here. We haven't met.
I make a better impression without 20 hours of plane on me.
And bus.
Oh, my God!
The screaming guy--
The spitting.
You gotta hear this.
We're on this 200-year-old bus.
At least 200.
And the chicken poops in her lap.
I'm so sorry.
I just gave away the ending.
I just heard this story in the cab and it is all I can think about.
This is amazing.
How did this happen?
We were in grad school together.
Haven't seen each other since. I land in China.
Guess who's in charge?
Julie!
Isn't that great?
Isn't it just kick-you-in-the-crotch, spit-on-your-neck fantastic?
It's an expression.
We just wanted to say a quick hi.
Then we'll see the baby.
Then get sleep.
It's 6:00 tomorrow, our time.
Don't tell us what will happen. I like surprises.
Bye!
Can I get some coffee?
Sure.
You talk to him yet?
No.
Then, no.
What happened to you in China?
When last we left, you were in love with....
I know I was.
But there was this voice that kept saying ''It'll never happen. Move on.'' You know whose voice it was?
God?
It was you, pal.
Maybe it was God doing me.
Aside from being almighty, he's a wiz at doing voices.
You were right. She looks at me as a friend. That's all.
Then I met Julie, and we're having a great time.
I never would've gone for it with her, if not for you.
Well, you owe me one, big guy.
Your lemonade.
Didn't order it.
Then go take that back. They'll charge you.
Go, go, go. Come on, come on.
So, what'd you find out?
He said....
He said they're having a great time. I'm sorry.
The silver lining, if you wanna see it is that he made this decision by himself without any outside help whatsoever.
How is that a silver lining?
You have to really wanna see it.
Ironically, these guys were picked last in gym.
Hey, Pheebs.
You know what I'm thinking?
Oh, okay.
How it's been so long since you've had sex you're wondering if they've changed it?
Not even close.
No. Although now that's what I'm thinking.
What were you thinking?
You gave the guys great haircuts. I thought you could do mine.
Oh. No.
Why not?
Because I'm just....
I'm incredibly anal, an unbelievable control freak.
No, you're not.
I know I'm not, but you are.
I was trying to spare your feelings.
Hold on. Ross, Julie for you.
Excuse me. Who gave her our phone number?
Okay, well.... Who had the motive?
Was it the actor?
The chef? The masseuse?
Or was it the guy who's dating her?
Guy who's dating her.
Hey. Anybody know a good tailor?
Need clothes altered?
No, I'm looking for a man to draw on me with chalk.
See Frankie. My family's been going to him forever.
He did my first suit when I was 1 5. No, wait, 1 6.
No, excuse me, 1 5.
All right, when was 1 990?
Stop the Q-Tip when there's resistance.
Okay. Okay. Sweetheart, I'll see you later.
Okay, bye.
That is so sweet.
Okay. No, you hang up.
No, you--
One, two, three.
You didn't either.
She didn't hang up.
No, you hang up.
You. You.
Sorry, I thought you were talking to me.
Rachel.
I'll just call her back.
I'm sorry. We got disconnected.
No, you hang up.
How did this happen to me?
A week ago, two weeks ago, I was fine.
Ross was just Ross. Just this guy.
Now all of a sudden, he's Ross this really great guy that I can't have.
Sweetie, I wanted you to have him too.
I know you did.
Hey, you wanna hit Chandler again?
I'm just gonna deal with it.
I gotta get out of here.
I don't care what you say. Something's bothering her.
You know, I think I was 1 6.
You know, I think I don't care.
Please, just a little bit off the back?
I'm still on ''no.''
Morning.
Could you close your eyes?
No, no, no. I'm not falling for that again.
What's going on?
I did a stupid thing last night.
What stupid thing?
Paolo, now you've seen everybody and they've all seen you.
How did this happen?
I kind of ran into him last night.
Where?
His apartment. Is this juice?
Whoa, the fact that you dumped him because he hit on Phoebe?
Oh, God, I know. I'm pathetic, I'm a loser.
You're not pathetic. You're just sad.
Upset people do stupid things.
If I had a nickel for every guy I wish I hadn't--
But this is about your horrible mistake.
Sorry we're late. We were....
Well, there was touching.
Hey, Ross.
Hey, Paolo.
What, uh...?
What are you doing here?
I do Raquel.
So he's back?
Yeah, he's back. Is that a problem?
No, not a problem.
Good. Glad it's not a problem.
You're gonna have to not touch my ass.
Well, despite the yummy bagels and palpable tension my pants need to be altered.
When you see Frankie, tell him Joey Tribbiani says hello.
He'll know what it means.
You sure he'll crack that code?
It's funny. The last time Paolo was here, my hair was so much cuter.
All right.
You have to promise that you will not be control-y and bossy and all Monica about it.
I promise.
All right, let's see.
Now, some of you are gonna get cut and some of you aren't.
But I promise none of you will feel a thing.
That's it. I quit.
What? I didn't say anything.
This isn't the face of a person who trusts a person.
This is the face of a person who doesn't trust a person.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's just a little shorter than what we had discussed.
Would you relax? I know what I am doing.
This is how he wears it.
How who wears it?
Demi Moore.
Demi Moore is not a ''he.''
Well, he was a ''he'' in Arthur and in 10.
That's Dudley Moore.
I said I wanted it like Demi Moore.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God! I'm sorry!
Which is Demi Moore?
She's the actress that was in Disclosure, Indecent Proposal, Ghost.
She's got gorgeous hair.
I know.
I wanted to look like her.
You know, my mom's dead.
Oh, my God.
Well, this is what my butt must look like to a fly.
How long do you want the cuffs?
At least as long as I have the pants.
I just got that.
Now we'll do your inseam.
How is she?
It's too soon to tell.
She's resting, which is a good sign.
How's the hair?
I'm not gonna lie to you. It doesn't look good.
There's nothing you can do?
At this point, it's a waiting game.
I put a clip on one side, which seems to stop the curling.
Can we see her?
Your hair looks too good. It would upset her.
Ross, why don't you come on in?
Well, how you doing?
I'm okay.
That bad, huh?
What?
I can sense when women are depressed and vulnerable.
It's one of my gifts.
Joey, when I saw him get off that plane with her I really thought I hit rock bottom.
But today, it's like there's rock bottom 50 feet of crap then me.
Tell Ross how you feel.
How can I just tell him? What about Julie?
What about her? It's only been two weeks.
Ross has been in love with you for 10 years.
I don't know. I don't know.
I've been with my share of women.
I've been with a lot of people's share of women.
But the point is I've never felt about anyone the way Ross felt about you.
Really?
Yo, paesan.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
Your tailor is a very bad man.
What are you talking about?
Hey, what's going on?
Joey's tailor...took advantage of me.
What?
No way.
I've been going to him for years.
He said he was doing my inseam.
Then he ran his hand up my leg and there was definite--
What?
Cupping.
That's how they do pants.
First, they go up one side, they move it over.
Then, up the other side, move it back. Then they do the rear.
Isn't that how a tailor measures pants?
Yes, yes, it is. In prison.
What's the matter with you?
What?
That's not?
Oh, my God.
I'll put on a pot of coffee.
Even Mary Tyler Moore would've been better.
Come on. It's not that bad. You never know.
Bell-bottoms came back.
I like it.
I do. I think it's a 10.
Thank you.
My hair is amused.
Come on, things could be worse.
You could ''get caught between the moon and New York City.''
''It's crazy, but it's true.''
Thank you.
Well, I gotta go. Bye.
Bye, Rach.
Wait, are you leaving?
That's what I meant by ''bye.''
Can I talk to you for a sec?
Okay.
When the doctor does that hernia test....
That's okay.
If your mechanic does it....
What's going on?
Well, okay, first of all Paolo and I are not back together.
That was a stupid thing I did.
If I could go back in time and do it again well, I wouldn't.
Second of all....
What?
Is this one of those things where you break up with a guy I tell you what I think, you get back together with him and I look like a complete idiot?
No.
Well, then, I think the guy's scum.
I hate him. I actually-- I physically hate him.
I always have.
And you are way too good to be with a guy like that.
Really?
You deserve someone who appreciates you and who gets how funny and sweet and amazing and adorable and sexy you are.
You know? Someone who wakes up every morning thinking ''Oh, my God. I'm with Rachel.''
You know? Someone who makes you feel good.
Like the way I do with Julie.
Was there a ''second of all''?
No, I think that was the whole ''all.''
I gotta go. Okay. Okay.
Okay.
No, I swear to God, Dad. That's not how they measure pants.
I was thinking shorter, like Andie MacDowell's haircut.
Yeah, I could do that.
Really?
You wanna do it now?
Great!
See you.
I just wanna make really sure this time.
Andie MacDowell is the girl from Four Weddings and a Funeral, right?
No.
That's Roddy McDowall.
Andie MacDowell is the guy from Planet of the Apes.
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
You're welcome.