But he had the game on, so we started watching.
At halftime, I was gonna give him what for.
He's got it on tap!
In his apartment. The thing is built into his bar. It's unbelievable!
Dad, did you talk about me?
Oh, right. Well, actually, we never got to you.
Look, you're a big girl. I just hope you know what you're doing.
I do.
So where did you get the hat?
I don't know.
You're wearing the tie I got you!
Yeah.
But he offered me a beer. Know what?
What?
And?
I was gonna punch him in the nose.
Hey, Dad. What are you doing here?
I just stopped by your boyfriend's.
So, what do you think? Casa de Joey.
I decorated it myself.
Get out!
Wow, Joey, this is....
Art.
Art it is.
Check this out. Is it a coffee table?
Is it a panther? There's no need to decide.
Hey, nice pillow.
So now tell me, is this genuine Muppet skin?
Hey, excellent water table thing.
Thanks. I love this. But you know what? It makes me want to pee.
Yeah, me too. I think that's the challenge.
How come Chandler didn't come?
It's because he had a thing with the thing.
Right. I got it.
So why don't you show us the rest of your casa?
The best part! Come on.
Nice toilet.
No. Behind it.
You have a phone in here?
That's right. I have a phone in here.
Promise me something.
Yeah?
Never call me from that phone.
Okay, here we go.
Sorry, they were all out of apple pie. Someone just got the last piece.
Oh, my God! You won't believe this!
I have just been discovered.
Now wait a minute. I claimed you in the name of France four years ago.
Anyway.
Don't freak out and say how great this is until I'm done.
I met this producer of this record company who said I have a fresh, offbeat sound and she wants to do a demo of ''Smelly Cat.''
I told you not to do that yet.
And she wants to do a video.
I'm not done yet, okay?
God!
If that goes well, they may even want to make an album.
I'm done now.
If you care for me, get the pie out of the man's hood.
Get the what?
There's a pie in the hood. Go!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry. My pie was in your hood.
I have to get the coffee out of that guy's pants and I'll be back in the hospital by 7.
Damn it, Ross! Get your butt out of the bathroom!
Calm down. I'm blow-drying.
Blow-drying what? You have no hair.
What's going on?
He's been in there for an hour.
It's like I live with him again.
He's here when I sleep, wake up and when I want to shower.
It's like I'm 1 6 again.
Well, you're not 1 6. You're both adults now.
Get out, you doofus!
Or, you know, he's rubber and you're glue.
All yours.
I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain.
Shut up!
Shut up.
Cut it out!
I've never wanted you more.
Hello?
Louie? Where's Howard?
He went home.
He said he might stop up.
He said to tell you he wasn't feeling so good.
Hey, what time do you get off?
I'm not feeling too good either.
So, what do you say, boys? Should I call him?
You know what they say: Ask your slippers a question you're going crazy.
Freaking art!
Hello.
Hey.
Hey!
Sorry I didn't make it over there.
That's okay.
You had a thing.
I hear the place looks great.
Forget about it. I'm having a ball!
How's the apartment doing?
It's terrific.
I mean, it's a regular space fest!
Well, great.
Yeah, I just wanted to call and say hey.
Well, okay.
Was that the oven timer?
That's right, my friend.
-It's time for....
-Baywatch!
You believe Stephanie has skin cancer?
I can't believe she's lieutenant!
That's because you love Yasmine Bleeth.
How could anyone not love Yasmine Bleeth?
They're running!
See, this is the brilliance of the show.
I say always keep them running.
All the time running!
Run!
Run, Yasmine! Run like the wind!
But you wanted to live by yourself.
I did. I thought it'd be great.
I figured I'd have time alone with my thoughts.
It turns out I don't have as many thoughts as you'd think.
Why don't you talk to Chandler and move back?
You really think he'd take me? We had a good talk last night but when I moved, I hurt him bad.
He would definitely want you back.
I'm telling you, no way he's moving back.
But we had one of the greatest talks we ever had last night.
I mean, it was--
It was like when we first lived together.
I know you don't want to hear this now but we've seen him in his new place. And he's happy.
He's decorated.
Chandler, he has moved on, okay? You have to, too.
You have to accept the fact that you're just friends now.
You're not roommates anymore.
Okay, you ready to try one?
Okay.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
Smelly, smelly Really bad smelling smelly cat
Whoa! Oh, my God!
I mean, like, who was that?
They're your backup singers. Behind you, hon.
I thought they were just watching me.
Like at an aquarium, you know?
They're so good. You're so good!
Alrighty!
Okay, now that everyone knows everyone, let's try it again.
From the top.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
Smelly, smelly, smelly, really bad Smelling smelly cat. It's not your--
Okay, sorry. I'm just not getting that everyone gets how smelly this cat actually is.
If we could talk about this. I need to feel that you care about the cat.
We can talk, but this costs $100 a minute to be in here.
Okay, so the cat stinks, but you love it. Let's go.
No, there is no way he was a velociraptor.
Look at the cranial ridge.
If Dino was a velociraptor, he would have eaten the Flintstones.
Were you taking a nap?
I was.
Can you hold on? That's the other line.
Hello?
Yeah, she's here, but can she call you back?
Okay, thanks.
Call Joanna.
She leave a number?
Did you see me write one down?
I don't have her number, butt-munch.
She'll call back. Don't be a baby.
You're the baby.
Off my back.
Get out of my face.
Wait, hold on, Tony. Hold on.
Hello?
Hi.
Yeah, No. she's right here. Hold on.
Tony, can I call you back? That's my sister's boyfriend.
Give me that.
Okay.
Sweetie, before I forget, did I leave my diaphragm at your place?
Hi, Mom.
So how's the palace?
Funny you should mention that, because I was thinking--
What's with the boxes?
Actually, I have some news.
Is Joey gonna pick up his moose hat or should I toss it?
Why don't you ask him yourself? This is my roommate, Eddie.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
I'll take that. It's what I came for.
So this is new. Where did you two meet?
At the supermarket in the ethnic food section.
I helped him pick a chorizo.
We got to talking. He needed a place and I had a spare room.
Oh, now it's a spare room?
Well, yeah. In that it's not being used and I have it to spare.
Well, I got what I came for.
I'll see you guys.
Hey, Joe.
When'd you start using moose in your hair?
Is this guy great or what?
Yeah, yeah, he is.
He has a new roommate? Who is he?
Eddie. He just met him.
It'll never last. He's just a rebound roommate.
Check it out! Check it out!
It's ''Smelly Cat,'' the video!
Now, I haven't seen it yet, so if you don't like it so what? None of you ever made a video.
Get out of here, cat! You stink!
Smoking!
Look at me!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
It's not your fault
Smelly, smelly, really bad smelling Smelly cat, it's not your fault
Smelly cat, smelly cat
Oh, my God!
I know.
I sound amazing!
They won't take you to the vet You're obviously not their favorite pet
Smelly cat, smelly cat
It's not your fault
Oh, no
I've never heard myself sing before. I mean, except in my own head.
This is so cool! Now I can hear what you hear!
Pretty different, huh?
I am sorry, but I'm incredibly talented!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
It's not your fault
Joey, what's going on, man?
Eddie.
Morning.
I just came by to pick up my mail.
Where's the mail?
Over on the table.
It's not on this table anymore?
No. Eddie likes to keep it over there.
All right, here you go, my friend. Eggs à Ia Eddie.
That's great.
What?
I thought you liked eggs with bread with the hole in the middle à Ia me!
I do, but Eddie makes them this way. They're darn good.
Wanna try some?
No, thanks.
All right. Well, you guys, I'm out of here.
See you, pals.
See you.
How are you two getting along?
I couldn't be happier.
Great. I'm happy for you.
All right, that's it!
He just comes in here, Mr. Johnny New Eggs, with his--
His moving the mail and his, ''See you, pals.''
There's no juice!
There's no juice for the people who need the juice. I need the juice!
There's another carton right over there.
This isn't about juice anymore, all right?
All right. What's it about?
Eggs!
Whose eggs do you like better, his or mine?
I like both eggs equally!
Come on!
Nobody likes two eggs equally! Which one do you like better?
What's the difference? Your eggs aren't here anymore!
You took your eggs and you left!
Did you expect me to never find new eggs?
Maybe this isn't about the eggs.
Maybe this is about the chicken that laid them.
What chicken? There's no chicken.
I can't talk to you!
I want Entertainment Tonight.
We're watching Predators of the Serengeti.
Would you guys stop?!
It's my TV!
Quit it!
Bite me!
Oh, my God!
Monica keeps changing the channel.
Great. Why don't you tell Mommy on me?
Now I'm Mommy in this little play?
Look, I refuse to get sucked into this weird little Geller dimension thing!
I'm gonna take a nice long, hot bubble bath because you kids are driving me crazy!
What do we do about this?
Tape Entertainment Tonight.
Not that! This! Us!
Oh, my God, Ross.... You're just....
Since you've been here, you drive....
Mon, you've gone ultrasonic again, all right?
I just can't stand you being here all the time!
Why? Why can't you stand me being here? We're just having fun.
Fun? You think this is fun?
We were fooling around, like when we were kids.
I hated you when we were kids!
You hated me when we were kids?
I hated you. I loved you in a you're-my-brother-so-I-have-to way, but basically I hated your guts.
Why did you hate me?
Because you were mean to me and you teased me and you always got your way.
And that wasn't fun for you?
I can't believe you hated me.
But now I love you.
And not just because I have to.
Really?
Yeah.
You're just gonna have to stop pissing me off.
I can do that.
Then I won't have to kill you.
So you wanna watch Entertainment Tonight?
Thanks.
Tonight, America's sport's magazine moves to--
You know what?
What?
If you really wanna watch that Serengeti thing, we can.
Okay.
Listen, you are not going to believe this but that is not me singing on the video.
How did you find out?
The record company sent a paper for me to sign saying it's okay for someone else to sing for me. That was a clue.
What will you do?
I can't work with people who do this.
Sure.
I mean, this poor woman.
What woman?
The voice woman.
She has a great voice, but she doesn't have a video.
Okay, Pheebs, what about you?
I have a video. Pay attention.
This voice woman, she's so talented.
But according to the producer people, she doesn't have the right look.
She's like one of those animals at the pound who nobody wants because they're not pretty enough.
Or some old dog who's kind of stinky and--
Oh, my God! She's ''Smelly Cat''!
That song has so many levels.
Hey, Eddie.
You wanna play some foosball?
No, thanks, man. I'm not really into sports.
Yeah, okay. All right.
Doesn't matter. Time for Baywatch!
You like that show?
You don't like that show?
It's just pretty people running around on the beach.
That's the brilliance of it.
The pretty people.
And the running.
I'm gonna go read in my room for a little while.
Okay, man.
I'm gonna start off with a little song called ''Smelly Cat.''
Oh, for those of you who are wondering, this is my real voice.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you? Everybody!
It's not your fault
-Monica!
-They won't take you to the vet
Chandler!
You're obviously not their favorite pet
-Joey!
-You may not be a bed of roses
Rachel!
You're no friend to those with noses
Ross, those are the only lines we have. Sorry.
Back to the chorus everybody! Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you
Smelly cat, smelly cat It's not your fault
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you
It's not your fault