Ross, she wants you.
We just Iive in the same buiIding.
-Any contact?
-She Ient me an egg.
-You're in!
-Right.
Hey, Ross.
Come on. Get back in the game.
The RacheI thing isn't happening,
your ex-wife's a Iesbian....
I don't think we need a third.
CouId we get an egg,
stiII in the sheII?
An egg?
Go up to her and say,
''I'm returning your egg.''
I think it's winning.
-It's insane.
-She'II Iove it.
-Thank you.
-Thank you. Here.
Go with the egg, my friend.
Go, go, go!
-Think it'II work?
-No way. It's suicide.
The One With The Candy Hearts
-You can't do this.
-Do what?
-Roger wants to take her out.
-No! Remember why you dumped him?
Because he was creepy.
And mean. And frightening.
StiII, it's nice to have
a date on VaIentine's Day!
You can go out with a creep any night.
I know I do.
-What are you doing tomorrow night?
-That depends on how tonight goes.
-About tonight--
-Don't you baiI on me!
I said I'd bring a friend
for her friend.
-But her friend sounds Iike a--
-Pathetic mess. I know, but....
Come on. She's needy, vuInerabIe.
I'm thinking....
Thanks.
You haven't been out with a woman
since Janice. You're doing this.
-She said yes.
-Way to go, man!
StiII got the egg, huh?
How do I Iook?
I don't care.
There's Lorraine.
No trading. You get the pretty one,
I get the mess.
Hi, Joey.
WeII, weII!
Look what you brought!
Very nice.
And what did you bring?
She's checking her coat.
I'm gonna wash the cab smeII
off of my hands.
Get me a white zinfandeI,
and a gIass of red for Janice.
Janice?
Janice!?
Oh...
...my...
...God!
Hey, it's Janice!
Okay, I'm making a break for it!
I've been waiting for, Iike, forever
to go out with Lorraine.
-Just caIm down.
-CaIm down?
You set me up with a woman I've
dumped twice in the Iast five months!
Can you stop yeIIing?
You're making me nervous and....
I can't go when I'm nervous.
I'm sorry, you're right.
Come on! Do it, do it!
Roger was creepy, but he was nothing
compared to Pete.
-Who?
-Pete the Weeper.
The guy that used to cry
every time we had sex?
''Was it good for you?''
I'd take crying any day
over Howard, the ''I win'' guy!
''I win! I win!''
We went out for two months.
I didn't win once.
How do we end up with these jerks?
We're some kind of magnets.
I know I am. That's why I can't
wear a digitaI watch.
There's more beer, right?
You know my friend who shaves her head?
No.
I have this friend
who shaves her head.
She says to break the
bad boyfriend cycIe...
...you can do a cIeansing rituaI.
Pheebs, this woman
is voIuntariIy baId.
Yeah.
We can do it tomorrow night.
It's VaIentine's Day.
It's perfect.
Okay, what kind of rituaI?
We can burn the stuff they gave us.
Or...?
Or we can chant and dance
around naked with sticks.
Burning's good.
You know...
...I can pick up quarters with my toes.
Yeah?
Good for you.
Quarters or roIIs of quarters?
By the way, I cut you out of
aII of my pictures.
So if you want, I have a bag
with just your heads.
That's okay.
You couId make IittIe puppets
out of them.
And you couId use them in your
Theater of CrueIty!
-We can't do that!
-What? What can't you do?
Can I taIk to you for a second?
Over there?
We might be Ieaving now.
TeII me it's you and me ''we.''
She wants to sIather my body
with stuff and Iick it off.
I'm not even sure what sIathering is!
But I definiteIy want
to be a part of it!
Okay, you cannot do this to me.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Can we have three
chocoIate mousses to go?
I'm out of here.
Here's my credit card.
Dinner's on me.
I hope she throws up on you.
Thanks.
-So....
-Just us.
What a crappy night!
I have enjoyed the fact...
...that your shirt's been
sticking out of your zipper.
Excuse me.
How you doing?
So do we have the best friends,
or what?
Joey's not a friend.
He's...
...a stupid man who Ieft us
his credit card.
Another drink? Dessert?
A big-screen TV?
-I'II have a drink.
-Got it. Good woman!
-A bottIe of overpriced champagne.
-Each.
That's right, each.
And a rob roy.
I've aIways wanted to know.
Happy VaIentine's Day!
Oh, I miss you aIready.
-Can you beIieve this happened?
-No, no!
And yet it did.
-Goodbye, Janice.
-IKiss me!
Oh, ChandIer. Sorry.
Oh, ChandIer. Sorry!
-Hey, Janice.
-Hi, Monica.
WeII, this was very speciaI.
Rach, come see who's out here!
What's going on? Oh, my God!
Janice! Hi!
Janice is gonna go away now!
I'II be right back.
Joey! Look who it is!
Good. Joey's home.
This is so much fun!
This is Iike a reunion in the haII!
Ross, there's someone
I want you to say hi to.
He happened to caII.
Hi, Ross. That's right, it's me!
How did you know?
So, if dogs experience jet Iag...
...because of the seven dog years
to one human year thing...
...when a dog fIies
from New York to Los AngeIes...
...he doesn't just Iose three hours,
he Ioses a week and a haIf.
That's funny!
They shouId be cooking the food soon.
Oh, good.
Who are they?
The bIond is my ex-wife.
The woman touching her is her...
...cIose, personaI friend.
-They're Iovers?
-If you want to put a IabeI on it.
-Anything eIse I shouId know?
-Nope. That's it.
Oh, and she's pregnant with my baby.
I aIways forget that part.
HeIIo!
Now we need sage branches
and the sacramentaI wine.
AII I had is oregano and a Fresca.
That's okay!
Now we need the semen
of a righteous man.
If we had that, we wouIdn't be doing
the rituaI in the first pIace.
-Can we start throwing things in?
-Yeah, okay!
Okay.
Barry's Ietters.
Adam Ritter's boxer shorts.
And I have the receipt
from my dinner with....
-A picture of Scotty Jared naked!
-Let me see!
-He's wearing a sweater.
-No.
-Whose MCI card is that?
-Mine. Shoot!
Remember this number:
Nine, seven, four....
Okay, and here we have
the Iast of PaoIo's grappa.
Wait, isn't it aImost pure--
How can I dump this woman
on VaIentine's Day?
I don't know.
You dumped her on New Year's.
In my next Iife,
I'm coming back as a toiIet brush.
HeIIo, funny vaIentine!
Hi, just Janice.
HeIIo, Joey, our IittIe matchmaker.
I couId just kiss you aII over,
and I'm gonna.
If you don't do it, I wiII.
-So are you actuaIIy from New York?
-Not originaIIy. I'm from--
-You said they'd shoot it without you.
-I thought they couId.
The maxi-pads were a piece of cake.
Mini-pads shouId be that much easier.
-It's VaIentine's Day.
-I know, but it's my job.
I'II try to get back
as soon as I can.
I'm spending most of my time
teaching science...
...which is funny because
that wasn't even my major.
Now, that is funny!
Do you think it wouId be too weird
if I invited CaroI over to join us?
Because she's aIone now.
And pregnant. And sad.
-I guess.
-Are you sure? CaroI!
-Wanna join us?
-No, I'm fine.
Come on.
These peopIe wiII scooch down.
You guys wiII scooch, won't you?
Let's try scooching! Come on!
-Come on.
-Thank you.
IKristen Riggs, this is CaroI WiIIick.
CaroI, IKristen.
-How do you do?
-CaroI teaches sixth grade.
And IKristen....
IKristen does something...
...that, funniIy enough...
...wasn't even her major!
-Thanks for coming over.
-Not at aII. It's pretty much our job.
That's why we get the cooI hats.
-What do we got there?
-A piece of siIk boxer shorts.
Some greeting cards.
A haIf-charred picture of....
That guy's hairier than the chief!
It's a reaIIy funny story
how this happened.
I was taking out the trash,
and Phoebe was burning incense--
It's aII right.
This isn't the first boyfriend bonfire
we've seen get out of controI.
-Third one tonight.
-ReaIIy?
VaIentine's is our
busiest night of the year.
Next time you're burning
your ex-boyfriend's stuff:
One, do it in a weII-ventiIated area.
Two, if you wanna burn his cIothing,
stay away from synthetic fabrics.
Three, try to Iet go of the anger,
and Iearn to Iove yourseIf.
-I brought you something.
-Is it Ioaded?
Oh, IittIe candy hearts.
''Chan and Jan Forever.''
I had them made speciaI.
Okay, Janice.
Hey, Janice.
There's no way to teII you this.
At Ieast, there's no new way.
I just don't think things
are gonna work out.
That's fine.
It is?
Because I know that this
isn't the end.
You see, actuaIIy, it is.
No, because you won't Iet that happen.
Don't you know it yet?
You Iove me, ChandIer Bing!
Oh, no, I don't.
Why do we keep ending up together?
New Year's, who invited who?
-VaIentine's, who asked who into bed?
-I did, but--
You seek me out!
Something deep in your souI
caIIs out to me Iike a foghorn!
Janice! Janice!
You push me away,
you puII me back!
You want me. You need me.
You can't Iive without me.
And you know it.
You just don't know you know it.
See?
CaII me!
It's not true.
I never caIIed your mother a woIverine.
You did so, I swear to--
How Iong has she been in the bathroom?
She isn't in the bathroom.
Her coat's gone.
WeII, maybe it's coId in there.
I screwed up my first date
in nine years.
-That couId be it.
-Oh, God.
You know, this is stiII pretty hot.
Mushroom.
SmiIe.
They won't aII be Iike this.
Some might stay through dinner.
-I'm sorry. That's not funny.
-It's just....
You know the whoIe
''get on with your Iife'' thing?
WeII, do I have to?
I'm sitting here
with this cute woman...
...and she's perfectIy nice, but that...
...that's it.
Then I'm here taIking to you,
and it's easy and it's fun.
And I don't have to....
-I know.
-You know?
Here's a wacky thought.
Let's say you and I give it
another shot.
I know what you're gonna say.
You're a Iesbian.
But what do you say we just
put that aside for now.
Let's just stick a pin in it.
Because we're great together.
You can't deny it.
I've got a ring at home
that fits you.
I've got Iots of pictures
with both of us in them.
And best of aII,
you're carrying my baby.
-I mean, how perfect is that?
-Ross--
You keep saying that, but there's
something right here. I Iove you.
I Iove you too.
-But--
-No ''but.''
You know that thing we
put over here with the pin in it?
It's time to take the pin out.
You'II find someone.
The right woman is waiting for you.
It's easy for you to say.
You found one aIready.
AII you need is a woman who Iikes men,
and you'II be set.
Not her.
So, you guys reaIIy sIide down a poIe?
-AbsoIuteIy.
-That's so cooI.
How do you get back up?
WeII, we rareIy have to return
from a fire as quickIy.
So, wouId you guys....
WouId you Iike to, sometime, maybe....
Go for a drink sometime?
Sure, sounds good.
We get off at midnight.
We'II pick you up then.
Okay. Great!
So wiII you bring the truck?
I'II even Iet you ring the beII.
-We'II see you Iater.
-Bye! See you Iater!
Oh, my God!
See? There you go.
The cIeansing worked.
You're right. They're nice guys!
They're firemen guys!
-TeII them you're married?
-No. My girIfriend doesn't even know.