-TeII him.
-Shut up.
-TeII me what?
You won't Iook at him.
I couId use another
reason why women won't Iook at me.
AII right. AII right.
Last night, I had a dream...
...that you and I were--
Doing it on this tabIe.
ExceIIent dream score.
Why wouId you dream that?
More importantIy...
...was I any good?
WeII, you were pretty damn good.
Interesting. In my dreams,
I'm surprisingIy inadequate.
Last night, you seemed to know
your way around the tabIe.
I Iove it when we share.
You okay?
I can't beIieve you two
had sex in her dream.
Sorry, it was a one-time thing.
I was very drunk, and it was
someone eIse's subconscious.
The One With The Ick Factor
HeIIo, RacheI.
Get off.
Ooh, give me. Can you see me
operating a driII press?
I don't know.
What are you wearing?
Why wouId you want to?
For short-term work. TiII I get
back my massage cIients.
Pirates again?
No. Nothing Iike that.
I'm just such a dummy.
I taught a ''Massage YourseIf at Home''
workshop. And they are.
Hey, Chan, she couId work for you.
Thanks, Joey. That's a good idea.
I couId. I couId do it. What is it?
My secretary's gonna be out.
She's having one of her boobs reduced.
It's a whoIe big boob story.
-I couId be a secretary.
-I don't know if it'd be your thing...
...because it invoIves being
normaI for a Iarge portion of the day.
I couId do that.
-What's that?
-My new beeper.
Why does a paIeontoIogist
need a beeper?
Is it for dinosaur emergencies?
HeIp. They're stiII extinct.
It's for when CaroI goes into Iabor.
AII she has to do is diaI 55-JIMBO.
A cooI number and
a possibIe name for the kid.
-See you Iater.
-Off to see young Ethan?
Thank you.
How young is young Ethan?
Young?
He's our age.
When we were....
-He's a senior in coIIege.
-CoIIege?
Rob that cradIe.
He's smart and mature and grown-up.
Mature and grown-up, he's a big boy.
This man-chiId has no probIem
with how oId you are?
No, of course not.
It's not even an issue...
...because I said I was 22.
-You what?
-What?
-Oh, I can't pass for 22?
-WeII, maybe 25, 26.
-I am 26.
-There you go.
Can you hear that?
That'II stop
when you pick up the phone.
-Oh, I'm on.
-Okay.
Mr. Bing's office.
-Sorry, he's in a meeting.
-I'm not in a meeting.
WiII he know what
this is in reference to?
And he has your number?
I'II see that he gets
the message. Bye-bye.
Ross says hi.
This is so fun.
What do we do now?
WeII, now I actuaIIy
have to get to work.
''Most IikeIy.''
Okay, I'm gonna be out there.
AII right. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
-Yes?
-What you doing?
Okay, windows are cIean.
CandIes are Iit.
BeIt's too tight.
Gotta change.
Did I turn the fish?
Nope, because I made Iasagna.
-Am I out of controI?
-Just a touch.
I don't understand.
You've been dating this guy since...
...his midterms.
Why, aII of a sudden,
are you so...?
-What?
-CouId tonight be the night?
I don't know. He's a great guy...
...and I Iove being with him.
But, you know...
...things happen when they happen.
You don't pIan these things.
-So, did you shave your Iegs?
-Yeah.
WouId you Iet it go?
It was just a dream.
It doesn't mean--
This is it. It's baby time!
AII right, reIax. Just reIax.
Be cooI.
Yeah, hi. I was just beeped.
No, Andre is not here.
Third time today.
Yes, I am sure.
I do not perform
those kind of services.
Services?
Oh, services.
Yeah, you want 55-JUMBO.
That's right.
JUMBO with a ''U,'' sir.
You don't want me.
Judging by his number,
I'd be a huge disappointment.
AIrighty, bye-bye.
How was the first day?
ExceIIent.
Everyone was so, so nice.
It pays to know the man
who wears my shoes.
Me.
-I didn't teII anyone I knew you.
-Why?
WeII, because, you know.
They don't Iike you.
-What?
-I thought you knew.
-Who doesn't Iike me?
-Everyone.
Except for....
No. Everyone.
-What are you taIking about?
-Don't feeI bad.
They used to Iike you a Iot.
But you got promoted, and now you're
Mr. Boss Man. Mr. Big.
Mr. Bing. Boss Man Bing.
-I can't beIieve it.
-Yeah. They even do you.
They ''do'' me?
You know, Iike, okay:
''CouId that report be any Iater?''
-I don't sound Iike that.
-Yeah, you do.
''The hiIIs are aIive
with the sound...
...of music.''
''My scone. My scone.''
I don't sound Iike that.
That is so not true.
That is so not--
That--
Oh, shut up.
-Did not.
-Up untiI I was 9...
...I thought ''gunpoint'' was
a pIace where crimes happened.
-How's that possibIe?
-It's aIways on the news.
''A man is being heId up at Gunpoint.''
''Tourists are terrorized
at Gunpoint.''
And I kept thinking,
''Why do peopIe continue to go there?''
I shouId go.
-UnIess--
-What?
UnIess you wanna stay over.
I mean, I'm going to. So....
Yeah, I'd reaIIy Iike that.
Before we get into any
staying-over stuff...
...there's something you shouId know.
Is this, Iike,
''I have an earIy cIass tomorrow''...
...or ''I'm secretIy married
to a goat''?
WeII, it's somewhere in between.
You see, in a strictIy technicaI
sense, of course, I'm not....
WeII, I mean, I haven't ever....
Ethan?
Are you a virgin?
If that's what you kids are
caIIing it these days, then...
...yes, I am.
I mean, you're just such a good kisser
I wouId never have known.
WeII, I've exceIIed at every IeveI
I've been to, I just....
I just haven't been to
that particuIar one yet.
I've kind of been waiting
for the right person.
-ReaIIy?
-Yeah.
You do know I was taIking
about you, right?
Wow.
You keep saying that.
You know, you read about it.
You see it in the movies.
Even when you practice it at home,
man, oh, man...
...it is nothing Iike that.
Listen, Iisten.
You toId me something
that was reaIIy difficuIt for you.
And I figure if you can
be honest, then I can too.
Don't teII me I did it wrong.
Nothing wrong about that.
Here goes.
I'm not 22.
I'm 25...
...and 13 months.
But I figure that shouIdn't
change anything.
What does it matter how oId we are?
BasicaIIy, I'm nuts about you.
I knew after the first time we kissed.
You didn't mention the Tic Tac.
I just thought
you were naturaIIy minty.
Listen...
...as Iong as we're
teIIing stuff...
...I have another one for you.
I'm a IittIe younger than I said.
-You're not a senior?
-Oh, I'm a senior...
...in high schooI.
What we did was wrong.
I just had sex with someone who
wasn't aIive during the bicentenniaI.
I just had sex.
Ethan, focus.
How couId you not teII me?
-You never said your age.
-It's different.
My Iie didn't make one of us
a feIon in 48 states.
-What were you thinking?
-I was too busy faIIing--
-Don't say it.
-In Iove with you.
-ReaIIy?
-Sorry.
WeII, faII out of it.
You shouIdn't be here.
It's a schooI night.
Oh, God.
I'm Iike those women
that you see...
...with shiny guys named Chad.
I'm Joan CoIIins.
Who?
Andre shouId be there
in about 45 minutes.
Yes, sir, the kimonos are extra.
AIrighty. Bye-bye.
It's just easier that way.
-You toId me about the Iast dream.
-No. Forget it.
Why not? Was I doing
something particuIarIy saucy?
AII right. Fine.
You were not the onIy one there.
Joey was there too.
AII right.
Was there...
...anybody eIse there?
You sure? Nobody...
...handing out mints or anything?
No, it was just the three of us.
So was it you and ChandIer...
...then you and me,
or you, me and ChandIer?
-You know what?
-What?
There were times...
...when it wasn't even me.
That is so sweet, you guys.
Mon, Ethan caIIed again.
-What?
-Ethan caIIed again.
-You're not seeing him anymore?
-No.
Sometimes, things don't work out.
This has nothing to do with him
needing a note to get out of gym?
I did not say anything. I swear.
-He stopped by.
-Next time you taIk to him...
...couId you ask him which one
the strongest Power Ranger is?
Oh, my Iife is just so amusing.
Can we drop it now?
Sorry.
''It's morphin' time.''
-Stegosaurus.
-Tyrannosaurus.
I gotta go.
Head rush.
One more, and then I have to go.
CooI.
Where you going?
A birthday party
with some work peopIe.
Work peopIe? Nobody toId me.
I know.
That's part of the whoIe...
...them-not-Iiking-you
extravaganza.
A month ago,
these peopIe were my friends.
I'm in charge,
but I'm not a different person.
Then come, hang out. Let them see
what a great guy you stiII are.
-You think I shouId?
-I reaIIy do.
But couId we not go together?
I don't wanna be the geek
who invited the boss.
-Hey, you okay?
-Yeah.
-This can't be easy for him either.
-I know.
This may take some time
for him to get over it...
...but, then at four,
Muppet Babies is on.
Go deep. Deep. Deep.
Sorry, SheIIy.
See, with the fun?
Last night was great.
The karaoke thing?
Tracy and I doing ''Ebony and Ivory.''
You were great.
But they stiII made fun of you.
-What?
-Now you're Mr. Caring Boss.
Mr. I'm-one-of-you Boss.
Mr. I-wanna-be-your-buddy
Boss Man Bing.
Then I don't get it.
You know what?
I think you just gotta face it.
You're the guy in the big office.
You're the one that hires
and fires them.
-They say you're a great boss.
-They do?
But they're not
your friends anymore.
-I just want--
-But you can't.
But I just want--
Are you gonna--?
CaroI and I have a new system.
If she punches in 9-1 -1 ...
...she's having a baby.
Otherwise, I just ignore it.
What about Andre?
He got a caII
from our cousin, Nathan.
FrankIy, it was a IittIe more
than I needed to know.
That was gonna be my opener.
Have you guys seen those
new hand dryers in the bathroom?
-I thought that was just a rumor.
-True story.
Look, I gotta teII you something.
I'm not 1 7. I said that so you'd
think I was vuInerabIe.
I'm actuaIIy 30. I have a wife
and a job. I'm your congressman.
This is ridicuIous.
We're great together.
We can taIk, make each other
Iaugh, and the sex....
I have no frame of reference,
but I thought that was great.
-It was.
-Then what's the probIem?
Ethan, it's....
It's icky.
''Icky''?
You're actuaIIy gonna throw this away
because it's ''icky''?
This isn't easy for me either.
I wish things were different.
If you were oIder
or I was younger...
...or we Iived in bibIicaI times...
-...I couId reaIIy--
-No, don't say it.
Love you.
-Are your hands stiII wet?
-Moist.
Let's dry them again.
Or, Iike, ''CouId these margaritas
be any stronger?''
Hey, ChandIer.
HeIIo, Mr. Bing.
Loved your Stevie Wonder Iast night.
Thanks. About the weekIy numbers, I'm
gonna need them on my desk by 9:00.
-Sure.
-No probIem.
You have to give them something.
That was Gerston, Santos, and
who's the other guy?
-Petrie.
-Petrie. Right, okay.
WeII, some peopIe
are gonna be working...
...this weekend.
Oh, that's nice.
Ross.
I'm here.
You are?
We were just....
What?
-Great. Now I'm having a baby.
-What?
I'm having a baby. I'm having a--
-The phone, the phone.
-I don't have the phone.
I'm hurt.
Let's go.
Come on, peopIe. Woman in Iabor.
-Look what I got going.
-Save it for the cab.
We're going to a hospitaI.
I can't Iook nice?
There are doctors there.
-Joey, get out of the fridge.
-AII right.
-What is that?
-For the ride.
-Like in a cab--
-Save it.
-Hating this.
-Monica, come on. Let's go.
Baby coming.
I can't beIieve I'm gonna be
an aunt.
-I'II have a nephew.
-That's nice. Get out.
AII right, I'm going.
I'm going.
Here we go. Come on.