Oh, here's IittIe Ben faIIing asIeep.
A IittIe bit Iater. Is he gonna sIeep?
Is he gonna sIeep? Is he gonna?
Yep, out Iike a Iight!
This sure trumps
the ''Has he pooped?'' series.
Ross, we Iove him, okay?
But right now he's just
a IittIe fat guy.
How excited can we get?
-What you got?
-400 pictures of Ben on a rug.
-Oh, my God!
-Let me see!
The One Where RacheI Finds Out
Here's IittIe Ben nodding off.
Look at Aunt Monica's IittIe boy!
-Look, he's got Ross' haircut.
-Let me see.
Oh, God!
Is he just the sweetest thing?
You must just wanna kiss him aII over.
That wouId be nice.
-Pardon?
-Nothing.
Just a IittIe extra air in my mouth.
Chan, can you heIp me out?
I'II pay you back.
Right. IncIuding the waffIes
Iast week, you now owe me...
...1 7 jiIIion doIIars.
-ReaIIy, I'II pay you back this time.
-Where's this money coming from?
I'm heIping out at the NYU
Med SchooI with research.
What kind of research?
Just, you know, science.
Science.
Yeah, I think I've heard of that.
It's a fertiIity study.
Joey, pIease teII me you're onIy
donating your time.
ActuaIIy, a IittIe more than that.
Thank you, God.
This wiII bring us so much joy.
Come on, it's not that big a deaI.
I just go down there
every other day...
...and make my contribution
to the project.
But at the end of two weeks,
I get $ 700!
You're gonna be making money
hand over fist.
That's funny. Very funny.
This is great. I actuaIIy know
somebody who Ioves what they do.
But what do you do to unwind
after a tough day at work?
Okay, we got the coIesIaw and buns.
The ground-up fIesh
of formerIy cute cows and turkeys.
I just Iove barbecuing with you.
Men are here!
We make fire.
Cook meat.
Put out fire by peeing,
no get invited back.
Cute.
-MeIanie caIIed. She'II be Iate.
-Okay.
How are things going? Is she
becoming your ''speciaI someone''?
I don't know. She's pretty great.
What does she think of
your IittIe science project?
You think I'd teII a girI I Iike
that I'm aIso seeing a cup?
Man's got a point.
The tough thing is,
she reaIIy wants to have sex.
Crazy bitch.
I got a week Ieft to go.
According to the ruIes...
...I can't conduct personaI
experiments, if you know what I mean.
Joey, we aIways know what you mean.
How Iong did you think
this barbecue wouId Iast?
-I'm going to China.
-Jeez, you say one thing, and....
-China?
-For the museum. Someone found a bone.
They don't want us to have it.
I'm going to try to persuade them.
It's a whoIe big bone thing.
Anyway, I'II be gone for a week.
If you want to reach me, you can't.
So here's my itinerary.
-Here's a picture of me.
-Oh, Iet me see.
CouId you show it to Ben every now
and then so he doesn't forget me?
''Hi, Ben. I'm your father.''
''I am The Head!''
This barbecue's gonna be very fun.
I wanted to wish RacheI
a happy birthday before I Ieft.
-She's out having drinks with CarI.
-Hey, who's CarI?
That guy she met at the coffeehouse.
-There's this guy she met at--
-The coffeehouse? Right.
So you do know who he is.
I'II go say goodbye to the guys.
Hey, you know what?
TeII them that bone story.
-I have to go to China.
-The country?
No, this big piIe of dishes
in my mom's breakfront.
Do you know who CarI is?
Let's see. AIvin, Simon, Theodore....
No.
RacheI's having
drinks with him tonight.
How can she, when she's never
shown interest in you?
-Forget about her.
-He's right.
PIease move on. Go to China.
Eat Chinese food.
Of course, there
they just caII it ''food.''
Yeah, I guess. I don't know.
AII right, just give her this
for me, okay?
We're Iooking out for you.
We want you to be happy.
I may onIy have a coupIe beers
in me, but I Iove you.
I'm stiII on my first.
I just think you're nice.
That's when we started
this fruit basket business.
We caII ourseIves
''The Three Basketeers.''
Like ''The Three Musketeers,''
onIy with fruit.
-How do you want your burgers?
-Presents first!
We're doing presents first.
Hey, hoId on there, tiger.
How are you hoIding up?
WeII, not so good.
She thinks tonight we're gonna...
...compIete the transaction,
if you know what-- And you do.
Have you ever thought about
being there for her?
What do you mean?
You know, just be there for her.
Not foIIowing you.
Think about it.
Okay. I'm guessing this is from....
-Thank you, MeIanie.
-This one right here is from me.
Okay. It's Iight. It rattIes.
It's...
...TraveI ScrabbIe!
Thank you.
This one's from Joey.
It feeIs Iike a book, I think it's
a book. And it's a book!
It's Dr. Seuss!
That book got me through
some tough times.
There's a IittIe chiId
inside this man.
The doctors say if they remove it,
he'II die.
-Who's this from?
-From Ross.
Oh, my God! He remembered!
-Remembered what?
-It was months ago.
We waIked by this antique store.
I saw this pin.
I toId him it was Iike one
my grandma had when I was IittIe.
I can't beIieve he remembered!
WeII, sure, but can you
pIay it on a pIane?
It's so pretty!
This must've cost him a fortune.
I can't beIieve it.
Remember when he
feII in Iove with CaroI...
...and bought her that
expensive crystaI duck?
What did you just say?
CrystaI duck.
No, no, no. The ''Iove'' part?
-Oh, my God!
-Oh, no, no, no.
That's good. Just keep rubbing
your head. That'II turn back time.
This is unbeIievabIe.
I mean, this is unbeIievabIe!
I know.
This is reaIIy, reaIIy huge.
No, it's not. It's smaII.
It's tiny. It's petite. It's wee.
I don't think any of our Iives
wiII ever be the same ever again.
Is there a mute button on this woman?
I think this is so great.
I mean, you and Ross!
-Did you have any idea?
-No, none!
My first night in the city,
he mentioned asking me out...
...but nothing ever happened.
What eIse did he say?
Does he wanna go out?
Given that he's in Iove with you...
...he wouIdn't mind getting
a cup of coffee.
Ross? AII this time?
I've gotta taIk to him.
-He's in China!
-The country.
Is his fIight gone?
Yes! He's watching a woman do this:
He's gone!
His fIight doesn't Ieave
for 45 minutes.
-What about time difference?
-From here to the airport?
-You'II never make it!
-I've gotta try.
What'II you say to him?
-I don't know.
-Then you shouIdn't go.
Right. If you're gonna
break his heart, that can wait.
But if it's good, teII him now.
-Maybe I'II know when I see him.
-AII right, does this heIp?
No. Look, aII I know is, I cannot
wait a week. This is just too big.
I've just gotta taIk to him.
Okay, I'II see you Iater.
RacheI, I Iove you!
DeaI with me first!
AII right.
-Ross! Excuse me, pardon me.
-Your boarding pass?
I need to taIk to my friend.
Sorry, you're not aIIowed here
without a pass.
He's right there,
in the bIue jacket! Can I--?
I'm sorry. FederaI reguIations!
Then couId you pIease
just give him a message for me?
-This is very important.
-AII right. What's the message?
I don't know.
Excuse me, sir! Excuse me, sir?
I have a message for you.
RacheI Ioved the present.
She'II see you when you get back.
What?
Toby, I don't know
what she's taIking about.
There's no RacheI.
Don't give me that deep freeze.
Oh, Joey, Joey, Joey!
I think I bIacked out there
for a minute.
It was nothing.
WeII, now we gotta
find something fun for you.
You know what?
Forget about me.
Let's give you another turn.
-Me, again?
-Sure. Why not?
Boy, somebody's gonna get
a big fruit basket tomorrow!
I gotta teII you, you are nothing Iike
I thought you'd be.
How do you mean?
I had you pegged as a guy
who's aIways, ''Me, me, me!''
But you, you're a giver.
You're the most generous man
I ever met.
I mean, you're practicaIIy a woman.
-You're just saying that.
-No.
A woman!
-So?
-I missed him.
-I'm so sorry.
-That's too bad.
Yeah, right.
No, I feeI bad for her. I do.
I can think of somebody
other than myseIf.
AII right, I'm going to bed.
-Happy birthday. Hang in there.
-Thanks.
Yes!
Pizza coupons.
Okay. You guys want heIp
cIeaning up this mess?
That'd be great.
So, Rach, you wanna save
this wrapping paper?
Are you gonna go for it with Ross
or shouId I throw it out?
I don't know. I don't know.
Thought about it
aII the way there...
...and I thought about it aII the way
back. You know, it's Ross!
You know what I mean? It's Ross.
-Sure!
-Sure.
I don't know. This is just
my initiaI gut feeIing...
...but I'm thinking
it'd be reaIIy great.
Oh, my God, me too!
We'd be Iike friends-in-Iaw!
The best part is you aIready
know aII about him.
You start on the 1 5th date.
But it wouId be Iike
starting on the 1 5th date.
Another good point.
I mean, on the 1 5th date,
you're aIready in a very...
...''reIationship-y'' pIace.
You're committed.
What happens if it doesn't work out?
-Why isn't it working out?
-Sometimes it doesn't.
Is he not cute enough?
Does he not make enough money?
-No, I'm just--
-Maybe there's someone eIse.
-Is there someone eIse?
-No, there is no one eIse.
Then why are you dumping my brother?
Hey, big-- Spender!
She's stiII asIeep.
-So how'd it go?
-You know how you think you're great?
The fact you'd even ask
shows how IittIe you know me.
Last night I couIdn't do the thing
that usuaIIy makes me great.
So I had to do aII this other stuff.
And the response I got! Man, oh, man!
It was Iike a ticker-tape parade!
I know. My room's very, very cIose
to the parade route.
It was amazing, and not just for her.
For me too!
It's Iike, aII of a sudden
I'm bIind...
...but aII my other senses
are heightened.
It's Iike I was abIe
to appreciate it...
...on another IeveI.
-I didn't know you had another IeveI.
-I know. Neither did I!
Is something going on with O.J.?
Hey, great skirt. Birthday present?
-From who?
-You.
I exchanged the bIouse you got me.
WeII, it's the thought.
Doesn't Ross' fIight get in
in a coupIe hours? At gate 27B?
Yeah. Monica, you know, I've been
thinking about it.
I've decided this Ross thing
is not a good idea.
Why?
I feeI Iike I wouIdn't
just be going out with him.
I'd be going out with aII of you.
There'd be pressure--
No pressure, no pressure!
Nothing has happened,
and you're aIready so--
I'm not ''so.'' Okay, I was a teensy
bit weird at first...
...but I'II be good. I promise.
-Who is it?
-It's me, Carl.
-Come on up.
-Behind my brother's back?
Is the kind of crazy thing
you won't be hearing from me.
-Seven hundred bucks!
-AII right, you did it!
Do we have any fruit?
Man, heII of a two weeks.
You know what?
I feeI I Iearned something.
You'II stick with this
''aII for her'' thing?
What are you, crazy?
When a bIind man gets his sight back,
does he waIk around Iike this?
If I see one more picture
of Ed BegIey Jr...
...in that stupid eIectric car,
I'm gonna shoot myseIf!
I'm not against
environmentaI issues, per se...
...it's just that guy!
I can't beIieve you'd rather
go out with him than me.
Excuse me, I'm trying
to have a date here.
Fine. Just stop thinking about me.
Can't do it, can you?
I'm thinking about you. So what?
I don't get it.
What do you see in this guy?
Happens to be a very nice guy.
I mean, come on, buddy!
Get a reaI car!
RacheI, come on. Give us a chance.
Ross, it's too hard.
Why, because it'II get weird
for everyone eIse? This is about us.
I've been in Iove with you
since the ninth grade.
You're Iike my best friend.
If we broke up, and I Iost you--
What makes you think that?
Have you been invoIved
where you haven't broken up?
No.
But it onIy has to happen once.
You and I both know we are perfect
for each other. Right?
So the onIy question is:
Are you attracted to me?
I don't know.
I mean, I've never Iooked at you
that way before.
WeII, start Iooking.
-Wow.
-ExactIy!
And I'm gonna be the guy...
...caught behind this hammerhead
in traffic!
Right! You're right.
You know what?
I'm supposed to pick up
a friend at the airport.
I am so sorry!
If you wanna finish your drinks,
pIease do.
-I'm sorry, I gotta go. I'm sorry.
-But....
-Where are you going?
-To get Ross.
-My God, this is so exciting!
-I know.
If you want the rest of my date,
I'm not gonna finish it.
-RacheI, he's not a sandwich.
-No, he's a banker with opera tickets.
HeIIo!
-Where you going?
-Airport.
You can't teII him.
There's so much I haven't done.
I haven't watched Baywatch
with Yasmine BIeeth!
ChandIer, reIax. This is a good
going to the airport.
Oh, weII then fIy, good woman,
fIy Iike the wind.
-I'm fIying!
-TeII him I'm the one who bIew it!
Yes, another successfuI case
for the Iove doctor.
Excuse me! Pardon me.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Toby, for God's sake,
wiII you Iet it go?
There's no RacheI!
Hey! I got that.
-Thanks, sweetie.
-No probIem.
I can't wait for you
to meet my friends.
You don't think they'II judge me?
-No, they wiII. I just....
-Can't wait!
Come on, they're gonna Iove you.