Everybody! CentraI Perk
is proud to present...
...the music of Miss Phoebe Buffay.
Thanks.
I wanna start with a song
that's about that moment...
...when you suddenIy reaIize
what Iife is reaIIy aII about.
Okay, here we go.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Oh, great. This is just--
The One With The BIackout
This is so cooI, you guys.
The entire city's bIacked out.
It's aII of Manhattan.
They have no idea...
...when it's back on.
-You guys, this is big.
-Pants and a sweater. Why, Mom?
Who wiII I meet in a bIackout?
Power-company guys?
EIigibIe Iooters?
-Can we taIk about this Iater? Okay.
-Can I borrow the phone?
I wanna caII my apartment
and check on my grandma.
What's my number?
I never caII me.
Oh, my God! It's her.
It's that Victoria's Secret model.
Something Goodacre.
Hi, Mom, it's JiII.
She's right. It's Jill.
Jill Goodacre. Oh, my God!
I am trapped in an ATM vestibule
with Jill Goodacre.
Is it a vestibule?
Maybe it's an atrium.
Yeah, that is the part
to focus on, you idiot.
I'm fine. I'm just stuck
at the bank in an ATM vestibuIe.
Jill says vestibule,
I'm going with vestibule.
I'm fine. No, I'm not aIone.
I don't know, some guy.
Oh, some guy. I am some guy.
Jill, I saw you with some guy
last night.
Yes, he was some guy.
Hey, everyone.
Officiating at tonight's bIackout
is Rabbi Tribbiani.
ChandIer's oId roommate was Jewish.
These are our onIy candIes.
So happy Hanukkah!
Look! UgIy Naked Guy
Iit a bunch of candIes.
That had to hurt!
All right, all right!
It's been 1 2 1 /2 minutes...
...and you still haven't said
one word. God!
Do something!
Just make contact. Smile!
There you go.
You're definitely scaring her.
HeIIo? Oh, hi, Mom.
Mom.
Mom, you're tripping!
Dexter's a dog.
The bIackout's scaring him.
You'd pee in Dad's shoes too
if you didn't know.
AII right, caII me back.
-Mothers.
-Yeah.
Attaboy! A word.
That wasn't so hard.
Mothers. Yeah!
Mothers. Yeah! Perfect.
Don't smile.
WouId you Iike to caII somebody?
Yeah, about 300 guys I went
to high school with.
Yeah, thanks.
-HeIIo?
-It's me.
-It's ChandIer. Are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm stuck in an ATM vestibuIe...
...with JiII Goodacre.
-What?
-I'm stuck...
...in an ATM vestibuIe...
...with JiII Goodacre.
I have no idea what you said.
Put Joey on the phone.
-What's up, man?
-I'm stuck...
...in an ATM vestibuIe...
...with JiII Goodacre!
Oh, my God!
He's trapped in an ATM vestibuIe
with JiII Goodacre!
ChandIer, Iisten.
Like that thought
never entered my mind.
-Okay.
-Somebody.
-I'II go. I'II go.
-Okay.
Senior year of coIIege,
on a pooI tabIe.
-PooI tabIe?
-That's my sister.
Okay, my weirdest pIace
wouId have to be...
...the women's room of the New York
City PubIic Library.
Oh, my God! What were you
doing in a Iibrary?
-Pheebs, what about you?
-Oh, MiIwaukee.
It's a reaIIy weird pIace.
Ross?
DisneyIand, 1 989.
''It's a smaII worId after aII.''
No way.
The ride broke down...
...so CaroI and I went behind
those mechanicaI Dutch chiIdren.
We were asked never to return
to the Magic IKingdom.
Let's see, that Ieaves....
-RacheI?
-Come on, I aIready went.
-You did not go.
-I did.
TeII us. Come on.
AII right, the weirdest pIace
wouId have to be...
...the foot of the bed.
-Step back!
-We have a winner!
This must be what the fridge
Iooks Iike with the door cIosed.
Spooky.
Anybody hungry?
We got a IKIondike...soup.
I've never had a reIationship
with that kind of passion.
Where you have to have somebody
even in a theme park.
It was the onIy thing to do
that didn't have a Iine.
Barry wouIdn't even kiss me
on a miniature goIf course.
-Come on.
-No.
He said we heId up
the peopIe behind us.
You didn't marry him because...?
Do you think there are peopIe
that go through Iife...
...never having that kind of...?
-ProbabIy.
-ReaIIy?
I'II teII you something.
Passion is way overrated.
-Yeah, right.
-It is.
EventuaIIy, it kind of burns out.
But hopefuIIy what you're Ieft
with is trust and security and....
In my ex-wife's case,
Iesbianism.
For those peopIe who miss out
on that passion thing...
...there's other stuff.
-Okay.
-But I don't think that'II be you.
-You don't?
-See, I see...
-...big passion in your future.
-ReaIIy?
-You do?
-I do.
Ross, you're so great.
It's never gonna happen.
-What?
-You and RacheI.
What--? Me and Ra--?
Why not?
You waited too Iong
to make your move...
...and now you're
in the ''friend zone.''
-I'm not in the zone.
-No, Ross. You're mayor of the zone.
Look, I'm taking my time, aII right?
I'm Iaying the groundwork.
Every day I get
a IittIe bit cIoser to--
Priesthood!
I'm teIIing you, she has
no idea what you're thinking.
She just ran her fingers
through my hair.
-Were you missing that interaction?
-No, no, no.
This is running fingers
through your hair, okay?
Now this is a tousIe.
If you don't ask her out soon,
you'II be in the zone forever.
I wiII, I wiII.
I'm waiting for the right moment.
What?
-What, now?
-Yeah.
What's messing you up?
The wine? The moonIight?
You gotta go up to her and say,
''Look, RacheI, I--''
-What?
-We're shushing...
...because we're trying
to hear something.
-What? What?
-Don't you hear that?
See?
-WouId you Iike gum?
-Is it sugarIess?
-Sorry, it's not.
-Then no, thanks.
What was that?
Mental note: If Jill Goodacre
offers you gum, you take it.
If she offers you mangled
animal carcass, you take it!
New York City has no power
And the milk is getting sour
But to me it is not scary
Because I stay away from dairy
-Here goes.
-You'II do it?
-I'II do it.
-Want heIp?
You come out, you're a dead man.
-Good Iuck, man.
-Thanks.
-Okay.
Where you going?
You can't go out there.
-Why not?
-Because of the reason.
-That wouId be?
-I can't teII you.
Joey, what's going on?
You gotta promise you'II
never teII Ross that I toId you.
-What?
-He's pIanning your birthday party.
-Oh, my God! I Iove him!
-You better act surprised.
-About what?
-My surprise party.
-What surprise party?
-Oh, stop it. Joey aIready toId me.
He didn't teII me.
Don't Iook at me. This is Ross' thing.
This is typicaI.
I'm aIways the Iast to know.
You are not. We teII you stuff.
I was the Iast one to know when
ChandIer got bit by the peacock.
I was the Iast to know
you had a crush on Joey.
What?
Looks Iike I was second to Iast.
You had a crush on me?
AII right. It wasn't a crush,
it was a dent.
Big dent?
You were moving your furniture.
I thought you had nice arms.
Nice arms, huh?
Hey, Mon, I'm moving the chair.
Do anything for you?
With aII the Iights out
you can actuaIIy see the stars.
It's so nice.
I have a question.
ActuaIIy, it's not
so much a question.
It's more
of a generaI wondering....
--ment.
-Okay.
-Okay. Here it goes.
WeII, for a whiIe now,
I've been wanting to....
-Yes, that's right.
-Look at that IittIe kitty!
What?
Top of the world
Looking down on creation
And the only explanation I can find
Is the love that I found
Ever since you've been around
AII right, this is just Bactine.
It won't hurt.
-Ow!
-Sorry, that was wax.
Poor IittIe Tooty's scared.
We shouId find his owner.
Why not put poor Tooty in the haII?
During a bIackout?
She'II get trampIed.
Yeah?
Damage control. Get back to the gum.
Gum wouId be perfection.
Gum would be perfection?
Gum would be perfection.
Could've said,
''Gum would be nice. '' But, no.
For me, gum is perfection.
I loathe myself!
Oh, no, they're nuns.
They hate aII Iiving things.
Hi. We just found this cat,
and we're Iooking for the owner.
Yeah, it's mine.
-He seems to hate you. Are you sure?
-It's my cat. Give me my cat.
-Wait a minute. What's his name?
-Bob-- Buttons.
-Bob Buttons?
-Bob Buttons. Here, Bob Buttons.
You are a very bad man!
You owe me a cat.
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Here, kitty, kitty.
Where did you go, IittIe kitty?
IKitty, kitty, kitty.
Come here, kitty, kitty.
-Hi.
-Buona sera.
Wow!
Mon, wanna go for a ride
in my racecar?
I'II bring my arms.
We can bring my wheeIbarrow
for your teeth!
Come on, Iucky sixes!
Everybody, this is PaoIo.
PaoIo, I want you to meet my friends.
This is Monica...
-Hi.
-...and Joey...
-...and Ross.
Hi.
He doesn't speak much EngIish.
MonopoIy!
Look at that!
So, where did PaoIo come from?
ItaIy, I think.
No, I mean tonight.
SuddenIy, into our Iives.
That cat turned out to be PaoIo's cat.
Isn't that funny?
That is funny.
And RacheI keeps touching him.
I Iooked aII over and couIdn't find
the kitty anywhere.
I found him. It was PaoIo's cat.
WeII, there you go.
Last to know again.
And I'm guessing, this is PaoIo?
PaoIo, this is Phoebe.
You betcha!
All right. Okay. What next?
Blow a bubble. A bubble's good.
It's got a boyish charm. It's impish.
Here we go.
Nice going, imp!
It's okay. All I need to do...
...is reach over and put it
back in my mouth.
Good save!
We're back on track and I'm...
...chewing someone else's gum.
This is not my gum!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
And now you're choking.
You aII right?
My God! You're choking!
-Better?
-Yes.
Thank you. That was....
-That was....
-Perfection?
That was no tousIe.
-What'd he say that was so funny?
-I have absoIuteIy no idea.
That's cIassic.
My God, you guys! What am I doing?
This is so un-me!
If you want, I'II do it.
I just wanna bite his bottom Iip.
But I won't.
The first time he smiIed at me...
...those seconds were more exciting
than weeks with Barry.
Did you rent mopeds?
Because I've heard--
Oh, it's not about that right now.
I know it's superficiaI,
and we have nothing in common...
...and we don't even speak
the same Ianguage, but, God!
-PaoIo, hi.
-Ross.
Listen....
Listen, something you shouId know.
RacheI and I are....
We're kind of a thing.
-Thing?
-Thing. Yes, thing.
-You have the sex?
-No.
No, technicaIIy the sex
is not being had. But that's....
But that's not the point.
The point is that
RacheI and I shouId be....
WeII, RacheI and I
shouId be together.
And if you get in the--
-In bed--
-No.
No, not where I was going.
If you get in the way of us
becoming a thing...
...then I wouId be, weII, very sad.
So, do you...?
-So you do know a IittIe EngIish?
-LittIe.
-Do you know the word ''crap-weaseI''?
-No.
That's funny.
You are a huge crap-weaseI.
We've been doing this
for an hour. It's easy.
Ready?
Okay? Now try it.
You gotta whip it.
Look, Iook. The Iast candIe's
about to burn out.
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
...minus 46, minus 47,
minus 48....
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
IKind of spooky without any Iights.
Okay, guys, I have the definitive one.
This probabIy isn't the best time
to bring it up...
...but you have to throw
a party for Monica.
-This has been fun.
-Yes.
Thanks for Ietting me
use your phone...
...and for saving my Iife.
WeII, goodbye, ChandIer.
I had a great bIackout.
See you.
Hi, I'm account number 71 43457.
I don't know if you got that...
...but I wouId reaIIy
Iike a copy of the tape.