Rachel: Everybody? Shh, shhh. Uhhh... Central Perk is proud to present the music of Miss Phoebe Buffay.
Phoebe: Hi. Um, I want to start with a song thats about that moment when you suddenly realize what life is all about. OK, here we go.  OK, thank you very much. LAUGH
Chandler: Oh, great. This is just...
Rachel: Wow, this is so cool, you guys. The entire city is blacked out! LAUGH
Monica: Mom says it's all of Manhattan, parts of Brooklyn and Queens, and they have no idea when it's coming back on.
Rachel: Wow, you guys, this is big.
Pants and a sweater. Why, Mom?
Who will I meet in a blackout?
Power-company guys?
Eligible looters?
Can we talk about this later? Okay.
Phoebe: Can I borrow the phone? I want to call my apartment and check on my grandma.  What's my number?
Phoebe: Well, I never call me.
Chandler: _Oh my God, it's that Victoria's Secret model. Something... something Goodacre.
_Jill:  Hi Mom, it's Jill.
Chandler: _She's right, it's Jill. Jill Goodacre. Oh my God. I am trapped in an ATM vestibule with Jill Goodacre! __ Is it a vestibule? Maybe it's an atrium. Oh, yeah, that is the part to focus on, you idiot!_
Jill:  Yeah, I'm fine. I'm just stuck at the bank, in an ATM vestibule.
Chandler: _Jill says vestibule... I'm going with vestibule._
Jill:  I'm fine. No, I'm not alone... I don't know, some guy.
Chandler: _Oh! Some guy. Some guy. 'Hey Jill, I saw you with some guy last night. Yes, he was some guy. _
Joey: Hi everyone.
Ross: And officiating at tonight's blackout, is Rabbi Tribbiani.
Joey: Well, Chandler's old roomate was Jewish, and these are the only candles we have, so... Happy Chanukah, everyone.
Phoebe:  Eww, look. Ugly Naked Guy lit a bunch of candles.
Rachel: That had to hurt!
Chandler: _Alright, alright, alright. It's been fourteen and a half minutes and you still have not said one word. Oh God, do something. Just make contact, smile!_
Chandler: _There you go!_
Chandler: _You're definitely scaring here._
Hello? Oh, hi, Mom.
Mom.
Mom, you're tripping!
Dexter's a dog.
The blackout's scaring him.
You'd pee in Dad's shoes too
if you didn't know.
All right, call me back.
Mothers.
Yeah.
Attaboy! A word.
That wasn't so hard.
Mothers. Yeah!
Mothers. Yeah! Perfect.
Don't smile.
Would you like to call somebody?
Chandler: _Yeah, about 300 guys I went to high school with._ Yeah, thanks.
Monica: Hello?
Chandler: Hey, it's me.
Monica:  Are you OK?
Chandler: Yeah, I'm fine.  I'm trppd in an ATM vstbl wth Jll Gdcr.
Monica: What?
Chandler: I'm trppd... in an ATM vstbl... wth Jll Gdcr!
Monica: I have no idea what you just said.
Chandler:  Put Joey on the phone.
Joey: What's up man?
Chandler: I'm trppd... in an ATM vstbl... wth JLL GDCR.
Oh, my God!
He's trapped in an ATM vestibule
with Jill Goodacre!
Chandler, listen.
Chandler: Yeah, like that thought never entered my mind.
Okay.
Rachel: Alright, somebody.
Monica: OK, I'll go. OK, senior year of college... on a pool table.
Pool table?
Ross: That's my sister.
Joey: OK... my weirdest place would have to be... the women's room on the second floor of the New York CIty public library.
Monica: Oh my God! What were you doing in a library?
Ross: Pheebs, what about you?
Phoebe: Oh... Milwaukee.
It's a really weird place.
Rachel: Um... Ross?
Ross: Disneyland, 1989, 'It's a Small World After All.'
All: No way!
Ross: The ride broke down. So, Carol and I went behind a couple of those mechanical Dutch children... then they fixed the ride, and we were asked never to return to the Magic Kingdom.
Let's see, that leaves....
Phoebe: Oh, Rachel.
Rachel: Oh come on, I already went.
Monica: You did not go!
I did.
All: Come on.
Rachel: Oh, alright. The weirdest place would have to be... ... oh, the foot of the bed.
Ross: Step back.
Joey: We have a winner!
This must be what the fridge
looks like with the door closed.
Spooky.
Anybody hungry?
We got a IKlondike...soup.
Rachel: I just never had a relationship with that kind of passion, you know, where you have to have somebody right there, in the middle of a theme park.
Ross: Well, it was the only thing to do there that didn't have a line.
Rachel: There, well, see? Barry wouldn't even kiss me on a miniature golf course.
Ross: Come on.
Rachel: No, he said we were holding up the people behind us.
Ross:  And you didn't marry him because...?
Rachel: I mean, do you think there are people who go through life never having that kind of...
Ross: Probably. But you know, I'll tell you something. Passion is way overrated.
Really?
Rachel: Yeah right.
Ross: It is. Eventually, it kind of... burns out. But hopefully, what you're left with is trust, and security, and... well, in the case of my ex-wife, lesbianism. So, you know, for all of those people who miss out on that passion... thing, there's all that other good stuff.
Rachel:  OK.
Ross: But, um... I don't think that's going to be you.
Rachel: You don't.
Ross: Uh-uh. See, I see.... big passion in your future.
Rachel: Really?
Rachel: You do?
Ross: I do.
Rachel: Oh Ross, you're so great.
Joey: It's never gonna happen.
Ross:  What?
Joey: You and Rachel.
What--? Me and Ra--?
Ross:  Why not?
Joey: Because you waited too long to make your move, and now you're in the friend zone.
Ross: No, no, no. I'm not in the zone.
Joey: Ross, you're mayor of the zone.
Ross: I'm taking my time, alright? I'm laying the groundwork. Yeah. I mean, every day I get just a little bit closer to...
Joey: Priesthood! Look Ross, I'm telling you, she has no idea what you're thinking. If you don't ask her out soon you're going to end up stuck in the zone forever.
She just ran her fingers
through my hair.
Were you missing that interaction?
No, no, no.
This is running fingers
through your hair, okay?
Now this is a tousle.
Joey: Priesthood! Look Ross, I'm telling you, she has no idea what you're thinking. If you don't ask her out soon you're going to end up stuck in the zone forever.
Ross: I will, I will. See, I'm waiting for the right moment.  What? What, now?
Joey: Yeeeeaaaahhh! What's messing you up? The wine? The candles? The moonlight? You've just got to go up to her and say, 'Rachel, I think that...'
What?
Ross: We're shushing... because... we're trying to hear something. Listen.  Don't you hear that?
What? What?
Ross: See?
Jill: Would you like some gum?
Chandler: Um, is it sugarless?
Jill:  Sorry, it's not.
Chandler: Oh, then no thanks. _What the hell was that? Mental note: If Jill Goodacre offers you gum, you take it. If she offers you mangled animal carcass, you take it._
New York City has no power
And the milk is getting sour
But to me it is not scary
Because I stay away from dairy
Ross:  OK, here goes.
Joey: Are you going to do it?
Ross: I'm going to do it.
Joey: Do you want any help?
Ross: You come out there, you're a dead man.
Joey: Good luck, man.
Ross: Thanks.  OK.
Joey: OK.
Joey: Hey, where are you going?
Joey: You can't go out there.
Monica: Why not?
Joey: Because of... the reason.
Monica: And that would be?
Joey: I, um, can't tell you.
Monica: Joey, what's going on?
Joey: OK, you've got to promise that you'll never, ever tell Ross that I told you.
Monica: About what?
Joey: He's planning your birthday party.
Monica: Oh my God! I love him!
Joey:  You'd better act surprised.
Phoebe: About what?
Monica: My surprise party!
Phoebe: What surprise party?
Monica: Oh stop it. Joey already told me.
Phoebe: Well, he didn't tell me.
Joey: Hey, don't look at me. This is Ross's thing.
Phoebe: This is so typical. I'm always the last one to know everything.
Monica: No, you are not. We tell you stuff.
Phoebe: Yuh-huh! I was the last one to know when Chandler got bitten by the peacock at the zoo. I was the last one to know when you had a crush on Joey when he was moving in.  Looks like I was second to last.
What?
You had a crush on me?
All right. It wasn't a crush,
it was a dent.
Big dent?
You were moving your furniture.
I thought you had nice arms.
Nice arms, huh?
Hey, Mon, I'm moving the chair.
Do anything for you?
With all the lights out
you can actually see the stars.
Rachel: Hmmm... this is so nice.
Ross: OK, I have a question. Well, actually, it's not so much a question as.. more of a general wondering... ment.
Rachel: OK.
Ross: OK. Here goes. For a while now, I've been wanting to, um....
Ross: Yes, yes, that's right...
Rachel: Oh, look at the little cat!
Ross: What?  Ow!
Monica, Joey, and Phoebe:  _I'm on top of the world, looking down on creation and the only explanation I can find, is the wonders I've found ever since..._
Monica:  This is just Bactine. It won't hurt.
Ow!
Joey: Sorry, that was wax.
Phoebe: Oh, poor little Tooty is scared to death. We should find his owner.
Ross: Why don't we just put 'poor little Tooty' out in the hall?
Rachel: During a blackout? He'd get trampled!
Ross:  Yeah?
Damage control. Get back to the gum.
Chandler: You know, on second thought, gum would be perfection.  _'Gum would be perfection'? 'Gum would be perfection.' Could have said 'gum would be nice,' or 'I'll have a stick,' but no, no, no, no. For me, gum is perfection. I loathe myself._
Phoebe:  Oh no, the Mendels, they hate all living things, right?
Rachel: Oh.  Hi. We just found this cat and we're looking for the owner.
Mr. Heckles: Er, yeah, it's mine.
Phoebe:  He seems to hate you. Are you sure?
Mr. Heckles: Yeah, it's my cat. Give me my cat.
Phoebe: Wait a minute. What's his name?
Mr. Heckles: Ehhhh... B-Buttons.
Rachel: Bob Buttons?
Mr. Heckles: Mmm. Bob Buttons. Here, Bob Buttons.
Phoebe:  Oooh! You are a very bad man!
Mr. Heckles:  You owe me a cat.
Rachel: Here, kitty-kitty. Here kitty-kitty. Where did you go, little kitty-kitty-kitty? Here kitty-kitty-kitty-kitty...
Hi.
-Buona sera.
Rachel: Wow.
Mon, wanna go for a ride
in my racecar?
I'll bring my arms.
We can bring my wheelbarrow
for your teeth!
Ross:  Lucky sixes....
Rachel:  Everybody, this is Paolo. Paolo, I want you to meet my friends. This is Monica.
Monica:  Hi!
Rachel: And Joey....
Monica: Hi!
Rachel: And Ross.
Rachel:  He doesn't speak much English.
Paolo:  _Monopoly_!
Rachel: Look at that!
Ross:  So, um... where did Paolo come from?
Rachel: Oh... Italy, I think.
Ross: No, I mean tonight, in the building. Suddenly. Into our lives.
Rachel: Well, the cat... the cat turned out to be Paolo's cat!
Isn't that funny?
Ross: That, that is funny... .... and Rachel keeps touching him.
Phoebe: Alright. I looked all over the building and I couldn't find the kitty anywhere.
Rachel: Oh, I found him. He was Paolo's cat.
Phoebe: Ah! Well! There you go! Last to know again! And I'm guessing... since nobody told me... this is Paolo.
Rachel: Ah, Paolo, this is Phoebe.
Phoebe:  You betcha!
Chandler:  _Ah, let's see. What next? Blow a bubble. A bubble's good. It's got a... boyish charm, it's impish. Here we go._
Chandler: _Nice going, imp. OK, it's OK. All I need to do is reach over and put it in my mouth._
Chandler: _Good save! We're back on track, and I'm..._  _..chewing someone else's gum. This is not my gum. Oh my God! Oh my God! And now you're choking._
Jill: Are you alright?
Jill: My God, you're choking!  That better?
Chandler:  Yes... thank you. That was... that was....
Jill: Perfection?
That was no tousle.
Ross: Wha-What did he say that was so funny?
Rachel: I have absolutely no idea.
Ross: That's... that's classic.
Rachel:  Oh my God, you guys, what am I doing? What am I doing? This is so un-me!
Monica: If you want, I'll do it.
Phoebe: I know, I just want to bite his bottom lip.  But I won't.
Rachel: God, the first time he smiled at me... those three seconds were more exciting than three weeks in Bermuda with Barry.
Phoebe: You know, did you ride mopeds? 'Cause I've heard... ... oh, I see... it's not about that right now. OK.
Rachel: Y'know, I know it's totally superficial and we have absolutely nothing in common, and we don't even speak the same language but Goooooooddddddd....
Ross: Paolo. Hi.
Paolo: Ross!
Ross: Listen. Um, listen. Something you should... know... um, Rachel and I... we're kind of a thing.
Paolo: Thing?
Ross: Thing, yes. Thing.
Paolo: Ah, you... have the sex?
Ross: No, no, no. Technically the... sex is not... being had, but that's... see, that's not the point. See, um, the point is that... Rachel and I should be, er, together. You know, and if you get in the.... um...
Paolo: Bed?
Ross: No, no, that's not where I was going. Er, if you get in the... way, of us becoming a thing, then I would be, well, very sad.
Ross: So you do know a little English.
Paolo: Poco... a leetle.
Ross: Do you know the word _crapweasel_?
Paolo: No.
Ross: That's funny, because you know, you are a huge crapweasel!
Jill: Chandler, we've been here for an hour doing this! Now watch, it's easy.
Jill: Ready?
Okay? Now try it.
Jill: No, you've got to whip it.
Phoebe: Oh, look look look. The last candle's about to burn out. 10, 9, 8, 7...
Ten, nine, eight, seven minus 46, minus 47,
minus 48....
Ross: Thank you.
Phoebe: Thanks.
Ross: Kinda... spooky without any lights.
Ross: OK, guys, guys? I have the definitive one. Mwwwooooo-hah-hah...
Joey: Hey Ross. This probably isn't the best time to bring it up, but you have to throw a party for Monica.
Jill: Well, this has been fun.
Chandler: Yes. Yes, thanks for letting me use your phone... and for saving my life.
Jill: Well, goodbye Chandler. I had a great blackout.  See ya.
Chandler: Hi, um, I'm account number 7143457. And, uh, I don't know if you got any of that, but I would really like a copy of the tape. LAUGH