Monica: Would you let it go? It's not that big a deal.
Ross: Not that big a deal? It's amazing. Ok, you just reach in there, there's one little maneuver, and bam, a bra right out the sleeve. All right, as far as I'm concerned, there is nothing a guy can do that even comes close. Am I right? LAUGH
Rachel: Come on! You guys can pee standing up.
Chandler: We can? All right, I'm tryin' that.
Joey: Ok, you know what blows my mind? Women can see breasts any time they want. You just look down and there they are. How you get any work done is beyond me.
Phoebe: Oh, ok, you know what I don't get? The way guys can do so many mean things, and then not even care.
Ross: Multiple orgasms! LAUGH
LAUGH
Chandler: So, Saturday night, the big night, date night, Saturday night, Sat-ur-day night!
Joey: No plans, huh? LAUGH
Chandler: Not a one.
Ross: Not even, say, breaking up with Janice?
Chandler: Oh, right, right, shut up. LAUGH
Monica: Chandler, nobody likes breaking up with someone. You just gotta do it. LAUGH
Chandler: No, I know, but it's just so hard, you know? I mean, you're sitting there with her, she has no idea what's happening, and then you finally get up the courage to do it, and there's the horrible awkward moment when you've handed her the note.
Joey: Why do you have to break up with her? Be a man, just stop calling.
Phoebe: You know, if you want, I'll do it with you.
Chandler: Oh, thanks, but I think she'd feel like we're gangin' up on her.
Ross: Tony?
Monica: Oh, you're breaking up with Tony?
Phoebe: Yeah, I know, he's sweet, but it's just not fun anymore, you know? I don't know if it's me, or his hunger strike, or, I don't know.
Rachel:  Does anybody want anything else? LAUGH
Ross: Oh, yeah, last week you had a wonderful, nutty, chocolatey kind of a cakey pie thing.  Nothing, just, just, I'm fine.
Phoebe:  What's the matter? Why so scrunchy?
Rachel: It's my father. He wants to give me a Mercedes convertible.
Ross: That guy, he burns me up.
Rachel: Yeah, well, it's a Mercedes if I move back home. Oh, it was horrible. He called me _young lady_. LAUGH
Chandler: Ooh, I hate when my father calls me that.
Monica: Did he give you that whole "You're-not-up-to-this" thing again?
Phoebe:  Uh-huh, uh-huh. LAUGH
Angela: Hi, Joey.
Joey: My god, Angela.
Monica: Wow, being dumped by you obviously agrees with her.
Phoebe: Are you gonna go over there?
Joey: No, yeah, no, ok, but not yet. I don't wanna seem too eager. One Mississippi, two Mississippi, three Mississippi. That seems pretty cool.  Hey, Angela.
Angela:  Joey.
Joey: You look good. LAUGH
Angela: That's because I'm wearing a dress that accents my boobs.
Joey: You don't say.
Ross: So, uh, Rachel, what are you, uh, what're you doing tonight?
Rachel: Oh, big glamour night. Me and Monica at Laundorama.
Ross: Oh, you uh, you wanna hear a freaky coincidence? Guess who's doing laundry there too?
Rachel: Who?
Ross: Me. Was that not clear? Hey, why don't, um, why don't I just join you both, here?
Rachel: Don't you have a laundry room in your building?
Ross: Yes, I do have a laundry room in my building, um, but there's a.... rat problem. Apparently they're attracted to the dryer sheets, and they're goin' in fine, but they're comin' out all.... fluffy. Anyway, say, sevenish?
Rachel: Sure.
Angela: Forget it Joey. I'm with Bob now.
Joey: Bob? Who the hell's Bob?
Angela: Bob is great. He's smart, he's sophisticated, and he has a real job. You, you go on three auditions a month and you call yourself an actor, but Bob... LAUGH
Joey: Come on, we were great together. And not just at the fun stuff, but like, talking too.
Angela: Yeah, well, sorry, Joe. You said let's just be friends, so guess what?
Joey: What?
Angela: We're just friends.
Joey: Fine, fine, so, why don't the four of us go out and have dinner together tonight? You know, as friends?
Angela: What four of us? LAUGH
Joey: Monica, I'm tellin' you, this guy is perfect for you.
Monica: Forget it. Not after your cousin who could belch the alphabet. LAUGH
Joey: Come on. This guy's great. His name's Bob. He's Angela's... brother. He's smart, he's sophisticated, and he has a real job. Me, I go on three auditions a month and call myself an actor, but Bob is...
Monica:  Oh, god help us.
Joey: What?
Monica: Ugly Naked Guy's laying kitchen tile. Eww! LAUGH
Joey: Eww! Look, I'm asking a favor here. If I do this for her brother, maybe Angela will come back to me.
Monica: What's going on here? You go out with tons of girls.
Hold on a sec.
You need to not touch any of those. LAUGH
Ross:  Well, Monica's not coming, it's just gonna be me and Rachel.
Chandler: Oh. Well, hold on camper, are you sure you've thought this thing through? LAUGH
Ross: It's laundry. The thinking through is minimal.
Chandler: It's just you and Rachel, just the two of you? This is a date. You're going on a date. LAUGH
Ross: Nuh-uh. LAUGH
Is it a date if she doesn't know?
Yes, absolutely.
Saturday night, all rules apply. LAUGH
Chandler: Yuh-huh.
Ross: So what're you saying here? I should shave again, pick up some wine, what? LAUGH
Chandler: Well, you may wanna rethink the dirty underwear. This is basically the first time she's gonna see your underwearyou want it to be dirty? LAUGH
Ross:  No.
Chandler: Oh, and uh, the fabric softener? LAUGH
Ross: Ok, ok, now what is wrong with my _Snuggles_? What, it says I'm a sensitive, warm kinda guy, you know, like a warm, fuzzy bear. Ok, I can pick something else up on the way. LAUGH
LAUGH
Monica: Thank you. So what does this Bob guy look like? Is he tall? Short?
Joey: Yep.
Monica: Which?
Joey: Which what?
Monica: You've never met Bob, have you?
Joey: No, but he's... LAUGH
Monica: Oh my god, Joey, for all we know this guy could be horribly...
Angela: Hey, Joey.
Chandler: Where are they? Where are they?
Phoebe: This is nice. We never do anything just the two of us. LAUGH
Chandler: It's great. Maybe tomorrow we can rent a car and run over some puppies. LAUGH
Phoebe: Eww, I don't wanna do that.
Chandler: Here we go.
Phoebe: Ok, have a good break-up.
Chandler: Hey, Janice. LAUGH
Janice: Oh, my god, I am so glad you called me. I had the most supremely awful day.
Chandler: Hey, that's not good. Can I get an espresso and a latte over here, please? LAUGH
Janice: We got the proofs back from that photo shoot, you know, the one with the little vegetables. Anyway, they pretty much sucked, so, I blew off the rest of the day, and I went shopping...... and I got you, I'm looking, I'm looking, I'm looking, I got you... LAUGH
Chandler: What?
Janice: What?
Chandler:  What... did you get me there? LAUGH
Janice: I got you...these.
Chandler: Bullwinkle socks. That's so sweet. LAUGH
Chandler: That's great.
Chandler: Well, I'm gonna get another espresso. Can I get you another latte?
Janice:  No, no, I'm still working on mine. LAUGH
Chandler: That's it?
Phoebe: Yeah, it was really hard.
Chandler: Oh, yeah, that hug looked pretty brutal. LAUGH
Sorry.
How are things going?
Going? Things are not going.
She got me socks.
These go with your Rockys. She really
cares about you-- I'm sorry.
Woman: Comin' through. Move, move.
Rachel: Oh, 'scuse me. I was kinda using that machine.
Woman: Yeah, well, now you're kinda not.
Rachel: But I saved it. I put my basket on top. LAUGH
Woman: Oh, I'm sorry, is that your basket? It's really pretty. Unfortunately, I don't see suds.
Rachel: What?
Woman: No suds, no save. Ok? LAUGH
Ross: What's goin' on?
Rachel: Hi, uh, nothing. That horrible woman just took my machine.
Ross: Was your basket on top?
Rachel: Yeah, but, there were no suds.
Ross: So?
Rachel: Well, you know, no suds, no save.
Ross: No suds? Excuse me, hold on a second.  That's my friend's machine.
Woman: Hey, hey, hey, her stuff wasn't in it.
Ross: Hey, hey, hey, that's not the rule and you know it. LAUGH
Ross:  Ok, let's do laundry. LAUGH
Rachel: That was amazing. I can't even send back soup.
Ross: Well, that's because you're such a sweet, gentle, uh...Do you, uh, do you...Oh, hey, uh you must need detergent. LAUGH
Rachel: What's that?
Ross: _Uberveiss_. It's new, it's German, it's extra-tough. LAUGH
Ross: Rach, do you uh, are you gonna separate those?
Rachel: Oh god. Oh, am I being like a total laundry spaz? I mean, am I supposed to use like one machine for shirts and another machine for pants?
Ross: Rach, have you never done this before? LAUGH
Rachel: Well, not myself, but I know other people that have. Ok, you caught me. I'm a laundry virgin. LAUGH
Ross: Uh, well, don't worry, I'll use the gentle cycle. Ok, um, basically you wanna use one machine for all your whites, a whole nother machine for colors, and a third for your uh, your uh, delicates, and that would be your bras and your under-panty things. LAUGH
Rachel:  Ok, Well, what about these are white cotton panties. Would they go with whites or delicates?
LAUGH
Monica:  So, where did you guys grow up?
Angela: Brooklyn Heights.
Bob: Cleveland.
Monica: How, how did that happen?
Joey: Oh my god.
Monica: What?
SCENE BREAK
Joey: So, you and Angela, huh? LAUGH
Bob: Yep. Pretty much.
Joey: You're a lucky man. You know what I miss the most about her? That cute nibbly noise when she eats. Like a happy little squirrel, or a weasel.
Bob: Huh, I never really noticed.
Joey: Oh, yeah, yeah, listen for it. LAUGH
SCENE BREAK
Monica: I've gotta tell you, Bob is terrific.
Angela: Yeah, isn't he?
Monica: It is so great to meet a guy who is smart and funny, and has an emotional age beyond, like eight. LAUGH
Angela: You know what else? He's unbelievable in bed.
SCENE BREAK LAUGH
LAUGH
Phoebe: Ok, you can do this. It's just like pulling off a Band-aid. Just do it really fast, and then the wound is exposed. LAUGH
This isn't about you. LAUGH
I know! It's about
your fear of commitment.
I'm not afraid.
Please.
I don't!
I don't! I'm ready to commit anytime.
Really? LAUGH
SCENE BREAK
LAUGH
Rachel: Ok, I know this is gonna sound really stupid, but I feel that if I can do this, you know, if I can actually do my own laundry, there isn't anything I can't do.
Ross: That does not sound stupid to me. You know, it's like the first time I had to make dinner for myself, after Carol left me?  Uh-oh.
Rachel: What uh-oh?
Ross:  Uh-oh the laundry's done, uh-oh, uh-oh.
Rachel: Ross, what's the matter? LAUGH
Ross: Nothing, nothing. Lee-lo, the laundry's done. LAUGH
Rachel: Come on, show me.
Ross: All right, all right, it's just that you left a red sock in with all your whites, and now, everything's kinda pink.
Rachel: Oh, everything's pink.
SCENE BREAK LAUGH
LAUGH
Monica: Something went wrong with Underdog, and they couldn't get his head to inflate. So anyway, um, his head is like flopping down Broadway, right, and I'm just thinking... how inappropriate this is. Um, I've got something in my eye, uh, Joey, could we check it in the light, please?
Monica: Oh my god.
Joey: What?
Monica: Hello! Were we at the same table? It's like... cocktails in Appalachia.
Joey: Come on, they're close. LAUGH
Monica: Close? She's got her tongue in his ear.
Joey: Oh, like you've never gotten a little rambunctious with Ross.
Monica: Joey, this is sick, it's disgusting, it's, it'snot really true, is it?
Joey: Well, who's to say what's true? I mean... LAUGH
Monica:  Oh!
Joey: Ow!
Monica:  I'm outta here.
Joey: Wait, wait, wait. You want him, I want her. He likes you.
Monica: Really? LAUGH
Joey: Yeah. I'm thinking, if we put our heads together, between the two of us, we can break them up.
SCENE BREAK LAUGH
Chandler: Here's the thing, Janice. You know, I mean, it's like we're different. I'm like the bing, bing, bing. You're like the boom, boom, ... boom. LAUGH
Janice: Ow!
Chandler: Oh, my god, I'm so sorry. Are you ok? LAUGH
Janice: Ow. Um, it's just my lens. It's just my lens. I'll be right back.
Chandler:  I hit her in the eye! I hit her in the eye! This is the worst break-up in the history of the world. LAUGH
Phoebe: Oh my god.  How many of those have you had?
Chandler: Oh, I don't know, a million? LAUGH
Phoebe: Chandler, easy, easy. Go to your happy place. La la la la la la la.
Chandler: I'm fine.
Phoebe: All right.
Chandler: I'm not fine. Here she comes. LAUGH
Phoebe: Wait here. Breathe. LAUGH
Chandler: How do you do that?
Phoebe: It's like a gift.
SCENE BREAK
Ross: You got the clothes clean. Now that's the important part. LAUGH
Rachel: Oh, I guess. Except everything looks like jammies now. LAUGH
Rachel: Whoa, I'm sorry. Excuse me. We had this cart.
Woman: Yeah, well, I had a 24-inch waist. You lose things. Now come on, get outta my way.
Rachel: I'm sorry, you know, maybe I wasn't being clear. Uh, this is our cart.
Woman: Hey, hey, hey there aren't any clothes in it.
Rachel: Hey, hey, hey, hey, quit making up rules!
Woman: Let go! LAUGH
Rachel: All right, listen, missy. If you want this cart, you're gonna have to take me with it!
Rachel:  Yes! Did you see that?
Ross: You were incredible! Brand new woman, ladies and gentlemen.
Rachel: I could not have done this without you.
SCENE BREAK
Rachel: Oh, are you sure you're ok?
Ross: Yeah. LAUGH
Rachel: Does it still hurt?
Phoebe:  What a neat idea. All your clothes match. I'm gonna do this.
Monica: Hi.
Phoebe: Hey, how'd it go?
Joey: Excellent.
Monica: We ripped that couple apart, and kept the pieces for ourselves.
Ross: What a beautiful story. Hey, I'm fine by the way.
Monica:  Oh, I'm sorry.
Rachel: Where's Chandler?
Phoebe: Oh, he needed some time to grieve.