[Scene: Chandler's Office, Chandler is on a coffee break.   Shelley enters.)
Shelley: Hey gorgeous, how's it going? LAUGH
Chandler: Dehydrated Japanese noodles under fluorescent lights... does it get better than this?
Shelley: Question. You're not dating anybody, are you, because I met somebody who would be perfect for you.
Chandler: Ah, y'see, perfect might be a problem. Had you said 'co-dependent', or 'self-destructive'...
Shelley: Do you want a date Saturday?
Chandler: Yes please.
Shelley: Okay. He's cute, he's funny, he's- LAUGH
Chandler: He's a he?
[Scene: Monica and Rachel's, everyone is there.) LAUGH
Chandler: ...Couldn't enjoy a cup of noodles after that. I mean, is that ridiculous? Can you believe she actually thought that?
Rachel: Um... yeah. Well, I mean, when I first met you, y'know, I thought maybe, possibly, you might be...
Chandler: You did?
Rachel: Yeah, but then you spent Phoebe's entire birthday party talking to my breasts, so then I figured maybe not.
Chandler: Huh. Did, uh... any of the rest of you guys think that when you first met me?
Monica: I did. LAUGH
Phoebe: Yeah, I think so, yeah.
Joey: Not me.
Ross: Nono, me neither. Although, uh, y'know, back in college, Susan Sallidor did.
Chandler: You're kidding! Did you tell her I wasn't? LAUGH
Ross: No. No, it's just 'cause, uh, I kinda wanted to go out with her too, so I told her, actually, you were seeing Bernie Spellman... who also liked her, so...
Chandler: Well, this is fascinating. So, uh, what is it about me?
Phoebe: I dunno, 'cause you're smart, you're funny...
Chandler: Ross is smart and funny, d'you ever think that about him? LAUGH
All: Yeah! Right!
Chandler: WHAT IS IT?!
Monica: Okay, I-I d'know, you-you just- you have a quality.
I think this is gonna work for you.
Excuse me?
Sure, sure.
Women find you less threatening,
they let their guards down you're like a stealth heterosexual.
All: Yes. Absolutely. A quality.
Chandler: Oh, oh, a quality, good, because I was worried you guys were gonna be vague about this.
Monica: Hello? Hello? Oh! Rachel, it's Paolo calling from Rome.
Rachel: Oh my God! Calling from Rome!  _Bon giorno, caro mio._
Ross:  So he's calling from Rome. I could do that. Just gotta go to Rome.
How you doing?
Hey, Dad.
SCENE BREAK
[Scene: The Hospital, Mr. and Mrs. Geller are there, along with Aunt Lillian. Ross and Monica enter and everyone says hi and kisses.)
Ross: So, uh, how's she doing?
Aunt Lillian: The doctor says it's a matter of hours.
Monica: How-how are you, Mom?
Mrs. Geller: Me? I'm fine, fine. I'm glad you're here. ...What's with your hair?
Monica: What? LAUGH
Mrs. Geller: What's different?
Monica: Nothing.
Mrs. Geller: Oh, maybe that's it.
Monica: She is unbelievable, our mother is...
Ross: Okay, relax, relax. We are gonna be here for a while, it looks like, and we still have boyfriends and your career to cover.
Monica: Oh God!
Monica: The fuzzy little mints at the bottom of her purse.
Ross: Oh! ...Yeah, they were gross. Oh, you know what I loved? Her Sweet 'n' Los. How she was always stealing them from- from restaurants. LAUGH
Mr. Geller: Not just restaurants, from our house.
Nurse: Mrs. Geller?
Aunt Phylis is dead?
Yeah, for like six years.
Where were--?
Can we focus, please?
Ross: She looks so small.
Monica: I know.
Ross: Well, at least she's with Pop-Pop and Aunt Phyllis now. LAUGH
Monica: G'bye, Nana.
Ross: Bye, Nana.
Monica: Ross!
Mrs. Geller: What is going on?!
Ross: Y'know how-how the nurse said that-that Nana had passed? Well, she's not, quite..
Mrs. Geller: What?
Ross: She's not- past, she's present, she's back.
Aunt Lillian:  What's going on?
Mr. Geller: She may have died.
Aunt Lillian: She may have died?
Mr. Geller: We're looking into it.
SCENE BREAK
Chandler: I just have to know, okay. Is it my hair?
Rachel:  Yes, Chandler, that's exactly what it is. It's your hair. LAUGH
Phoebe: Yeah, you have homosexual hair.
Rachel: So, um, did she...
Ross: Twice.
Joey: Twice?
Phoebe: Oh, that sucks!
Joey: You guys okay?
Ross: I dunno, it's weird. I mean, I know she's gone, but I just don't feel, uh...
Phoebe: Maybe that's 'cause she's not really gone. LAUGH
Ross: Nono, she's gone. LAUGH
Monica: We checked. A lot.
Phoebe: Hm, I mean maybe no-one ever really goes. Ever since my mom died, every now and then, I get the feeling that she's like right here, y'know?  Oh! And Debbie, my best friend from junior high- got struck by lightning on a miniature golf course- I always get this really strong Debbie vibe whenever I use one of those little yellow pencils, y'know? ...I miss her.
Rachel: Aw. Hey, Pheebs, want this?
Phoebe: Thanks! LAUGH
Dad, let's just make a decision. LAUGH
You're right.
It's going into the ground.
We should get the most basic thing.
''The non-protective corrugated
fiberboard with white laminate.''
Dad, we can't bury Nana
in a dresser from Ikea.
This is why your mother
buys my clothes.
I hate to shop. I hate it. LAUGH
Isn't this more about
the fact that once you decide, it's like
acknowledging Nana's actually gone?
No, I really hate to shop.
SCENE BREAK
LAUGH
Ross: I thought it was gonna be a closed casket.
Mrs. Geller: Well, that doesn't mean she can't look nice! LAUGH
SCENE BREAK
Mr. Geller: I was just thinking. When my time comes- LAUGH
Monica: Dad!
Mr. Geller: Listen to me! When my time comes, I wanna be buried at sea.
Monica: You what?
Mr. Geller: I wanna be buried at sea, it looks like fun.
Monica: Define fun.
Mr. Geller: C'mon, you'll make a day of it! You'll rent a boat, pack a lunch... LAUGH
Monica: ...And then we throw your body in the water... Gee, that does sound fun.
SCENE BREAK
Chandler: Hey, gorgeous.
Shelley:  Hey. Look, I'm sorry about yesterday, I, um-
Chandler: No, nono, don't- don't worry about it. Believe me, apparently other people have made the same mistake.
Shelley: Oh! Okay! Phew! LAUGH
Chandler: So, uh... what do you think it is about me?
Shelley: I dunno, uh... you just have a-a...
Chandler: ...Quality, right, great.
Shelley: Y'know, it's a shame, because you and Lowell would've made a great couple.
Chandler: Lowell? Financial Services' Lowell, that's who you saw me with? LAUGH
Shelley: What? He's cute!
Chandler: Well, yeah... 's'no Brian in Payroll.
Shelley: Is Brian...?
Ross:  This one?
Aunt Lillian: No.
Ross: I have shown you everything we have. Unless you want your mother to spend eternity in a lemon yellow pant-suit, go with the burgundy.
Aunt Lillian: You know, whatever we pick, she would've told us it's the wrong one.
Mrs. Geller: You're right. We'll go with the burgundy. LAUGH
Ross: Oh! A fine choice. I'm coming out.
Aunt Lillian: Wait! We need shoes!
Ross: Okay. Um, how about these?
Mrs. Geller: That's really a day shoe. LAUGH
Ross: And where she's going everyone else'll be dressier?
Aunt Lillian: Could we see something in a slimmer heel?
Ross:  Okay, I have nothing in an evening shoe in the burgundy. I can show you something in a silver that may work.
Aunt Lillian: No, it really should be burgundy. LAUGH
Mrs. Geller: Mm. Unless we go with a different dress?
Ross: No! Nonono, wait a sec. I may have something in the back.
SCENE BREAK
LAUGH
Ross:  How we doing, you guys ready?
Monica: Mom already called this morning to remind me not to wear my hair up. Did you know my ears are not my best feature?
Ross: Some days it's all I can think about.
Rachel: Oh, you-you mean your earrings? LAUGH
Phoebe: What'd I say?
Rachel:  Hm-m.
Monica: Are these the shoes?
Rachel: Yes. Paolo sent them from Italy.
SCENE BREAK
LAUGH
Monica: It was a really beautiful service.
Mrs. Geller: It really was. Oh, c'mere, sweetheart.  Y'know, I think it might be time for you to start using night cream.
Joey: What?
Chandler: Nothing, just your overcoat sounds remarkably like Brent Mussberger.
Joey: Check it out, Giants-Cowboys.
Chandler: You're watching a football game at a funeral?
Joey: No, it's the pre-game. I'm gonna watch it at the reception.
Chandler: You are a frightening, frightening man.
Rachel: Oh no! My new Paolo shoes!
Ross: Oh, I hope they're not ruined. LAUGH
Phoebe: God, what a great day. ...What? Weather-wise!
SCENE BREAK
Ross: What, what is it? LAUGH
Phoebe: You missed a belt loop.
Phoebe: Okay, it's in spasm. LAUGH
Mrs. Geller: Here, sweetie, here. I took these when I had my golfing accident. LAUGH
Chandler: Oh, no-
Andrea: Sorry- Hi, I'm Dorothy's daughter.
Chandler: Hi, I'm Chandler, and I have no idea who Dorothy is.
Phoebe: Hey, look who's up! How do you feel?
Ross: I feel great. I feel- great, I fleel great.
Monica: Wow, those pills really worked, huh?
Phoebe: Ooh! That's so nice...
Ross: ...Chandler!
Chandler: Hey.
Ross:  And listen, man, if you wanna be gay, be gay. Doesn't matter to me.
Andrea:
Ross: Rachel. Rachel Rachel.  I love you the most.
Rachel:  Oh, well you know who I love the most?
Ross: No.
Rachel: You!
Ross: Oh.. you don't get it!
Mr. Geller: Whaddya got there?
Joey:  Just a, uh... hearing disability.
Mr. Geller: What's the score? LAUGH
Joey: Seventeen-fourteen Giants... three minutes to go in the third.
Mr. Geller: Beautiful!
Rachel:  Pheebs, could you maybe hand me a cracker?
Mrs. Geller:  Your grandmother would have hated this.
Monica: Well, sure, what with it being her funeral and all.
Mrs. Geller: No, I'd be hearing about 'Why didn't I get the honey-glazed ham?', I didn't spend enough on flowers, and if I spent more she'd be saying 'Why are you wasting your money? I don't need flowers, I'm dead'.
Monica: That sounds like Nana. LAUGH
Mrs. Geller: Do you know what it's like to grow up with someone who is critical of every single thing you say?
Monica: ...I can imagine.
Mrs. Geller: I'm telling you, it's a wonder your mother turned out to be the positive, life-affirming person that she is.
Monica: That is a wonder. So tell me something, Mom. If you had to do it all over again, I mean, if she was here right now, would you tell her?
Mrs. Geller: Tell her what?
Monica: How she drove you crazy, picking on every little detail, like your hair... for example.
Monica: Do you think things would have been better if you'd just told her the truth?
Mrs. Geller: ...No. I think some things are better left unsaid. I think it's nicer when people just get along.
Monica: Huh.
Mrs. Geller: More wine, dear?
Monica: Oh, I think so.
Mrs. Geller:  Those earrings look really lovely on you.
Oh, look. My first grade picture.
Please ignore the Dy-no-mite T-shirt.
SCENE BREAK
Rachel: Hey, who's this little naked guy?
Ross: That little naked guy would be me.
Rachel: Aww, look at the little thing.
Ross: Yes, yes, fine, that is my penis. Can we be grown-ups now?
Chandler: Who are those people?
Ross: Got me.
Monica: Oh, that's Nana, right there in the middle.  'Me and the gang at Java Joe's'.
Rachel: Wow, Monica, you look just like your grandmother. How old was she there?
Monica: Let's see, 1939... yeah, 24, 25?
SCENE BREAK
Chandler: Hey, Lowell.
Lowell: Hey, Chandler.
Chandler: So how's it going there in Financial Services?
Lowell: It's like Mardi Gras without the paper mache heads. How 'bout you?
Lowell: I know. That's what I told her.
Chandler: Really.
Lowell: Yeah.
Chandler: So- you can tell?
Lowell: Pretty much, most of the time. We have a kind of... radar.
Chandler: So you don't think I have a, a quality?
Lowell: Speaking for my people, I'd have to say no. By the way, your friend Brian from Payroll, he is. LAUGH