Monica:
Phoebe: Oh, look at these! Hey, Ben. Just do it.  Oh my God, oh, ok, was that too much pressure for him? LAUGH
Susan: Oh, is he hungry already?
Carol: I guess so.
Chandler: You know, it's...
Joey:  I gotta get one, too.
Ross:  What are you guys doing? LAUGH
Chandler: We're just hanging out by the spoons. Ladle? LAUGH
Ross: Look, would you guys grow up? That is the most natural beautiful thing in the world.
Joey: Yeah, we know, but there's a baby suckin' on it. LAUGH
Ross: This is my son having lunch, ok? It's gonna happen a lot, so you'd better get used to it. Now if you have any problem with it, if you're uncomfortable, just ask questions. Carol's fine with it, now come on.
Ross: Carol?
Chandler: Carol? I was just wondering if Joey could ask you a question about breast-feeding?
Carol: Sure.
Joey: Uh, does it hurt?
Carol: It did at first, but not anymore.
Joey: Chandler?
Chandler: So, uh, how often can you do it?
Carol: As much as he needs.
Joey: Ok, I got one, I got one. Uh, if he blows into one, does the other one get bigger?
Julie: Rachel, do you have any muffins left?
Rachel: Yeah, I forget which ones.
Julie: Oh, you're busy, that's ok, I'll get it. Anybody else want one?
All: No thanks.
Julie:
Rachel:  What a bitch.
Julie: Oh, listen you guys. I have this friend at _Bloomingdale's_ who's quitting tomorrow and he wants to abuse his discount. So, anyone want to come with me and take advantage of it? LAUGH
Phoebe: I can't, I have to take my grandmother to the vet. LAUGH
Monica: Ok, um, I'll go with you.
Julie: Great.
Ross:  Hi, honey.
Chandler: Hey, sweetums. LAUGH
Ross: Hello to the rest.
Joey: Monica what're you doin'? You can't go shopping with her? What about Rachel?
Monica: It's gonna be a problem, isn't it?
Chandler: Come on, you're going to _Bloomingdale's_ with Julie? That's like cheating on Rachel in her house of worship. LAUGH
Phoebe: Monica, she will kill you. She will kill you like a dog in the street. LAUGH
Ross:  So, uh, Jules tells me you guys are going shopping tomorrow?
Monica: Yeah, uh, it's actually not that big a deal.
Ross: It's a big deal to me. This is great, Monica. I really appreciate this.
Monica: You're welcome.
Joey:  Hey Annabelle. LAUGH
Annabelle: Hey, Joey. So did you hear about the new guy? LAUGH
Joey: Who?
Annabelle: Nobody knows his name. Me and the girls just call him the Hombre man.
Hombre Man:
Joey: What's he doin' in my section?
Annabelle: I guess he doesn't know.
Joey: Well, he's gonna. I'll see you a little later, ok?  Hey, how ya doin'?
Hombre Man: Mornin'.
Joey: Listen, I know you're new, but it's kinda understood that everything from Young Men's to the escalator is my territory.
Hombre Man: Your territory, huh? LAUGH
Joey: Yeah. Bijan for men?
Guy: No thanks.
Hombre Man: Hombre?
Guy: Yeah. All right.
Hombre Man:  You were saying? LAUGH
Monica: Phoebe, listen. You were with me, and we were shopping all day. LAUGH
Phoebe: What?
Monica: We were shopping, and we had lunch.
Phoebe: Oh, all right. What did I have?
Monica: You had a salad.
Phoebe: Oh, no wonder I don't feel full.
Rachel:  Hey, guys, what's up.
Phoebe: I went shopping with Monica all day, and I had a salad.
Rachel: Good, Pheebs. What'd you buy?
Phoebe: Um, we went shopping for um, for, fur.
Rachel: You went shopping for fur?
Phoebe: Yes, and then I realized I'm against that, and uh, so then we bought some,  uh, boobs.
Rachel: You bought boobs?
Phoebe:  Bras! We bought bras! We bought bras.
Joey:  Hey, Annabelle, Uh, listen, I was wondering if maybe after work you and I could go maybe grab a cup of coffee.
Annabelle: Oh, actually I sorta have plans.
Hombre Man:  Ready, Annabelle? LAUGH
Annabelle: You bet.  Maybe some other time?
Joey:  Bijan for men?! LAUGH
Carol: Ok, and this is Funny Clown. Funny Clown is only for after his naps, not before his naps or he won't sleep.
Ross: Carol, we've been through this before, ok? We have a good time. We laugh, we play. It's like we're father and son. LAUGH
Susan: Honey, relax. Ross is great with him.  Don't look so surprised. I'm a lovely person.
Rachel: Oh, this is so cute.
Susan: Oh, I got that for him.
Ross: My mommies love me. That's clever. LAUGH
Monica: Hello? Oh, Hi, Ju LAUGH
Rachel: Did you just say Hi, Jew?
Monica: Yes. Uh, yes, I did. That was my friend, Eddie Moskowitz. Yeah, he likes it. Reaffirms his faith.
He's going through
this whole religious thing.
Monica: Yes. Uh, yes, I did. That was my friend, Eddie Moskowitz. Yeah, he likes it. Reaffirms his faith.
Phoebe: Ben, dinner! LAUGH
Ross: Thanks Aunt Pheebs. Hey, you didn't microwave that, did you, because it's breast milk, and you're not supposed to do that.
Phoebe: Duh, I think I know how to heat breast milk. Ok.
Chandler: What did you just do? LAUGH
Phoebe: I licked my arm, what?
Ross: It's breast milk.
Phoebe: So?
Rachel: Phoebe, that is juice, squeezed from a person.
Joey: What is the big deal? LAUGH
Chandler: What did you just do?
Ross: Ok, would people stop drinking the breast milk?
Phoebe: You won't even taste it?
Ross: No!
Phoebe: Not even if you just pretend that it's milk?
Ross: Not even if Carol's breast had a picture of a missing child on it.
Monica: Hey, where is everybody?
Rachel: They took Ben to the park. Where've you been?
Monica: Just out. Had some lunch, just me, little quality time with me. Thanks for your jacket.
Rachel: Oh, no problem. You can borrow it, by the way. LAUGH
Rachel: Mon, if uh you were at lunch alone, how come it cost you uh 53 dollars?
Monica: You know what probably happened? Someone musta stolen my credit card. LAUGH
Rachel: And sorta just put the receipt back in your pocket?
Monica: That is an excellent excellent question. That is excellent. LAUGH
Rachel: Monica, what is with you? Who'd you have lunch with?
Monica: Judy.
Rachel: Who?
Monica: Julie.
Rachel: What?!
Monica: Jody! LAUGH
Rachel: You were with Julie?
Monica: Look, when it started I was just trying to be nice to her because she was my brother's girlfriend. And then, one thing led to another and, before I knew it, we were...shopping. LAUGH
Rachel: Oh. Oh my God.
Monica: Honey, wait. We only did it once. It didn't mean anything to me. LAUGH
Monica: Really, Rachel, I was thinking of you the whole time. Look, I'm sorry, all right. I never meant for you to find out! LAUGH
Rachel: Oh, please, you wanted to get caught.
Monica: That is not true!
Rachel: Oh, so you just sort of happened to leave it in here?
Monica: Did it ever occur to you that I might just be that stupid?
Rachel: Ok, Monica. I just have to know one thing. Did you go with her to _Bloomingdale's_?
Monica:  Hi, Steve. LAUGH
Carol: How did we do?
Phoebe: Oh, I tasted Ben's milk, and Ross freaked out.
Ross: I did not freak out.
Carol: Why'd you freak out?
Ross: Because it's breast milk. It's gross.
Carol: My breast milk is gross?
Susan: This should be fun.
Ross: No, no, Carol. There's nothing wrong with it. I just, I just don't think breast milk is for adults.
Chandler: Of course the packaging does appeal to grown-ups and kids alike.
Carol: Ross, you're being silly. I've tried it, it's no big deal. Just taste it.
Ross:  That would be no.
Come on. Try it.
It's natural.
Phoebe: Come on. It doesn't taste bad.
Joey: Yeah, it's kinda sweet, sorta like, uh...
Susan: Cantaloupe juice.
Joey: Exactly.
Ross:  You've tasted it? You've tasted it.
Ross: Oh, you've tasted it.
Susan: You can keep saying it, but it won't stop being true.
Ross:
Chandler: Howdy.
Joey:  Gimme a box a juice. Well, they switched me over to Hombre.
Chandler: Well, maybe it's because of the way you're dressed.
Joey: Or maybe it's because this guy's doing so good they wanna put more people on it.  You should see this guy, Chandler, he goes through two bottles a day.
Chandler:  What do you care? You're an actor. This is your day job. This isn't supposed to mean anything to you.
Joey: I know, but, I was the best, you know? I liked being the best.  I don't know. Maybe I should just get outta the game. They need guys up in housewares to serve cheese.
Chandler:  All right, say you do that. You know sooner or later somebody's gonna come along that slices a better cheddar. And then where're you gonna run?
Joey: Yeah I guess you're right.
Chandler: You're damn right I'm right. I say you show this guy what you're made of. I say you stand your ground. I say you show him that you are the baddest hombre west of the lingerie.
Joey: I'm gonna do it.
Chandler: All right. Now go see Miss Kitty and she'll fix you up with a nice hooker.
Monica: I don't know what else to say.
Rachel: Well that works out good, because I'm not listening.
Monica: I feel terrible, I really do.
Rachel: Oh, I'm sorry, did my back hurt your knife?
Monica: Rachel,  say that I'm friends with her, we spend some time together. Is that so terrible?
Monica: It's that terrible?
Rachel: Yes. Monica, you don't get it. It's bad enough that she's stolen the guy who might actually be the person that I am supposed to be with, but now, she's actually , but now she's actually stealing you.
Monica: Me? What are you talking about? Nobody could steal me from you. I mean, just because I'm friends with her doesn't make me any less friends with you. I mean,  you're my...We're, we're...Oh, I love you.
Rachel: I love you too.
Phoebe: You guys, um I know that this really doesn't have anything to do with me, but um I love you guys too.
Monica: Look, I know that you're in a place right now where you really need to hate Julie's guts, but she didn't do anything wrong. I mean, she was just a girl who met a guy, and now they go out. I really think that if you gave her a chance, you'd like her. Would you just give that a chance, for me?
Rachel:  I'd do anything for you, you know that.
Monica:
Phoebe: Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Joey: Mornin'.  I said, mornin'.
Hombre Man: I heard ya.
Store Guy: All right, everybody, I'm openin' the doors. You boys ready?
Hombre Man: Ready.
Joey: Yeah, I'm ready.
Customer: You idiot, you stupid cowboy, you blinded me, I'm suing!
Store Guy: Oh my god, Todd! What the hell did you do?
Hombre Man: I'm sorry. I am such a doofus. I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
Annabelle:  My god, what happened?
Joey: These new kids, they never last. Sooner or later, they all...stop lastin'. Listen, uh, what do you say I buy you that cup of coffee now?
Annabelle: Sure.
Julie: So.
Rachel: So. I just thought the two of us should hang out for a bit. I mean, you know, we've never really talked. I guess you'd know that, being one of the two of us, though, right?
Julie: I know, I probably shouldn't even tell you this, but I'm pretty much totally intimidated by you.
Rachel: Really? Me?
Julie: Yes. Oh my god, are you kidding? Ross is so crazy about you, and I really wanted you to like me, and, it's probably me being totally paranoid, but I kinda got the feeling that maybe you don't.
Rachel: Well, you're not totally paranoid.
Rachel: Um, ok, uh, oh god, um, when you and uh Ross first started going out, it was really hard for me, um, for many reasons, which I'm not gonna bore you with now, but um, I just, I see how happy he is, you know, and how good you guys are together, and um, Monica's always saying how nice you are, and god I hate it when she's right.
Julie: Thanks. Hey, listen, would you like to go to a movie sometime or something?
Rachel: Yeah, that'd be great. I'd love it.
Julie: I'd love it too. Shoot, I gotta go. So, I'll talk to you later.
Rachel: All right, Julie.
Rachel: Bye.  What a manipulative bitch.
Ross:  That's not bad. LAUGH