ROSS: Man, I sure miss Julie.
CHANDLER: Spanish midgets. Spanish midgets wrestling. Julie. Ok, yes, I see how you got there. LAUGH
ROSS: You ever figure out what that thing's for? LAUGH
CHANDLER: No, see, I'm trying this new screening thing. You know, I figure if I'm always answering the phone, people'll think I don't have a life. My god, Rodrigo never gets pinned.
people will think I have no life.
My God! LAUGH
Rodrigo is never pinned!
After the beep,
you know what to do.
: Here comes the beep, you know what to do.
I was thinking about how great it was.
I know it's been three years but I was hoping LAUGH
we could hook up again.
I barely had the nerve
to call... LAUGH
-...so you know what I did?.
JADE: Hello, I'm looking for Bob. This is Jane. I don't know if you're still at this number, but I was just thinking about us, and how great it was, and, well, I know it's been three years, but, I was kinda hoping we could hook up again. I barely had t he nerve to make this call, so you know what I did?
CHANDLER: What? LAUGH
JADE: I got a little drunk...and naked.
CHANDLER: Bob here. LAUGH
CHANDLER:  What've you been up to?
And in case you wondered those are my legs on
the new James Bond poster.
JADE: Oh, you know, the usual, teaching aerobics, partying way too much. Oh, and in case you were wondering, those are my legs on the new James Bond poster.
CHANDLER: Can you hold on a moment? I have another call.  I love her.
ROSS: I know.
CHANDLER: I'm back.
JADE: So, are we gonna get together or what?
5-ish?
CHANDLER: Um, absolutely. Uh, how 'bout tomorrow afternoon? Do you know uh, Central Perk in the Village, say, five-ish?
JADE: Great, I'll see you then.
CHANDLER: Ok. Ok. Having a phone has finally paid off.
hey, you're not Bob.
You see Tattoo.... LAUGH
Jade's fantasy is to rekindle
the love she had with Bob.
My fantasy is that you
talk like a normal person.
ROSS: Even though you do do a good Bob impression, I'm thinkin' when she sees you tomorow, she's probably gonna realize, "hey, you're not Bob." LAUGH
of the wry stranger at the next table.
CHANDLER: I'm hoping that when Bob doesn't show up, she will seek comfort in the open arms of the wry stranger at the next table. LAUGH
ROSS: Oh my god. You are pure evil.
CHANDLER: Ok, pure evil, horny and alone. I've done this. LAUGH
ROSS:  Yeah, yeah, everybody's here. Hey, everybody, say hi to Julie in New Mexico.
ALL: Hi, Julie!
RACHEL:  Hi, Julie. LAUGH
CHANDLER: Ok, while Ross is on the phone, everybody owes me 62 bucks for his birthday. LAUGH
PHOEBE: Um, is, is there any chance that you're rounding up? You know, like from, like 20? LAUGH
CHANDLER: Hey, come on, we got the gift, the concert, and the cake.
JOEY: Do we need a cake?
RACHEL: Yeah, whoosh!
CHANDLER: But it's Ross. LAUGH
PHOEBE: It's Ross.
I know.
All right.
JOEY: All right. LAUGH
CHANDLER: I'll see you guys later, I gotta go...do a thing.
You're not going through with this,
are you?
You know, I think I might just. LAUGH
CHANDLER: You know, I think I might just. LAUGH
RACHEL: So uh, what are you guys doing for dinner tonight?
I guess I'll stay home
and eat dust bunnies.
JOEY: Well I guess I gotta start savin' up for Ross's birthday, so I guess I'll just stay home and eat dust bunnies.
PHOEBE: Can you believe how much this is gonna cost?
that we don't make that much money?
RACHEL: Do you guys ever get the feeling that um, Chandler and those guys just don't get that we don't make as much money as they do? LAUGH
Really?
RACHEL: Do you guys ever get the feeling that um, Chandler and those guys just don't get that we don't make as much money as they do?
Like we can afford to go
here and there.
JOEY: Yes! Yeah, it's like they're always saying "let's go here, let's go there". Like we can afford to go here and there.
And we can't say anything about it,
because this is a birthday for Ross.
PHOEBE: Yes, yes, and it's, and we always have to go to, you know, someplace nice, you know? God, and it's not like we can say anything about it, 'cause, like this birthday thing, it's for Ross.
JOEY: For Ross. LAUGH
RACHEL: For Ross, Ross, Ross.
MONICA:  Oh my god.
RACHEL: What? LAUGH
The manager calls me into his office.
They fired the lunch chef.
Guess who got it?
MONICA: I'm at work, ordinary day, you know, chop chop chop, sauti, sauti, sauti. All of a sudden, Leon, the manager, calls me into his office. It turns out they fired the head lunch chef, and guess who got the job. LAUGH
JOEY: If it's not you, this is a horrible story.
That's so cool!
Anyway, I think we
should go out and celebrate. LAUGH
MONICA: Fortunately, it is me. And, they made me head of purchasing, thank you very much. Anyway, I just ran into Ross and Chandler downstairs, and they think we should go out and celebrate. You know, someplace nice.
Someplace nice. LAUGH
How much you think
I can get for my kidney?
JOEY: Yeah, someplace nice. LAUGH
ROSS: I'm tellin' you. You can't do this.
conventional methods.
CHANDLER: Oh, come on. I can never get a girl like that with conventional methods.
Bob could be
who she was meant to be with.
You may be destroying
a chance for happiness. LAUGH
We don't know Bob.
Okay, we know me. We like me.
Please let me be happy.
CHANDLER: We don't know Bob, ok? We know me. We like me. Please let me be happy. LAUGH
ROSS: Go over there and tell that woman the truth.
CHANDLER: All right. LAUGH
ROSS: Go.
CHANDLER: Hi.
JADE: Hi. LAUGH
CHANDLER: Listen, I have to, uh, um, I have to, I have to confess something.
JADE: Yes?
CHANDLER: Whoever stood you up is a jerk. LAUGH
JADE: How did you--?
that's me, I'm weird and sensitive.
Tissue?
CHANDLER: I don't know. I just had this weird sense. You know, but that's me. I'm weird and sensitive. Tissue?
JADE: Thanks. LAUGH
CHANDLER: No, you keep the pack. I'm all cried out today. LAUGH
ROSS: Ok, ok, here is to my sister, the newly-appointed head lunch chef--
MONICA: Who is also in charge of purchasing. LAUGH
ROSS: Newly appointed head lunch chef who is also in charge of purchasing--
MONICA: Who has her own little desk when Roland's not there.
ROSS: Uh, lunch chef, purchasing, own little desk when Roland's not there. Here's to my little sister--
MONICA: Oh, wait, and I got a beeper!
JOEY: Cool.
PHOEBE: Let's see!
ROSS: That's fine, I'll just wait! LAUGH
JOEY: Sorry, sorry.
ROSS: Monica!
WAITER: Are we ready to order?
RACHEL: Oh, you know what, we haven't even looked yet. LAUGH
WAITER: Well, when you do, just let me know. I'll be right over there on the edge of my seat.
PHOEBE: Wow, look at these prices.
RACHEL: Yeah, these are pretty ch-ching. LAUGH
JOEY: What are these, like famous chickens?
Thanks.
I'm not sorry. How incredible
was my afternoon with Jade?
CHANDLER: Hey, sorry I'm late. Congratulations, Mon.  I'm not sorry I'm late. How incredible was my afternoon with Jade?
Why is this woman leaving a message
for you on my machine?
ROSS: Well, pretty incredible according to the message she left you on my machine. Hey, Chandler, why is this woman leaving a message for you on my machine?
my number is Bob's number.
Tell me again.
CHANDLER: Oh, see, I had to tell her that my number was your number, because I couldn't tell her that my number was my number because she thinks that my number is Bob's number.
ROSS: Hey, tell me again, what do I do when Mr. Roper calls?
WAITER: Do I dare ask?
MONICA: Yes, I will start with the carpaccio, and then I'll have the grilled prawns.
ROSS: That sounds great. Same for me.
WAITER: And for the gentleman?
and leeks and stuff, is it cheaper?
JOEY: Yeah, I'll have the Thai chicken pizza. But, hey, look, if I get it without the nuts and leeks and stuff, is it cheaper?
WAITER: You'd think, wouldn't you? Miss?
RACHEL: Ok, I will have the uh,  side salad. LAUGH
WAITER:  And what will that be on the side of?
RACHEL: Uh, I don't know. Why don't you put it right here next to my water? LAUGH
WAITER: And for you?
PHOEBE: Um, I'm gonna have a cup of the cucumber soup, and, um, take care. LAUGH
CHANDLER: I will have the uh, Cajun catfish.
WAITER: Anything else? LAUGH
in my fish, aren't you?
Does anybody else feel like LAUGH
they just gave birth to an alien?
No!
CHANDLER: Yes, how 'bout a verse of Killing Me Softly. You're gonna sneeze on my fish, aren't you? LAUGH
ROSS:  Plus tip, divided by six. Ok, everyone owes 28 bucks.
RACHEL: Um, everyone?
ROSS: Oh, you're right, I'm sorry.
JOEY: Thank you. LAUGH
ROSS: Monica's big night, she shouldn't pay.
MONICA: Oh, thank you!
ROSS: So five of us is, $33.50 apiece.
PHOEBE: No, huh uh, no way, I'm sorry, not gonna happen.
CHANDLER: Whoa, whoa, prom night flashback. LAUGH
for 30-something bucks? No! LAUGH
PHOEBE: I'm sorry, Monica, I'm really happy you got promoted, but cold cucumber mush for thirty-something bucks? No! Rachel just had that, that, that salad, and, and Joey with his like teeny pizza! It's just...
Joey with a teeny pizza! It's just....
Okay, Pheebs.
How about we'll each pay for
what we had? It's no big deal.
ROSS: Ok, Pheebs! How 'bout we'll each just pay for what we had. It's no big deal. LAUGH
PHOEBE: Not for you.
MONICA: All right, what's goin' on?
JOEY: Yeah.
CHANDLER: You can tell us. LAUGH
Yeah.
ROSS: Hello, it's us, all right? It'll be fine. LAUGH
We don't have LAUGH
as much money as you.
JOEY: Ok, um, uh, we three feel like, that uh, sometimes you guys don't get that uh, we don't have as much money as you.
MONICA: Ok.
ROSS: I hear ya.
CHANDLER: We can talk about that. LAUGH
Fine.
PHOEBE: Well, then...Let's.
ROSS: I, I just never think of money as an issue.
RACHEL: That's 'cause you have it.
ROSS: That's a good point.
CHANDLER: So um, how come you guys haven't talked about this before?
JOEY: 'Cause it's always somethin', you know, like Monica's new job, or the whole Ross's birthday hoopla. LAUGH
There's gonna be a hoopla?
ROSS: Wha--? Whoa, hey, I don't want my birthday to be the source of any kind of negative--there's gonna be a hoopla? LAUGH
RACHEL: Basically, there's the thing, and then there's the stuff after the thing.
MONICA: If it makes anybody feel better, then we can just forget the thing, and we'll just do the gift.
ROSS: G-gift? The thing's not the gift?
CHANDLER: No, the thing was, we were gonna go see Hootie and the Blowfish.
ROSS: Hootie and the--oh my. I, I can catch them on the radio.
PHOEBE: No, now I feel bad. You wanna go to the concert. LAUGH
ROSS: No, look, hey, it's my birthday, and the important thing is that we all be together.
CHANDLER: Together.
ROSS: Not at the concert.
JOEY: Yeah. LAUGH
RACHEL: Thank you.
JOEY: Thanks.
PHOEBE: Yeah. LAUGH
CHANDLER: So, the ebola virus. That's gotta suck, huh? LAUGH
CHANDLER: Gee, Monica, what's in the bag?
MONICA: I don't know, Chandler. Let's take a look.
PHOEBE: Oh, it's like a skit. LAUGH
PHOEBE: Cool.
MONICA: Yeah, we switched meat suppliers at work, and the new guys gave me the steaks as sort of a thank-you.
ROSS: But wait, there's more. Hey, Chandler, what is in the envelope? LAUGH
ROSS: Come on. LAUGH
CHANDLER: Why, it's six tickets to Hootie and the Blowfish! The Blowfish! LAUGH
MONICA: It's on us, all right, so don't worry. It's our treat.
PHOEBE: So...Thank you.
ROSS: Could you be less enthused?
JOEY: Look, it's a nice gesture, it is. But it just feels like--
MONICA: Like? LAUGH
JOEY: Charity.
MONICA: Charity?
ROSS: We're just tryin' to do a nice thing here.
RACHEL: Ross, you have to understand that your nice thing makes us feel this big.
PHOEBE: Actually, it makes us feel that big. LAUGH
ROSS: I don't, I don't understand. I mean, you, it's like we can't win with you guys.
CHANDLER: If you guys feel this big, maybe that's not our fault. Maybe that's just how you feel. LAUGH
JOEY: Oh, now you're tellin' us how you feel.
RACHEL: Ok, we never shoulda talked about this.
Just not in a Hootie place right now. LAUGH
PHOEBE: I'm just gonna pass on the concert, 'cause I'm just not in a very Hootie place right now.
RACHEL: Me neither.
JOEY: Me too. LAUGH
MONICA: Guys, we bought the tickets.
for all your tiaras and stuff.
PHOEBE: Oh, well, then you'll have extra seats, you know, for all your tiaras and stuff. LAUGH
CHANDLER: Why did you look at me when you said that?
MONICA: Well, I guess now we can't go. LAUGH
RACHEL: What? Come on, you do what you want to do. Do we always have to do everything together?
MONICA: You know what? You're right.
RACHEL: Fine.
MONICA: All right. We're gonna go. It's not for another six hours. We're gonna go then. LAUGH
ROSS: Chandler! LAUGH
CHANDLER: Yeah?
ROSS: Geez! Are you ready?
CHANDLER: Yeah. Just let me grab my jacket and tell you I had sex today.
ROSS: Whoa! You had sex today? LAUGH
to stop from screaming.
CHANDLER: Wow, it sounds even cooler when somebody else says it. I was awesome, ok? She was biting her lip to stop from screaming.
ROSS: Wow.
CHANDLER: Now I know it's been awhile, but I took it as a good sign.
ROSS: Still doing the screening thing? LAUGH
CHANDLER: I had sex today. I never have to answer that phone again.
MACHINE: Here comes the beep, you know what to do.
when you didn't show up. LAUGH
And just so you know,
I ended up meeting a guy.
JADE: Hey, Bob, it's Jade. Listen, I just wanted to tell you that I was really hurt when you didn't show up the other day, and just so you know, I ended up meeting a guy.
CHANDLER: Bob here. LAUGH
JADE: Oh, hi.
CHANDLER: So, uh, you met someone, huh? LAUGH
JADE: Yes, yes, I did. In fact, I had sex with him 2 hours ago.
CHANDLER: So, uh, how was he?
JADE: Eh. LAUGH
CHANDLER: Eh?
screaming your name.
JADE: Oh, Bob, he was nothing compared to you. I had to bite my lip to keep from screaming your name. LAUGH
CHANDLER: Well, that makes me feel so good.
ROSS:  Bumpy?
Maybe get used to it.
CHANDLER: Well, maybe he had some kind of uh, new, cool style, that you're not familiar with. And uh maybe you have to get used to it. LAUGH
JADE: Well there really wasn't much time to get used to it, you know what I mean? LAUGH
MONICA: You know what? I'm not gonna be able to enjoy this.
ROSS: Yeah, I know, it's my birthday. We all should be here.
CHANDLER: So, let's go.
ROSS: Well maybe, you know, maybe we should stay for one song.
CHANDLER: Yeah, I mean, it would be rude to them for us to leave now.
MONICA: You know, the guys are probably having a great time.
JOEY: Come on you guys, one more time.
PHOEBE: Ok. One.
JOEY: Nooo. LAUGH
MONICA: That was amazing!
ROSS: Excellent, that was excellent.
CHANDLER: I can't believe the guys missed this. LAUGH
ROSS: What guys? Oh, yeah.
STEVE: Excuse me, you're Monica Geller aren't you?
MONICA: Do I know you?
STEVE: You used to be my babysitter. LAUGH
MONICA: Oh my god, little Stevie Fisher? How've you been?
STEVE: Good, good, I'm a lawyer now. LAUGH
MONICA: You can't be a lawyer. You're eight.
STEVE: Listen, it was nice to see you. I gotta run backstage.
MONICA: Uh, wait, backstage? LAUGH
STEVE: Oh, yeah, my firm represents the band.
ROSS: Ross.
CHANDLER: Chandler.
Yeah!
that fooled around with my dad?
STEVE: How are you? Look, you guys wanna meet the group? Come on. So, are you one of the ones who fooled around with my dad? LAUGH
ROSS: Hey, you guys.
RACHEL: Happy birthday.
ROSS: Oh, thank you, thanks. So uh, how was your night last night? LAUGH
RACHEL: Oh, well, it pretty much sucked. How was yours?
MONICA: Yeah, ours pretty much sucked, oh, but, I did run into little Stevie Fisher. Remember him? LAUGH
RACHEL: Oh yeah. I used to babysit him. Hey, how's his dad?
MONICA: Uh, good.
ROSS: Uh, aside from that, the whole evening was pretty much a bust.
CHANDLER: Yeah, we really missed you guys.
JOEY: Yeah, look, we were just saying, this whole thing is really stupid. LAUGH
Is that a hickey?
PHOEBE: We just have to really, really, really, not let stuff like money get-- is that a hickey? LAUGH
MONICA: No, I just, I fell down.
RACHEL: On someone's lips? Where'd you get the hickey?
MONICA: You know, a party, or--
RACHEL: What party?
ROSS: It wasn't so much a party as...a gathering of people, with food, and music, and, and the band.
JOEY: You partied with Hootie and the Blowfish?
CHANDLER: Yes, apparently Stevie and the band are like this.
RACHEL: Who gave you that hickey?
RACHEL: Oh!
and having fun and all:
''Hey, Blowfish, suck on my neck!''
PHOEBE: Oh! I can't believe it. I can't believe this. We're just like, sitting at home, trying to guess Joey's fingers, and you guys are out like partying and having fun, and you know, all, "hey, Blowfish, suck on my neck".
ROSS: Look, don't blame us. You guys coulda been there, you know.
RACHEL: What, as part of your poor friends outreach program?
MONICA: It's work.
We're not gonna feel guilty.
We work hard.
CHANDLER: I don't know what to say. I'm sorry that we make more money than you. But we're not gonna feel guilty about it. We work really hard for it.
JOEY: And we don't work hard?
MONICA:  Yeah, hi, it's Monica. I just got a page.
CHANDLER: I'm just saying that sometimes we like to do stuff that costs a little more.
JOEY: And you feel like we hold you back.
CHANDLER: Yes.
CHANDLER: No. LAUGH
That was not a kickback.
I'll just replace them and we can forget the whole thing.
What corporate policy?
No--
Yeah.
Okay.
I just got fired.
PHOEBE: Oh. LAUGH
WAITRESS: Here's your check. That'll be $4.12. LAUGH
JOEY: Let me get that.  You got five bucks? LAUGH
MACHINE: Here comes the beep, you know what to do. LAUGH
I'm probably way out of line here. LAUGH
It's been three years,
and you're probably seeing someone but if we could have one night,
for old times' sake....
One hot, steamy, wild night.... LAUGH