JOEY: Alright, no peeking. No peeking, no peeking, no peeking.
CHANDLER: Alright, alright, but you better be wearing clothes when I open my eyes. LAUGH
JOEY: Alright open your eyes.
CHANDLER: Sweet mother of all that is good and pure. LAUGH
JOEY: Huh? _Days of our Lives_ picked up my option.
CHANDLER: Congratulations!
chandler: Now we can finally watch _Green Acres_ the way it was meant to be seen. LAUGH
CHANDLER: So uh, which one is mine?
JOEY: Whichever one you want, man. Whichever one you want.  Not that one.
Whichever one you want!
Not that one. LAUGH
Oh, yes!
JOEY:  Ohh yeah, that's the stuff. LAUGH
Do we dare?
We dare.
LAUGH
PHOEBE: I can't believe two cows made the ultimate sacrifice so you guys could watch TV with your feet up.
in the wild.
CHANDLER: Well they were chair-shaped cows. They never would have survived in the wild.
ALL: Woah! LAUGH
MONICA: Rose Marie really belongs on a smaller screen, doesn't she?
RACHEL: Hi you guys.
Hey, you.
CHANDLER and JOEY: Woah, hey, yo.
RACHEL: So, uh, how was your day?
ROSS: Oh you know, pretty much the usual, uh, sun shining, birds chirping.
RACHEL: Really? Mine too. LAUGH
PHOEBE: Hey cool, mine too.
ROSS:  Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got to get to the museum. So um, I'll see you tonight.
RACHEL: OK.
ALL: Bye.
CHANDLER and JOEY: Hey, yo. LAUGH
MONICA: What's tonight?
RACHEL: It is our first official date. Our first date.
MONICA: Uh, hello. LAUGH
RACHEL: Hi.
MONICA: Tonight you're supposed to waitress for me, my catering thing, any of those words trigger anything for you? LAUGH
RACHEL: God, oh God Monica, I forgot. This is our first date.
MONICA: Yes but my mom got me this job.
PHOEBE: OK, I can be a waitress, I can be a waitress.
See? Phoebe! Phoebe!
RACHEL: Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you. See Phoebe, Phoebe.
MONICA: Really Phoebs? Because, you know, you'd have to be an actual waitress. This can't be like your 'I can be a bear cub' thing. LAUGH
I can be a waitress. Watch this.
Give me two number ones, 86 the bacon.
One Adam and Eve on a raft
and wreck them!
LAUGH
PHOEBE: It's James Bond.
MONICA: Sorry we're late.
I was told she was. LAUGH
Dr. Burke, it's me.
MONICA: Dr. Burke, it, it's me. LAUGH
DR. BURKE: Monica? My God you used to be so. . . I mean you, you, you, you must have lost like. . . You look great.
MONICA: Thank you. This is my friend Phoebe. She's gonna be helping me tonight.
How you been? LAUGH
DR. BURKE: Hi Phoebe, nice to meet you.  So, how ya been?
MONICA: I've been great, just great. How have you been?
DR. BURKE: Oh, well obviously you know Barbara and I split up, otherwise you wouldn't have done the head tilt.
MONICA: The head tilt?
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Believe me, I do it too.
I always answer with the
''I'm okay'' head bob. ''I'm okay.'' LAUGH
''You're sure?''
''Yeah, I'm fine.''
I gotta set up the music.
I got a new CD changer.
The divorce only left
me with four CDs to change.
That's too bad.
I'll survive.
Two larges, extra cheese on both. LAUGH
But listen don't ring the buzzer for 1 9.
Ring 20. Geller/Greene.
They'll let you in, okay?
If you buzz our door,
there's no tip for you. LAUGH
Okay, thanks.
Pizza's on the way.
I told you we wouldn't have to get up.
What if we have to pee? LAUGH
I'll cancel the sodas.
Get out there. LAUGH
It's your party!
They're so dull!
They're all ophthalmologists.
You're an ophthalmologist.
That's what my parents wanted.
I wanted to be a sheriff.
That's funny. Cadillac, cataract.
I get it.
No! You stay out there! LAUGH
You see?
I tell you what.
DR. BURKE: See.
with some sort of kebab emergency. LAUGH
MONICA: Alright, I'll tell you what. I'll come get you in 5 minutes with some sort of um, kabob emergency.
Watch this.
Who needs glasses?
DR. BURKE: OK. You better. Oh God, here we go. Hey wanna see 'em go nuts? Watch this. LAUGH
PHOEBE: You are so smitten.
MONICA: I am not. LAUGH
Dr. Burke?
PHOEBE: Oh, you are so much the smitten kitten. You should ask him out. LAUGH
MONICA: Dr. Burke? I don't think so. I mean, like, he's a grown up.
PHOEBE: So. You two are totally into each other.
MONICA: Phoebe, he's a friend of my parents. He's like 20 years older than me.
PHOEBE: OK, so what, you're just never gonna see him again?
MONICA: Not never. I mean, I'm gonna see him tomorrow at my eye appointment. LAUGH
PHOEBE: Didn't you like, just get your eyes checked? LAUGH
They're picking teams to play
''Guess my prescription.'' Help me!
LAUGH
RACHEL: C'mon, I'm not saying it was a bad movie, I'm just saying, you know, it was a little. . . hard to follow. LAUGH
ROSS: I told you there was going to be sub-titles.
RACHEL: I know, I just didn't want to wear my glasses on my first date.
RACHEL: Monica. LAUGH
ROSS: It would really help when I'm kissing you if you didn't shout out my sister's name.
ROSS: Oh.
RACHEL: Monica.
ROSS: Mon. LAUGH
ROSS: What, what.
down to my butt it was, like,
''Whoa! Ross's hands are on my butt!'' LAUGH
And that's funny. Why?
Well, it's not. LAUGH
ROSS: And that's, that's funny why?
I mean, it's you. You know, it's us.
We're crossing that line.
It's sort of a big thing.
RACHEL: Well it's not, honey I'm sorry, I guess I'm just nervous. I mean, it's you, ya know, it's us. I mean, we're crossing that line, sort of a big thing. LAUGH
RACHEL: OK.
ROSS: OK, my hands were no where near your butt. LAUGH
I was thinking about
the last time they were there.
I'm sorry. Look! I promise.
I won't laugh anymore.
Put your hands back.
No, see, now I can't.
I'm feeling too self-conscious.
Touch my butt.
Just one cheek.
The moment's gone. LAUGH
I'll back up into your hands.
That's romantic.
-Touch it.
-No.
-Come on, squeeze it.
-No!
-Rub it?
-No.
Oh, come on!
Would you just grab my ass?
Wow! Look at that! LAUGH
its expensive paint job is protected by the Miracle Wax.
JOEY: Wow, look at that. The car is on fire, yet somehow it's expensive paint job is protected by the Miracle Wax. LAUGH
CHANDLER and JOEY: Hey. LAUGH
JOEY: What're you doin' here? Aren't you supposed to be out with Rachel?
We gotta set the clock on this. LAUGH
So how'd it go?
CHANDLER: So how'd it go?
fooling around with a girl and she started laughing?
ROSS: Oh. Listen, have you ever been uh, you know, foolin' around with a girl and uh, she started laughin'? LAUGH
CHANDLER: Yeah, but uh, it was 1982 and my flock of seagulls haircut was tickling her chin.
It could have been worse.
I could have been naked. LAUGH
I've wanted this since 9th grade.
I want it to be perfect and right and....
Why isn't that laser
cutting through the paint?
ROSS: Yeah. I don't know, I've been wanting this since like ninth grade typing, ya know. And I just want it to be perfect and right and. . . why isn't that laser beam cutting through the paint? LAUGH
CHANDLER: It's the Miracle Wax.
Hi, you guys.
Hey.
ROSS: Hey.
RACHEL: Hi. Listen, I was um, thinkin' about. . . LAUGH
Hallway?
Yeah.
CHANDLER: Listen can you guys uh, speak up, it's harder for us to hear you when you lower your voice. LAUGH
RACHEL: OK, listen, I'm sorry about last night and I really want to make it up to you. LAUGH
ROSS: No, you, ya know there's no need to make it u. . . how?
And then maybe going
back to my place for dessert.
That sounds perfect.
What's this? LAUGH
RACHEL: What's this.
LAUGH
DR. BURKE: I'm going to look into your eyes now.
MONICA: Really.
Look into the light.
Now look at me.
Okay! LAUGH
Your eyes look good.
Those are good eyes.
DR. BURKE: Yeah, that's my job. Alright, look up. . . look down, now open your eyes, now look down. That's right, look into the light. Now look at me. . . OK. Your eyes look good. Those are good eyes.
MONICA: Good, they feel good, in my head.
DR. BURKE: So, it's great to see ya.
DR. BURKE: You too.
MONICA: OK, um. Goodbye.
DR. BURKE: Drops!
MONICA: What?
DR. BURKE: Drops. Here, they're free. LAUGH
MONICA: Thanks. So, I guess I better be going.
DR. BURKE: Oh, OK, yeah. I'll see ya later.
CHANDLER and JOEY: Hey, woah, hey, woah. LAUGH
PHOEBE: You know you should go outside and be with the three-dimensional people. LAUGH
JOEY: No, inside good, outside bad. LAUGH
PHOEBE: You guys are so pathetic, I, oh, OH, XANADU! OH. LAUGH
CHANDLER: She's one of us now.
RACHEL: Hi you guys.
CHANDLER, JOEY, and PHOEBE: Hey. LAUGH
ROSS: Well we just wanted to stop by and uh, say goodnight.
CHANDLER, JOEY, and PHOEBE: Goodnight.
ROSS: Look at that, they won't even turn their heads.
RACHEL: Alright you guys, I'm takin' off my shirt. LAUGH
JOEY:  Naa, she's lyin'. LAUGH
MONICA: Stop sending food to our apartment.
ROSS: Well, why're you all dressed up?
PHOEBE: You're not the only one who has a date tonight.
ROSS: What? You have a date? Who with?
MONICA: No one.
ROSS: C'mon, what's his name?
MONICA: Nothing.
ROSS: Come on, tell me.
Promise you won't get
big-brothery and judgmental.
MONICA: Alright, but I'm very excited about this OK, so you gotta promise you won't get all big-brothery and judgmental.
ROSS: Oh, I promise, what.
MONICA: It's Richard Burke.
Dr. Burke?
You have a date with Dr. Burke? LAUGH
Why? Why? Why should that bother me?
I love that man.
He's like a a brother to Dad.
Here we go. LAUGH
No, I think it's great that he's 50.
He'll be an inspiration to men who are
almost retired all over the world. LAUGH
He's the brightest, most sophisticated,
sexiest man I've ever been with.
MONICA: Well for your information he happens to be one of the brightest, most sophisticated, sexiest men I've ever been with.
ROSS: Doctor Burke is sexy? LAUGH
Damn!
It's the museum again.
Can I--?
Dr. Burke kissed me once.
RACHEL: Ya know, Dr. Burke kissed me once.
MONICA: When?
he kissed me right here.
RACHEL: When I was um, 7, I crashed my bike right out in front of his house and to stop me from crying he kissed me right here.
PHOEBE: Oh you are so lucky.
Australopithecus isn't supposed LAUGH
to be in that display.
No, Homo habilis was erect.
Australopithecus was never fully erect.
Well, maybe he was nervous.
Oh, look!
I can't believe this!
Homo habilis can't use tools yet,
and he has clay pots?
Why don't they just
give him a microwave?
Clearly he'd have no place
to plug it in.
Sorry. LAUGH
I'm sorry this is taking so long.
It's longer than I expected.
We will have dinner.
It's fine.
Karl! LAUGH
Oh, God.
LAUGH
MONICA: Wow, is that Michelle?
DR. BURKE: Yep.
she got so dru--
Emotional.
MONICA: I've not seen her since high school graduation. Oh my God, that night she got so dru. . . motional. LAUGH
DR. BURKE: Ya know, she's having another baby.
MONICA: I thought she just had one.
and everything. Here.
He told me he liked me
better than his other grandpa.
In all fairness, his other
grandpa's a drunk, but still.... LAUGH
You're a grandpa.
Yeah.
Are we nuts here?
I don't know. Maybe.
DR. BURKE: Yeah. Are we nuts here? LAUGH
MONICA: I don't know, maybe. I mean I'm dating a man who's pool I once peed in.
Hell, I'm a whole ''person
who can drink'' older than you. LAUGH
DR. BURKE: I didn't need to know that. I guess 21 years is a lot. I mean, hell, I'm a whole person who can drink older than you.
MONICA: Yeah.
DR. BURKE: So.
MONICA: So maybe we should just. . .
DR. BURKE: Yeah, yeah, maybe.
MONICA: Wow, this really sucks.
DR. BURKE: Yeah, it sure does.
MONICA: Well, we don't really have to decide anything right now, do we?
DR. BURKE: No, no, there's no rush or anything.
DELIVERY GUY: Pizza delivery. LAUGH
RACHEL: Oh.
ROSS: I'm done.
RACHEL: Yeah well, you know what, so is uh, Sorentino's.
ROSS: Wha, OK, I'm sorry, let's uh, why don't we find someplace else.
We'll do it again.
RACHEL: No, you know what, it's late, everything's gonna be closed. Why don't we just do it another night?
ROSS: No, no, we won't.
RACHEL: We won't?
ROSS:  C'mon.
RACHEL: What is this? What are we doing?
ROSS: Shh. Do you want cran-apple or cran-grape?
RACHEL: Grape.
ROSS:
Billions of years ago,
Earth was only--
Sorry.
ROSS: Sorry. LAUGH
RACHEL: Ah, so what are we looking at? LAUGH
That is Ursa Major.
Really?
RACHEL: Really? LAUGH
ROSS: I've no idea, could be. Listen, I'm sorry I had to work tonight.
RACHEL: Oh it's OK. You were worth the wait, and I don't just mean tonight. LAUGH
ROSS: You're not laughing.
Loosen the knot.
Oh, God!
Honey? That's okay.
What?
RACHEL: Ah, oh God. Oh, honey, oh that's OK.
ROSS: What. Oh no, you just rolled over the juice box.
ROSS: Hi.
RACHEL: Hi you. I can't believe I'm waking up next to you.
ROSS: I know it is pretty unbelievaaaaah.
RACHEL: What?
JOEY: Is that the fire alarm?
CHANDLER: Yeah.  Oh it's not warm yet, we still have time.
-Yeah, yeah. Cool! LAUGH