JOEY: Man this is weird. You ever realize Captain Crunch's eyebrows are actually on his hat?
CHANDLER: That's what's weird? Joey, the man's been captain of a cereal for the last 40 years. LAUGH
JOEY: What?
CHANDLER: The spoon. You licked and-and you put. You licked and you put. LAUGH
JOEY: Yeah, so.
CHANDLER: Well don't you see how gross that is? I mean that's like you using my toothbrush.  You used my toothbrush? LAUGH
You used my toothbrush!
JOEY: Well, that was only 'cause I used the red one to unclog the drain.
CHANDLER: Mine is the red one! Oh God. Can open, worms everywhere. LAUGH
JOEY: Hey, why can't we use the same toothbrush, but we can use the same soap?
CHANDLER: Because soap is soap. It's self-cleaning.
JOEY: Alright, well next time you take a shower, think about the last thing I wash and the first thing you wash. LAUGH
JOEY: Hey. LAUGH
PHOEBE: Ooh, look at you fancy lads. What's the occasion?
that's in a coma?
He's having a brunch. LAUGH
PHOEBE: Ahh.
RACHEL:  OK, ready when you are.
PHOEBE: Okey-doke.
MONICA: I can't believe you guys are actually getting tattoos.
CHANDLER: Excuse me, you guys are getting tattoos?
RACHEL: Yes, but you can not tell Ross 'cause I want to surprise him.
I'm getting a lily.
For my mom, because her name's Lily. LAUGH
That's lucky. What if her name
was Big Ugly Splotch?
Where you getting it?
My shoulder.
What?
What's on your shoulder?
A chip.
I've got a big attitude problem. LAUGH
A tattoo. I'm getting a tattoo.
A tattoo?
Why? Why would you wanna do that?
You don't think they're kind of cool?
No. Sorry, I don't.
Why would anyone pay
to scar their body for life?
What if it doesn't come out right?
It's like having a bad haircut
all the time. LAUGH
Why is everyone staring at me?
Sign this card for Dad.
Richard will be here soon.
He's going to the party?
He's my parents' best friend.
So is today the day
you tell them about you two?
Yeah, for my dad's birthday,
I decided to give him a stroke. LAUGH
No, I think you should tell them.
I don't know how serious he is.
Until I do, I say nothing.
I don't think
Mom and Dad would mind.
Remember when you were 9
and Richard was 30, Dad said:
''God, I hope they get together.''
Hello? LAUGH
-I'm double-parked.
Okay. Come on, Ross.
Bye, you.
Bye.
Bye, you. LAUGH
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
Okay, wait, wait. LAUGH
It's gonna be fine.
Are you not nervous?
I'm terrified.
This is just a very absorbent suit. LAUGH
Shall we?
Yes.
No. You know what?
Ross, let's switch places.
Get in the middle.
This looks like we're trying
to cover something up.
You could come in straddling him,
they still wouldn't believe it. LAUGH
We're here!
Hi, kids! Hi, darling!
Happy birthday, Dad.
Thank you.
Happy birthday!
You kids thanked
Dr. Burke for the ride?
Actually, Mom, I think Monica
thanked him for the both of us. LAUGH
So you kids take the train in?
No, Richard Burke gave them a ride.
Speaking of whom, I hear he's got
some 20-year-old twinkie in the city. LAUGH
Finger cramp! Oh, God!
Sorry. Here, let me get that, Mom.
So Richard's shopping
in the junior section?
Are we still on that?
You just know she's got
the IQ of a napkin.
She's probably not even pretty.
Just young enough so that
everything is still pointing up. LAUGH
Can you believe this?
It's a great apartment.
In the bathroom,
there's mirrors on both sides.
It's like peeing with the Rockettes.
Well, there's my fantasy come true. LAUGH
No, seriously.
We were just saying, great apartment!
Thanks. You want it?
I'm moving to a bigger place.
You should take this one.
Can you see me in a place like this?
Why not?
You hate park views and high ceilings?
Come on, I'll show you the kitchen.
That's okay,
I saw a kitchen this morning.
On TV.
Stop talking. Okay!
Come on, tell us! LAUGH
Is she really 20?
I am not telling you anything.
Come on, it's my birthday.
Let me live vicariously!
You don't want to do that.
What's a little midlife crisis
between friends?
Let it go.
I know what it's like.
When I turned 50, I got the Porsche.
You got your own little speedster. LAUGH
Seriously, it's not like that.
Tell you what.
Maybe one weekend
you can borrow the car and I could--
I beg you not
to finish that sentence! LAUGH
What? I'm kidding!
You know I'd never let him
touch the Porsche.
Okay, Rach. Which lily?
This lily or that lily?
Well, I--
I like this lily. LAUGH
It's more open. That's like my mom.
She had a more open, giving spirit.
Foghorn Leghorn! LAUGH
Blond girl? You're in room two.
Not-so-blond girl, you're with me. LAUGH
Here we go!
You're not going.
Is this because of what Ross said?
No.
Well, yeah, maybe.
I don't believe this.
Is this how this relationship is
gonna work? Ross equals boss? LAUGH
Come on, what is this, 1 922?
What's 1 922?
Just, you know, a long time ago. LAUGH
When men used to tell women
what to do a lot.
Then there was suffrage, which
was good. But it sounds horrible. LAUGH
Do you want this tattoo?
I do. It's just that Ross--
Okay, hey!
Is your boyfriend the boss of you?
No.
Okay, who is the boss of you?
You? LAUGH
No! You are the boss of you!
You march in there and get
that heart tattooed on your hip! Go! LAUGH
I haven't even gotten my tattoo
and I'm already tougher. LAUGH
How you doing?
I'm a twinkie!
Really? I'm a hero.
This is so hard. LAUGH
Yeah, I know. I hate it too.
Look, maybe we should just tell them.
Maybe we should just tell
your parents first.
My parents are dead.
God, you are so lucky! LAUGH
I mean-- You know what I mean.
I know.
Just hang in there, okay?
Okay, I'll go out first, all right?
All right.
Judy! Going to the bathroom.
Good for you!
Thank you, Richard. LAUGH
I appreciate the support.
Honey. Seen my Harmon Killebrew bat? LAUGH
Bob won't believe I have one.
I have no idea.
Did you know Richard
has a twinkie in the city?
I know. He's like a new man.
It's like a scene from Cocoon. LAUGH
I never would have pictured
Richard with a bimbo.
He told Johnny Shapiro
that she's quite a girl.
He said he's falling in love with her.
Really?
I've never seen him this happy.
So, Jack. Ever think about trading
me in for a younger model?
Of course not.
With you, it's like
I've got two 25-year-olds. LAUGH
Oh, Jack, stop!
Come on!
It's my birthday!
Can we drop this? I am not
interested in the guy's apartment.
Please. I saw the way you were
checking out his moldings. You want it. LAUGH
Why would I want another apartment?
I've already got one I love.
It wouldn't kill you
to say it once in a while. LAUGH
All right. You want the truth?
I'm thinking about it.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm 28. I've never lived alone
and I'm finally at a place where I got enough money
that I don't need a roommate anymore.
I don't need a roommate either.
I can afford to live here by myself.
I may have to bring in somebody
every week to lick the silverware. LAUGH
Why are you so bent out of shape? We
didn't agree to live together forever.
We're not Bert and Ernie.
I'm aware that we're not LAUGH
gay puppets, all right?
You know what?
If this is the way you feel,
then maybe you should take it.
That's how I feel.
Then take it!
Maybe I will!
Fine!
Great! You can spend more time
with your real friends, the spoons!
Whose drink can I freshen? LAUGH
Almost time for cake! LAUGH
Mon, are you okay? LAUGH
You remember that video
I found of Mom and Dad?
Well, I just caught the live show. LAUGH
Hey, there.
MONICA: Hey there.
RICHARD: What?
MONICA: Nothing, I just heard something nice about you.
RICHARD: Humm, really?
MRS. GELLER: Richard. Richard. Your son isn't seeing anyone is he?
RICHARD: Uhh, not that I know of. LAUGH
MRS. GELLER: Well, I was thinking, why doesn't he give Monica a call?
RICHARD: That - that's an idea.
MONICA: Well, actually, I'm already seeing someone.
ROSS: Ohh. LAUGH
MRS. GELLER: She never tells us anything. Ross, did you know Monica's seeing someone?
and some aren't. Is that crystal? LAUGH
ROSS: Mom, there are so many people in my life. Some of them are seeing people and some of them aren't. Is that crystal?
MRS. GELLER: So, who's the mystery man?
MONICA: Well, uh, he's a doctor.
MRS. GELLER: A real doctor? LAUGH
And he's sweet,
and I know you'd like him.
MONICA: No, a doctor of meat. Of course he's a real doctor. And he's handsome, and he's sweet, and know you'd like him.
MRS. GELLER: Well that's wonderful. . . I LAUGH
MONICA: Mom, it's OK.
RICHARD: It is Judy. LAUGH
MRS. GELLER: Jack. Could you come in here for a moment? NOW!
MR. GELLER:  Found it. LAUGH
ROSS: I'll take that dad.
MRS. GELLER: It seems your daughter and Richard are something of an item. LAUGH
MR. GELLER: That's impossible, he's got a twinkie in the city.
MONICA: Dad, I'm the twinkie.
MR. GELLER: You're the twinkie?
RICHARD: She's not a twinkie.
MONICA: Al-alright, l-look you guys, this is the best relationship I've been in. . .
MRS. GELLER: Oh please, a relationship.
MONICA: Yes, a relationship. For your information I am crazy about this man.
RICHARD: Really?
MONICA: Yes.
MR. GELLER: Am I supposed to stand here and listen to this on my birthday?
MONICA: Dad, dad this is a good thing for me. Ya know, and you even said yourself, you've never seen Richard happier.
MR. GELLER: When did I say that? LAUGH
I know, so do I.
I'm so glad you made me do this.
Okay, let me see yours.
Let's see yours again. LAUGH
We just saw mine. Let me see yours.
Oh, okay.
Oh, no!
It's gone! That's so weird. LAUGH
I don't know where it went.
You didn't get it?
No.
Why not?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
How could you do this?
This was your idea!
I know! I was gonna get it,
but he came in with this needle.
Did you know
they do this with needles? LAUGH
Really? You don't say?
Because mine was licked on by kittens! LAUGH
I'm sorry.
Seriously, does it hurt a lot?
No, it's just a pinch. Like that--
Oh, my God! LAUGH
That really hurt me!
Oh, that's gonna leave a mark.
I'm sorry about what--
Yeah, me too.
JOEY: I know. Yeah. LAUGH
CHANDLER: Yeah. So do we need to hug here or. . .
JOEY: No, we're alright. LAUGH
CHANDLER: So I got ya something.
JOEY: Plastic spoons. Great. LAUGH
CHANDLER: Lick away my man.
JOEY: These'll go great in my new place. You know, 'till I get real ones.
CHANDLER: What? LAUGH
JOEY: Well, I can't use these forever. I mean, let's face it, they're no friend to the environment.
CHANDLER: No-no, I mean what, what's this about your new place?
JOEY: I'm movin' out like we talked about. LAUGH
I thought that was just a fight.
CHANDLER: Well I didn't think that was serious.  Ya know I thought that was just a fight.
I think it would be good for me.
Help me to grow or whatever.
JOEY: Well, it was a fight. . . based on serious stuff, remember. About how I never lived alone or anything. I just think it would be good for me, ya know, help me to grow or. . . whatever. LAUGH
CHANDLER: Well, there you go.
JOEY: Hey, are you cool with this. I mean, I don't want to leave you high and dry. LAUGH
Put the foosball table in there.
CHANDLER: Hey, no, I've never been lower or wetter. I'll be fine. I'll just turn your, uh, bedroom into a game room or somethin', you know, put the foosball table in there.
JOEY: Woah. Why do you get to keep the table?
CHANDLER: I did pay for half of it.
JOEY: Yeah. And uh, I paid for the other half.
CHANDLER: Alright I'll tell you what, I'll play you for it.
JOEY: Alright, you're on. I can take two minutes out of my day to kick your ass. LAUGH
CHANDLER: Your little men are gonna get scored on more times than your sister.
LAUGH
MONICA: So, are you sorry that I told them?
RACHEL: Oh. LAUGH
MONICA: Oh. Well did you get it? Let me see.
RACHEL: Is Ross here?
MONICA: No he went out to get pizza.
RACHEL: Oh really, OK.
MONICA: That's great.
RICHARD: Very tasteful.
PHOEBE: Wanna see mine, wanna see mine?
MONICA: Yes.
RACHEL: What? You didn't get one.
PHOEBE: OK, well then what is this? LAUGH
RICHARD: What're we looking at? That blue freckle?
PHOEBE: OK, that's my tattoo.
I got her in the chair,
he barely touched her she screamed and that was it.
Okay, hi! LAUGH
RACHEL: That is not a tattoo, that is a nothing. I finally got her back in the chair, bairly touched her with a needle, she jumped up screaming, and that was it.
from a great, great distance. LAUGH
It's the way my mother
sees me from heaven.
PHOEBE: OK, hi. For your information this is exactly what I wanted. This is a tattoo of the earth as seen from a great distance. It's the way my mother sees me from heaven. LAUGH
Your mother's in heaven going,
''Where the hell's my lily, you wuss?!'' LAUGH
Okay? That is not a tattoo!
This is a tattoo! LAUGH
RACHEL: Oh, what a load of crap. That is a dot. Your mother is up in heaven going, 'Where the hell is my lily, you wuss?' OK, Phoebe, that is not a tattoo, this is a tattoo.
ROSS: You got a tattoo?
Phoebe got the whole world! LAUGH
RACHEL: Maybe. But just a little one. Phoebe got the whole world.
ROSS: Lemme see.
RACHEL: Well?
ROSS: Well it's really. . . sexy. I wouldn't have thought it would be but. . . wow. LAUGH
RACHEL: Really?
ROSS: Yeah, so uh, is it sore or can you do stuff? LAUGH
RACHEL: I guess.
Get it out of the corner! LAUGH
Pass it! Pass it!
JOEY: Get out of the corner. Pass it, pass it. LAUGH
CHANDLER: Stop talkin' to your men.
JOEY: Yes! And the table is mine.
LAUGH
JOEY: Hey, you guys are still gonna come visit me, right?
Except when we are here.
CHANDLER: Oh yeah, you got the big TV. We'll be over there all the time. . .  except when we are here.
PHOEBE: I know you're just moving uptown but I'm really gonna miss you.
MONICA: I know, how can you not be accross the hall anymore.
Is that my bra?
What are you doing with my bra?
RACHEL: Yeah, who's gonna eat all our food, and tie up our phone lines, and - is that my bra? What the hell you doin' with my bra?
water balloons off the roof.
Remember? Those kids couldn't
even get theirs across the street.
JOEY: Oh no-no, it's uh, it's not what you think. We uh, we used it to, you know, fling water balloons off the roof. Remember that, those junior high kids couldn't even get theirs accross the street.
CHANDLER:  Yeah, I remember.
ROSS: Hey, let's bring the rest of these down to the truck.
CHANDLER: So, uhh, em, you want me to uh, give you a hand with the foosball table?
JOEY: Naa, you keep it, you need the practice.
CHANDLER: Thanks.
JOEY: So, I guess this is it.
CHANDLER: Yeah, right, yeah, I guess so.
JOEY: Listen, uh, I don't know when I'm gonna see you again.
CHANDLER: Well, I'm guessing uh, tonight at the coffee house.
JOEY: Right, yeah. OK. Um, take care. LAUGH