The One Where It AII Began (PiIot)
There's nothing to teII.
It's just some guy I work with.
You're going out with the guy.
There has to be something
wrong with him.
AII right, Joey.
Be nice.
So does he have a hump
and a hairpiece?
Wait, does he eat chaIk?
I don't want her to go through
what I did with CarI.
Okay, everybody reIax.
This is not even a date.
It's just two peopIe going out
to dinner and not having sex.
Sounds Iike a date to me.
I'm in high schooI,
in the cafeteria...
...and I reaIize I'm totaIIy naked.
I've had that dream.
Then I Iook down and I reaIize
there is a phone...
...there.
-Instead of--
-That's right!
Never had that one.
AII of a sudden,
the phone starts to ring.
What do I do?
Everyone starts Iooking at me.
They weren't Iooking at you before?
FinaIIy, I figure
I'd better answer it.
And it turns out it's my mother.
Which is very, very weird
because she never caIIs me.
Hi.
He says, ''HeIIo,''
I want to kiII myseIf.
You okay?
I feeI Iike someone puIIed my
intestine out of my mouth...
-...and tied it around my neck.
-Cookie?
CaroI moved her stuff out today.
-Let me get you some coffee.
-Thanks.
No, don't!
Stop cIeansing my aura.
-Just Ieave my aura aIone, okay?
-Fine, be murky.
-I'II be fine. I hope she'II be happy.
-No, you don't.
No, I don't.
To heII with her. She Ieft me!
You never knew she was a Iesbian?
No! Okay?
Why does everyone
keep fixating on that?
She didn't know.
How shouId I know?
Sometimes I wish I was a Iesbian.
Did I say that out Ioud?
I toId Mom and Dad Iast night.
They took it pretty weII.
Oh, reaIIy?
So that hystericaI phone caII
from a woman sobbing...
...''I'II never have grandchiIdren,''
was what? A wrong number?
Sorry.
Look, you're feeIing
a Iot of pain right now.
You're angry.
You're hurting.
Can I teII you what
the answer is?
Strip joints!
Hey, you're singIe.
Have some hormones.
But I don't want
to be singIe, okay?
I just want to be married again.
And I just want a miIIion doIIars!
-RacheI?
-Oh, Monica! Thank God!
I went to your buiIding...
...and a guy with a hammer
said you'd be here, and you are.
-Can I get you some coffee?
-Decaf.
Everybody, this is RacheI,
a LincoIn High survivor.
This is everybody.
ChandIer and Phoebe...
...Joey.
Remember my brother, Ross?
Sure!
You want to teII us now, or are we
waiting for four wet bridesmaids?
WeII, it started about
a haIf-hour before the wedding.
I was in the room
with aII the presents...
...and I was Iooking at this
reaIIy gorgeous Limoges gravy boat.
When aII of a sudden--
Sweet 'N Low?
I reaIized I was more turned on by
this gravy boat than Barry.
I got freaked out,
and it hit me:
How much Barry Iooks
Iike Mr. Potato Head.
I aIways knew
he Iooked famiIiar, but....
I had to get out of there,
and I started wondering...
...''Why am I doing this,''
and ''Who am I doing it for?''
I didn't know where to go,
and I know we've drifted apart...
...but you're the onIy person
I know here.
-Who wasn't invited to the wedding.
-I hoped that wouIdn't be an issue.
I guess he bought her the pipe organ,
and she's reaIIy not happy about it.
''Tuna or egg saIad!
Decide!''
''I'II have whatever
Christina's having.''
Daddy, I just--
I can't marry him.
I'm sorry.
I just don't Iove him.
WeII, it matters to me!
''If I Iet go of my hair,
my head wiII faII off.''
She shouId not be
wearing those pants.
Push her down the stairs!
Push her!
Come on, Daddy, Iisten!
AII my Iife, everyone's
aIways toId me, ''You're a shoe!''
''You're a shoe!''
What if I don't want to be a shoe?
What if I want to be a purse?
Or a hat?
No, I don't want you
to buy me a hat!
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
You can see where he'd have troubIe.
Look, Daddy,
it's my Iife.
WeII, maybe I'II just stay
here with Monica.
I guess we've estabIished
she's staying with Monica.
WeII, maybe that's my decision.
Maybe I don't need your money.
Wait!
I said maybe!
Just breathe. That's it.
Try to think of nice, caIm things.
Raindrops on roses
And whiskers on kittens
Doorbells and sleigh bells
And something with mittens
La la la something
And noodles with string
I'm aII better now.
I heIped.
This is probabIy for the best.
Independence. ControIIing your Iife.
The whoIe hat thing.
You can aIways come to Joey.
Me and ChandIer Iive across the haII.
He's away a Iot.
Stop hitting on her!
It's her wedding day.
Like there's a ruIe, or something?
I got it.
PIease don't do that again.
It's a horribIe sound.
It's Paul.
Oh, God, is it 6:30?
Buzz him in.
-Who's PauI?
-PauI, the wine guy?
Maybe.
Your ''not a reaI date''
is with PauI, the wine guy?
-He finaIIy asked you out?
-Yes!
It's a ''Dear Diary'' moment.
-Rach, I can canceI.
-PIease, go, I'II be fine.
Ross, are you okay?
Do you want me to stay?
That'd be good.
-ReaIIy?
-Go on! It's PauI, the wine guy!
Does he seII it, drink it?
Or he just compIains a Iot?
Hi, come in!
PauI, this is...
...everybody.
Everybody, this is PauI.
-The wine guy.
-I didn't catch your name. PauI?
I'II be right back.
I've just gotta go--
A-wandering?
Change.
Sit down.
Two seconds.
I just puIIed out four eyeIashes.
That can't be good.
Hey, PauI, here's a tip.
She reaIIy Iikes it when you
rub her neck in the same spot...
...untiI it starts to get red.
Shut up, Joey!
What are you up to tonight?
I was supposed to be headed
for Aruba on my honeymoon...
...so, nothing.
Right. You're not even
getting your honeymoon.
AIthough, Aruba.
This time of year?
TaIk about your...
...big Iizards.
If you don't want
to be aIone tonight...
...Joey and ChandIer are
heIping me with my furniture.
We're very excited about it.
Thanks. But I'm just
going to hang out here.
-It's been a Iong day.
-Oh, sure.
Pheebs, wanna heIp?
I wish I couId,
but I don't want to.
Love is sweet as summer showers
Love is a wondrous work of art
But your love
Oh, your love, your love
Is like a giant pigeon
Crapping on my heart
Thank you.
I'm supposed to attach a bracket-y
thing to the side things...
...using a bunch of these
IittIe worm guys.
I have no bracket-y thing.
I see no worm guys whatsoever...
...and I cannot feeI my Iegs.
-We got a bookcase.
-It's beautifuI.
What's this?
I wouId have to say
that is an L-shaped bracket.
-Which goes where?
-I have no idea.
-Done with the bookcase.
-AII finished.
This was CaroI's favorite beer.
She aIways drank it out of the can.
I shouId have known.
-Start with that, we're out of here.
-PIease don't spoiI aII this fun.
Let me ask you.
She got the furniture,
the stereo, the good TV.
What did you get?
-You guys.
-You got screwed.
-Oh, my God.
-I know. I'm such an idiot.
I shouId've known when she went to
the dentist five times a week.
I mean, how cIean can teeth get?
My brother's going through that.
How did you get over it?
He might accidentaIIy
break something vaIuabIe of hers.
-Say her--
-Leg?
That's one way of doing it.
I went for the watch.
You actuaIIy broke her watch?
The worst I ever did was shred
my oId boyfriend's favorite toweI.
-Steer cIear of you.
-That's right.
Barry, I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
You probabIy think it's about making
Iove with your socks on, but it isn't.
It's about me.
And I just--
The machine cut me off again.
Anyway....
I know that some Iucky girI is going
to become Mrs. Barry FinkeI.
But it isn't me.
It's not me.
Not that I have any idea who ''me'' is
right now, but you just--
I'm divorced.
-I'm onIy 26, and I'm divorced!
-Shut up!
That onIy took me an hour.
We haven't had a reIationship
that's Iasted Ionger than a Mento.
You have had the Iove of a woman
for four years.
Four years of cIoseness and sharing,
after which she ripped your heart out.
That is why we don't do it!
I don't think that was my point!
IKnow what's scary? What if there's
onIy one woman for everybody?
I mean, what if you get one
woman, and that's it?
UnfortunateIy, in my case,
there was onIy one woman for her.
What are you taIking about?
One woman.
That's Iike saying there's onIy
one fIavor of ice cream.
Let me teII you something.
There's Iots of fIavors out there.
Rocky road and cookie dough
and bing cherry vaniIIa.
You can get them with jimmies
or nuts or whipped cream.
It's the best thing
to happen to you!
You got married.
You were Iike, what, 8?
WeIcome back to the worId.
Grab a spoon!
-I don't know if I'm hungry or horny.
-Then stay out of my freezer.
Ever since she waIked out on me....
What?
You wanna speII it out with noodIes?
It's more of a fifth date
kind of reveIation.
So there's going to be
a fifth date?
Isn't there?
Yeah, yeah.
I think there is.
What were you going to say?
Ever since she Ieft me...
...I haven't been abIe to perform...
...sexuaIIy.
Oh, God!
I'm so sorry.
Being spit on is probabIy
not what you need right now.
How Iong?
-Two years.
-Wow.
I'm gIad you smashed her watch.
So you stiII think you might
want that fifth date?
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
We are gathered here
to join Joanie Louise Cunningham...
...and Charles.
Chachi, Chachi, Chachi...
...in the bonds of holy matrimony.
See!
But Joanie Ioved Chachi.
That's the difference.
''Grab a spoon.''
Do you know how Iong it's been
since I grabbed a spoon?
Do the words, ''BiIIy, don't be
a hero,'' mean anything to you?
Great story.
But I gotta go.
I got a date with Andrea.
AngeIa. No, Andrea.
Andrea's the screamer.
AngeIa has cats.
Right, thanks. It's JuIie.
I'm out of here.
Here's the thing. Even if
I couId get it together enough...
...to ask a woman out...
...who am I going to ask?
Isn't this amazing?
I've never made coffee in my Iife.
-That is amazing.
-CongratuIations.
If I can make coffee,
there isn't anything I can't do.
I think it's, ''If I can invade PoIand,
there's nothing I can't do.''
If you feeI Iike you have to make
a Western omeIet or something....
AIthough, actuaIIy
I'm reaIIy not that hungry.
Oh, good.
Lenny and Squiggy are here.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
-Morning, PauI.
-HeIIo, PauI.
-Hi. PauI, is it?
-Thank you so much.
-Stop.
Last night was Iike
aII my birthdays, both graduations...
...pIus the barn-raising scene
in Witness.
We'II taIk Iater.
Thank you.
That wasn't a reaI date.
What the heII do you do
on a reaI date?
Shut up and put my tabIe back.
I've got to get to work.
If I don't input those numbers,
it doesn't make much of a difference.
So, Iike, you guys aII have jobs?
Yeah, we aII have jobs.
That's how we buy stuff.
-Yeah, I'm an actor.
-Have I seen you in anything?
I doubt it.
MostIy regionaI work.
UnIess you saw the Wee One's
production of Pinocchio...
...at the IittIe theater
in the park?
It was a job!
''Look, Geppetto.
I'm a reaI Iive boy.''
-I wiII not take this abuse.
-You're right, I'm sorry.
Once I was a wooden boy
A little wooden boy
You shouId both know
that he's a dead man.
Oh, ChandIer!
How are you doing today?
SIeep okay?
Did you taIk to Barry?
I can't stop smiIing.
I see that. You Iook Iike you
sIept with a hanger in your mouth.
I know.
He's just so....
-Remember you and Tony Demarco?
-Oh, yeah.
WeII, it's Iike that.
With feeIings.
-Wow, are you in troubIe!
-Big time!
Want a wedding dress?
HardIy used.
I think we're getting a IittIe
ahead of ourseIves.
I'm going to get up, go to work,
and not think about him aII day.
Or eIse I'm going to get up
and go to work.
-Wish me Iuck!
-What for?
I'm gonna go get one
of those job things.
-Hi, Monica.
-Franny, weIcome back.
-How was FIorida?
-You had sex, didn't you?
-How do you do that?
-I hate you.
I'm pushing my aunt through
Parrot JungIe, you're having sex.
So, who?
You know PauI?
PauI, the wine guy?
Yeah, I know PauI.
You mean, you know PauI
Iike I know PauI?
What?
I take credit for PauI.
Before me, there was no snap in his
turtIe for two years.
Of course it was a Iine.
Why wouId anybody
do something Iike that?
I assume we want an answer
more sophisticated than:
''To get you into bed.''
I hate men.
Don't hate. You don't want
to put that out into the universe.
Is it me?
Is it Iike I have some sort of
beacon that onIy dogs...
...and men with emotionaI probIems
can hear?
Come here.
Give me your feet.
I just thought he was nice, you know?
I can't beIieve
you didn't know it was a Iine.
-Guess what?
-You got a job?
Are you kidding?
I'm trained for nothing.
-I was Iaughed out of 1 2 interviews.
-You're surprisingIy upbeat.
You'd be too,
if you found these boots on saIe...
...50% off.
How weII you know me.
They're my
''I don't need a job...
...I've got great boots'' boots.
-How did you pay?
-Credit card.
And who pays for that?
My father.
Is this reaIIy necessary?
I can stop charging any time.
You can't Iive off your parents.
I know that.
That's why I was getting married.
Give her a break.
It's hard being on your own.
Thank you.
I remember when I first
came to this city, I was 1 4.
Mom had kiIIed herseIf,
stepdad was in jaiI.
I didn't know anybody here.
I ended up Iiving with this aIbino
guy who was cIeaning windshieIds.
And then he kiIIed himseIf.
Then I found aromatherapy.
So I know exactIy how you feeI.
The word you're Iooking for is:
''Anyway....''
-You ready?
-No, how can I be ready?
''Ready to jump out of the pIane
with no parachute?''
-I can't do this.
-I know you can.
-No.
-You made coffee, you can do anything.
Cut. Cut. Cut.
You know what?
I think we can Ieave it at that.
-IKind of a symboIic gesture.
-RacheI, that was a Iibrary card.
If you Iisten cIoseIy, you can hear
a thousand retaiIers scream.
WeIcome to the reaI worId!
It sucks.
You're gonna Iove it.
That's it.
Are you going to crash on the couch?
-No, I gotta go home sometime.
-Are you gonna be okay?
Look what I just
found on the fIoor.
What?
That's PauI's watch.
Just put it back where you found it.
Oh, boy!
AII right.
-Good night, everybody.
-Good night.
-I'm sorry. Have it, I don't want it.
-SpIit it?
You probabIy didn't know this,
but in high schooI...
...I had a major crush on you.
I knew.
You did?
I figured you thought
I was Monica's geeky brother.
I did.
Listen, do you think...?
Try not to Iet my vuInerabiIity
become a factor here.
Do you think it wouId be okay
if I asked you out sometime?
Yeah.
Maybe.
Okay.
Okay, maybe I wiII.
-Good night.
See you.
Wait, wait.
What's with you?
I just grabbed a spoon.
-I can't beIieve what I'm hearing.
-Can't believe what I'm hearing
-What? I said--
-What? I said
-WouId you stop?
-Was I doing it again?
Yes!
I said you had a nice butt.
It's just not a great butt.
-You won't know a butt if it bit you.
-There's an image.
WouId anybody Iike more coffee?
You made it,
or you're serving it?
-I'm just serving it.
-I'II have a cup of coffee.
IKids, new dream.
I'm in Las Vegas.
Miss, more coffee?
CouId you give this
to that guy over there?
Go ahead.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Okay, Las Vegas.
I'm in Las Vegas.
I'm Liza MinneIIi....