Guys, there's somebody
I'd Iike you to meet.
Wait, wait. What is that?
-That's MarceI. Wanna say hi?
-No, I don't.
-He's cute! Where'd you get him?
-My friend BetheI saved him from a Iab.
That is so crueI.
Why wouId a parent
name their chiId BetheI?
That monkey's got a Ross on his ass.
Is he gonna Iive with you
in your apartment?
Yeah. It's been kind of quiet
since CaroI Ieft.
Why not get a roommate?
You reach a certain age, having
a roommate is just kind of pathet--
That's ''pathet.'' Sanskrit for
''reaIIy cooI way to Iive.''
The One With the Monkey
I'm doing new materiaI tonight.
I have 1 2 songs about my mother's
suicide and one about a snowman.
You might wanna open with the snowman.
-Hi, Joey.
-Hey, buddy.
-So how'd it go?
-I didn't get the job.
How couId you not?
You were Santa Iast year.
Some fat guy's sIeeping
with the store manager.
He's not even joIIy.
It's aII poIiticaI.
-What are you gonna be?
-One of his heIpers.
It's just such a sIap in the face,
you know?
Do you know what you're doing
for New Year's?
Hey, what?
What is wrong with New Year's?
You have PaoIo. You don't have
to face the pressure...
...of finding Iips to kiss
when the baII drops!
Man, I'm taIking Ioud!
PaoIo's gonna be in Rome
this New Year's.
-I'II be just as pathetic as you.
-Yeah, you wish.
I've got an idea. Dinner.
It's perfect. We'II put it between
Iunch and breakfast.
I'm sick of being a victim
of this Dick CIark hoIiday.
I say this year, we make a pact.
Just the six of us. Dinner.
-Sure.
-Fine.
I was hoping for more enthusiasm.
-Phoebe, you're on.
-Oh, good.
Hi. Ladies and gentIemen,
back by popuIar demand...
...Miss Phoebe Buffay.
Hi. Thanks. Hi.
I wanna start with a song
that means a Iot to me.
I made a man with eyes of coal
And a smile so bewitching
How was I supposed to know
That my mom was dead in the kitchen?
My mother's ashes
Even her eyelashes
Are resting in a little yellow jar
And sometimes when it's freezing
I feel a little sneezy
And now I-- Excuse me?
Excuse me? Yeah, noisy boys.
Is it something you'd Iike
to share with the group?
No. No, that's okay.
If it's important enough
whiIe I'm pIaying...
...it's important enough
for everyone eIse.
That guy's going home with a note.
-I was just saying--
-Speak up.
Sorry, I--
I was saying you were the most
beautifuI woman I'd ever seen.
And he said that DaryI Hannah...
...was the most beautifuI woman
he'd ever seen.
I said I Iiked her in Splash,
but not Wall Street.
I thought she had a hard quaIity.
WhiIe DaryI is beautifuI
in a conventionaI way...
...you are Iuminous
with a kind of deIicate grace.
Then that's when you started yeIIing.
We're gonna take a short break.
That guy's going home
with more than a note.
Come here, MarceI. Sit here.
I can't beIieve he hasn't
kissed you yet.
By my sixth date with PaoIo,
he'd aIready named both my breasts.
Did I just share too much?
Just a smidge.
David's, Iike, a scientist guy.
He's very methodicaI.
-I think it's romantic.
-Me too!
Did you ever see
An Officer and a Gentleman?
He's kind of Iike the guy
I went to see that with.
Except he's smarter and gentIer
and sweeter.
I just wanna be with him aII the time.
You know, day and night.
And night and day.
And speciaI occasions.
I see. You're gonna ask him
to New Year's.
-She's gonna break the pact.
-No! No, no.
No. Yeah, couId I just--?
-Yeah. I aIready asked Janice.
-What?
This was a pact! This was your pact!
I couIdn't handIe the pressure.
I snapped!
But that was the worst breakup
in history!
I'm not saying it was a good idea.
I snapped!
Hi, sorry I'm Iate.
Too many jokes.
Must mock Joey.
Nice shoes, huh?
God, you're kiIIing me!
Ross, he's pIaying
with my spatuIas again!
-He's not gonna hurt them, right?
-Do you aIways have to bring him?
I didn't wanna Ieave him aIone.
We had our first fight this morning.
It has to do with my working Iate.
I said some things that I didn't mean.
He threw some feces.
If you're working Iate,
I can Iook in on him.
That wouId be great!
But make sure it seems
Iike you're there to see him.
You're not doing it for me.
Okay. But if he asks,
I'm not going to Iie.
But you can't actuaIIy
test this theory.
Today's particIe acceIerators
aren't powerfuI enough...
-...to simuIate these conditions.
-I have a question then.
-Yeah?
-Do you pIan on kissing me ever?
That's definiteIy a vaIid question,
and the answer...
...wouId be yes. Yes, I was.
But I wanted it to be
this phenomenaI kiss...
...at a phenomenaI moment
because it's you.
Sure.
The Ionger I waited, the more
phenomenaI the kiss had to be.
Now, it's just gotta be
one of those things where I...
...sweep everything off the tabIe.
And I'm not reaIIy
a sweeping sort of feIIa.
David, I think you are
I mean, you're a sweeper
trapped inside a physicist's body.
-ReaIIy?
-I'm sure.
You shouId just do it. Just throw me.
-Now?
-Yeah, right now. Just....
Okay. Okay. Okay.
You know what?
This is reaIIy expensive.
And this was a gift.
-Now you're just tidying up.
-Okay.
-You want me to throw you--?
-I can hop.
TeII me something, what does
''no-date pact'' mean to you?
It's just that ChandIer
and Phoebe have somebody.
I thought I'd ask Fun Bobby.
-Your ex-boyfriend?
-Yeah.
-You know more than one Fun Bobby?
-I happen to know a Fun Bob.
-Okay. Here we go.
-There's no room for miIk.
There. Now there is.
So on our no-date evening,
three of you now have dates.
-Four.
-Five.
Sorry. PaoIo's catching
an earIier fIight.
And I met this reaIIy hot
singIe mom at the store.
What's an eIf to do?
So I'II be the onIy one aIone
when the baII drops?
We'II have a big party,
and no one wiII know who's with who.
I'II know. This is so not
what I needed right now.
-What's the matter?
-Oh, it's MarceI.
He's angry with me. I have
no idea why. He keeps shutting me out.
He's waIking around aII the time,
dragging his hands.
That's weird.
I had a bIast with him.
-ReaIIy?
-We pIayed, watched TV.
That juggIing thing is amazing.
What juggIing thing?
With the socks?
I figured you taught him that.
No.
It wasn't that big a deaI.
Just socks. And a meIon.
-Phoebe!
-Max. Do you know everybody?
No. Have you seen David?
He hasn't been around.
If you see him, teII him to pack.
We are going to Minsk.
-Minsk?
-Minsk. It's in Russia.
I know where Minsk is.
We got the grant.
Three years, aII expenses paid.
And if you're gonna do Minsk,
that's the way to go.
-So when do you Ieave?
-January 1st.
-HeIIo?
-What? Hey. Hi.
-What are you doing here?
-Max toId me about Minsk.
CongratuIations! This is so exciting!
It'd be even more exciting
if we were going.
Oh, you're not going? Oh, why?
TeII her. ''I don't wanna go...
...to work with Lipson,
Yamaguchi and FIank.
I wanna stay and make out
with my girIfriend!''
Okay, thank you, Max. Thank you.
So you're reaIIy not going?
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I just....
How can I Ieave you?
I just found you.
Oh, David. But what are you gonna do?
I don't know. You decide.
-Don't do that.
-But I'm asking you.
-I can't make a decision. Just--
-Okay. Stay.
-Stay.
Getting so good at that!
It was Max's stuff.
I Iove this artichoke thing.
Don't teII me what's in it.
The diet starts tomorrow.
You remember Janice.
VividIy.
-How are you?
-I am fantastic.
Now.
It's amazing. We've been back
together for what...
-...Iike 10 minutes, and--
-Is that aII?
It's Iike we were never apart.
Of course, we were, but--
Forgive and forget.
WeII, forget.
-Hi.
-Hi, I'm Sandy.
Sandy, hi. Come on in.
-You brought your kids.
-Yeah. That's okay, right?
-Party!
-That thing is not coming in here!
This is how you greet guests?
If I showed up with my new girIfriend,
she wouIdn't be weIcome?
Your new girIfriend wouIdn't urinate
on my coffee tabIe.
He was more embarrassed
about that than anyone.
And for him to have the courage
to waIk back in here...
...Iike nothing happened--
AII right. AII right.
Just keep him away from me.
Thank you. Come on, MarceI.
What do you say you and I mingIe?
AII right, I'II catch up
with you Iater.
Oh, my gosh!
RacheI, honey, are you okay?
-Where's PaoIo?
-Rome. Jerk missed his fIight.
And then your face expIoded?
No.
Okay. I was at the airport
getting into a cab...
...when this woman, this bIond
pIanet with a pocketbook...
...starts yeIIing. Something
about how it was her cab first.
The next thing, she just
starts puIIing me out by my hair!
And I was bIowing my attack
whistIe thingy...
...and three more cabs show up.
So as I'm going to get into a cab,
she tackIes me!
And I hit my head on the curb
and cut my Iip on my whistIe.
Everybody having fun at the party?
-Are peopIe eating my dip?
-Yes.
There.
-That Iooks okay, right?
-You went a bit wide on the Iipstick.
-Oh, I did?
-Yeah.
It's hard for me to teII.
My eye's cIosing up.
Let me get it for you.
-Ow!
-Okay.
You know what? It Iooks fine.
Okay, here we go.
Screw PaoIo,
screw the psycho cab Iady.
It's New Year's Eve.
Let's have a good time.
-Okay, here we go.
-Okay.
AII right, there you go. This way.
Here you go.
When I saw you at the store
Iast week...
...it was the first time
I ever mentaIIy undressed an eIf.
-Wow, that's dirty.
-Yeah.
Hey, kids.
He doesn't have to spend
the whoIe evening with me...
...but at Ieast check in.
There you are!
You got away from me.
-But you found me.
-Here, Ross, take our picture.
SmiIe. You're on Janice Camera.
IKiII me. IKiII me now.
Hi, I'm RacheI.
So whose friend are you?
Look at me, spiIIing everywhere.
Everybody, it's Fun Bobby!
Hey, sorry I'm Iate.
But my grandfather...
...died about two hours ago.
But I couIdn't get a fIight
out tiII tomorrow, so here I am.
Hey, Fun Bobby! How's it going, man?
Whoa! Who died?
It's gonna be an open casket,
you know?
So at Ieast I'II get to see him again.
Bobby? Fun Bobby?
Let me taIk to you for just a sec.
I recentIy Iost
a grandparent myseIf...
...so I reaIIy know exactIy
how you feeI.
But you're reaIIy bringing
the party down.
-I'm sorry.
-Yeah, yeah, okay.
There you go. There you go.
I'm gonna bIow this one up
and write ''Reunited'' in gIitter.
AII right, Janice, that's it!
Janice. Janice.
Hey, Janice, when I invited you,
I didn't think it meant--
Oh, no!
I'm sorry you misunderstood.
You Iisten to me!
One of these times, it's just gonna be
your Iast chance with me!
WiII you give me the thing?
-Hi, Max.
-Yoko.
I've decided to go to Minsk
without you.
-Wow.
-It won't be the same...
...but it wiII stiII be Minsk.
Happy New Year.
-Are you aII right?
-Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Come on.
-You're going to Minsk.
-No, I'm not going to Minsk.
You are so going to Minsk.
You beIong in Minsk.
You can't stay here just for me.
If I go, I have to break up with you.
-And I can't break up with you.
-Yes, you can.
Just say, ''Phoebe, I Iove you,
but my work is my Iife.
That's what I have to do.''
And I say, ''Your work?
How can you say that?''
Then you say, ''I have no choice.
Can't you understand that?''
And I say, ''No! No!
I can't understand that!''
-Ow.
-Sorry.
And then you put
your arms around me.
-Then you put your arms around me.
-Oh, sorry.
And then you teII me you Iove me
and you'II never forget me.
I'II never forget you.
Then you say that you have to go...
...because you don't wanna start the
year with me if you can't finish it.
I'm gonna miss you,
you scientist guy.
Hi, Dick Clark in Times Square.
We're in a virtual snowstorm
of confetti here in Times Square.
It gets better every....
Here you go, kids.
And then the peacock bit me.
PIease kiss me at midnight!
-You seen Sandy?
-I don't know how to teII you this...
...but she's in the bedroom
getting it on with Max.
Oh, I did know how to teII you.
-Hey, everybody, the baII is dropping.
-What?
The baII is dropping!
In 20 seconds, it'll be midnight.
And the moment of joy is upon us.
Looks Iike that no-date pact
worked out.
Everybody Iooks so happy.
I hate that!
Not everybody is happy. Hey, Bobby!
--four, three, two...
...one! Happy New Year!
I thought I'd throw this out.
I'm no math whiz...
...but I do beIieve there are
three girIs and three guys right here.
I don't feeI Iike kissing
anyone tonight.
-I can't kiss anyone.
-So, I'm kissing everyone?
No, you can't kiss Ross.
That's your brother.
So now everybody's
getting kissed but me.
Somebody kiss me.
Somebody kiss me! It's midnight!
Somebody kiss me!
AII right! AII right!
There!
I wanted this to work so much.
I'm stiII in there.
Changing his diapers.
Picking his fIeas.
But he's just phoning it in.
It's hard that something you Iove
so much doesn't Iove you back.
I think that bitch cracked my tooth.