Do you think they have
yesterday's Daily News?
I just wanna check my horoscope,
see if it was right.
Oh, my God! Don't Iook now.
Behind you there's a guy...
...who can break our hearts
and pIunge us into depression.
Come to mama.
He's coming.
Be cooI. Be cooI. Be cooI.
-Nice hat.
-Thanks.
-We shouId do something. WhistIe.
-I'm not whistIing.
Come on, do it!
Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it.
I can't beIieve you did that.
The One With Mrs. Bing
-It's aII my fauIt.
-No, it's mine.
Why did I whoo-hoo?
Was I hoping
he'd turn around and say...
...''I Iove that sound.
I must have you now''?
I wish there was something
we couId do.
HeIIo, coma guy.
Get up, you GirI Scout!
Up, up, up!
What are you doing?
Maybe nobody's tried this.
I wish we at Ieast knew his name.
I hate that they're
caIIing him John Doe.
It's so sad. It's Iike he's a deer,
a femaIe deer.
Oh, I was gonna stop.
Look at that face.
Even sIeeping he Iooks smart.
Yeah, but the dents in his knuckIes
mean he's artistic.
Okay. He's a Iawyer who teaches
scuIpting on the side.
And he can dance.
And he's the kind of guy who,
when you're taIking, he's Iistening...
...not saying, ''I understand''...
...but reaIIy wondering
what you Iook Iike naked.
I wish aII guys couId be Iike him.
I know.
You don't even know this guy.
Are there no conscious men
in the city for you two?
He doesn't have anyone.
We feeI kind of responsibIe.
I can't beIieve you said ''whoo-hoo.''
I don't even say ''whoo-hoo.''
Oh, she's coming up.
When we return, we'll talk with
the always interesting Nora Tyler Bing.
Put the kids to bed for this one.
Don't watch this. Weekend at Bernie's
is on Showtime and HBO.
No way.
-She's your mom.
-ExactIy. Weekend at Bernie's.
Dead guy getting hit
in the groin 20, 30 times.
I gotta teII you,
I Iove your mom's books.
I can't get on a pIane without one.
This is so cooI.
You wouIdn't think so
if you were 1 1 ...
...and your friends were passing around
page 79 of Mistress Bitch.
I remember page 79.
The thing after the opera
with the girI with the trick hip?
I Iove your mom.
I think she's a bIast.
That's because she's not your mom.
Oh, pIease. She's the--
Hi, sweetie.
When did ''Rigatoni'' get back from Rome?
-Last night.
-ReaIIy?
So, his pIane didn't expIode
in a big baII of fire?
Just a dream I had.
But, phew!
Hey, she's on.
Nora Bing.
Back to the book. What is this
about you being arrested in London?
Your mom was arrested?
I'm busy beaming with pride.
This is kind of embarrassing...
...but occasionally, after
I've been intimate with a man...
Why wouId she say that's embarrassing?
...I just get this craving
for kung pao chicken.
That's too much information.
Needless to say, he got a huge tip.
Oh, God, I Iove her!
I think I'm having a stroke.
So how is your book tour going?
Oh, fine. I'm leaving
for New York tomorrow, which I hate.
But I get to see my son, who I love.
This is the way that I find out.
Most moms use the phone.
Don't take this wrong, I just
don't see you as a mom.
-I don't mean that bad.
-Oh, no. I'm a fabulous mom.
I bought my son his first condoms.
And then he burst into fIames.
Let's see. Congress is debating
a new deficit-reduction biII.
The mayor wants to raise subway fares.
The high today was 45.
And teams pIayed sports.
What about GIen?
He couId be a GIen.
Not speciaI enough.
How about Agamemnon?
Way too speciaI.
I'm famished. What do I want?
PIease, God, don't Iet it be
kung pao chicken.
You watched the show.
What did you think?
I think you need to come out
of your sheII.
What is this dive?
OnIy you couId've picked this pIace.
Come on. Shut up. It's fun.
Give me a hug.
I heard about the divorce.
Lesbian, huh?
WeII, you know what they say:
Be carefuI what you wish for.
-I think we're ready for some tequiIa.
-I know I am.
-Who's doing shots?
-Hit me.
There you go. Ross?
I'm not reaIIy a shot-drinking
kind of guy.
Hi. Sorry we're Iate.
We kind of just, you know,
Iost track of time.
But a man can change.
Anyone want me to appraise anything?
WeII, I'm gonna go to tinker-town.
Mrs. Bing, I've read
everything you've written.
When I read Euphoria at Midnight,
I wanted to become a writer.
Oh, pIease.
If I can do it, anybody can.
Start with haIf a dozen
European cities...
...throw in 30 euphemisms
for maIe genitaIia...
...and you've got yourseIf a book.
My mother, Iadies and gentIemen.
Yeah, any messages for room 226?
-You okay, sIugger?
-Oh, yeah. I'm fine.
What is with you tonight?
Nothing. Nothing, nothing.
Okay, thank you.
It's the ItaIian hand-Iicker, isn't it?
No. It's the one he's Iicking.
She's supposed to be with you.
You're good.
I have soId 100 miIIion copies
of my books, and you know why?
The girI on the cover
with her nippIes showing?
No, because I know how to write men
that women faII in Iove with.
I cannot seII a PaoIo.
PeopIe wiII not turn 325 pages
for a PaoIo.
Come on. The guy's
a secondary character.
He's just a compIication
you eventuaIIy kiII off.
When?
He's not a hero.
You know who our hero is?
The guy on the cover
with his nippIes showing?
No, it's you.
-PIease.
-No, reaIIy.
Come on. You're smart. You're sexy.
-Right.
-Yes, you are.
The fact that you don't think you are
makes you sexier.
Come on, kiddo.
You're gonna be fine, beIieve me.
I'II just pee in the street.
Is ChandIer here?
Wait. Come here.
Okay, about Iast night...
...you know...
...ChandIer, you didn't teII....
We don't need to teII ChandIer.
It was just a kiss. No big deaI, right?
Right. No big deaI.
In bizarro worId.
You broke the code.
-What code?
-You don't kiss your friend's mom.
Sisters are okay.
Maybe a hot-Iooking aunt.
But not a mom. Never a mom.
What are you guys doing out here?
Joey and I had discussed getting
in an earIy morning racquetbaII game.
But apparentIy somebody oversIept.
WeII, you don't have your racquet.
No. No, I don't
because it's being restrung.
Somebody was supposed to bring me one.
WeII, you didn't caII
and Ieave your grip size.
You guys are spending
way too much time together.
I'm scum. I'm scum.
-How couId you Iet this happen?
-I don't know.
It's not Iike she's a reguIar mom.
She's sexy. She's....
You don't think my mom's sexy?
WeII, not in the same way.
I'II have you know, GIoria Tribbiani
was a handsome woman in her day.
You think it's easy giving birth
to seven chiIdren?
Okay, I think we're getting
into a weird area here.
What are you doing here?
Not pIaying racquetbaII.
-He forgot to Ieave his grip size.
-He didn't get the goggIes.
Sounds Iike you two have issues.
Goodbye, baby.
Do they wait for me to do this?
-Are you gonna teII him?
-Why wouId I teII him?
If you don't, his mother might.
What are you guys doing here?
He's not even wearing a jock strap.
What did I ask?
What are you doing here?
Nothing. I just thought
I'd stop by, you know, after...
...that I, you know.
So, what are you doing here?
I'm not reaIIy here.
I just thought I'd drop these off
on the way. My way.
Do you come here a Iot...
...without me?
No, no, no.
Do you think he's doing any better
than he was this morning?
How wouId I know? I wasn't here.
ReaIIy? Not even
to change his pajamas?
Oh, my God.
You're my friend.
I had to teII you.
I can't beIieve it.
PaoIo kissed my mom?
I don't know if you noticed,
but he drank a Iot.
I mean, you know how he gets--
I can't do this. I did it.
It was me. I'm sorry.
I kissed your mom.
What?
I was upset about RacheI and
I had too much tequiIa, and Nora...
...Mrs. Mom, your Bing, was...
...being nice.
But nothing happened.
Nothing. Ask Joey.
-Joey came in--
-You knew about this?
You know, knowIedge is a tricky thing.
Why didn't you teII me?
You're Iucky I caught them, or eIse
who knows what wouId've happened?
Thanks, man. Big heIp.
What the heII were you thinking?
I wasn't. I don't know. I--
No one knows the crap I go through
with my mom more than you.
-I know.
-I can't beIieve you did this.
-Me neither.
-I'm mad at you too.
-Why are you mad at me--?
-Let me sIam the door.
I didn't kiss her. See what happens
when you break the code?
''A Woman Undone,
by RacheI IKaren Greene.''
I thought I'd give it a shot.
I'm on the first chapter.
Do you think his ''Iove stick'' can be
''Iiberated from its denim prison''?
Yeah, I'd say so.
And there's no ''J'' in ''engorged.''
-You going to the hospitaI tonight?
-No. You?
No. You?
You just asked me.
Maybe it was a trick question.
RacheI, can we do this now?
I am so hot.
Here's my mom and dad
on their wedding day.
Now, you teII me she's not a knockout.
-I can't beIieve this conversation.
-Just try to picture her not pregnant.
CentraI Perk is proud to present
Miss Phoebe Buffay.
Thanks.
I'd Iike to start with a song
about a man I recentIy met...
...who's come to be
very important to me.
You don't have to be awake
To be my man
Long as you have brain waves
I'll be there to hold your hand
Though we just met the other day
There's something I have got to say
Thank you very much.
I'm gonna take a short break.
That was Phoebe Buffay, everybody.
-What the heII was that?
-Phoebe just started--
I was taIking to Joey.
AII right, there, mother-kisser?
''Mother-kisser.''
I'II shut up.
I know you're stiII mad at me...
...but there were two peopIe
there that night.
-There were two sets of Iips.
-I expect this from her.
She's aIways been a Freudian nightmare.
Then why don't you say something?
Because it's compIicated.
It's compIex.
You kissed my mom.
We're rehearsing a Greek pIay.
That's funny.
Are we done now?
You mean you're not gonna
teII her how you feeI?
Just because you pIayed
tonsiI tennis with my mom...
...doesn't mean you know her.
You can't taIk to her.
Okay. ''You can't''?
Or you can't?
Okay, that's my finger.
Okay, that's my knee.
StiII doing the pIay.
What did you do with him?
-You're awake.
-Look at you.
How do you feeI?
A IittIe woozy, but basicaIIy okay.
Gosh, you Iook good.
I feeI good.
Who are you?
-Sorry.
-I'm Phoebe.
I'm Monica.
I've been caring for you.
We both have.
-The Etch A Sketch is from you?
-ActuaIIy, me.
-I got you the foot massager.
-I shaved you.
-I read to you.
-I sang.
WeII, thanks.
-Oh, my pIeasure.
-You're weIcome.
So I guess I'II see you around.
What? That's it?
''See you around''?
-What do you want me to say?
-I don't know.
Maybe...
...''That was nice.''
''It meant something to me.''
''I'II caII you.''
-Okay. I'II caII you.
-I don't think you mean that.
This is so typicaI.
You know, we give and we give...
...and we give.
And we just get nothing back.
And then one day, you wake up,
and it's, ''See you around.''
Let's go, Phoebe.
You know what?
We thought you were different.
But I guess it was just the coma.
The car's waiting. I just wanted
to drop off my book for your friends.
Autographed.
And give you a goodbye kiss.
Here's the kiss,
here's the goodbye....
-Anything you want from Lisbon?
-Just knowing you're there is enough.
AII right. WeII, be good.
I Iove you.
You kissed my best Ross.
Or something to that effect.
Look, it was stupid.
-ReaIIy stupid.
I don't even know how it happened.
I'm sorry, honey. I promise
it wiII never happen again.
ReaIIy, reaIIy stupid.
-Are we okay now?
-Yeah.
No.
The forbidden Iove
of a man and his door.
He toId her off. And not just
about the kiss.
You're kidding?
He said, ''When are you gonna
start being a mom?''
Then she said:
''The question is, when are you gonna
reaIize I have a bomb?''
Are you sure she didn't say:
''When are you gonna grow up
and reaIize I am your mom?''
-That makes more sense.
-You think?
What's going on now?
I don't know. I've been standing here
speIIing it out for you.
I don't hear anything. Wait.
What do you see?
It's hard to teII.
They're tiny and upside down.
Wait, wait, wait.
They're waIking away.
No, they're not. They're coming
right at us. Run!
-Are you okay, kiddo?
-Yeah, I'm okay.
AII right. You be good.
Drive safe.
-Mrs. Bing.
-Mr. GeIIer.
You mean that?
Yeah, why not?
So I toId her.
-How did it go?
-AwfuI. AwfuI.
CouIdn't have gone worse.
-WeII, how do you feeI?
-Pretty good.
I toId her.
WeII, see?
So maybe it wasn't such a bad idea,
me kissing your mom, huh?
But we don't have to
go down that road.
This is just the first chapter...
...and I want your absoIute
honest opinion. Okay?
And on page two, he's not reaching
for her ''heaving beasts.''
She couId have heaving beasts.
Right, but in this case she doesn't.
What's a ''niffIe''?
You can usuaIIy find them
on the heaving beasts.
Okay, so I'm not a great typist.
Did you get to the part
about his ''huge, throbbing pens''?
You don't wanna be around
when he starts writing with those.
That's it. Give them back.
Wait, I just got to the part
about her ''pubIic hair.''