Can't get the monkey off your back?
Then put it in your mouth...
... with Monkeyshine Beer.
Get it, monkey
Get it, get it, monkey
Monkey, monkey
Monkeyshine Beer.
'Cause it's a jungle out there.
That commerciaI aIways makes me sad.
But the guy opens his beer,
the girIs run at him...
...so everything works out okay.
I meant,
the monkey reminds me of MarceI.
I can see that.
Because they both have those big
brown eyes and the IittIe pouty chin.
And the fact that
they're both monkeys?
Did I do the right thing,
giving him away?
Ross, you had to.
He was humping everything in sight.
My MaIibu Barbie won't
be wearing white to her wedding.
Remember when he'd borrow your hat...
...and when you got it back,
there'd be monkey raisins in it?
He Ioved that joke.
When he did it, it was funny.
When I did it to my boss...
...suddenIy I had this big
attitude probIem.
The One After the SuperbowI
Hey, check it out.
Guess what I got?
Rhythm?
No. My first fan maiI.
''Dear Dr. Ramoray:
I Iove you and wouId do
anything to have you.''
My gosh. ''Your not-so-secret
admirer, Erika Ford.''
Oh, wait.
''P.S. EncIosed, pIease find
1 4 of my eyeIashes.''
In Crazy WorId, that means
you're married.
It's not addressed to Days of our
Lives. It came to your apartment.
-She was in our buiIding.
-Oh, my God.
I got my very own staIker.
You're so Iucky.
I have to share with guys at work.
Remember we taIked about ''good thing,
bad thing''? This is a bad thing.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
Where are you off to?
There's a paIeontoIogy
conference in L.A.
I figured I'd go, drive down
to the zoo and surprise MarceI.
He wiII be surprised.
TiII he reaIizes he's a monkey...
...and isn't capabIe of that emotion.
Phoebe?
That cute guy is here again.
Okay, so everyone...
...pretend I'm teIIing a story.
It's reaIIy funny.
So everyone just Iaugh.
Now!
I know, I know.
-HeIIo.
-Hi.
-I'm Rob Donnen.
-Hi, Rob Donnen.
I don't know a thing about music
but I think you're great.
Oh! Wow.
Anyway, I scheduIe performers
for chiIdren's Iibraries.
I was thinking, have you thought
about pIaying your songs for kids?
I wouId Iove to have kids...
...hear me pIay the songs
that I wiII write for them.
What'II we do for dinner?
We couId cook for ourseIves.
-HeIIo.
-It's Erika.
My God. The staIker!
It's open.
Hit her with a frying pan.
Good idea.
But we want a backup pIan,
in case she isn't a cartoon.
Let's get out of here.
The one time they're not home.
We'II Ieave. When we pass her, she
won't know it's me. We've never met.
That's how radio stars
escape staIkers.
She's coming.
It's me.
This is it.
This is how we're gonna die.
You ready?
Wait, wait, wait.
Erika!
-Mr. GeIIer?
-Yes, hi.
Dean Lipson, zoo administrator.
You had a question?
I can't find the monkey
I donated Iast year.
He's a capuchin,
answers to the name MarceI?
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
MarceI has passed on.
Oh, my God! What happened?
He got sick,
and then he got sicker...
...then he got a IittIe better.
But then he died.
I can't beIieve this.
I'm sorry, Mr. GeIIer.
But you know, there's an oId saying:
''Sometimes monkeys die.''
It's not a great saying...
...but it certainIy is fitting today.
-Someone shouId've caIIed me.
-I'm sorry.
Look, I know this can't bring him
back, but here. It's just a gesture.
Zoo doIIars?
Yes, and come see the bird show at 4.
The macaws wear hats.
It's cuter if your monkey
hasn't just died.
I know.
I can't beIieve Joey's having Iunch
with his staIker. What is she Iike?
Remember Kathy Bates in Misery?
WeII, she Iooks
the exact opposite of that.
And she's not crazy?
Oh, no.
She's a totaI whack-job.
She thinks that Joey is
actuaIIy Dr. Drake Ramoray.
Oh, my God.
And he's going out with her?
He cannot pursue this.
Just because she thinks she can truIy
see Joey through her magic box...
...doesn't mean she's not a person.
Does she not deserve happiness
or Iove?
Why are you Iooking at me?
He wants to boff the maniac.
Are you okay?
No, I'm nervous.
Maybe if I picture them
in their underwear....
That's not a good idea.
That's why the Iast guy got fired.
I'm used to pIaying for grownups.
Grownups drink coffee,
do their grownup thing.
And kids Iisten.
It's just a huge responsibiIity.
What?
Are you gonna kiss me?
I was thinking about it.
Okay.
AIrighty. Let's pIay some tunes.
Let's go find our seats.
ChandIer?
HoId on a second.
He thinks he can.
Oh, what the heII?
He can.
-Hi, everybody. I'm Phoebe.
-Hi, Phoebe!
I'm gonna pIay some songs
about grandparents, okay?
Now Grandma's a person
Who everyone likes
She bought you a train
And a bright shiny bike
But lately she hasn't
Been coming to dinner
And last time you saw her
She looked so much thinner
Now, your mom and your dad said
She moved to Peru
But the truth is she died
And someday you will too
I'II have the griIIed saImon.
And the doctor wiII have the risotto.
-Oh, Drake, isn't it amazing?
-Yeah, it is.
What?
WeII, here we sit, deviI-may-care...
...and a whiIe ago you were
re-attaching Simone's spinaI cord.
That was a tricky one.
In reaIity, that operation takes 10
hours. They onIy showed two minutes.
Who's ''they''?
No one.
Drake, you are so taIented.
Let me see those hands.
These hands, these beautifuI hands.
I couId just eat them.
But I won't.
Otherwise my watch wouId faII off.
No, seriousIy.
These hands, these miracIe,
magicaI, Iife-giving hands.
Just to be near them, touch them,
maybe even Iick one?
AII right. Just one.
You're good at that.
-Oh, my God! Someone, he's choking.
-Is anyone here a doctor?
Yes, the best doctor in SaIem.
Dr. Drake Ramoray.
Meet me in the nocturnaI
house in 1 5 minutes.
Hey, Iook. I don't reaIIy enjoy
being with other men that way.
But...zoo doIIars?
It's about your monkey.
It's aIive.
I don't understand.
Why didn't you heIp that man?
Because I'm a neurosurgeon...
...and that was cIearIy a case of...
...''foodaI chokage.''
I gotta teII you something--
No.
You don't have to teII me anything.
You don't have to expIain yourseIf.
Who am I to question
the great Dr. Ramoray?
-I shouId be happy to be near you.
-Hey, I--
Hey what?
That's it. Just hey.
Like at the end of a dance. ''Hey!''
There'll be times when you get older
When you'll want to sleep with people
Just to make them like you
But don't!
'Cause that's another thing...
...that you don't wanna do
Everybody!
That's another thing
That you don't wanna do
-ExceIIent!
-Very informative.
Not at aII inappropriate.
Thank you for coming.
There are cookies in the back.
That was great.
The kids Ioved you.
I rock.
You know why?
Because you toId the truth.
Nobody teIIs kids the truth.
You were incredibIe.
But...?
-How'd you know there was a ''but''?
-I sense things.
It was either ''but'' or ''butter.''
I think some of the parents....
They were hoping that...
...you'd pIay songs
about barnyard animaIs.
I can do that.
ReaIIy?
Because that wouId be fantastic.
What? You wanna kiss me?
I'm thinking about it.
If I get a Iibrary card,
can I take you out some time?
What?
I'm unempIoyed.
The bat.
Ambassador of darkness.
FIitting out of his cave
Iike a winged messenger.
SightIess specter of the macabre.
Buddy, my monkey?
Oh, yeah, right.
There was a break-in
a few months back. Inside job.
Your monkey was taken.
AIong with a snowy egret,
a two-toed sIoth...
...and three sweatshirts
from the zoo gift shop.
But the zoo toId me
that my monkey was dead.
The zoo.
You beIieve everything
the zoo teIIs you?
That's the onIy thing
the zoo's ever toId me.
Of course they say that.
They don't want bad pubIicity.
It's a big cover-up.
Do you have any idea
how high up this thing goes?
That guy Lipson?
Lipson knows?
-Who eIse knows?
-I onIy know Lipson.
Lipson knows, huh?
HeIIo, Mr. Possum.
Enigma of the trees,
upside-down denizen of the night.
-Taunting gravity--
-Buddy, my monkey?
Word on the street--
When I say ''street,''
I mean those pretend streets here.
Of course.
Your monkey found a new career...
...in the entertainment fieId.
That's aII I know.
This is unbeIievabIe!
So, what is this information
worth to you, my friend?
Are you trying
to get me to bribe you?
Maybe.
But you aIready toId me everything.
Check it out.
He actuaIIy is the Monkeyshine monkey.
What'II you do?
I'II caII the beer company
and try to find him.
That's what I did
when I Iost my CIydesdaIes.
Okay, hi again.
Hi, Phoebe.
Today we're gonna start with
some songs about barnyard animaIs.
The cow in the meadow goes moo
The farmer hits him and grinds him up
And that's how we get hamburgers
Now chickens!
-You're the only one who can save her.
-Damn it. I'm a doctor. I'm not God.
There goes my beIief system.
It's Erika.
-Quick. Shut off the TV.
-I wanna see what happens.
I get LesIie out of the coma.
We kiss.
You were just kissing Sabrina.
RacheI, it's a worId
where Joey is a neurosurgeon.
Hey, Erika. Come in.
How'd you get here so fast?
I just saw you in SaIem.
Right, they choppered me in.
What's up?
You're having a party too.
-Is she here?
-Who?
Sabrina. I know about you two.
I saw you
kissing in the doctor's Iounge.
It's not what you think--
You toId me I was the onIy one.
AII right, Iook.
That's it.
We shouIdn't see each other.
I shouId have toId you before...
...but I am not Drake Ramoray.
I'm not a doctor. I'm an actor.
I pretend to be a doctor.
Oh, my God.
Do the peopIe at the hospitaI know?
Somebody wanna heIp me out here?
Oh, I know. I know.
Where am I?
University Hospital...
... where you've been for 18 years.
How can you be here and there?
Because it's a TV show.
What are you getting at?
Nice girI. Not great with concepts.
I'm not Drake.
That's right.
He's not Drake. He's...
...Hans Ramoray, Drake's eviI twin.
Is this true?
Yes. Yes, it is true.
And I know this...
...because he pretended
to be Drake to sIeep with me.
And he toId me
he wouId run away with me.
And he didn't.
And you Ieft the toiIet seat up,
you bastard!
Is aII this true?
Yes, I'm afraid it is.
You deserve much better than me.
You deserve to be with the reaI Drake,
who you feII in Iove with.
Go to SaIem. Find him.
He's the guy for you.
Oh, Hans.
Hans?
Hans.
Yo, eviI twin!
Right. Goodbye, Erika.
Good Iuck in SaIem.
Take care.
I'II never forget you, Hans.
-Okay, the peopIe who threw the water!
-HeIping you out.
Fired?
Why?
The Iibrary board got compIaints
from parents about your songs.
I can't beIieve it. The Iibrary?
Books. Free speech.
-Newspapers on sticks.
-I know.
And the kids? Did you teII your board
that the kids want to hear the truth?
No.
I see.
Maybe if you just pIayed
some reguIar kiddie songs....
No. What do you want me to be?
Like some...
...stupid, big, Iike, purpIe dinosaur?
-You don't have to be Barney.
-Who's Barney?
You'II never beIieve it.
-Let me guess.
-What?
Some WeebIes actuaIIy do faII down?
A stitch in time now onIy saves seven?
What do you got?
WeII...
...never mind.
What? What?
I tracked down MarceI.
He's heaIthy, he's happy...
...and he's in New York fiIming
Outbreak 2: The Virus Takes Manhattan.
You're kidding!
-This is amazing.
-I know.
I finaIIy get on TV and
the monkey's making movies.
RacheI, I'm ready.
Excuse me. Is this where the
singing Iady is, who teIIs the truth?
I guess that's me.
She's here!
Sometimes men love women
Sometimes men love men
Then there are bisexuals
Though some just say
They're kidding themselves
I haven't seen my monkey in a year.
You never Iook down in the shower?
I'm not aIIowed one joke
in the ''monkey is penis'' genre?
Back up, pIease.
Back up. Come on.
Excuse me.
Where can we find the monkey?
It's a cIosed set.
You don't understand.
I'm a friend of his.
We used to Iive together.
I have a timeshare
in the Poconos with FIipper.
There he is!
Hey! Buddy!
MarceI. MarceI!
In the jungle
The mighty jungle
The lion sleeps tonight
In the jungle
The mighty jungle
The lion sleeps tonight
Excuse me, this is a--
CIosed set. We know.
We're friends with the monkey.
Good morning.
Look who I brought!
Your friend, Harry EIefante.
Whoa, dude. Burn.
I don't get it. He seemed
so happy to see me yesterday.
Don't take it personaI. He's under
pressure, starring in a movie.
How big of a star is MarceI?
In human terms? I'd say...
...CybiII Shepherd.
So you guys in the movie
or you just reaIIy paranoid?
Hey, SaI?
-Jerry's asking if the monkey's ready.
-Excuse me?
Jerry is the director?
Which one's he?
The one in the director's chair.
Gotcha.
-Pheebs, waIk with me.
-Okay.
Why am I waIking with you?
We're going over here
so we can get away from...
...the horribIe fIesh-eating virus!
For the Iove of God,
Iisten to me!
Is he Iooking? Is he Iooking?
-We've got a probIem.
-TeII me.
Can't do Chris' makeup.
She won't acknowIedge her mustache.
-Is it bad?
-It Iooks Iike her eyebrow feII down.
UnIess we convince her to bIeach it,
Van Damme wiII be kissing Gabe KapIan.
I'II taIk to her.
I hate actors.
Nice camoufIage. For a minute,
I aImost didn't see you.
Excuse me.
Is your name ChandIer?
-Yes, it is.
-ChandIer Bing?
Do you know me
or are you just good at this game?
I'm Susie Moss.
Fourth grade? GIasses?
I carried a box of
animaI crackers Iike a purse?
Susie Moss.
Right. Yeah. Wow.
You Iook....
Great job growing up.
It's nice to see you don't stiII
wear the cap with the mirrors.
I graduated fourth grade
and reaIized I wasn't a pimp.
Remember the cIass pIay?
You puIIed up my skirt and the
entire auditorium saw my underpants?
Yes. Back then,
I used humor as a defense mechanism.
Thank God I don't do that anymore.
So? What have you
been doing since chiIdhood?
WeII, I got a new beIt.
I wondered.
-Oh, my God.
-What? What?
It's Jean-CIaude Van Damme.
I didn't know he was in this.
He is so hot.
You think?
The MuscIes from BrusseIs?
Wham-Bam Van Damme?
Did you see Timecop?
-No. Was he any good in it?
-RacheI, he totaIIy changed time.
So why don't you go taIk to him?
Go teII him he's cute.
What couId happen?
He couId hear me.
-I'm doing it for you.
-Don't you dare. Don't.
Don't!
TeII him I cook.
-Excuse me. Hi.
-Hi.
This is gonna sound kind of goofy...
...but my friend over there...
...who cooks, by the way....
She thinks you're cute.
You don't think I'm cute?
I don't know.
Do you think you're cute?
We're getting off the track.
I was supposed to teII you...
...my friend thinks you're cute.
What shouId I teII her?
You can teII her
I think her friend is cute.
Stephen Hurs wouId
eat things for money.
David Stein had no eIbows.
Who got caught masturbating?
That's not what he was doing.
He was Iooking for his bus money.
-Makeup!
-That's me. I gotta go.
Oh. Okay.
How many times must I touch you on
the arm before you ask me on a date?
WeII, Iet's try one more.
There you go. Ernie's, 8:00?
I'II be there.
And if things go weII, maybe this time
I'II get to see your underwear.
No one was around to hear that?
So, what did he say?
What a jerk!
I kept taIking about you
and he kept asking me out.
NaturaIIy, you know, I said no.
Thanks anyway.
He just kept asking...
...and asking, asking, asking....
If you want to go out with him,
you can.
Sounds Iike a jerk to me, but--
Jean-CIaude, she said yes.
I'II see you tonight.
Thank you.
Then Jean-CIaude took me
to Crossroads...
...where we hung out
with Drew Barrymore.
Oh, man. She's so smoking.
She has the greatest set--
No guys around, huh?
-Anybody need anything?
-I'II have espresso.
I'II get it. If I ask you,
you'II end up drinking it yourseIf.
-That is so unfair.
-I know.
Like you'd drink her coffee after
what you did with Van Damme?
I have to canceI racquetbaII tonight.
MarceI's trainer wiII Iet me
have him for a whiIe.
-You're bIowing me off?
-We can rescheduIe for Saturday.
UnIess you hook up
with a bunch of pigeons.
Stick a fork in me...
...I am done.
-Stick a fork what?
-Like when you're cooking a steak.
I don't eat meat.
How do you know
when vegetabIes are done?
You don't.
You eat them and you can teII.
Then eat me, I'm done.
I've met the perfect woman.
We're on her couch, fooIing around...
...and then she turns to me and says:
''Ever want to do it in an eIevator?''
-What did you say?
-I beIieve my exact words were:
-How do you know if you wanna do that?
-You just know.
We gotta go.
Got a reservation in 30 minutes.
No. What I had pIanned shouIdn't take
more than two, three minutes, tops.
Two hundred seconds of passion!
We gotta go.
But...
...here's an idea.
Have you ever worn
women's underwear?
WeII, yes, actuaIIy...
...but they were my Aunt Edna's.
And there were three of us in there.
I was thinking
it wouId be kind of sexy...
...if you wore mine tonight at dinner.
You want me to wear your panties?
CouId you?
If I wear your underwear,
then what wouId you be wearing?
You're sweII.
Got the music. Got the dinner.
I made MarceI's favorite dish,
banana cake...
...with meaIworm.
CandIe.
What do you think's
gonna happen here tonight?
HeIIo.
Hi, are you on your way over--?
No, I understand.
A monkey's gotta work.
It's no big deaI. It's not Iike
I had anything speciaI pIanned.
Yeah. Okay.
Okay. Bye.
I'm sorry, man.
-FeeI that?
-What?
The moment we shouId have
stopped hoIding hands?
RacheI, why don't you
start taIking first?
AII right.
This is totaIIy unjustified.
She gave me the green Iight.
I did nothing--
Do you think I can't
see you in the TV set?
If there is something
you'd Iike to share--
You had no right.
-That's the most ridicuIous--
-You soId me out.
-I did not.
-You absoIuteIy--
WouId you Iet me taIk?
Did you just fIick me?
You wouIdn't Iet me finish and I was--
That hurt.
Quit fIicking.
-Stop fIicking!
-You fIicked me first!
Let's not do this.
Happy thoughts. Happy thoughts.
Now I'm gonna kick some ass.
AII right.
Now, I wiII Iet go if you both stop.
You want me to stop seeing him?
You want me to teII him
you're seeing him instead?
-Is that what you want?
-Okay.
That's what you want?
Yes.
-Fine.
There we go.
If we were in prison,
you guys wouId be my bitches.
-Thanks for Ietting me tag aIong.
-Forget about it.
How you doing there, squirmy?
I'm hanging in.
And a IittIe out.
So, assistant to the director?
That's an exciting job.
You must have responsibiIities--
I don't do the casting.
What are you guys gonna eat?
How come aII I can think about is
putting that ice in my mouth...
...and Iicking you aII over?
'Cause I went to an aII-boys high
schooI and God is making up for it?
I want you right here...
...right now.
Right now, right here?
Don't you think
we're in a pubIic pIace?
They do have the shrimp.
Meet me in the bathroom.
I'm going to the bathroom now.
He Iikes to keep us in the Ioop.
Come on.
I can't beIieve we're doing this.
AII right, mister.
Let's see those panties.
AIrighty.
But you know what
wouId be even sexier?
What?
If you didn't have
your shirt tucked into them.
AII right. Now, I wouId Iike
to see you wearing nothing but them.
Take your cIothes off.
I hope you reaIize we'II miss
hearing about the speciaIs.
Come on, hurry.
Do you want this done quick
or done right?
AII right, turn around.
I wanna see you from behind.
Somebody's been doing
his Buns of Steel video.
So you want me
to cIench anything or...?
Susie?
This is for the 4th grade.
-What do you mean?
-What do I mean?
I mean underpants, mister.
That's what.
What? What do you mean?
My skirt...
...you Iifted. Kids Iaughing.
I was Susie Underpants tiII I was 18.
That was 4th grade.
How couId you stiII be upset?
CaII me in 20 years and teII me
if you're stiII upset about this.
I hope you reaIize you're not
getting these underpants back.
I can't beIieve this.
Just two weeks ago,
I was watching Sudden Death...
...and now I'm on a date
with Jean-CIaude Van Damme.
Can you beat up that guy?
-Can you beat up that guy?
-Sure.
This is so wiId.
I gotta admit, I was surprised
that you agreed to go on a bIind date.
NormaIIy I wouId not do it.
What made you make
the exception for me?
RacheI toId me...
...you wanted a threesome
with me and Drew Barrymore.
By the way,
Drew has some ground ruIes and....
-Say you're sorry.
-No.
-Say it!
-No! I'm not gonna.
Say it. Say it.
Oh, great.
Say you're sorry
or your sweater gets it.
That is my favorite sweater.
My third-date sweater.
Say you're sorry.
You wanna pIay?
Okay, Iet's pIay.
Let's pIay.
What'II you do?
Give me my sweater
or it's handbag marinara.
You don't have the guts.
At Ieast I wasn't too chicken
to teII a guy he was cute.
Stop! Stop the madness!
This is crazy.
Who can even remember
why you're fighting?
Yes, that's right.
But stiII....
Look at your purse.
Look at your sweater.
Look at yourseIves.
I'II heIp you fix your sweater.
I'II heIp you...
...throw out your purse.
I'm sorry I made you stop seeing him.
I'm sorry I went out with him
when I knew you Iiked him.
I'm sorry that I borrowed your gIoves.
-Joey?
-Ma?
Joey.
ChandIer?
You're stiII here?
I thought you guys took off.
She took off with my cIothes.
-Are you naked in there?
-WeII, not exactIy.
I'm wearing panties.
You aIways wear panties?
No, no. This is the first time.
Wow! TaIk about your bad Iuck.
The first time you try panties and
someone waIks off with your cIothes.
I was not trying them out.
Susie asked me to wear them.
Let me see.
No. I'm not Ietting you
or anybody eIse see, ever.
AII right, aII right.
Someone's fIossing.
Joey, some peopIe don't Iike that.
ChandIer's wearing panties.
-What? Let me see.
-You don't have to see.
Hi, tushy.
One of you give me your underpants.
Can't heIp you. I'm not wearing any.
How can you not be wearing any?
I'm getting heat from the guy
in the hot pink thong.
Look, Ross. I'II give you
$50 for your underpants.
-Can I have the miIk?
-I'm aImost done.
Keep your panties on.
I'm in the movie!
-What happened?
-A victim caIIed in sick.
Cathy recommended me and boom!
I'm dying on a gurney.
MarceI finished his Iast scene
if you want to say goodbye.
That's okay. He's probabIy
got parties to go to and stuff.
He's moved on.
That's the way it goes, right?
-Oh, my God.
-What?
Sorry it didn't work out between us.
Or us.
Drew was very disappointed.
Okay. WeII, bye.
Goodbye.
WeII, bye for me too.
Okay. WeII, bye-bye again.
Okay.
Perhaps the three of us just couId:
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Are you sure?
I can crush a waInut with my butt.
-Oh, no, no, no. Impressive.
-But no.
Maybe if I were baking.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Bye, MarceI.
See you on the big screen.
You keep peopIe drinking
that beer, okay?
I'II miss you, buddy.
Bye.
I think I want to write
a song about aII this.
Except one of the strings
on my guitar is broken.
ChandIer, can I borrow your G-string?
-How Iong you been waiting to say that?
-About 20 minutes!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
Cut!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
Cut!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
Mommy!
Can't you see what's going on?
This man is dead!