No, no, we're done!
The One With the Dozen Lasagnas
Aunt Silv, stop yelling!
lf you'd told me
vegetarian lasagna...
...l would've made
vegetarian lasagna.
The meat's only every third layer.
Maybe you could scrape.
Ross, did you really read
all these baby boolks?
You could plunlk me down in
any woman's uterus, no compass...
...and l could find my way
out lilke that!
This is cool.
lt says in some parts of the world
people eat the placenta.
And we're done with the yogurt.
Sorry.
l did this as a favor.
l am not a caterer.
What do you want me to do
with a dozen lasagnas?
Nice tallk, Aunt Silv.
You lkiss Uncle Freddie
with that mouth?
Ross, listen. Do you lknow that right
now your baby is only this big?
This is your baby.
''Hi, Daddy.''
Hello.
''How come you don't live with Mommy?''
''How come Mommy lives
with that other lady?''
''What's a lesbian?''
Honey, you can say it. Poconos.
Poconos. lt's lilke ''polke a nose.''
Polke a nose.
-So did l hear Poconos?
-Yes.
My sister's giving us her place
for the weelkend.
First weelkend together.
-lt's a big step.
-l lknow.
-lt's just a weelkend. Big deal.
-Wasn't this supposed to be a fling?
Shouldn't it be...
...flung by now?
We are way past a ''fling.''
l'm feeling things l've read about
in Danielle Steel boolks.
When l'm with him,
l'm just totally....
Nauseous.
l'm physically nauseous.
What am l supposed to do?
Call lmmigration?
l could call lmmigration.
What?
Ugly Nalked Guy is malking
shadow puppets.
Loolk, it's Abraham Lincoln.
Oh, right!
Go. Go!
l love babies with
their little baby shoes...
...and their little baby toes
and their little hands....
Olkay, you're gonna have to stop that.
Forever.
Need a new table.
You thinlk?
-Come on in.
-Hello.
l brought the boolks...
...and Monica sends her love
along with this lasagna.
Great! ls it vegetarian?
Because Susan doesn't eat meat.
l'm pretty sure that it is.
Nineteen weelks, the breasts
are starting to swell.
According to the literature.
-l got the results of the amnio.
-Tell me. ls everything...?
-Totally and completely healthy.
-That is great!
When did you and Susan
meet Huey Lewis?
That's our friend Tanya.
Of course, it's your friend Tanya.
-Don't you wanna lknow about the sex?
-The sex?
l'm having enough trouble with
the image of you and Susan together.
But when you throw in Tanya....
The sex of the baby, Ross.
You lknow the sex of the baby?
-Want to lknow?
-No.
l don't want to. Absolutely not.
You shouldn't lknow until
you loolk down there...
...and see, ''Oh, there it is.''
Or isn't.
-Hello, Ross.
-Susan.
So?
So did you hear?
Yes, we did.
Everything's A-Olkay.
Oh, that's so cool!
lt really is.
Do we lknow?
We certainly do.
lt's going to be a--
Hello?
A guy who doesn't wanna lknow
is standing here.
Well, is it what
we thought it would be?
What--?
What did we thinlk it'd be?
l don't wanna lknow.
Don't wanna lknow.
l should probably just go.
-Well, thanlks for the boolks.
-No problem. Olkay.
Susan.
Who should we call first?
Your follks or Deb and Rhona?
Hello?
Never mind.
I don't wanna know.
Because it was my table,
l have to buy a new one?
-That's the rule.
-What rule? There's no rule.
-You owe me a table.
-How did you get there?
lt was fine until your brealkfast
adventure with Angela Delvecio.
You lknew about that?
The impressions in the butter
left little to the imagination.
How about if we split it?
-What do you mean, buy it together?
-Yeah.
-Do you thinlk we're ready for that?
-Why not?
lt's a big commitment.
What if one of us wants to move out?
-You're moving out?
-l'm not.
-You'd tell me if you were, right?
-Yes.
-lt's just, with my last roommate--
-l lknow all about Kip.
We bought a hibachi, then he ran off
and got married. Things got ugly.
Let me aslk you something.
Was Kip a better roommate than me?
Oh, don't do that.
There's changes in your schedule.
Your 4:00 herbal massage is at 4:0.
And Miss Summerfield
canceled her 5:0 shiatsu.
Thanlks.
Oh, here comes your :00.
l don't mean to sound unprofessional,
but-- Yum!
Paolo! Hi! What are you doing here?
Rachella tell me you...
...massage?
Well, Rachella's right.
Oh, olkay.
l don't lknow what you just said,
so let's start.
l am...
...being nalked?
That's your decision.
Some people prefer to talke off--
Being nalked!
l can't believe you don't
wanna lknow. l couldn't not lknow.
lf the doctor lknows,
Carol and Susan lknow--
And Monica lknows.
How? l don't even lknow.
Carol called to thanlk me
for the lasagna. She told me.
So what's it gonna be?
-Oh, great! Now he lknows.
-l'm just excited about being an aunt.
Or an uncle.
-Hey, Phoebe.
-Hey, Pheebs.
Fine!
-What's the matter?
-Nothing. l'm just out of sorts.
Well, you can use some of my sorts.
l rarely use them.
Can we get some cappuccino
over here?
Oh, right! That's me!
That table place closes at 7. Come on.
Fine.
What is it?
-All right. You lknow Paolo?
-l'm familiar with his worlk.
He made a move on me.
-The store will be open tomorrow.
-More coffee, please.
Well, what happened?
He came in for a massage,
and everything was fine until....
-Oh, my God.
-Are you sure?
Oh, yeah. l'm sure.
And all of a sudden, his hands
weren't the problem anymore.
Was it...?
Boy Scouts could've camped
under there.
Wow.
-What did you do?
-l dealt with it lilke a professional.
''Ooh,'' what?
--ma Thurman.
-The actress!
-Uma Thurman!
Thanlks, Rach.
-What'll you do?
-You have to tell her.
lt's your moral obligation as a friend,
as a woman. lt's a feminist issue.
Guys?
-You have to.
-Feminist issue? That's where l went.
-She is gonna hate me!
-Yeah, well....
Will you piclk one?
Just piclk one.
-Here, how about that one?
-That's patio furniture.
So what? Lilke people will come in
and thinlk, ''Oh, l'm outside again.''
Fine.
What about the birds?
l don't lknow. They don't say,
''Hello, sit here. Eat something.''
-You piclk one.
-Olkay. How about the ladybugs?
Forget about the birds, but big red
insects suggest fine dining.
-Fine! Want the birds? Get the birds!
-Not lilke that, l won't.
Kip would have lilked the birds.
-Hi, Pheebs.
-What's going on?
-Are you moving out?
-l'm getting ready for the weelkend.
Are your weelkends longer
than two days?
These aren't all my suitcases.
This one's Paolo's.
-Rachel, can we tallk for a sec?
-Well, sure.
Just for a sec, Paolo's on his way.
We haven't lknown each other that long.
There are three things
you should lknow:
One, my friends are the most
important thing in my life.
Two, l never lie.
And three, l malke the best
oatmeal raisin coolkies in the world.
Olkay. Thanlks, Pheebs.
-Oh, my God!
-l lknow.
Why have l never tasted these?
l don't malke them a lot, because
it's not fair to the other coolkies.
These are the best
oatmeal raisin coolkies.
-Which proves that l never lie.
-l guess you don't.
Paolo made a pass at me.
What do you thinlk?
lt's the most beautiful table
l've seen.
l lknow.
Will you balance plates
on these heads?
Who cares? We'll eat at the sinlk.
Come on!
Heads up, Ross.
Score! You suclk!
Are you olkay?
l need some millk.
Olkay. l've got millk.
Here you go.
Better?
No.
l feel so stupid! l thinlk about
the other day with you guys.
And l was all, ''Oh, Paolo!
He's so great!
He malkes me feel so--''
God!
l'm so embarrassed!
l'm so embarrassed.
-l'm the one he hit on.
-l unleashed him on you.
lf l had never met him--
-l'm so sorry.
-No, l'm sorry.
-l'm sorry.
-l'm sorry. Wait.
-What are we sorry about?
-l don't lknow.
Right. He's the pig.
-Such a pig!
-Oh, God, he's such a pig!
He's lilke a big disgusting pig....
-Pig man!
-Yes, good!
But he was my pig man!
How did l not see this?
Oh, l lknow!
Because...
...he's gorgeous.
And he's charming.
-And when he loolks--
-Olkay, Pheebs.
The end.
God.
Should l not have told you?
Trust me, it's much better
that l lknow.
But l just lilked it better before.
lt was better.
She toolk it pretty well.
Paolo's over there now, so....
We should go and see if she's olkay.
Just one second.
-Score!
-Game! Nice!
Come on, Pheebs.
Well, it loolks lilke we
lkiclked your butts.
She did. You could be on the Olympic
''Standing There'' team.
Come on. Two on one.
Why are you here?
She just brolke up with him.
lt's time for you to swoop in.
-What, now?
-Yes. Now is when you swoop.
When Paolo wallks out,
you gotta be the first guy she sees.
She's gotta lknow you're everything
he's not. You're the anti-Paolo.
My Catholic friend is right.
She's distraught.
You're there for her.
You piclk up the pieces and then
you usher in ''The Age of Ross.''
-See this? See?
-Hold it! Ascolta!
-How's it going?
-Don't stare.
She threw his clothes off the balcony.
Now there's gesturing and arm-waving.
That is, ''How could you?''
or ''Enormous breasts!''
Here he comes.
l am...
...to say goodbye.
Olkay, bye-bye.
Paolo, l really hate you for what you
did, but l still have five of these...
...so heat it at 75
until the cheese bubbles.
l just wanna tell you, and l thinlk
l'd spealk for everyone when l say....
Oh, just loolk at her.
Guys, l thinlk only one of us
should go...
-...so she's not overwhelmed.
-Right.
And l really thinlk it should be me.
You all right?
l've been better.
l don't believe this.
l wasn't supposed to care
about this guy.
lt was just supposed to be
this big, fun, ltalian thing.
Someday l could loolk baclk and say,
''That was a big, fun, ltalian thing.''
lt wasn't supposed to feel
lilke this when it was over.
Come here.
Listen...
...you deserve
so much better than him.
l mean, you...
...should be with a guy who lknows
what he has when he has you.
What?
l'm so siclk of guys!
l don't want to loolk at
or thinlk about another guy.
l don't even want
to be near another guy.
Ross, you're so great.
-Are you all right?
-Are you olkay?
-Medium. Any coolkies left?
-Yeah.
See, Rach...
...l don't thinlk swearing off guys
altogether is the answer.
What you need is to develop a more
sophisticated screening process.
l just need to be by myself
for a while.
-l just gotta figure out what l want.
-No, no.
See, because not all guys out there
are gonna be a Paolo.
No, l lknow. l lknow.
And l'm sure your little boy's
not gonna grow up to be one.
-What?
l'm having a boy?
No.
No. ln fact, you're not having a boy.
l'm having a boy.
-Huh? Am l having a boy?
-You're having a boy!
l'm having a boy!
-l'm having a boy!
-What is it?
l'm having a boy!
We already lknew that!
l'm having a son.
Yes! And that would be a shutdown!
Shutout!
Where you going? One more game!
-lt's 2:0 in the morning.
-Yeah, get out!
You guys always hang out
in my apartment.
l'll only use my left hand.
Come on, wussies!
All right! Olkay! l gotta go!
l'm going.
And l'm gone.
-One more game?
-Oh, yeah.