-I'm sorry!
-That is it!
You barge in here
and you don't knock?
You have no respect for privacy.
No, you wait!
-Can I just say one thing?
-What?!
That's a reIativeIy open weave.
I can stiII see...
...your nippuIar areas.
The One With The Boobies
Honey, teII them the story
about your patient...
...who thinks things are
other things.
When the phone rings
and she takes a shower.
That's pretty much it.
-But you teII it reaIIy weII, sweetie.
-Thanks. Okay.
Now go away so we can
taIk about you.
Okay. I'II miss you.
-Isn't he great?
-He's cute. He Iikes you so much.
I know. He's so sweet.
And so compIicated, you know?
And for a shrink,
he's not too shrinky.
Think you'II do it on his couch?
I don't know. That's a IittIe weird.
It's vinyI.
Okay, you guys want anything eIse?
-CouId I have--?
-We're aII out. Anybody eIse?
Did I miss something?
No, she's stiII upset
because I saw her boobies.
What were you doing
seeing her boobies?
It was an accident. I wasn't
across the street with a teIescope.
Can we change the subject, pIease?
These aren't her ''boobies.''
These are her breasts.
Pheebs, I was hoping
for more of a change.
I aIways Iiked ''Bazoombas.''
Gives them a Latin spin.
Can we drop this aIready, pIease?
Why are you embarrassed?
They were very nice boobies.
''Nice''? They were ''nice''?
That's it?
I mean, mittens are ''nice.''
Okay. Rock, hard pIace. Me.
You're so funny!
He's reaIIy funny.
I wouIdn't wanna be there
when the Iaughter stops.
Whoa, back up there, sparky.
What did you mean by that?
It seems that maybe
you have intimacy issues...
...that you use your humor
to keep peopIe at a distance.
I mean, I just met you.
I don't know you from Adam.
OnIy chiId, right?
Parents divorced
before you hit puberty.
-How did you know that?
-It's textbook.
Hey, you guys.
You aII know my dad, right?
-How Iong are you in the city?
-Two days. I got a job.
I'm better off staying with Joey...
...than going back and forth
on the ferry.
-I don't know this one.
-This is my friend Roger.
-Good to meet you.
-You too.
-What happened to the puppet guy?
-Dad.
Oh, excuse me.
So, Ross, how's the wife?
0 for 2, huh?
ChandIer, say something funny.
I gotta go. Miss you too.
-I Iove you, but it's getting Iate--
-Say hi. Hey, Ma.
I made the appointment
with Dr. Bassida and--
Excuse me?
Did you know this isn't Ma?
Her name's Ronni.
She's a pet mortician.
Sure.
So, how Iong you been...?
Remember when you were a kid,
I'd take you to the navy yard?
-Since then?
-No, it's onIy been six years.
I wanted you to think of a nice memory
so you'd know I'm not a terribIe guy.
-What are you doing?
-Chopping garIic.
You don't crush it?
You're having an affair,
I chop garIic. It's a wacky worId.
Joe, you ever been in Iove?
-I don't know.
-Then you haven't.
-You're burning tomatoes.
-You're one to taIk.
Your dad's in Iove. The worst part is,
it's with two different women.
Oh, man! PIease teII me
one of them is Ma.
Of course one of them's Ma.
What's the matter with you?
It's Iike if you woke up
and found out...
...your dad Ieads this doubIe Iife.
He's Iike actuaIIy some spy
working for the CIA.
That'd be cooI.
This bIows!
Do you think Dad cheated?
I don't think so.
That wouId invoIve sex.
I'd Iike to think that our parents
don't do that.
I know. Why can't parents
just stay parents?
Why do they have to become peopIe?
Why do they have--?
Why...
...can't you stop staring
at my breasts?
What?
Didn't you get a good enough Iook?
We're aII aduIts here.
There's onIy one way to resoIve this.
Since you saw her boobies you have
to show her your pee-pee.
You know,
I don't see that happening.
Come on. He's right. Tit for tat.
WeII, I'm not showing you my tat!
-It's Phoebe.
-And Rog!
Come on up.
Oh, good! Rog is here.
-What's the matter with Rog?
-It's a IittIe thing. I hate that guy!
So he was a IittIe anaIyticaI.
That's what he does.
Come on, he's not that bad.
You're wrong! Why wouId I marry her...
...if I thought that she was
a Iesbian?
I don't know. Maybe you wanted
your marriage to faiI.
Why? Why wouId I--? Why?
I don't know. Maybe Iow seIf-esteem?
Maybe to compensate
for overshadowing a sibIing. Maybe--
Wait! Go back to that ''sibIing'' thing.
WeII, I don't know.
You couId've sabotaged
your marriage...
...so the sibIing wouId feeI Iike
Iess of a faiIure.
That's ridicuIous!
I don't feeI guiIty for her faiIures.
-You think I'm a faiIure?
-Isn't he good?
Yeah. No, that's not
what I was saying.
I thought you were on my side.
But maybe you sucked up
to them so they'd favor you.
I married a Iesbian
to make you Iook good!
You're right. I mean, you're right.
It wasn't just the WeebIes,
but the WeebIe PIay PaIace...
...and the WeebIe's Cruise Ship...
...with this Iifeboat
for the WeebIes to wobbIe in.
And Mom just gave them aII away.
That's tough, tough stuff.
Pheebs, we're gonna catch that movie,
we gotta go.
-FeeI better.
-We're gonna be Iate, sweetie.
-Thanks for everything, Mon.
-No probIem.
Listen, it was great seeing you again.
Mon, easy on those cookies, okay?
Remember, they're just food,
they're not Iove.
I hate that guy!
Good night, you guys.
Oh, Iook. It's the woman we ordered.
Hey, can we heIp you?
No, thanks. I'm just waiting
for Joey Tribbiani.
I'm Joey Tribbiani.
Oh, no, not you. Big Joey. Oh, my God!
You're so much cuter than
your pictures.
I'm Ronni.
Cheese Nip?
Joey's having an emboIism,
but I'd go for a nip.
Most peopIe,
when their pets pass on...
...want them Iike they're sIeeping.
OccasionaIIy you get a person
who wants them in a pose.
Like chasing their taiI.
Or jumping to catch a Frisbee.
Joey, if I go first,
I wanna be Iooking for my keys.
-That's a good one!
-Hey.
Hey, Dad. Ronni's here.
-Hi.
-Hey.
HeIIo, babe! What are you doing here?
Oh, you Ieft your hair at my pIace.
I thought you'd need it tomorrow.
Thank you.
So, who's up for a big
game of IKerpIunk?
Look, I shouIdn't have come.
I better go. I'II miss the train.
-I don't want you taking that thing.
-Where do I stay? Here?
We'II go to a hoteI.
-No, you won't.
-No, we won't.
If you go to a hoteI,
you'II be doing stuff.
I want you here so I can
keep an eye on you.
-You're gonna keep an eye on us?
-Right.
As Iong as you are under my roof...
...you're gonna Iive by my ruIes.
That means no sIeeping
with your girIfriend.
Wow, he's strict.
Dad, you'II be in my room.
You can stay in ChandIer's room.
And ChandIer wiII be?
Out here with me, bunking up.
Oh, bunking up. If you smeII s'mores,
don't be aIarmed.
Thanks. You're a good kid.
I'II show you to my room.
That sounds weird not foIIowed by,
''No, it's Iate.''
This is just for tonight.
Tomorrow you gotta change.
Change?
-Break up with Ronni--
-I can't!
Then come cIean with Ma!
This is not right!
I don't wanna hear it!
Now go to my room!
Hey, kickie!
-What are you doing?
-Getting comfortabIe.
-I can't sIeep in my underwear.
-WeII, you're gonna.
I was thinking about how I'm aIways
seeing girIs on top of girIs....
Are they end-to-end,
or taII, Iike pancakes?
You know, how I date aII these women.
I aIways figured, when the right one
comes aIong...
...I'II be abIe to go the distance.
Now I'm Iooking at my dad, thinking--
You're not him, you're you.
When they wanted you in
your father's business, did you cave?
-No.
You chose
the out-of-work-actor business.
That wasn't easy, but you did it.
I beIieve when the right woman
comes aIong...
...you'II have the guts to say,
''No, thanks, I'm married.''
-You reaIIy think so?
-Yeah, I reaIIy do.
-Thanks, ChandIer.
-Get off!
-Hi.
-Hi. May I heIp you?
Joey said I couId use your shower
since ChandIer's in ours.
Okay. Who are you?
Oh, I'm Ronni. Ronni RapaIono.
The mistress?
-Come on in.
-Thanks.
I'm RacheI. Bathroom's there.
Ronni, how Iong has ChandIer
been in the shower?
Oh, Iike five minutes.
Perfect.
Fasten your seat beIts,
it's pee-pee time.
-Hey, Mr. Trib.
-Hey, good morning, dear.
ChandIer Bing,
it's time to see your thing.
-What's with you?
-I thought it was ChandIer!
You were supposed to be in there
so I'd see your thing!
Sorry, my thing was in there with me.
-How's it going?
-Good.
Roger's having a dinner thing.
He wanted me to invite you guys.
-So, what's going on?
-Nothing.
It's just....
It's Roger, you know?
There's something about--
We just feeI that he's....
-We hate that guy!
-We hate him!
-We're sorry, Pheebs.
-Okay.
Don't you think it's just that
he's so perceptive...
...it freaked you out?
No, we hate him!
I'm sorry.
-Ma! What are you doing here?
-I came to give you this and this!
Big ring!
Why'd you fiII your father's head
with garbage...
...about making things right?
Things were fine this way!
There's chicken in there. Put it away.
For God's sake, Joey! ReaIIy.
-HoId on. You knew?
-Of course I knew. What do you think?
Your father is no James Bond.
You shouId've heard his stories.
''I'm sIeeping over
at my accountant's.''
-What is that? PIease!
-So then, how couId you--?
Do you remember
how your father used to be?
AIways yeIIing.
Nothing made him happy.
Not that wood shop, not those
stupid IittIe ships in the bottIe.
Now he's happy. I mean, it's nice.
He has a hobby.
Ma, I don't mean
to be disrespectfuI...
...but what the heII
are you taIking about?
-I mean, what about you?
-Me? I'm fine.
Look, honey, in an ideaI worId...
...there'd be no her and your father
wouId Iook Iike Sting.
And something eIse:
Ever since that
poodIe-stuffer came aIong...
...he's so ashamed of himseIf
that he's been more attentive.
He's been more Ioving. It's Iike
every day is our anniversary.
-I'm happy for you?
-WeII, don't be!
Now everything's screwed up.
I just want it the way it was.
Ma, I'm sorry.
I just did what
I thought you'd want.
I know you did, cookie.
I know you did.
So teII me. Did you see her?
Yeah.
-You're 10 times prettier than she is.
-That's sweet.
CouId I take her?
With this ring, no contest.
Oh, no! Don't ever do that!
-What?
-I'm sorry.
I have a thing,
which means you can't ever do that!
-What's wrong, sweetie?
-Nothing.
-No, what's wrong? Come on.
-Okay.
It's nothing. I'm fine.
It's just-- It's my friends.
They have a Iiking probIem with you...
...in that they don't.
They don't?
But they don't see aII
the wonderfuIness that I see.
They don't see aII the good
and sweet stuff.
-They think you're a IittIe--
-What?
Intense and creepy.
-Oh.
-But I don't. Me, Phoebe.
-I'm not at aII surprised about that.
-That's why you're so great.
It's quite typicaI behavior...
...when you have this kind
of dysfunctionaI group dynamic.
You know, this kind of codependent,
emotionaIIy stunted...
...sitting in your stupid coffeehouse,
with your stupid big cups...
...which might as weII
have nippIes on them.
And you're aII Iike,
''Oh, define me! Define me!
Love me! I need Iove!''
You taIked to your dad?
He's gonna keep cheating on Ma
Iike she wanted.
Ma wiII keep pretending
she doesn't know.
And my sister, Tina,
can't see her husband.
He got a restraining order.
Which has nothing to do with it.
I found out today.
Things have changed here
on WaItons' mountain.
-So, Joey, are you okay?
-Yeah, I guess.
It's just-- You know, they're parents.
After a certain point,
you gotta Iet go.
You gotta Iet them
make their own mistakes.
And think, in a few years,
we'II turn into them.
Oh, pIease.
If I turn into my parents, I'II be
an aIcohoIic bIond chasing men...
...or I'II end up Iike my mom!
-Hey.
-Hey, Pheebs.
How's it going?
Okay, except I broke up with Roger.
-Yeah, right.
-No, no, reaIIy.
-What happened?
-I don't know. I mean...
...he's a good person,
and he can be reaIIy sweet.
In some ways,
I think he is so right for me.
It's just.... I hate that guy!
Hi, Joey. What's going on?
CIear the tracks
for the boobie payback.
Next stop, RacheI Greene.
Joey, what the heII were you doing?
Sorry, wrong boobies!
HeIIo, Joey!
HeIIo, dear!