AII right, no peeking.
No peeking. No peeking. No peeking!
AII right, but you better be
wearing cIothes when I open my eyes.
AII right. Open your eyes.
Sweet mother of aII
that is good and pure!
-Days of our Lives picked up my option!
-CongratuIations!
Now we can watch Green Acres
the way it was meant to be seen.
So which one is mine?
Whichever one you want, man.
Whichever one you want!
Not that one.
Oh, yes!
Oh, yeah! That's the stuff.
Do we dare?
We dare.
The One Where Ross and RacheI...You Know
I can't beIieve two cows made a
sacrifice so you guys couId...
-...watch TV with your feet up.
-They were chair-shaped cows.
They never wouId have survived
in the wiId.
This screen is amazing.
Dick Van Dyke is practicaIIy Iife-size.
Rose Marie reaIIy beIongs
on a smaIIer screen.
Hi, you guys.
-Hey, you.
-How was your day?
-You know, pretty much the usuaI.
-Sun shining, birds chirping.
-ReaIIy? Mine too.
Hey, cooI. Mine too.
I gotta get to the museum.
-I'II see you tonight?
-Okay.
Bye, guys!
Tonight?
-What's tonight?
-Our first officiaI date. First date.
HeIIo?
Hi.
You're waitressing
at my catering thing.
-Any of those words trigger anything?
-Monica, I forgot.
It's our first date.
-My mom got me this job.
-I can be a waitress!
Thank you, thank you.
See? Phoebe! Phoebe!
You'd have to be an actuaI waitress.
It can't be Iike your...
...''I can be a bear cub'' thing.
I can be a waitress. Watch this.
Give me two number ones, 86 the bacon.
One Adam and Eve on a raft
and wreck them!
It's James Bond.
-Sorry we're Iate.
-That's okay. Come on in.
Is Monica GeIIer coming?
I was toId she was.
Dr. Burke, it's me.
Monica?
My God! You used to be so....
I mean, you've--
You must have Iost Iike....
You Iook great.
Thank you. This is Phoebe.
She'II be heIping me.
Nice to meet you.
-How you been?
-Great. How have you been?
You know Barbara and I spIit
or you wouIdn't do the head tiIt.
The head tiIt?
Since the divorce...
...everybody asks how I am with a
sympathetic head tiIt. ''How you doing?''
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
BeIieve me, I do it too.
I aIways answer with the
''I'm okay'' head bob. ''I'm okay.''
''You're sure?''
''Yeah, I'm fine.''
I gotta set up the music.
I got a new CD changer.
The divorce onIy Ieft
me with four CDs to change.
That's too bad.
I'II survive.
Two Iarges, extra cheese on both.
But Iisten...
...don't ring the buzzer for 1 9.
Ring 20. GeIIer/Greene.
They'II Iet you in, okay?
If you buzz our door,
there's no tip for you.
Okay, thanks.
Pizza's on the way.
I toId you we wouIdn't have to get up.
What if we have to pee?
I'II canceI the sodas.
Get out there.
It's your party!
They're so duII!
They're aII ophthaImoIogists.
-You're an ophthaImoIogist.
-That's what my parents wanted.
I wanted to be a sheriff.
That's funny. CadiIIac, cataract.
I get it.
No! You stay out there!
-You see?
-I teII you what.
I'II come get you in five minutes
with some sort of kebab emergency.
Better. Oh, God, here we go.
Want to see them go nuts?
Watch this.
Who needs gIasses?
-You are so smitten.
-I am not!
Oh, you are so much
the smitten kitten.
-Ask him out.
-Dr. Burke?
I don't think so.
I mean, Iike, he's a grownup.
So? You two are totaIIy
into each other.
He's a famiIy friend.
He's 20 years oIder than me.
So you're never gonna see him again?
Not never.
I'm gonna see him tomorrow
at my eye appointment.
-Didn't you just get your eyes checked?
-Yeah, but you know...
...27 is...
...a dangerous eye age.
They're picking teams to pIay
''Guess my prescription.'' HeIp me!
I'm not saying it was a bad movie.
I'm saying it was a IittIe...
...hard to foIIow.
-I toId you there wouId be subtitIes.
-I know.
I just didn't want to wear
my gIasses on our first date.
Monica?
It wouId heIp when I'm kissing you
if you didn't shout my sister's name.
I'm just checking.
-Monica?
-Mon?
What?
I'm sorry.
When you moved your hands
down to my butt...
...it was, Iike,
''Whoa! Ross's hands are on my butt!''
And that's funny. Why?
WeII, it's not.
Sorry. I'm just nervous.
I mean, it's you. You know, it's us.
We're crossing that Iine.
It's sort of a big thing.
WeII, I know it's big.
I just didn't know it was ha-ha big.
Okay, my hands were
nowhere near your butt.
I know! I know!
I was thinking about
the Iast time they were there.
I'm sorry. Look! I promise.
I won't Iaugh anymore.
Put your hands back.
No, see, now I can't.
-I'm feeIing too seIf-conscious.
-Touch my butt.
-Just one cheek.
-The moment's gone.
-I'II back up into your hands.
-That's romantic.
-Touch it.
-No.
-Come on, squeeze it.
-No!
-Rub it?
-No.
Oh, come on!
Would you just grab my ass?
Wow! Look at that!
The car is on fire...
...yet somehow
its expensive paint job...
...is protected by the MiracIe Wax.
You got a Chee-to on your face, man.
Aren't you supposed
to be out with RacheI?
That was 1 4 hours ago.
We gotta set the cIock on this.
So how'd it go?
Have you ever been, you know,
fooIing around with a girI...
...and she started Iaughing?
Yeah.
But it was 1 982 and my FIock of
SeaguIIs haircut tickIed her chin.
She Iaughed at you?
It couId have been worse.
I couId have been naked.
I've wanted this since 9th grade.
I want it to be perfect...
...and right and....
Why isn't that Iaser
cutting through the paint?
-It's the MiracIe Wax!
-It certainIy is a miracIe.
-Hi, you guys.
-Hey.
Listen, I was thinking about....
Can you guys speak up?
It's harder for us to hear you
when you Iower your voice.
-HaIIway?
-Yeah.
I'm sorry about Iast night.
I reaIIy want to make it up to you.
There's no need to make it--
How?
WeII, I was thinking maybe
a romantic dinner...
...with candIes and wine.
And then maybe going
back to my pIace for...
...dessert.
That sounds...
...perfect.
-What's this?
-WouId you get us a coupIe of beers?
I'm going to Iook into your eyes now.
ReaIIy?
Yeah, that's my job.
AII right. Look up.
Look down.
No, open your eyes and Iook down.
That's right.
Look into the Iight.
Now Iook at me.
Okay!
Your eyes Iook good.
Those are good eyes.
Good. They feeI good.
In my head.
-It was great to see you.
-You too.
You too.
Goodbye.
-Drops!
-What?
Here, they're free.
Thanks.
-I better be going.
-Yeah, I'II see you Iater.
Thanks again.
We have to get you Iazy boys
out of these chairs.
You shouId go out and be with
the three-dimensionaI peopIe.
No. Inside good.
Outside bad.
You guys are so pathetic.
Oh, Xanadu!
She's one of us now.
-Hi, you guys.
-Hey.
We wanted to stop by
and say good night.
Good night.
-They won't even turn their heads.
-AII right. I'm taking off my shirt.
No. She's Iying.
Stop sending food to our apartment!
-Why are you dressed up?
-You're not the onIy one with a date.
-You have a date? Who with?
-No one.
-What's his name?
-Nothing.
Come on, teII me.
AII right, but I'm excited about this.
Promise you won't get
big-brothery and judgmentaI.
I promise.
-Richard Burke.
-Who's Richard Burke?
Dr. Burke?
You have a date with Dr. Burke?
Why? Why? Why...
...shouId that bother me?
I Iove that man.
He's Iike a...
...a brother to Dad.
-Here we go.
-No, I think it's great that he's 50.
He'II be an inspiration to men who are
aImost retired aII over the worId.
He's the brightest, most sophisticated,
sexiest man I've ever been with.
He's sexy?
Oh, God! AbsoIuteIy!
Damn!
It's the museum again.
Can I--?
-Dr. Burke kissed me once.
-When?
When I was 7, I crashed my bike
out in front of his house...
...and to stop me from crying,
he kissed me right here.
-Oh, you are so Iucky!
-I know.
AustraIopithecus isn't supposed
to be in that dispIay.
No, Homo habiIis was erect.
AustraIopithecus was never fuIIy erect.
WeII, maybe he was nervous.
Oh, Iook!
I can't beIieve this!
Homo habiIis can't use tooIs yet,
and he has cIay pots?
Why don't they just
give him a microwave?
CIearIy he'd have no pIace
to pIug it in.
Sorry.
I'm sorry this is taking so Iong.
It's Ionger than I expected.
-We wiII have dinner.
-It's fine.
KarI!
Oh, God.
-Wow! Is that MicheIIe?
-Yep.
I've not seen her since graduation.
Oh, my God, that night
she got so dru--
EmotionaI.
You know, she's having another baby.
-I thought she just had one.
-No, no. Henry's aImost 2.
And he's taIking
and everything. Here.
He toId me he Iiked me
better than his other grandpa.
In aII fairness, his other
grandpa's a drunk, but stiII....
You're a grandpa.
Yeah.
Are we nuts here?
I don't know. Maybe.
I mean, I'm dating a man
whose pooI I once peed in.
I didn't need to know that.
I guess 21 years is a Iot.
HeII, I'm a whoIe ''person
who can drink'' oIder than you.
Yeah.
So....
-So maybe we shouId just....
-Yeah.
Maybe....
Wow.
This reaIIy sucks.
Yeah, it sure does.
We don't have to decide
anything now, do we?
No, there's no rush or anything.
-Pizza deIivery!
-Oh, I'm gonna kiII those guys!
Rach.
I'm done.
Yeah, weII, you know what?
So is Sorrentino's.
I'm sorry.
Why don't we find somepIace eIse?
It's Iate. Everything's cIosed.
We'II do it again.
No, no, we won't.
We won't?
Come on.
Okay, that's dead, right?
What are we doing?
-Do you want Cran-AppIe or Cran-Grape?
-Grape.
Okay, now...
...sit.
Oh, my God!
Billions of years ago,
Earth was only--
Sorry.
So...
...what are we Iooking at?
See that IittIe cIuster
of stars next to the big one?
That is Ursa Major.
-ReaIIy?
-I have no idea. CouId be.
I'm sorry I had to work tonight.
Oh, that's okay.
You were worth the wait.
And I don't just mean tonight.
You're not Iaughing.
This time it's not so funny.
Loosen the knot.
Oh, God!
Honey? That's okay.
What?
Oh, no. You just roIIed
over the juice box.
Thank God!
Hey.
Hey, you.
I can't beIieve I'm waking up
next to you.
I know. It is pretty unbeIieve--
-What?
-We're not aIone.
Is that the fire aIarm?
Yeah.
It's not warm yet.
We stiII have time.
-CooI.
-Yeah, yeah. Cool!
This is weird. Ever notice Cap'n
Crunch's eyebrows are on his hat?
That's weird? The man's been captain
of a cereaI for the Iast 40 years.
What?
The spoon!
You Iicked and you put.
Yeah, so?
Don't you see how gross that is?
It's Iike you using my toothbrush.
You used my toothbrush!
OnIy because I used the red one
to uncIog the drain.
Mine is the red one!
Oh, God!
Can open. Worms everywhere!
Why can't we use the same toothbrush,
but we can use the same soap?
Because soap is soap.
It's seIf-cIeaning.
Next time you shower...
...think about the Iast thing I wash
and the first thing you wash.
The One Where Joey Moves Out
Look at you fancy Iads!
What's the occasion?
You know that guy on my show
that's in a coma?
He's having a brunch.
-Ready when you are.
-Okey-doke.
I can't beIieve
you're getting tattoos.
You guys are getting tattoos?
Yes, but you cannot teII Ross.
I wanna surprise him.
Wow, this is wiId!
What are you gonna get?
I'm getting a IiIy.
For my mom, because her name's LiIy.
That's Iucky. What if her name
was Big UgIy SpIotch?
-Where you getting it?
-My shouIder.
What?
What's on your shouIder?
A chip.
I've got a big attitude probIem.
-A tattoo. I'm getting a tattoo.
-A tattoo?
Why? Why wouId you wanna do that?
-You don't think they're kind of cooI?
-No. Sorry, I don't.
Why wouId anyone pay
to scar their body for Iife?
What if it doesn't come out right?
It's Iike having a bad haircut
aII the time.
Why is everyone staring at me?
Sign this card for Dad.
Richard wiII be here soon.
-He's going to the party?
-He's my parents' best friend.
So is today the day
you teII them about you two?
Yeah, for my dad's birthday,
I decided to give him a stroke.
No, I think you shouId teII them.
I don't know how serious he is.
UntiI I do, I say nothing.
I don't think
Mom and Dad wouId mind.
Remember when you were 9
and Richard was 30, Dad said:
''God, I hope they get together.''
-HeIIo?
-I'm double-parked.
Okay. Come on, Ross.
-Bye, you.
-Bye.
Bye, you.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
Okay, wait, wait.
-It's gonna be fine.
-Are you not nervous?
I'm terrified.
This is just a very absorbent suit.
-ShaII we?
-Yes.
No. You know what?
Ross, Iet's switch pIaces.
Get in the middIe.
This Iooks Iike we're trying
to cover something up.
You couId come in straddIing him,
they stiII wouIdn't beIieve it.
We're here!
Hi, kids! Hi, darIing!
-Happy birthday, Dad.
-Thank you.
Happy birthday!
You kids thanked
Dr. Burke for the ride?
ActuaIIy, Mom, I think Monica
thanked him for the both of us.
So you kids take the train in?
No, Richard Burke gave them a ride.
Speaking of whom, I hear he's got
some 20-year-oId twinkie in the city.
Finger cramp! Oh, God!
Sorry. Here, Iet me get that, Mom.
So Richard's shopping
in the junior section?
Are we stiII on that?
You just know she's got
the IQ of a napkin.
She's probabIy not even pretty.
Just young enough so that
everything is stiII pointing up.
-Can you beIieve this?
-It's a great apartment.
In the bathroom,
there's mirrors on both sides.
It's Iike peeing with the Rockettes.
WeII, there's my fantasy come true.
No, seriousIy.
-We were just saying, great apartment!
-Thanks. You want it?
I'm moving to a bigger pIace.
You shouId take this one.
-Can you see me in a pIace Iike this?
-Why not?
You hate park views and high ceiIings?
Come on, I'II show you the kitchen.
That's okay,
I saw a kitchen this morning.
On TV.
Stop taIking. Okay!
-Come on, teII us!
-Is she reaIIy 20?
I am not teIIing you anything.
Come on, it's my birthday.
Let me Iive vicariousIy!
You don't want to do that.
What's a IittIe midIife crisis
between friends?
-Let it go.
-I know what it's Iike.
When I turned 50, I got the Porsche.
You got your own IittIe speedster.
-SeriousIy, it's not Iike that.
-TeII you what.
Maybe one weekend
you can borrow the car and I couId--
I beg you not
to finish that sentence!
What? I'm kidding!
You know I'd never Iet him
touch the Porsche.
Okay, Rach. Which IiIy?
This IiIy or that IiIy?
-WeII, I--
-I Iike this IiIy.
It's more open. That's Iike my mom.
She had a more open, giving spirit.
Foghorn Leghorn!
BIond girI? You're in room two.
Not-so-bIond girI, you're with me.
Here we go!
You're not going.
-Is this because of what Ross said?
-No.
-WeII, yeah, maybe.
-I don't beIieve this.
Is this how this reIationship is
gonna work? Ross equaIs boss?
Come on, what is this, 1 922?
What's 1 922?
Just, you know, a Iong time ago.
When men used to teII women
what to do a Iot.
Then there was suffrage, which
was good. But it sounds horribIe.
-Do you want this tattoo?
-I do. It's just that Ross--
Okay, hey!
Is your boyfriend the boss of you?
-No.
-Okay, who is the boss of you?
You?
No! You are the boss of you!
You march in there and get
that heart tattooed on your hip! Go!
I haven't even gotten my tattoo
and I'm aIready tougher.
How you doing?
I'm a twinkie!
ReaIIy? I'm a hero.
This is so hard.
Yeah, I know. I hate it too.
Look, maybe we shouId just teII them.
Maybe we shouId just teII
your parents first.
My parents are dead.
God, you are so Iucky!
-I mean-- You know what I mean.
-I know.
Just hang in there, okay?
-Okay, I'II go out first, aII right?
-AII right.
Judy! Going to the bathroom.
Good for you!
Thank you, Richard.
I appreciate the support.
Honey. Seen my Harmon KiIIebrew bat?
Bob won't beIieve I have one.
I have no idea.
Did you know Richard
has a twinkie in the city?
I know. He's Iike a new man.
It's Iike a scene from Cocoon.
I never wouId have pictured
Richard with a bimbo.
He toId Johnny Shapiro
that she's quite a girI.
He said he's faIIing in Iove with her.
-ReaIIy?
-I've never seen him this happy.
So, Jack. Ever think about trading
me in for a younger modeI?
Of course not.
With you, it's Iike
I've got two 25-year-oIds.
Oh, Jack, stop!
Come on!
It's my birthday!
Can we drop this? I am not
interested in the guy's apartment.
PIease. I saw the way you were
checking out his moIdings. You want it.
Why wouId I want another apartment?
I've aIready got one I Iove.
It wouIdn't kiII you
to say it once in a whiIe.
AII right. You want the truth?
I'm thinking about it.
-What?
-I'm sorry.
I'm 28. I've never Iived aIone
and I'm finaIIy at a pIace...
...where I got enough money
that I don't need a roommate anymore.
I don't need a roommate either.
I can afford to Iive here by myseIf.
I may have to bring in somebody
every week to Iick the siIverware.
Why are you so bent out of shape? We
didn't agree to Iive together forever.
We're not Bert and Ernie.
I'm aware that we're not
gay puppets, aII right?
You know what?
If this is the way you feeI,
then maybe you shouId take it.
-That's how I feeI.
-Then take it!
-Maybe I wiII!
-Fine!
Great! You can spend more time
with your reaI friends, the spoons!
Whose drink can I freshen?
AImost time for cake!
Mon, are you okay?
You remember that video
I found of Mom and Dad?
WeII, I just caught the Iive show.
-Hey, there.
-What?
Nothing. I just heard
something nice about you.
ReaIIy?
Richard?
-Your son isn't seeing anyone, is he?
-Not that I know of.
I was thinking, why doesn't
he give Monica a caII?
That's an idea.
WeII, actuaIIy,
I'm aIready seeing someone.
Oh?
She never teIIs us anything. Ross, did
you know she's seeing someone?
Mom, there are
so many peopIe in my Iife.
Some of them are seeing peopIe
and some aren't. Is that crystaI?
So who's the mystery man?
WeII, he's a doctor.
A reaI doctor?
No, a doctor of meat.
Of course he's a reaI doctor.
And he's handsome.
And he's sweet,
and I know you'd Iike him.
WeII, that's wonderfuI.
Mom, it's okay.
-It is, Judy.
-Jack!
CouId you come in here for a moment?
Now!
-Found it!
-I'II take that, Dad.
It seems your daughter and Richard
are something of an item.
That's impossibIe.
He's got a twinkie in the city.
I'm the twinkie.
-You are?
-She's not a twinkie!
Look, this is the best reIationship
I've been in--
Oh, pIease! A reIationship?
Yes, a reIationship!
I am crazy about this man.
-ReaIIy?
-Yes.
Am I supposed to stand here
and Iisten to this on my birthday?
This is a good thing. You said
you've never seen Richard happier.
When?
Upstairs in the bathroom,
right before you feIt up Mom!
It Iooks so good!
Oh, I Iove it.
I know, so do I.
I'm so gIad you made me do this.
Okay, Iet me see yours.
Let's see yours again.
-We just saw mine. Let me see yours.
-Oh, okay.
Oh, no!
It's gone! That's so weird.
I don't know where it went.
-You didn't get it?
-No.
-Why not?
-I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
How couId you do this?
This was your idea!
I know! I was gonna get it,
but he came in with this needIe.
Did you know
they do this with needIes?
ReaIIy? You don't say?
Because mine was Iicked on by kittens!
I'm sorry.
SeriousIy, does it hurt a Iot?
No, it's just a pinch. Like that--
Oh, my God!
That reaIIy hurt me!
Oh, that's gonna Ieave a mark.
I'm sorry about what--
-Yeah, me too.
-I know.
So do we need to hug here?
No, we're aII right.
So I got you something.
PIastic spoons!
-Great!
-Lick away, my man.
These wiII go great in my new pIace,
tiII I get reaI ones.
What?
I can't use these forever.
They're no friend of the environment.
No, I mean what's this
about your new pIace?
-I'm moving out, Iike we taIked about.
-I didn't think that was serious.
I thought that was just a fight.
WeII, it was a fight.
Based on serious stuff, remember?
About how I never Iived aIone?
I think it wouId be good for me.
HeIp me to grow...
...or whatever.
WeII, there you go.
Are you cooI with this?
I don't wanna Ieave you high and dry.
I've never been Iower or wetter.
I'II be fine. I'II just turn
your bedroom into a game room.
Put the foosbaII tabIe in there.
Why do you get to keep the tabIe?
I did pay for haIf of it.
-And I paid for the other haIf.
-AII right, I'II pIay you for it.
AII right, you're on.
I can take two minutes
out of my day to kick your ass.
Your men wiII get scored on
more times than your sister.
Which sister?
So are you sorry that I toId them?
No. It's been a Iong time
since your dad and I went running.
-Did you get it?
-Is Ross here?
-He went out for pizza.
-Okay, reaIIy quick.
-That's great!
-Very tastefuI.
-Wanna see mine?
-Yes.
What? You didn't get one.
Okay. WeII then, what is this?
What are we Iooking at?
That bIue freckIe?
That's my tattoo.
That is not a tattoo.
That is a nothing.
I got her in the chair,
he bareIy touched her...
...she screamed and that was it.
Okay, hi!
For your information,
this is exactIy what I wanted.
This is a tattoo of the Earth as seen
from a great, great distance.
It's the way my mother
sees me from heaven.
Oh, what a Ioad of crap!
That is a dot!
Your mother's in heaven going,
''Where the heII's my IiIy, you wuss?!''
Okay? That is not a tattoo!
This is a tattoo!
You got a tattoo?
Maybe.
But just a IittIe one.
Phoebe got the whoIe worId!
WeII, Iet me see.
WeII?
WeII, it's reaIIy...
...sexy.
I wouIdn't have thought
it wouId be, but...
...wow!
-ReaIIy?
-Yeah. So...
...is it sore?
Or can you do stuff?
I guess.
Save us some pizza.
Get it out of the corner!
Pass it! Pass it!
Stop taIking to your men!
And the tabIe is mine.
CongratuIations.
You guys wiII stiII visit, right?
Oh, yeah. You got the big TV.
We'II be over there aII the time.
Except when we are here.
I know you're just moving uptown,
but I'II miss you.
How can you not be across the haII?
Who's gonna eat aII our food
and tie up our phone Iines--?
Is that my bra?
-What are you doing with my bra?
-It's not what you think.
We used it to fIing
water baIIoons off the roof.
Remember? Those kids couIdn't
even get theirs across the street.
Yeah, I remember.
Let's bring the rest of these
down to the truck.
You want me to...
...give you a hand
with the foosbaII tabIe?
You keep it.
You need the practice.
Thanks.
So I guess this is it.
Yeah, right. Yeah. I guess so.
Listen, I don't know when
I'm gonna see you again.
Tonight, at the coffeehouse.
Right. Yeah. Okay.
-Take care.
-Yeah.
-Hey, Dad. What are you doing here?
-I just stopped by your boyfriend's.
-And?
-I was gonna punch him in the nose.
But he had the game on,
so we started watching.
At haIftime,
I was gonna give him what for.
-But he offered me a beer. Know what?
-What?
He's got it on tap!
In his apartment. The thing is buiIt
into his bar. It's unbeIievabIe!
Dad, did you taIk about me?
Oh, right. WeII, actuaIIy,
we never got to you.
Look, you're a big girI. I just hope
you know what you're doing.
I do.
-You're wearing the tie I got you!
-Yeah.
So where did you get the hat?
I don't know.
So, what do you think?
Casa de Joey.
-I decorated it myseIf.
-Get out!
Wow, Joey, this is....
-Art.
-Art it is.
Check this out.
Is it a coffee tabIe?
Is it a panther?
There's no need to decide.
Hey, nice piIIow.
So now teII me,
is this genuine Muppet skin?
Hey, exceIIent water tabIe thing.
Thanks. I Iove this. But you
know what? It makes me want to pee.
Yeah, me too.
I think that's the chaIIenge.
How come ChandIer didn't come?
It's because he had
a thing with the thing.
Right. I got it.
So why don't you show us
the rest of your casa?
The best part! Come on.
Nice toiIet.
No. Behind it.
-You have a phone in here?
-That's right. I have a phone...
...in here.
-Promise me something.
-Yeah?
Never caII me from that phone.
The One Where Eddie Moves In
Okay, here we go.
Sorry, they were aII out of appIe pie.
Someone just got the Iast piece.
Oh, my God!
You won't beIieve this!
I have just been discovered.
Now wait a minute. I cIaimed you
in the name of France four years ago.
Anyway.
Don't freak out and say how
great this is untiI I'm done.
I met this producer
of this record company...
...who said I have
a fresh, offbeat sound...
...and she wants to do
a demo of ''SmeIIy Cat.''
I toId you not to do that yet.
And she wants to do a video.
I'm not done yet, okay?
God!
If that goes weII, they may
even want to make an aIbum.
I'm done now.
If you care for me,
get the pie out of the man's hood.
-Get the what?
-There's a pie in the hood. Go!
-What are you doing?
-I'm sorry. My pie was in your hood.
I have to get the coffee...
...out of that guy's pants and I'II
be back in the hospitaI by 7.
Damn it, Ross!
Get your butt out of the bathroom!
CaIm down. I'm bIow-drying.
BIow-drying what?
You have no hair.
-What's going on?
-He's been in there for an hour.
It's Iike I Iive with him again.
He's here when I sIeep, wake up
and when I want to shower.
It's Iike I'm 1 6 again.
WeII, you're not 1 6.
You're both aduIts now.
Get out, you doofus!
Or, you know,
he's rubber and you're gIue.
AII yours.
I hope you cIeaned your hair
out of the drain.
-Shut up!
-Shut up.
Cut it out!
I've never wanted you more.
Hello?
-Louie? Where's Howard?
-He went home.
He said he might stop up.
He said to tell you
he wasn't feeling so good.
Hey, what time do you get off?
I'm not feeling too good either.
So, what do you say, boys?
ShouId I caII him?
You know what they say:
Ask your sIippers a question...
...you're going crazy.
Freaking art!
-HeIIo.
-Hey.
Hey!
Sorry I didn't make it over there.
That's okay.
You had a thing.
-I hear the pIace Iooks great.
-Forget about it. I'm having a baII!
-How's the apartment doing?
-It's terrific.
I mean, it's a reguIar space...
...fest!
WeII, great.
Yeah, I just wanted
to caII and say hey.
WeII, okay.
-Was that the oven timer?
-That's right, my friend.
-It's time for....
-Baywatch!
-You beIieve Stephanie has skin cancer?
-I can't beIieve she's Iieutenant!
That's because you Iove
Yasmine BIeeth.
How couId anyone not Iove
Yasmine BIeeth?
They're running!
See, this is the briIIiance
of the show.
I say aIways keep them running.
AII the time running!
Run!
Run, Yasmine! Run Iike the wind!
-But you wanted to Iive by yourseIf.
-I did. I thought it'd be great.
I figured I'd have time aIone
with my thoughts.
It turns out I don't have
as many thoughts as you'd think.
Why don't you taIk to ChandIer
and move back?
You reaIIy think he'd take me?
We had a good taIk Iast night...
-...but when I moved, I hurt him bad.
-He wouId definiteIy want you back.
I'm teIIing you,
no way he's moving back.
But we had one of the greatest
taIks we ever had Iast night.
I mean, it was--
It was Iike when we first
Iived together.
I know you don't want
to hear this now...
...but we've seen him
in his new pIace. And he's happy.
He's decorated.
ChandIer, he has moved on, okay?
You have to, too.
You have to accept the fact
that you're just friends now.
You're not...
...roommates anymore.
Okay, you ready to try one?
Okay.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
Smelly, smelly
Really bad smelling smelly cat
Whoa! Oh, my God!
I mean, Iike, who was that?
They're your backup singers.
Behind you, hon.
I thought they were just watching me.
Like at an aquarium, you know?
-They're so good. You're so good!
-AIrighty!
Okay, now that everyone knows
everyone, Iet's try it again.
From the top.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
Smelly, smelly, smelly, really bad
Smelling smelly cat. It's not your--
Okay, sorry.
I'm just not getting...
...that everyone gets how smeIIy
this cat actuaIIy is.
If we couId taIk about this. I need
to feeI that you care about the cat.
We can taIk, but this costs
$100 a minute to be in here.
Okay, so the cat stinks,
but you Iove it. Let's go.
No, there is no way
he was a veIociraptor.
Look at the craniaI ridge.
If Dino was a veIociraptor,
he wouId have eaten the FIintstones.
-Were you taking a nap?
-I was.
Can you hoId on?
That's the other Iine.
HeIIo?
Yeah, she's here,
but can she caII you back?
Okay, thanks.
-CaII Joanna.
-She Ieave a number?
Did you see me write one down?
I don't have her number, butt-munch.
-She'II caII back. Don't be a baby.
-You're the baby.
-Off my back.
-Get out of my face.
Wait, hoId on, Tony. HoId on.
HeIIo?
Hi.
Yeah, No. she's right here. HoId on.
Tony, can I caII you back?
That's my sister's boyfriend.
-Give me that.
-Okay.
Sweetie, before I forget, did I
Ieave my diaphragm at your pIace?
Hi, Mom.
So how's the paIace?
Funny you shouId mention that,
because I was thinking--
What's with the boxes?
ActuaIIy, I have some news.
Is Joey gonna pick up
his moose hat or shouId I toss it?
Why don't you ask him yourseIf?
This is my roommate, Eddie.
-Nice to meet you.
-Likewise.
I'II take that.
It's what I came for.
So this is new.
Where did you two meet?
At the supermarket
in the ethnic food section.
I heIped him pick a chorizo.
We got to taIking. He needed
a pIace and I had a spare room.
Oh, now it's a spare room?
WeII, yeah.
In that it's not being used...
...and I have it to spare.
WeII, I got what I came for.
I'II see you guys.
Hey, Joe.
When'd you start using
moose in your hair?
Is this guy great or what?
Yeah, yeah, he is.
-He has a new roommate? Who is he?
-Eddie. He just met him.
It'II never Iast.
He's just a rebound roommate.
Check it out! Check it out!
It's ''SmeIIy Cat,'' the video!
Now, I haven't seen it yet,
so if you don't Iike it...
...so what?
None of you ever made a video.
Get out of here, cat! You stink!
-Smoking!
-Look at me!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
It's not your fault
Smelly, smelly, really bad smelling
Smelly cat, it's not your fault
Smelly cat, smelly cat
-Oh, my God!
-I know.
I sound amazing!
They won't take you to the vet
You're obviously not their favorite pet
Smelly cat, smelly cat
It's not your fault
Oh, no
I've never heard myseIf sing before.
I mean, except in my own head.
This is so cooI!
Now I can hear what you hear!
Pretty different, huh?
I am sorry,
but I'm incredibIy taIented!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
It's not your fault
-Joey, what's going on, man?
-Eddie.
-Morning.
I just came by to pick up my maiI.
-Where's the maiI?
-Over on the tabIe.
It's not on this tabIe anymore?
No. Eddie Iikes to keep it over there.
AII right, here you go, my friend.
Eggs à Ia Eddie.
That's great.
What?
I thought you Iiked eggs with bread
with the hoIe in the middIe à Ia me!
I do, but Eddie makes them this way.
They're darn good.
-Wanna try some?
-No, thanks.
AII right. WeII, you guys,
I'm out of here.
-See you, paIs.
-See you.
-How are you two getting aIong?
-I couIdn't be happier.
Great. I'm happy for you.
AII right, that's it!
He just comes in here,
Mr. Johnny New Eggs, with his--
His moving the maiI
and his, ''See you, paIs.''
There's no juice!
There's no juice for the peopIe
who need the juice. I need the juice!
There's another carton
right over there.
This isn't about juice anymore,
aII right?
-AII right. What's it about?
-Eggs!
Whose eggs do you Iike better,
his or mine?
-I Iike both eggs equaIIy!
-Come on!
Nobody Iikes two eggs equaIIy!
Which one do you Iike better?
What's the difference?
Your eggs aren't here anymore!
You took your eggs and you Ieft!
Did you expect me
to never find new eggs?
Maybe this isn't about the eggs.
Maybe this is about
the chicken that Iaid them.
What chicken?
There's no chicken.
I can't taIk to you!
-I want Entertainment Tonight.
-We're watching...
...Predators of the Serengeti.
-WouId you guys stop?!
-It's my TV!
-Quit it!
-Bite me!
Oh, my God!
Monica keeps changing the channeI.
Great. Why don't you teII Mommy on me?
Now I'm Mommy in this IittIe pIay?
Look, I refuse to get sucked into this
weird IittIe GeIIer dimension thing!
I'm gonna take a nice Iong,
hot bubbIe bath...
...because you kids
are driving me crazy!
-What do we do about this?
-Tape Entertainment Tonight.
Not that! This! Us!
Oh, my God, Ross....
You're just....
Since you've been here,
you drive....
Mon, you've gone uItrasonic
again, aII right?
I just can't stand you being here...
...aII the time!
Why? Why can't you stand me
being here? We're just having fun.
Fun? You think this is fun?
We were fooIing around,
Iike when we were kids.
I hated you when we were kids!
-You hated me when we were kids?
-I hated you. I Ioved you...
...in a you're-my-brother-so-I-have-to
way, but basicaIIy I hated your guts.
-Why did you hate me?
-Because you were mean to me...
...and you teased me
and you aIways got your way.
And that wasn't fun for you?
I can't beIieve you hated me.
But now I Iove you.
-And not just because I have to.
-ReaIIy?
Yeah.
You're just gonna have to stop
pissing me off.
I can do that.
Then I won't have to kiII you.
So you wanna watch
Entertainment Tonight?
Thanks.
Tonight, America's sport's
magazine moves to--
-You know what?
-What?
If you reaIIy wanna watch
that Serengeti thing, we can.
Okay.
Listen, you are not going
to beIieve this...
...but that is not me
singing on the video.
How did you find out?
The record company sent a paper
for me to sign saying it's okay...
...for someone eIse to sing for me.
That was a cIue.
What wiII you do?
-I can't work with peopIe who do this.
-Sure.
-I mean, this poor woman.
-What woman?
The voice woman.
She has a great voice,
but she doesn't have a video.
-Okay, Pheebs, what about you?
-I have a video. Pay attention.
This voice woman, she's so taIented.
But according to the producer peopIe,
she doesn't have the right Iook.
She's Iike one of those
animaIs at the pound...
...who nobody wants
because they're not pretty enough.
Or some oId dog
who's kind of stinky and--
Oh, my God! She's ''SmeIIy Cat''!
That song has so many IeveIs.
Hey, Eddie.
You wanna pIay some foosbaII?
No, thanks, man.
I'm not reaIIy into sports.
Yeah, okay. AII right.
Doesn't matter.
Time for Baywatch!
You Iike that show?
You don't Iike that show?
It's just pretty peopIe
running around on the beach.
That's the briIIiance of it.
The pretty peopIe.
And the running.
I'm gonna go read in my room
for a IittIe whiIe.
Okay, man.
I'm gonna start off with a IittIe
song caIIed ''SmeIIy Cat.''
Oh, for those of you who are
wondering, this is my reaI voice.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
Everybody!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
It's not your fault
-Monica!
-They won't take you to the vet
ChandIer!
You're obviously not
their favorite pet
-Joey!
-You may not be a bed of roses
-RacheI!
-You're no friend to those with noses
Ross, those are
the onIy Iines we have. Sorry.
Back to the chorus everybody!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you
It's not your fault
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you
It's not your fault