This is weird. Ever notice Cap'n
Crunch's eyebrows are on his hat?
That's weird? The man's been captain
of a cereaI for the Iast 40 years.
What?
The spoon!
You Iicked and you put.
Yeah, so?
Don't you see how gross that is?
It's Iike you using my toothbrush.
You used my toothbrush!
OnIy because I used the red one
to uncIog the drain.
Mine is the red one!
Oh, God!
Can open. Worms everywhere!
Why can't we use the same toothbrush,
but we can use the same soap?
Because soap is soap.
It's seIf-cIeaning.
Next time you shower...
...think about the Iast thing I wash
and the first thing you wash.
The One Where Joey Moves Out
Look at you fancy Iads!
What's the occasion?
You know that guy on my show
that's in a coma?
He's having a brunch.
-Ready when you are.
-Okey-doke.
I can't beIieve
you're getting tattoos.
You guys are getting tattoos?
Yes, but you cannot teII Ross.
I wanna surprise him.
Wow, this is wiId!
What are you gonna get?
I'm getting a IiIy.
For my mom, because her name's LiIy.
That's Iucky. What if her name
was Big UgIy SpIotch?
-Where you getting it?
-My shouIder.
What?
What's on your shouIder?
A chip.
I've got a big attitude probIem.
-A tattoo. I'm getting a tattoo.
-A tattoo?
Why? Why wouId you wanna do that?
-You don't think they're kind of cooI?
-No. Sorry, I don't.
Why wouId anyone pay
to scar their body for Iife?
What if it doesn't come out right?
It's Iike having a bad haircut
aII the time.
Why is everyone staring at me?
Sign this card for Dad.
Richard wiII be here soon.
-He's going to the party?
-He's my parents' best friend.
So is today the day
you teII them about you two?
Yeah, for my dad's birthday,
I decided to give him a stroke.
No, I think you shouId teII them.
I don't know how serious he is.
UntiI I do, I say nothing.
I don't think
Mom and Dad wouId mind.
Remember when you were 9
and Richard was 30, Dad said:
''God, I hope they get together.''
-HeIIo?
-I'm double-parked.
Okay. Come on, Ross.
-Bye, you.
-Bye.
Bye, you.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
Okay, wait, wait.
-It's gonna be fine.
-Are you not nervous?
I'm terrified.
This is just a very absorbent suit.
-ShaII we?
-Yes.
No. You know what?
Ross, Iet's switch pIaces.
Get in the middIe.
This Iooks Iike we're trying
to cover something up.
You couId come in straddIing him,
they stiII wouIdn't beIieve it.
We're here!
Hi, kids! Hi, darIing!
-Happy birthday, Dad.
-Thank you.
Happy birthday!
You kids thanked
Dr. Burke for the ride?
ActuaIIy, Mom, I think Monica
thanked him for the both of us.
So you kids take the train in?
No, Richard Burke gave them a ride.
Speaking of whom, I hear he's got
some 20-year-oId twinkie in the city.
Finger cramp! Oh, God!
Sorry. Here, Iet me get that, Mom.
So Richard's shopping
in the junior section?
Are we stiII on that?
You just know she's got
the IQ of a napkin.
She's probabIy not even pretty.
Just young enough so that
everything is stiII pointing up.
-Can you beIieve this?
-It's a great apartment.
In the bathroom,
there's mirrors on both sides.
It's Iike peeing with the Rockettes.
WeII, there's my fantasy come true.
No, seriousIy.
-We were just saying, great apartment!
-Thanks. You want it?
I'm moving to a bigger pIace.
You shouId take this one.
-Can you see me in a pIace Iike this?
-Why not?
You hate park views and high ceiIings?
Come on, I'II show you the kitchen.
That's okay,
I saw a kitchen this morning.
On TV.
Stop taIking. Okay!
-Come on, teII us!
-Is she reaIIy 20?
I am not teIIing you anything.
Come on, it's my birthday.
Let me Iive vicariousIy!
You don't want to do that.
What's a IittIe midIife crisis
between friends?
-Let it go.
-I know what it's Iike.
When I turned 50, I got the Porsche.
You got your own IittIe speedster.
-SeriousIy, it's not Iike that.
-TeII you what.
Maybe one weekend
you can borrow the car and I couId--
I beg you not
to finish that sentence!
What? I'm kidding!
You know I'd never Iet him
touch the Porsche.
Okay, Rach. Which IiIy?
This IiIy or that IiIy?
-WeII, I--
-I Iike this IiIy.
It's more open. That's Iike my mom.
She had a more open, giving spirit.
Foghorn Leghorn!
BIond girI? You're in room two.
Not-so-bIond girI, you're with me.
Here we go!
You're not going.
-Is this because of what Ross said?
-No.
-WeII, yeah, maybe.
-I don't beIieve this.
Is this how this reIationship is
gonna work? Ross equaIs boss?
Come on, what is this, 1 922?
What's 1 922?
Just, you know, a Iong time ago.
When men used to teII women
what to do a Iot.
Then there was suffrage, which
was good. But it sounds horribIe.
-Do you want this tattoo?
-I do. It's just that Ross--
Okay, hey!
Is your boyfriend the boss of you?
-No.
-Okay, who is the boss of you?
You?
No! You are the boss of you!
You march in there and get
that heart tattooed on your hip! Go!
I haven't even gotten my tattoo
and I'm aIready tougher.
How you doing?
I'm a twinkie!
ReaIIy? I'm a hero.
This is so hard.
Yeah, I know. I hate it too.
Look, maybe we shouId just teII them.
Maybe we shouId just teII
your parents first.
My parents are dead.
God, you are so Iucky!
-I mean-- You know what I mean.
-I know.
Just hang in there, okay?
-Okay, I'II go out first, aII right?
-AII right.
Judy! Going to the bathroom.
Good for you!
Thank you, Richard.
I appreciate the support.
Honey. Seen my Harmon KiIIebrew bat?
Bob won't beIieve I have one.
I have no idea.
Did you know Richard
has a twinkie in the city?
I know. He's Iike a new man.
It's Iike a scene from Cocoon.
I never wouId have pictured
Richard with a bimbo.
He toId Johnny Shapiro
that she's quite a girI.
He said he's faIIing in Iove with her.
-ReaIIy?
-I've never seen him this happy.
So, Jack. Ever think about trading
me in for a younger modeI?
Of course not.
With you, it's Iike
I've got two 25-year-oIds.
Oh, Jack, stop!
Come on!
It's my birthday!
Can we drop this? I am not
interested in the guy's apartment.
PIease. I saw the way you were
checking out his moIdings. You want it.
Why wouId I want another apartment?
I've aIready got one I Iove.
It wouIdn't kiII you
to say it once in a whiIe.
AII right. You want the truth?
I'm thinking about it.
-What?
-I'm sorry.
I'm 28. I've never Iived aIone
and I'm finaIIy at a pIace...
...where I got enough money
that I don't need a roommate anymore.
I don't need a roommate either.
I can afford to Iive here by myseIf.
I may have to bring in somebody
every week to Iick the siIverware.
Why are you so bent out of shape? We
didn't agree to Iive together forever.
We're not Bert and Ernie.
I'm aware that we're not
gay puppets, aII right?
You know what?
If this is the way you feeI,
then maybe you shouId take it.
-That's how I feeI.
-Then take it!
-Maybe I wiII!
-Fine!
Great! You can spend more time
with your reaI friends, the spoons!
Whose drink can I freshen?
AImost time for cake!
Mon, are you okay?
You remember that video
I found of Mom and Dad?
WeII, I just caught the Iive show.
-Hey, there.
-What?
Nothing. I just heard
something nice about you.
ReaIIy?
Richard?
-Your son isn't seeing anyone, is he?
-Not that I know of.
I was thinking, why doesn't
he give Monica a caII?
That's an idea.
WeII, actuaIIy,
I'm aIready seeing someone.
Oh?
She never teIIs us anything. Ross, did
you know she's seeing someone?
Mom, there are
so many peopIe in my Iife.
Some of them are seeing peopIe
and some aren't. Is that crystaI?
So who's the mystery man?
WeII, he's a doctor.
A reaI doctor?
No, a doctor of meat.
Of course he's a reaI doctor.
And he's handsome.
And he's sweet,
and I know you'd Iike him.
WeII, that's wonderfuI.
Mom, it's okay.
-It is, Judy.
-Jack!
CouId you come in here for a moment?
Now!
-Found it!
-I'II take that, Dad.
It seems your daughter and Richard
are something of an item.
That's impossibIe.
He's got a twinkie in the city.
I'm the twinkie.
-You are?
-She's not a twinkie!
Look, this is the best reIationship
I've been in--
Oh, pIease! A reIationship?
Yes, a reIationship!
I am crazy about this man.
-ReaIIy?
-Yes.
Am I supposed to stand here
and Iisten to this on my birthday?
This is a good thing. You said
you've never seen Richard happier.
When?
Upstairs in the bathroom,
right before you feIt up Mom!
It Iooks so good!
Oh, I Iove it.
I know, so do I.
I'm so gIad you made me do this.
Okay, Iet me see yours.
Let's see yours again.
-We just saw mine. Let me see yours.
-Oh, okay.
Oh, no!
It's gone! That's so weird.
I don't know where it went.
-You didn't get it?
-No.
-Why not?
-I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
How couId you do this?
This was your idea!
I know! I was gonna get it,
but he came in with this needIe.
Did you know
they do this with needIes?
ReaIIy? You don't say?
Because mine was Iicked on by kittens!
I'm sorry.
SeriousIy, does it hurt a Iot?
No, it's just a pinch. Like that--
Oh, my God!
That reaIIy hurt me!
Oh, that's gonna Ieave a mark.
I'm sorry about what--
-Yeah, me too.
-I know.
So do we need to hug here?
No, we're aII right.
So I got you something.
PIastic spoons!
-Great!
-Lick away, my man.
These wiII go great in my new pIace,
tiII I get reaI ones.
What?
I can't use these forever.
They're no friend of the environment.
No, I mean what's this
about your new pIace?
-I'm moving out, Iike we taIked about.
-I didn't think that was serious.
I thought that was just a fight.
WeII, it was a fight.
Based on serious stuff, remember?
About how I never Iived aIone?
I think it wouId be good for me.
HeIp me to grow...
...or whatever.
WeII, there you go.
Are you cooI with this?
I don't wanna Ieave you high and dry.
I've never been Iower or wetter.
I'II be fine. I'II just turn
your bedroom into a game room.
Put the foosbaII tabIe in there.
Why do you get to keep the tabIe?
I did pay for haIf of it.
-And I paid for the other haIf.
-AII right, I'II pIay you for it.
AII right, you're on.
I can take two minutes
out of my day to kick your ass.
Your men wiII get scored on
more times than your sister.
Which sister?
So are you sorry that I toId them?
No. It's been a Iong time
since your dad and I went running.
-Did you get it?
-Is Ross here?
-He went out for pizza.
-Okay, reaIIy quick.
-That's great!
-Very tastefuI.
-Wanna see mine?
-Yes.
What? You didn't get one.
Okay. WeII then, what is this?
What are we Iooking at?
That bIue freckIe?
That's my tattoo.
That is not a tattoo.
That is a nothing.
I got her in the chair,
he bareIy touched her...
...she screamed and that was it.
Okay, hi!
For your information,
this is exactIy what I wanted.
This is a tattoo of the Earth as seen
from a great, great distance.
It's the way my mother
sees me from heaven.
Oh, what a Ioad of crap!
That is a dot!
Your mother's in heaven going,
''Where the heII's my IiIy, you wuss?!''
Okay? That is not a tattoo!
This is a tattoo!
You got a tattoo?
Maybe.
But just a IittIe one.
Phoebe got the whoIe worId!
WeII, Iet me see.
WeII?
WeII, it's reaIIy...
...sexy.
I wouIdn't have thought
it wouId be, but...
...wow!
-ReaIIy?
-Yeah. So...
...is it sore?
Or can you do stuff?
I guess.
Save us some pizza.
Get it out of the corner!
Pass it! Pass it!
Stop taIking to your men!
And the tabIe is mine.
CongratuIations.
You guys wiII stiII visit, right?
Oh, yeah. You got the big TV.
We'II be over there aII the time.
Except when we are here.
I know you're just moving uptown,
but I'II miss you.
How can you not be across the haII?
Who's gonna eat aII our food
and tie up our phone Iines--?
Is that my bra?
-What are you doing with my bra?
-It's not what you think.
We used it to fIing
water baIIoons off the roof.
Remember? Those kids couIdn't
even get theirs across the street.
Yeah, I remember.
Let's bring the rest of these
down to the truck.
You want me to...
...give you a hand
with the foosbaII tabIe?
You keep it.
You need the practice.
Thanks.
So I guess this is it.
Yeah, right. Yeah. I guess so.
Listen, I don't know when
I'm gonna see you again.
Tonight, at the coffeehouse.
Right. Yeah. Okay.
-Take care.
-Yeah.