We're running Iow on résumés.
You want a job
with Popular Mechanics?
If you're gonna work for mechanics,
those are the ones.
Guys, I'm going for anything here.
I can't be a waitress anymore.
I'm sick of the Iousy tips.
I'm sick of being caIIed ''Excuse Me.''
-Paper cut! Paper cut!
-Here.
Grapefruit juice! Grapefruit juice!
Okay, we're aImost done.
OnIy 20 more to go.
-Rach, did you proofread these?
-Yeah. Why?
Nothing. I'm sure they'II be
impressed with your ''compuper'' skiIIs.
Oh, my God!
Do you think it's on aII of them?
No, I'm sure the Xerox machine
caught a few.
The One With the Poker
They caII this a Iove seat but I'm not
feeIing anything speciaI towards you.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
Hi, Iadies.
Can I get you anything?
Did you bring the maiI?
-Lots of responses.
-ReaIIy? Sure, we have scones Ieft!
Read them.
''Dear Miss Greene:
Thank you for your inquiry. However--''
-We have appIe cinnamon--
-''Dear Ms. Greene....'' Yeah, yeah! No.
-What?
-Your Visa biII is huge!
Give me that.
Linda's great.
Why won't you go out with her?
-I don't know.
-Is this about her...
...''The FIintstones couId
have reaIIy happened'' thing?
It's not just that. I want someone
who does something for me...
...who gets my heart pounding.
Who makes me....
LittIe pIaythings with yarn?
What?
CouId you want her more?
Who?
Dee, the sarcastic sister
from What's Happening!!.
Look, I'm totaIIy over her.
-Hi!
-Coffee?
-No, we're fine.
-Okay.
-Shut up!
-We're not saying anything.
-What?
-Joey cried Iast night.
-Thank you.
-We were pIaying poker--
There was chocoIate on the three.
It Iooked Iike an eight.
You shouId have seen him.
''Read them and weep!''
And then he did.
Now, how come you guys
have never pIayed poker with us?
Yeah, what is that?
Like some kind of sexist guy thing?
-It's poker, so onIy guys can pIay?
-No. Women can pIay.
Then, what is it? Some kind of, Iike,
some kind of, you know--
AII right, what is it?
There are just no women
in our game.
We just don't know any
women who know how to pIay poker.
That is a Iame excuse.
It's a typicaI guy response.
Do you know how to pIay?
No.
-But you couId teach us.
-No.
Okay, so now we draw cards.
So I wouIdn't need any.
I have a straight.
-Oh, good for you!
-CongratuIations!
-Pheebs, how many do you want?
-I just need two.
The 10 of spades and the 6 of cIubs.
-No, you can't--
-I have the 10 of spades! Here.
Thanks!
-No, you can't do that.
-Don't need them. I'm going for fours.
Oh, you're--
You're going for fours.
ChandIer, couId you--? Thanks, man.
Here we go.
We've got saImon rouIettes
and crudités.
What are you doing?
In poker, there's no food
with more than one syIIabIe.
It's got to be Iike chips
or dip or pretz--
I hope you'II Iet it sIide just
this once. I was aII out of ''pretz.''
Now the deaIer--
We got it. Let's pIay for reaI.
High stakes. Big bucks!
You sure? Phoebe just threw away two
jacks because they didn't Iook happy.
But I'm ready. So just deaI.
Okay, Iast-minute Iesson!
Joey....
Three.
Eight.
Eight. Three.
AII right, very good.
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
Joey had two fives showing,
so for you to raise was--
Yes?
Downright gutsy.
-I see, so you were Iying.
-About what?
-About how good your cards were.
-I was bIuffing.
And what is bIuffing?
Is it not another word for Iying?
Sorry to break up this party, but I've
got to go fax résumés before work.
-We've got to settIe.
-SettIe what?
The Jamestown coIony of Virginia.
See, IKing George is giving us
the Iand....
-The game, RacheI. You owe us money.
-Right.
It's their first time.
Let's forget about the money.
HeII, no. We'II pay!
Monica, I had another
answer aII ready.
And you know what?
We want a rematch.
That's fine with me.
CouId use some money.
-You're enjoying this, aren't you?
-WeII, yeah, I am.
So you get your ya-yas
by taking money from your friends.
Yes, and I get my ya-yas from IIKEA.
You have to put them together
yourseIf, but they cost Iess.
Look, this is poker.
I pIay to win.
For me to win,
others have to Iose.
If you're gonna pIay,
don't expect me to be nice.
Because once those cards are deaIt....
Yeah?
I'm not a nice guy.
AII right, Iet's eat.
Did you get that
from the ''I Love RacheI Pizzeria''?
-You stiII on that?
-What was with that BIack Bart speech?
''When I pIay poker,
I'm not a nice guy.''
You're way off.
No, I don't think so,
because I think you Iove her!
No. I might have had feeIings
for her at one time. Not anymore.
I just--
MarceI! Where are you going
with that disk?
You are not putting that on again.
If you press that button,
you are in very big troubIe.
You beIieve what a jerk
Ross was being?
-Yeah, I know.
-He can get reaIIy competitive.
What?
''HeIIo, kettIe? This is Monica.
You're bIack!''
PIease!
I'm not as bad as Ross.
I beg to differ.
The Pictionary incident?
That wasn't an incident.
I was gesturing and the pIate
sIipped out of my hand.
-I got an interview!
-You're kidding! Where?
Saks Fifth Avenue.
Oh, RacheI!
It's Iike the mother ship
is caIIing you home.
-What's the job?
-Assistant buyer.
I wouId be shopping!
For a Iiving!
That's Aunt Iris. She's been
pIaying poker since she was 5.
You've got to Iisten
to every word she says.
-Is Tony RandaII dead?
-I don't think so.
-He may be now. I hit him with my car.
-My God, reaIIy?
No, that's bIuffing.
Lesson number one.
Let me teII you something. Everything
you hear at a poker game is pure crap!
-Nice earrings.
-Thank you.
-GirIs, sit down.
-Aunt Iris, this is Phoebe and RacheI.
Listen, I'm parked at a meter.
Let's do it. Okay?
We'II start with five-card draw.
Then we'II go into the studs and the
hoId 'ems. I taIked to Cousin Nathan.
Don't touch the cards
when somebody is deaIing.
How is Nathan?
Now he thinks he's a man
in a woman's body.
Don't you mean
a woman in a man's body?
It shouId be so simpIe.
Ross, couId we pIease Iisten
to anything eIse?
AII right.
I'm gonna pay for that tonight.
Hi. Guys, guess what?
The fifth dentist caved, and now
they're aII recommending Trident?
No, the interview!
UnbeIievabIe!
She absoIuteIy Ioved me.
We taIked for over two hours.
We've the same taste in cIothes.
And I went to camp with her cousin.
-The job is perfect! I can do this.
-That's great!
-Then she toId a funny story.
-Great, teII us and we'II Iaugh.
Let's pIay poker!
Listen, we taIked about it and
if you don't wanna pIay, it's okay.
Yes, we can pIay some other game.
Like Pictionary?
Very funny.
-But we'd Iike to try poker again.
-Yes, I think we shouId.
-Do you want me to shuffIe those?
-That's okay, I'm gonna give it a go.
So Pheebs owes $ 7.50.
Monica owes $10.00.
And RacheI, you owe 1 5 big ones!
Thanks for teaching us Cross-Eyed
Mary. We gotta pIay that other way.
AII right, here's my $ 7.50.
But this money is cursed.
-What?
-I cursed it!
Now bad things wiII happen
to the spender.
I'II take it.
Bad things happen to me anyway.
This way, I can spIit them up
with a movie.
So that just Ieaves the big Greene
poker machine, who owes 1 5.
CouId you be any smugger?
Let's see. Rach, I'm opening up
a new art gaIIery...
...and I couId sure use the portraits
of LincoIn and HamiIton.
It's so typicaI.
''I'm a man! I have a penis!
I have to win money
to exert my power over women!''
This isn't over.
We'II pIay you again.
We'II win. You'II Iose.
You'II beg. We'II Iaugh.
We'II take every Iast dime you have.
And you'II hate yourseIves forever!
IKind of stepped on
my point there, Mon.
I can't beIieve you Iost!
How much did they take?
Like 30 bucks.
-I'II give you that money back.
-ReaIIy?
No, I'm bIuffing!
You guys haven't Iearned crap!
-Hand me the cards!
-Can I?
Yes!
Wanna give us your money now? We can
skip the formaIity of reaIIy pIaying.
No, that's fine. We'II see who has
the Iast Iaugh, monkey boy.
Done with chitchat?
Ready for serious poker?
You guys, Iook! The one-eyed jack
foIIows me wherever I go.
Right. Serious poker.
-Mon, got any more of those saImon--?
-You want to eat or pIay poker?
-Where are you going?
-To the bathroom.
Want to go to the bathroom
or pIay poker?
Go to the bathroom.
-WeII, I'm gonna order a pizza.
-No!
I'm waiting to hear from that job.
The store cIoses at 9:00. Eat then.
That's fine. I'II just have a Tic Tac
to hoId me over.
AII right. Cincinnati. No bIinds.
Everybody, ante.
Yes!
Or no.
-AII right! Your money's mine, Greene.
-Your fIy's open, GeIIer.
You know what I just reaIized?
Joker is poker with a ''J''!
Coincidence?
That's jo-incidence with a ''C''!
-Phoebe?
-Yeah, I'm out.
-I'm in.
-Me too.
Me too.
What do you got?
You better hop out of the shower,
because I got a fIush.
WeII, weII, weII!
Hop back in, bucko,
because I got four sixes!
I got four sixes! I won!
I actuaIIy won! Oh, my God!
You know what?
I'II make a IittIe Ross piIe.
Look!
I think that one was Ross'.
And I think that one was Ross'.
Well, I have got your money
And you'll never see it
And your fly's still open
I made you look
-I'm in.
-I couIdn't be in-er.
Monica, in or out?
I hate this game!
Joey, your bet.
I foId Iike a hooker
who got hit in the stomach...
...by a fat guy
with sores on his face.
I'm out.
-Ross?
-I'm very in.
-ChandIer?
-CouIdn't be more out.
Me too. RacheI?
I wiII see you and I'II raise you.
Do you wanna waste another buck?
No, not this time.
What did you have?
-I'm not teIIing.
-Show them.
-No.
-Show them!
-Get your hands out of there!
-I've had dates Iike this.
Boy, you reaIIy can't stand
to Iose, can you?
Your whoIe face is getting red.
Veins popping out of your tempIe!
PIus, that shirt doesn't reaIIy
match those pants.
-I'm not Iosing.
-You're definiteIy Iosing.
HeIIo. RacheI Greene.
Excuse me. It's about the job!
Barbara, hi! How are you?
No, I understand.
Come on. No, I'm fine.
Don't be siIIy. Yeah.
But if anything eIse
opens up, pIease--
HeIIo?
Sorry, Rach.
There's gonna be Iots
of other stuff.
Okay.
Where were we?
Five-card draw. Jacks are better.
Nothing wiId. Everybody, ante.
-Look, Rach, we don't have to do this.
-Yes, we do.
-AII right. Check.
-Check.
-I'm in for 50 cents.
-CaII.
I'm in.
I see your 50 cents...
...and I raise you $5.
I thought it was a 50-cent Iimit.
I just Iost a job,
I'd Iike to raise it $5.
Does anyone have
a probIem with that?
-Not at aII.
-No.
Loser?
-No, I foId.
-What do you mean, you foId?
I thought that, ''Once the cards
are deaIt, I'm not a nice guy.''
Were you just fuII of it?
I'm in.
-How many do you want?
-One.
DeaIer takes two.
-What do you bet?
-I bet $2.
Okay. I see your $2...
...and I raise you...
...20.
I see your $20...
...raise you $25.
I see your $25
and Monica, get my purse.
RacheI, there's nothing in it.
Okay, then get me your purse.
-Here you go. Good Iuck!
-Thank you.
I saw your $25 and I raise you...
...seven.
--teen!
Joey, I'm a IittIe shy.
That's okay, Ross. You can ask me.
-What do you need?
-1 5.
-Here's 10.
-I got 5.
-Thank you.
-Good Iuck.
I am caIIing your 1 7.
What do you got?
FuII house.
You got me.
-That's tough to beat.
-I thought we had it!
When you don't have the cards,
you don't have the cards.
But Iook how happy she is.
-AirmaiI.
-AirpIane. Airport. Airport '75!
Airport '77! Airport '79!
Time's up!
Bye Bye Birdie!
That's a bird?
That's a bird!
Okay, it's my turn.
Go!
Bean! Bean!
The Unbearable Lightness of Being!
That you get?
That you get?!