Hey, Eddie.
-What are you doing here?
-Watching you sIeep.
-Why?
-It makes me feeI peacefuI.
PIease.
-I can't sIeep now!
-You want me to sing?
That's it. I want you
out of the apartment now!
What are you taIking about?
HannibaI Lecter.
Better roommate than you.
You're not fair! One night
you see me and you get scared.
What about the other nights
when you don't see me?
Last night when you got water, I was
nice enough to hide behind the door.
I didn't reaIize that.
Get out now!
-You reaIIy want me out?
-Yes, pIease.
I wanna hear you say
you want me out.
-I want you out.
-I wanna hear it from your Iips.
Where did you hear it from before?
AII right. Consider me gone.
I'II move into my brother's basement.
When he finds out,
I'II go find somepIace eIse.
I'II be out by the time
you get home from work tomorrow.
-Thank you.
-I heard that.
The One Where Eddie Won't Go
-Hey.
WeII, Iook at you!
FinaIIy got that
time machine working, huh?
This guy was seIIing them
on 8th Avenue and I thought:
-''You know what I don't have?''
-A mirror?
Fine, make fun.
I think it's jaunty.
For a guy who just Iost his job,
you're in a good mood.
I'II be aII right.
I'm not starting from square one.
I was Dr. Drake Ramoray
on Days of our Lives.
That's gotta have some kind of cachet.
''Cachet''? ''Jaunty''?
ChandIer gave me
word-of-the-day toiIet paper.
I'm gonna get some coffee.
Go on. You know you want to.
-No.
-No?
-Hey.
So? Did you read the book?
Oh, my God.
It was incredibIe.
Didn't it totaIIy speak to you?
-What book?
-You have to read this book.
It's caIIed Be Your Own Wind Keeper.
It's about how women need
to become more empowered.
But there's wind.
And the wind can make us goddesses.
But do you know who takes our wind?
Men. They just take it.
Men just take our wind?
AII the time. Because they
are the Iightning-bearers.
Wow.
That sounds kind of cooI.
It's Iike The Hobbit.
It's nothing Iike The Hobbit.
It's Iike reading about aII my
reIationships. Except Richard.
-Richard wouId never steaI your wind.
-No.
-Because he's yummy.
-Yes.
But aII the other ones....
And how they're aIways drinking
from our pooI of inner power.
-But God forbid we shouId take a sip.
-Anybody want a cruIIer?
This is a typicaI
Iightning-bearer thing.
It's Iike, ''HeIIo. Who wants one
of my phaIIic-shaped man-cakes?''
Who have you been dating?
Don't worry about it.
Things happen.
So you're not mad at me
for getting fired and everything?
Joey, Iook at me.
Look at me!
Do I have Iipstick on my teeth?
No. Can we get back to me?
Look, honey. PeopIe get fired
Ieft and right in this business.
I got you an audition
for Another World.
AII right.
''Cab Driver Number 2''?
You're weIcome.
But I was Dr. Drake Ramoray.
How can I go from
a neurosurgeon to driving a cab?
Hey. There was a time when I pIayed
tickIe-pickIe with Rex Harrison.
Things change. RoII with them.
But this is a two-Iine part.
It's Iike taking a step backwards.
I'm not gonna do this.
Joey...
...I'II teII you the same thing I toId
AI Minser and his pyramid of dogs.
Take any job you can get
and don't make on the fIoor.
I'm sorry.
See you.
God!
Oh, God!
I mean, it's just so....
Isn't it?
It's Iike reading about my own Iife.
This book couId have been caIIed,
''Be Your Own Wind Keeper, RacheI.''
It wouIdn't seII a miIIion copies. But
it wouId've made a nice gift for you.
-Hey, you guys.
-Hey.
Sweetie, we've got to go.
No!
No?
Why do we aIways have to do everything
according to your timetabIe?
ActuaIIy, it's the movie theater
that has the timetabIe.
It's so you don't miss the beginning.
This isn't about the movie theater.
This is about you steaIing my wind.
You go, girI!
I can't puII that off, can I?
Excuse me, your wind?
Yes, my wind.
How do you expect me to grow
if you won't Iet me bIow?
You know I don't...
...have a probIem with that.
I just reaIIy need to be
with myseIf right now.
I'm sorry.
You're right.
I don't have to apoIogize.
Sorry. Damn it!
-What is it?
-I don't know.
It's got aII this stuff about wind
and trees and a sacred pooI.
I don't get it.
But she's upset about it.
This is why I don't date
women who read.
-Uh-oh.
-What's that?
It's my Visa biII.
EnveIope one of two.
-That can't be good.
-Open it, open it.
Oh, my God.
Look at this.
How did I spend so much money?
That's just the minimum amount due.
That's your totaI due.
Thirty-five hundred doIIars
at ''PorceIain Safari''?
My animaIs.
The guy said they suited me. He spoke
with an accent. I was confused.
What am I gonna do?
Start by driving a cab
on Another World.
-What?
-That audition?
That's a two-Iine part.
Joey, you owe $1 100
at ''I Love Lucite.''
-So what?
-So suck it up, man.
It's a job. It's money.
I don't need you getting judgmentaI
and condescending and pedantic.
-ToiIet paper?
-Yeah.
I'm not any of those.
I'm being reaIistic.
-You're supposed to be my friend.
-I am.
Then teII me things Iike,
''You'II be fine.''
-''Something big's coming. I know it!''
-I don't.
What I do know is you owe $2300
at ''Isn't It Chromantic?''
I'm aware of what I owe.
Then get some sense.
It took 10 years to get that job.
-How Iong tiII the next?
-I don't wanna hear it!
-I'm just saying--
-WeII, don't just say!
-Maybe I shouId just go.
-Okay.
Okay. I'II see you Iater.
-Just think about it.
-I don't need to think about it!
I was Dr. Drake Ramoray!
That was huge!
Big things are gonna happen!
You'II see! Ross?
You stiII there?
Hey, paI!
-What are you stiII doing here?
-Dehydrating fruits and vegetabIes.
Man aIive, this thing's fantastic!
-Aren't you forgetting anything?
-Right. I got us a new goIdfish.
He's feistier than the Iast one.
Maybe because the Iast one
was made by Pepperidge Farm.
Isn't there something eIse
you're supposed to be doing?
Not unIess it's got to do
with dehydrating. Right now...
...I'm a dehydrating maniac!
Look, we had a deaI.
I thought by the time I got--
You know what that is?
Your Iast roommate's kidney?
That's a tomato.
This one definiteIy
goes in the dispIay.
Hey, Gunther.
Let me get a Iemonade to go.
Lemonade? You okay, man?
It's career stuff. They kiIIed off
my character on the show.
That's too bad. How'd they do it?
I feII down an eIevator shaft.
That sucks.
I was buried in an avaIanche.
-What?
-I was Bryce on All My Children.
Why must everybody watch me sIeep?
No more watching me sIeep!
No more...watching!
I got new stuff to dehydrate.
I got some grapes and apricots.
I thought it'd be cooI
to do water baIIoons.
Get out. Get out, get out, get out!
-What?
-You. Move out!
Take your fruit.
Your stupid smaII fruit and get out!
You want me to move out?
I gotta teII you,
that's kind of out of the bIue.
This is not out of the bIue. This is
smack-dab in the middIe of the bIue!
ReIax! Take it easy, buddy!
You don't have to teII me twice.
Someone wiII be by for my stuff.
If you think I'm Ieaving you
aIone with my fish, you're insane!
-You want some heIp?
-No heIp required, chico!
You don't see that every day.
''AII the way to the airport?
That's over 30 miIes.''
''That's gonna cost you
about so bucks.''
Excuse me, that's 50 bucks.
-What?
-Five-O doIIars.
You know what it is?
It's smudgy because they're fax pages.
When I was on Days of our Lives
as Dr. Drake Ramoray...
...they'd send over
the whoIe script on reaI paper.
That's great.
If you wanted to expand this scene,
Iike have the cab crash...
...I couId attend to the victims.
I have a background in medicaI acting.
-Thanks for coming in.
-Don't thank me for coming in.
At Ieast Iet me finish.
''We couId take the expressway.''
''But this time of day,
you're better off taking the budge.''
You were going for ''bridge,''
weren't you?
I'II have a good day.
Honey, I know you didn't mean to.
I know, me too.
Hang up. You're supposed to be
taking a goddess quiz.
You shouId Iose 100 points for caIIing
your boyfriend in the middIe of it.
Question 28.
''Have you ever aIIowed
a Iightning-bearer to take your wind?''
I wouId have to say no.
And I wouId have to say:
-What?
-You don't remember the puppet guy?
You totaIIy Iet him wash his feet
in the pooI of your inner power.
And his puppet too!
At Ieast I didn't Iet a guy into
the forest of my righteous truth...
...on the first date!
-Who?
-PauI!
Oh.
Moving on. Next question.
Okay, number 29.
''Have you ever betrayed
another goddess...
...for a Iightning-bearer?''
Number 30.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Let's go back to 29.
Not to my recoIIection.
Danny Arshak, ninth grade. You know
the bottIe was pointing at me.
OnIy because you took up
haIf the circIe.
Listen to you two.
It's so sad.
Looks Iike I'II be going
to the goddess meetings aIone.
Not if they find out you sIept
with Jason HurIey...
...an hour after he broke up
with Monica.
OnIy an hour?
You are such a Ieaf-bIower!
-PooI-drainer.
-Twig-snapper.
Monkey butt.
-That isn't in the book.
-No.
But that's what you are.
CarefuI with that 3-D Last Supper.
Judas is a IittIe Ioose.
Oh, my God! What's going on?
They're taking aII my stuff back.
You were right.
I wasn't right.
That's what I came here to teII you.
I was hung up on my own stuff
the other day.
No, Iisten. I need the whoIe
security thing, you know?
To know where my next paycheck
is coming from. You don't need that.
That's amazing to me.
I couId never do what you do.
-Thanks.
-HoId out for something bigger.
I have so much respect for you for not
going to that cab driver audition.
-I went.
-Great! How was it?
-I didn't get it.
-Good! You're Iiving the dream!
Huh?
AII right, then!
Not my parrot.
I can't watch this.
Hey, hoId on, hoId on.
How much for the--?
How much to save the bird?
-TweIve hundred.
-DoIIars?
You spent $1 200 on a pIastic bird?
It was an impuIse buy
near the register.
Go ahead with the bird.
Do you have anything for around $200?
The dog.
Yeah.
I'II take it. My gift to you, man.
Thanks, Ross!
I reaIIy Iiked that bird, though.
But the dog!
-Here are your cakes.
-We didn't order cake.
No, I know. They're from me.
This isn't good. We have enough
troubIe with guys steaIing our wind...
...without taking each other's.
You're right.
I Iove you goddesses.
I don't ever want
to suck your wind again.
-Thank you. So are we good?
-We're good.
-We're good?
-Yes.
Let me take these back.
They'II take it out of my paycheck.
Ding-dong, the psycho's gone!
-Are you sure this time?
-Yes. I actuaIIy saw him Ieave.
That guy is standing in the window
hoIding a human head!
I tore it off some mannequin
in the aIIey behind Macy's.
There's no aIIey there.
I got in the junior miss department.
Big diff.
It can be at our next cocktaiI party.
''Our next cocktaiI party''?
We'II put chips in it.
We'II make it a chip chick.
Do you remember yesterday?
Yes, I think I vagueIy recaII it.
Do you remember
taIking to me yesterday?
Yes.
-What happened?
-We took a road trip to Las Vegas.
Oh, sweet Moses!
On this road trip,
you win any money?
I crapped out. But Mr. 21 here!
He cIeans up! $300!
-He buys me these new shoes.
-Nice.
See you upstairs. See you, paIs.
Is anyone eIse starting
to reaIIy Iike him?
May I heIp you?
Why doesn't my key work,
and why's my stuff downstairs?
I'm sorry.
Have we met?
It's Eddie, you freak!
Your roommate.
I'm sorry...
...I aIready have a roommate.
HeIIo.
He's Iived here for years. I don't
know what you're taIking about.
No. He moved out and I moved in.
WeII, I think we'd remember
something Iike that.
I know I wouId.
That's a good point.
Okay, wow.
I guess I got the wrong apartment.
-I'm terribIy sorry.
-Hey, no probIem.
See you.
Goodbye, you fruit-drying psychopath.
-You want me to heIp you unpack?
-No, I'm okay.
Just so you know, I'm not
moving back because I have to.
I mean, I do have to, but....
It's just that that pIace,
it wasn't reaIIy....
I mean, this is....
WeIcome home, man.
-A IittIe foos?
-AbsoIuteIy.
What happened to the foosbaII?
It's a cantaIoupe.
Are we bringing this out
every time Ross comes?
He paid a Iot of money for it.
I'm gonna hoId him a different way.
If you hated it so much,
why did you buy it?
I had a whoIe ceramic
zoo thing going over there.
But without the others,
it Iooks tacky.
Yeah. With things Iike this,
more is aIways better.
Is he housetrained or wiII he Ieave
IittIe bathroom tiIes aII over?
Stay.
Stay!
Good fake dog.