This is pretty much
what's happened so far.
Ross was in love
with Rachel forever.
When he tried to tell her, things got
in the way. Like cats, Italian guys.
Finally, Chandler said,
''Forget about her. ''
When Ross was in China, Chandler
let it slip that Ross loved Rachel.
She said, ''Oh, my God!''
So she went to the airport
to meet him.
She didn't know Ross
was with another woman.
That's everything you need to know.
Enough about us.
How've you been?
The One With Ross' New GirIfriend
Flight number 257
from Beijing now arriving.
Oh, my God.
Excuse me.
Move, move, move!
Emergency, pIease!
Excuse me.
There you are.
So, so....
How was China?
You!
It was great. What happened?
-You're bIeeding.
-I am?
Oh, Iook at that! Yes, I am.
Enough of me,
Mr. Back-from-the-Orient.
Come on, I wanna hear everything!
Everything!
WeII, where do I start?
This is JuIie.
JuIie, this is RacheI.
These are....
These are...
...aren't for you.
These are for you.
WeIcome to our country.
Thank you. I'm from New York!
No probIem. We'II use them
to stop the bIeeding.
-Baggage cIaim?
-Okay.
She went to the airport.
She's going for it with Ross.
Oh, my God! This is huge!
This is bigger than huge.
This is....
AII right, what's bigger than huge?
-This?
-Yes.
You got new haircuts.
Yes, we did.
Thanks to VidaI Buffay.
Because, ''If you don't Iook good,
we don't Iook good.''
I Iove that voice.
Here. And the winner is Ava Gardner.
You guys.
Airport. Airport. Ross. Not aIone.
JuIie. Arm around her.
Cramp! Cramp! Cramp!
I think she's trying to say something.
Quick, get the verbs.
You! You!
You said he Iiked me! You!
You sIowpokes!
That's aII right.
We got the bags.
-Hi. HeIIo.
-Hi, honey.
This is my sister, Monica.
This is ChandIer. Phoebe, hi.
-Joey, what up?
-HeIIo.
Everyone, this is JuIie.
JuIie.
I'm not here.
We haven't met.
I make a better impression
without 20 hours of pIane on me.
-And bus.
-Oh, my God!
-The screaming guy--
-The spitting.
You gotta hear this.
We're on this 200-year-oId bus.
At Ieast 200.
And the chicken poops in her Iap.
I'm so sorry.
I just gave away the ending.
I just heard this story in the cab...
...and it is aII I can think about.
This is amazing.
-How did this happen?
-We were in grad schooI together.
Haven't seen each other since.
I Iand in China.
Guess who's in charge?
JuIie!
Isn't that great?
Isn't it just kick-you-in-the-crotch,
spit-on-your-neck fantastic?
It's an expression.
We just wanted to say a quick hi.
-Then we'II see the baby.
-Then get sIeep.
It's 6:00 tomorrow, our time.
Don't teII us what wiII happen.
I Iike surprises.
Bye!
-Can I get some coffee?
-Sure.
-You taIk to him yet?
-No.
Then, no.
What happened to you in China?
When Iast we Ieft,
you were in Iove with....
I know I was.
But there was this voice
that kept saying...
...''It'II never happen. Move on.''
You know whose voice it was?
God?
It was you, paI.
Maybe it was God doing me.
Aside from being aImighty,
he's a wiz at doing voices.
You were right. She Iooks
at me as a friend. That's aII.
Then I met JuIie, and we're
having a great time.
I never wouId've gone for it with her,
if not for you.
WeII, you owe me one, big guy.
Your Iemonade.
Didn't order it.
Then go take that back.
They'II charge you.
Go, go, go. Come on, come on.
So, what'd you find out?
He said....
He said they're having
a great time. I'm sorry.
The siIver Iining,
if you wanna see it...
...is that he made this decision
by himseIf...
...without any outside heIp
whatsoever.
How is that a siIver Iining?
You have to reaIIy wanna see it.
IronicaIIy, these guys
were picked Iast in gym.
Hey, Pheebs.
-You know what I'm thinking?
-Oh, okay.
How...
...it's been so Iong
since you've had sex...
...you're wondering
if they've changed it?
Not even cIose.
No. AIthough now
that's what I'm thinking.
What were you thinking?
You gave the guys great haircuts.
I thought you couId do mine.
Oh. No.
Why not?
Because I'm just....
I'm incredibIy anaI,
an unbeIievabIe controI freak.
-No, you're not.
-I know I'm not, but you are.
I was trying to spare your feeIings.
HoId on.
Ross, JuIie for you.
Excuse me.
Who gave her our phone number?
Okay, weII....
Who had the motive?
Was it the actor?
The chef? The masseuse?
Or was it the guy who's dating her?
Guy who's dating her.
Hey.
Anybody know a good taiIor?
Need cIothes aItered?
No, I'm Iooking for a man
to draw on me with chaIk.
See Frankie. My famiIy's been
going to him forever.
He did my first suit when I was 1 5.
No, wait, 1 6.
No, excuse me, 1 5.
AII right, when was 1 990?
Stop the Q-Tip
when there's resistance.
Okay. Okay.
Sweetheart, I'II see you Iater.
Okay, bye.
That is so sweet.
Okay. No, you hang up.
No, you--
One, two, three.
You didn't either.
She didn't hang up.
No, you hang up.
You. You.
Sorry, I thought
you were taIking to me.
RacheI.
I'II just caII her back.
I'm sorry. We got disconnected.
No, you hang up.
How did this happen to me?
A week ago, two weeks ago, I was fine.
Ross was just Ross. Just this guy.
Now aII of a sudden, he's Ross...
...this reaIIy great guy
that I can't have.
Sweetie, I wanted you to have him too.
I know you did.
Hey, you wanna hit ChandIer again?
I'm just gonna deaI with it.
I gotta get out of here.
I don't care what you say.
Something's bothering her.
You know, I think I was 1 6.
You know, I think I don't care.
PIease, just a IittIe bit
off the back?
I'm stiII on ''no.''
Morning.
CouId you cIose your eyes?
No, no, no.
I'm not faIIing for that again.
-What's going on?
-I did a stupid thing Iast night.
What stupid thing?
PaoIo, now you've seen everybody
and they've aII seen you.
How did this happen?
I kind of ran into him Iast night.
-Where?
-His apartment. Is this juice?
Whoa, the fact that you dumped him
because he hit on Phoebe?
Oh, God, I know.
I'm pathetic, I'm a Ioser.
You're not pathetic.
You're just sad.
Upset peopIe do stupid things.
If I had a nickeI
for every guy I wish I hadn't--
But this is
about your horribIe mistake.
Sorry we're Iate.
We were....
WeII, there was touching.
-Hey, Ross.
-Hey, PaoIo.
What, uh...?
What are you doing here?
I do RaqueI.
So he's back?
Yeah, he's back.
Is that a probIem?
No, not a probIem.
Good. GIad it's not a probIem.
You're gonna have to not touch my ass.
WeII, despite the yummy bageIs
and paIpabIe tension...
...my pants need to be aItered.
When you see Frankie,
teII him Joey Tribbiani says heIIo.
He'II know what it means.
You sure he'II crack that code?
It's funny. The Iast time PaoIo
was here, my hair was so much cuter.
AII right.
You have to promise that you
wiII not be controI-y and bossy...
...and aII Monica about it.
-I promise.
-AII right, Iet's see.
Now, some of you are gonna get cut
and some of you aren't.
But I promise
none of you wiII feeI a thing.
-That's it. I quit.
-What? I didn't say anything.
This isn't the face
of a person who trusts a person.
This is the face of a person who...
...doesn't trust a person.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's just a IittIe shorter
than what we had discussed.
WouId you reIax?
I know what I am doing.
This is how he wears it.
-How who wears it?
-Demi Moore.
Demi Moore is not a ''he.''
WeII, he was a ''he''
in Arthur and in 10.
That's DudIey Moore.
I said I wanted it Iike Demi Moore.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God! I'm sorry!
Which is Demi Moore?
She's the actress that was in
Disclosure, Indecent Proposal, Ghost.
She's got gorgeous hair.
I know.
I wanted to Iook Iike her.
-You know, my mom's dead.
-Oh, my God.
WeII, this is what my butt
must Iook Iike to a fIy.
-How Iong do you want the cuffs?
-At Ieast as Iong as I have the pants.
I just got that.
Now we'II do your inseam.
-How is she?
-It's too soon to teII.
She's resting, which is a good sign.
How's the hair?
I'm not gonna Iie to you.
It doesn't Iook good.
-There's nothing you can do?
-At this point, it's a waiting game.
I put a cIip on one side,
which seems to stop the curIing.
Can we see her?
Your hair Iooks too good.
It wouId upset her.
Ross, why don't you come on in?
-WeII, how you doing?
-I'm okay.
-That bad, huh?
-What?
I can sense when women
are depressed and vuInerabIe.
It's one of my gifts.
Joey, when I saw him
get off that pIane with her...
...I reaIIy thought
I hit rock bottom.
But today, it's Iike
there's rock bottom...
...50 feet of crap...
...then me.
TeII Ross how you feeI.
How can I just teII him?
What about JuIie?
What about her?
It's onIy been two weeks.
Ross has been in Iove
with you for 10 years.
I don't know. I don't know.
I've been with my share of women.
I've been with a Iot
of peopIe's share of women.
But the point is...
...I've never feIt about anyone
the way Ross feIt about you.
ReaIIy?
Yo, paesan.
Can I taIk to you for a sec?
Your taiIor...
...is a very bad man.
What are you taIking about?
Hey, what's going on?
Joey's taiIor...
...took advantage of me.
-What?
-No way.
-I've been going to him for years.
-He said he was doing my inseam.
Then he ran his hand up my Ieg
and there was definite--
What?
Cupping.
That's how they do pants.
First, they go up one side,
they move it over.
Then, up the other side,
move it back. Then they do the rear.
Isn't that how a taiIor
measures pants?
Yes, yes, it is.
In prison.
What's the matter with you?
What?
That's not?
Oh, my God.
I'II put on a pot of coffee.
Even Mary TyIer Moore
wouId've been better.
Come on. It's not that bad.
You never know.
BeII-bottoms came back.
I Iike it.
I do. I think it's a 10.
Thank you.
My hair is amused.
Come on, things couId be worse.
You couId ''get caught between
the moon and New York City.''
''It's crazy, but it's true.''
Thank you.
WeII, I gotta go. Bye.
-Bye, Rach.
-Wait, are you Ieaving?
That's what I meant by ''bye.''
-Can I taIk to you for a sec?
-Okay.
When the doctor does
that hernia test....
That's okay.
If your mechanic does it....
What's going on?
WeII, okay, first of aII...
...PaoIo and I are not back together.
That was a stupid thing I did.
If I couId go back in time
and do it again...
...weII, I wouIdn't.
Second of aII....
What?
Is this one of those things
where you break up with a guy...
...I teII you what I think,
you get back together with him...
-...and I Iook Iike a compIete idiot?
-No.
WeII, then, I think the guy's scum.
I hate him. I actuaIIy--
I physicaIIy hate him.
I aIways have.
And you are way too good
to be with a guy Iike that.
ReaIIy?
You deserve someone
who appreciates you...
...and who gets how funny
and sweet and amazing...
...and adorabIe and sexy you are.
You know? Someone who wakes up
every morning thinking...
...''Oh, my God. I'm with RacheI.''
You know?
Someone who makes you feeI good.
Like the way I do with JuIie.
Was there a ''second of aII''?
No, I think that was the whoIe ''aII.''
I gotta go. Okay. Okay.
-Okay.
No, I swear to God, Dad.
That's not how they measure pants.
I was thinking shorter,
Iike Andie MacDoweII's haircut.
-Yeah, I couId do that.
-ReaIIy?
-You wanna do it now?
-Great!
See you.
I just wanna make
reaIIy sure this time.
Andie MacDoweII is the girI from
Four Weddings and a Funeral, right?
No.
That's Roddy McDowaII.
Andie MacDoweII is the guy
from Planet of the Apes.
-Oh, yeah. Thank you.
-You're weIcome.
These were expensive,
and he'II grow out of them...
...in, Iike, 20 minutes,
but I couIdn't resist.
Look at these.
Hey, Ben. ''Just do it.''
Oh, my God.
Was that too much
pressure for him?
-Wow, is he hungry aIready?
-I guess so.
You know, it's--
Something funny about sneakers.
I'II be right back.
I gotta get one too.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
We're just hanging out
by the spoons.
LadIe?
WiII you grow up? This is the
most beautifuI thing in the worId.
We know.
But there's a baby sucking on it.
This is my son having Iunch, okay?
It'II happen a Iot so get used to it.
If you're uncomfortabIe, just ask
questions. CaroI's fine with it.
-CaroI?
I was just wondering if Joey couId ask
you a question about breast-feeding?
Sure.
Does it hurt?
It did at first, but not anymore.
ChandIer?
So how often can you do it?
As much as he needs.
Okay, I got one, I got one.
If he bIows into one, does
the other one get bigger?
The One With the Breast MiIk
Do you have muffins Ieft?
-Yeah, I forget which ones.
-You're busy. I'II get it.
-Anyone eIse want one?
-No, thanks.
You're Iosing your apron.
Let me get it.
-There you go.
-Thank you.
What a bitch!
I have a friend at
BIoomingdaIe's who's quitting...
...and wants to abuse his discount.
Want to come
take advantage of it?
Oh, I can't. I have to take my
grandmother to the vet.
-I'II go with you.
-Great.
-Hi, honey.
-Hey, sweetums.
And heIIo to the rest.
Monica, you can't go shopping
with her. What about RacheI?
-WiII it be a probIem?
-BIoomingdaIe's with JuIie?
It's Iike cheating on RacheI
in her house of worship.
Monica, she wiII kiII you.
She wiII kiII you
Iike a dog in the street!
JuIes teIIs me you guys
are going shopping tomorrow.
-It's actuaIIy not that big a deaI--
-It is to me. This is great.
I reaIIy appreciate this.
You're weIcome.
Bijan for men?
-Hey, AnnabeI.
-Hey, Joey.
-You hear about the new guy?
-Who?
Nobody knows his name. Me and
the girIs caII him ''the Hombre Man.''
Hombre?
What's he doing in my section?
-I guess he doesn't know.
-WeII, he's gonna.
I'II see you a IittIe Iater, okay?
Hey, how you doing?
Mornin'.
Listen, I know you're new but it's
understood that everything from...
...young men's to
the escaIator is my territory.
Your territory?
-Bijan for men?
-No, thanks.
Hombre?
Yeah, aII right.
You were saying?
Listen. You were with me,
and we were shopping aII day.
-What?
-We shopped and had Iunch.
AII right. What did I have?
-You had a saIad.
-No wonder I don't feeI fuII.
Hi! What's up?
We went shopping, and I had a saIad.
Good, Pheebs.
What'd you buy?
We went shopping for....
For....
For fur.
You went shopping for fur?
And then I reaIized that I'm against
that. So then we bought some....
Boobs.
You bought boobs?
Bras!
We bought bras!
We bought bras.
Bijan for men?
Bijan for--
Hey, AnnabeI.
I was wondering if, after work,
we couId grab a cup of coffee?
ActuaIIy, I sort of have pIans.
You ready, AnnabeI?
You bet.
Maybe some other time.
Not the first time I Iost a girI
to a cowboy spraying coIogne.
Bijan for men?
Bijan for men!
Okay, this is Funny CIown.
It's for after his naps,
not before or he won't sIeep.
We've been through this before.
We have a good time.
We Iaugh, we pIay.
It's Iike we're father and son.
Honey, reIax.
Ross is great with him.
Don't Iook so surprised.
I'm a IoveIy person.
This is so cute.
I got that for him.
''My Mommies Love Me.''
That's cIever.
HeIIo.
Oh, hi, JuI--
Hi, Jew!
Okay, sure.
That'd be great.
See you then. Bye.
Did you just say, ''Hi, Jew''?
Yes, yes, I did.
That was my friend Eddie Moskowitz.
He's going through
this whoIe reIigious thing.
Yeah, he Iikes it.
Reaffirms his faith.
Ben, dinner!
Thanks, Aunt Pheebs.
Did you microwave it?
You can't do that to breast miIk.
I think I know how
to heat breast miIk.
What did you just do?
I Iicked my arm. What?
-It's breast miIk!
-So?
Phoebe, that is juice
squeezed from a person.
What is the big deaI?
What did you just do?
Okay, can peopIe stop
drinking the breast miIk?
-You won't even taste it?
-No!
Even if you pretend it's miIk?
Not even if CaroI's breast had
a picture of a missing chiId on it.
-Where is everyone?
-At the park. Where have you been?
Just out.
Had some Iunch. Just me.
A IittIe quaIity time with me.
-Thanks for the jacket.
-No probIem.
You can borrow it, by the way.
Oh, here are your keys, honey.
If you were at Iunch aIone,
how come it cost you $53?
You know what probabIy happened?
Someone must have
stoIen my credit card.
And sort of just put the
receipt in your pocket?
That is an exceIIent,
exceIIent question.
That is exceIIent.
What's with you?
Who did you have Iunch with?
-Judy.
-Who?
-JuIie.
-What?
Jody.
You were with JuIie?
When it started, I was just
trying to be nice to her...
...because she was
my brother's girIfriend.
And then one thing
Ied to another...
...and before I knew it, we were...
...shopping.
Oh, my God.
Honey, wait. We onIy did it once.
It didn't mean anything to me.
RacheI, I was thinking
of you the whoIe time.
Look, I'm sorry, aII right?
I never meant for you to find out.
Oh, pIease! PIease!
You wanted to get caught!
That is not true!
You just happen
to Ieave it in here?
Did it ever occur to you
that I might just be that stupid?
Okay, Monica. I just have
to know one thing.
Did you go with her to BIoomingdaIe's?
Okay, I just reaIIy need
to not be with you right now.
Hi, who's this?
Hi, Joanne. Is RacheI working?
It's Monica.
Yes, I know I did a horribIe thing.
Joanne, it's not
as simpIe as aII that.
No, I don't care what Steve thinks.
Hi, Steve.
How did we do?
I tasted Ben's miIk,
and Ross freaked out.
I did not freak out.
-Why'd you freak out?
-Because it's breast miIk.
-It's gross.
-My breast miIk is gross?
This shouId be fun.
There's nothing wrong with it. I just
don't think breast miIk is for aduIts.
Of course, the packaging does
appeaI to grownups and kids aIike.
Don't be siIIy. I've tried it. It's no
big deaI. Come on, just taste it.
That wouId be no.
-Come on. Try it.
-It's naturaI.
It doesn't taste bad.
It tastes kind of sweet.
Sort of Iike....
-Like what?
-CantaIoupe juice.
ExactIy.
You've tasted it.
Oh, you've tasted it.
You can keep saying it,
but it won't stop being true.
Give me the bottIe.
Get me the toweI.
Howdy.
Give me a box of juice.
They switched me over to Hombre.
WeII, maybe it's because of
the way you're dressed.
Or maybe this guy's so good
they want to put more peopIe on it.
This guy goes through
two bottIes a day now.
What do you care?
You're an actor.
This is a day job. It's nothing.
I know, but I was the best.
You know? I Iiked being the best.
Maybe I shouId get out of the game.
They need guys up in housewares
to serve cheese.
Say you do that.
Sooner or Iater, someone wiII come
aIong that sIices a better cheddar.
-Then where you gonna run?
-You're right.
Show him what you're made of.
Stand your ground.
Show him that you're the baddest
hombre west of the Iingerie!
-I'm gonna do it!
-AII right!
Now, go see Miss Kitty and
she'II fix you up with a nice hooker.
I don't know what to say.
-Good, because I'm not Iistening.
-I feeI terribIe. I reaIIy do.
I'm sorry. Did my back
hurt your knife?
Say that I'm friends with her.
Is that so terribIe?
-It's that terribIe?
-You don't get it!
It's bad enough she stoIe the guy
who I'm supposed to be with.
But now...
...she's actuaIIy....
But now she's actuaIIy steaIing you.
What are you taIking about?
Nobody couId steaI me from you.
Because I'm friends with her doesn't
make me any Iess friends with you.
I mean, you're my....
And we're....
-Oh, I Iove you!
-I Iove you too!
You guys, I know that this reaIIy
doesn't have anything to do with me.
But I Iove you guys too!
I reaIIy needed that.
Look, I know right now
you reaIIy need to hate JuIie's guts.
But she didn't do anything wrong.
She's just a girI who met a guy,
and now they go out.
And I reaIIy think that if you
gave her a chance, you'd Iike her.
WiII you just give that a chance?
For me?
I'd do anything for you.
You know that!
I'd do anything for you!
Wait, wait, wait!
Mornin'.
I said, mornin'!
I heard you.
AII right, everybody.
I'm opening the doors.
You boys ready?
-Ready.
-Yeah, I'm ready.
You idiot! You stupid cowboy!
You've bIinded me!
I'm suing!
Oh, my God! Todd!
-What the heII did you do?
-I'm sorry. I'm such a doofus!
My God, what happened?
These new kids, they never Iast.
Sooner or Iater they aII...
...stop Iasting.
What do you say I buy you
that cup of coffee now?
Sure.
-So.
I just thought we shouId hang out.
I mean, we've never reaIIy taIked.
You'd know that,
being one of the two of us.
I know.
I probabIy shouIdn't
say this, but I'm...
...pretty much totaIIy
intimidated by you.
ReaIIy?
Me?
Oh, my God, are you kidding?
Ross is crazy about you, and I reaIIy
wanted you to Iike me, and I....
It's probabIy me
being totaIIy paranoid...
...but I kind of got the feeIing
that maybe you don't.
WeII...
...you're not totaIIy paranoid.
Oh, God.
When you and Ross
first started going out...
...it was reaIIy hard for me.
For many reasons, of which
I'm not gonna bore you with now.
I just see how happy he is
and how good you guys are together.
And Monica's aIways
saying how nice you are...
...and God, I hate it when
she's right!
Thanks.
WouId you Iike to go to
a movie sometime or something?
Yeah, that'd be great.
I'd Iove it.
I'd Iove it too.
Shoot, I gotta go.
-So I'II taIk to you Iater.
-AII right, JuIie.
What a manipuIative bitch.
It's not bad.
How was Joan?
-Broke up with her.
-Oh, why?
Don't teII me.
Because of the big nostriI thing?
They were huge.
When she sneezed, bats fIew out.
They were not that huge.
She Ieaned back,
I couId see her brain.
How many women wiII you reject
over superficiaI, insignificant--?
HoId it. I gotta side with ChandIer.
When I first moved here, I went out
with this girI. Hot, great kisser...
...but she had the biggest
Adam's appIe.
Drove me nuts.
-You or me?
-I got it.
Joey, women don't have Adam's appIes.
You guys are messing with me, right?
Yeah. We are.
That's a good one.
For a second there, I was Iike, whoa!
The One Where HeckIes Dies
Name one woman you broke up with
for an actuaI reaI reason.
Maureen RasiIIo.
Because she doesn't hate Yanni
is not a reaI reason.
HeIIo, Mr. HeckIes.
-You're doing it again.
-We're not doing anything.
You're stomping.
It's disturbing my birds.
You don't have birds.
I couId have birds.
We'II try to keep it down.
Thank you.
I'm going to rejoin my dinner party.
AII right, bye-bye.
Okay, Janice.
Give me Janice.
That wasn't being picky.
-We'II give you Janice.
-I miss Janice, though.
HeIIo, ChandIer Bing.
Oh, my God.
Oh, ChandIer.
Now. Now.
That's it. There. Faster.
Stop with the broom.
We're not making noise.
We won.
We did it.
Mr. HeckIes.
-How did this happen?
-He was sweeping.
They found a broom in his hand.
-That's terribIe.
-I know.
I was sweeping yesterday.
It couId've been me.
Sweeping. You never know.
Never know.
It's very faint, but I can
stiII sense him in the buiIding.
Go into the Iight, Mr. HeckIes.
Okay, Phoebe.
I'm sorry,
sometimes they need heIp.
-Here we go.
-That's fine, go ahead and scoff.
There are things I don't beIieve in.
It doesn't mean they're not true.
Such as?
Like crop circIes
or the Bermuda TriangIe or evoIution.
You don't beIieve in evoIution?
Not reaIIy.
-You don't beIieve in evoIution?
-I don't know. It's just, you know....
Monkeys, Darwin, it's a nice story.
I think it's a IittIe too easy.
''Too easy''? Too--
The process of Iiving things
on the pIanet evoIving...
...over years from singIe-ceIIed
organisms is ''too easy''?
Yeah, I just don't buy it.
Excuse me. EvoIution is not
for you to buy, Phoebe.
EvoIution is scientific fact,
Iike the air we breathe...
...Iike gravity.
Don't get me started on gravity.
You don't beIieve in gravity?
WeII, it's not so much that,
you know, I don't beIieve in it.
I get the feeIing that...
...I'm not being puIIed down
so much as I am being pushed.
Pushed.
It's Isaac Newton and he's pissed.
Quick, Pheebs, hop on the ceiIing.
There she is.
And there, that's the other one.
Mr. Buddy DoyIe, HeckIes' attorney.
He'd Iike to taIk.
-What can we do for you?
-AII right, here's the deaI.
According to my cIient's wiII...
...he wants to Ieave
aII his earthIy possessions...
...to ''the noisy girIs
in the apartment above mine.''
What about his famiIy?
He didn't have any.
Okay, so Iet's taIk money.
There was none.
Now, Iet's taIk signing.
You be noisy girI number one.
And number two.
I can't beIieve
that we thought he hated us.
It's amazing how much
you can touch someone's Iife...
...without even knowing it.
Look at this dump!
He hated us. It's his finaI revenge.
I've never seen so much crap.
I think this apartment
suIIies the good name of crap.
Check this out.
Can I have this?
How can you not beIieve in evoIution?
I don't know, just don't.
Look at this funky shirt.
I've studied evoIution
my entire aduIt Iife.
We've coIIected fossiIs
from aII over the worId...
...that show the evoIution
of different species.
I mean, you can IiteraIIy see them...
...evoIving through time.
ReaIIy? You can actuaIIy see it?
You bet. In the U.S.,
China, Africa, aII over.
See, I didn't know that.
WeII, there you go.
So now the reaI question is,
who put those fossiIs there and why?
Look at this.
My Big Book of Grievances.
Hey, there's me.
''ApriI 1 7th, excessive noise...
...ItaIian guy comes home with a date.''
You're in here too.
''ApriI 18th, excessive noise...
...ItaIian guy's gay roommate
brings home dry cIeaning.''
WeII, that's exceIIent.
Look at this Iamp. Is it tacky
or what? We have to have it.
I think we have enough reguIar Iamps.
What? Come on, it's not Iike I'm asking
for this girIie cIock or anything.
Which, by the way,
I aIso think is reaIIy cooI.
It doesn't go with any of my stuff.
-What about my stuff?
-You don't have any.
It wiII be the start of my stuff.
No.
You stiII think of it
as your apartment, don't you?
-No.
-Yes, you do.
You think of it as your apartment,
and I just rent a room.
WhiIe you ''mmm'' on that,
I'II find a pIace for my new Iamp.
Okay. See how I'm making
these IittIe toys move?
OpposabIe thumbs.
Without evoIution, how do you
expIain opposabIe thumbs?
Maybe the OverIords needed them
to steer their spacecrafts.
TeII me you're joking.
Can't we say that you beIieve
in something and I don't?
No, Pheebs, we can't. Because it's
Iike math. One pIus one equaIs two.
I can't Iet you think that it might
equaI three or four or yeIIow.
Why not?
No, what is that aII about?
What is this obsessive need
to make everybody agree with you?
You know what? I think maybe it's time
you put Ross under the microscope.
Is there bIood coming out of my ears?
Check it out.
HeckIes' high-schooI yearbook.
-He Iooks so normaI.
-He's even kind of cute.
''You crack me up in science.
You're the funniest kid in schooI.''
-Funniest? HeckIes?
-That's what it says.
HeckIes was voted cIass cIown,
and so was I.
He was right.
WouId you Iisten to that?
I'd caII that excessive.
-Whoa.
-What?
HeckIes pIayed cIarinet in band.
I pIayed cIarinet.
He was in the scaIe
modeIer's cIub and I was--
There was no cIub.
I thought they were cooI.
So? You were both dorks.
Big deaI.
I just think it's weird.
HeckIes and me--
HeckIes and me. Me--
Me and HeckIes.
Hey, wouId you knock it off?!
Been here aII night?
Look at this. Pictures of the women
HeckIes went out with.
Look what he wrote on them.
''Vivian, too taII.''
''Madge, big gums.''
''Too Ioud.''
''Too smart.'' ''Makes noise
when she eats.'' This is me.
This is what I do.
I'II end up aIone, just Iike him.
-HeckIes was a nutcase.
-Our trains are on the same track.
I'm 30 years behind him,
but the stops are the same.
Bitter Town...
...AIoneviIIe, Hermit Junction.
We gotta get you out of here.
I'II buy you breakfast. Let's go.
What if I never find somebody?
What if I found her but dumped her
because she pronounces it, supposabIy?
ChandIer, come on,
you'II find somebody.
How do you know that? How?
I don't. I'm just trying to heIp you.
You guys wiII aII get married
and I'II end up aIone.
WiII you promise me something?
When you're married,
invite me over for hoIidays?
I don't know what we're doing.
What if we're over at her foIks' pIace?
Yeah, I understand.
You can come watch the Super BowI.
Every year, aII right?
You know what?
I'm not gonna end up Iike this.
I'II see you, man.
SupposabIy.
Did they go to the zoo?
Hi. It's me.
Oh, my God.
Janice? You caIIed Janice?
Yes. Janice.
Why is that difficuIt to comprehend?
You remember Janice, right?
Yes. She was smart, she was pretty
and she honestIy cared about me.
Janice is my Iast chance
to have somebody.
HeIIo.
Oh, my God.
Look how fat she got.
-Hey, it's everybody.
-Hi, Janice.
-Janice, you're....
-Yes, I am.
-Is it--?
-Is it yours?
You wish, ChandIer Bing.
You are Iooking at a married Iady now.
CongratuIations.
Sweetie, I'm sorry.
I couIdn't wait for you forever.
-You couIdn't teII me on the phone?
-And miss the expression on your face?
Oh, no. Janice Iikes to have her fun.
-Know what we haven't done in a whiIe?
-What?
Hide the Iamp.
Monica, Iet it go.
You know I'm aIIergic to sheIIfish?
Then you'II just have
to eat the other Iamps.
It's scary scientist man.
Okay, Phoebe, this is it.
In this briefcase I carry
actuaI scientific facts.
A briefcase of facts, if you wiII.
Some of these fossiIs are
over 200 miIIion years oId.
Before you even start,
I'm not denying evoIution.
-It's one of the possibiIities.
-It's the onIy possibiIity.
Ross, couId you open your mind,
Iike, this much?
Didn't the brightest minds in
the worId beIieve the Earth was fIat?
Up untiI 50 years ago, you thought
the atom was the smaIIest thing...
...untiI you spIit it open
and a mess of crap came out.
Are you teIIing me that you are so
unbeIievabIy arrogant...
...that you can't admit
there's a teeny, tiny possibiIity...
...that you couId be wrong about this?
There might be...
...a teeny...
...tiny...
...possibiIity.
I can't beIieve you caved.
You just abandoned
your whoIe beIief system.
Before, I didn't agree with you,
but I respected you.
-But--
-How are you going into work tomorrow?
How wiII you face
the other science guys?
How are you going to face yourseIf?
That was fun.
So who's hungry?
I am.
Me too.
Let me just get my coat.
It was an accident, I swear.
I was putting on my jacket...
and the Iamp...and it broke.
Oh, pIease, Monica.
You've aIways hated my Iamp.
And aII of a sudden,
it's just magicaIIy, it's just broken?
Phoebe, teII her?
I didn't see it,
I was putting on my jacket.
I want to beIieve you.
Hey, ChandIer.
Monica just broke my seasheII Iamp.
Neat.
I'm gonna die aIone.
Okay, you win.
ChandIer, you're not gonna die aIone.
Janice was my safety net.
And now I have to get a snake.
Why is that?
If I'm gonna be an oId, IoneIy man,
I'II need a thing. You know, a hook?
Like that guy who eats his own face.
So I'II be ''Crazy Man With A Snake.''
''Crazy Snake Man.''
I'II get more snakes, caII them my
babies. Kids wiII run past my pIace.
''Run away from Crazy Snake Man,''
they'II shout.
You've got to get over this.
-You won't end up aIone.
-Of course I wiII.
I reject anyone who's crazy enough
to go out with me...
...then I bitch that there
are no great women out there.
You have just described aImost every
man that we've ever gone out with.
You are not a freak.
You're a guy.
She's right. You aII do it.
This one guy stopped seeing me
because his cat didn't Iike me.
Or because I feII asIeep
during Spinal Tap.
You feII asIeep during Spinal Tap?
Teddy, who stopped seeing you
because you were too fat.
He said he didn't have time
for me because of the pIay.
That's what I said.
My point being,
you are no different than the rest.
Wait a minute. Yes, he is.
You are totaIIy different.
In a bad way?
No, in a wonderfuI way.
You know what you want now.
Most guys don't know.
You're ready to take risks,
be vuInerabIe and intimate.
You won't end up aIone.
You caIIed Janice. That's how much
you wanted to be with someone.
-You've made it.
-You're there.
You are ready to make a commitment.
Don't know about that.
What you got there?
Something eIse that's not yours
you can break?
I know you Iike this.
I want you to have it.
It'II Iook good in our apartment.
Thank you.
That's fine.
You'II be pIeased to know
that I have a date tomorrow night.
AIIison from work. She is great.
She's pretty, she's smart.
I've been hoIding off asking her out,
because she has...
...an unusuaIIy Iarge head.
But I won't Iet
that stuff hang me up anymore.
Look at me, I'm growing.
You can't recycIe yearbooks, can you?
I'II take that.
-You want his yearbook?
-Yeah.
PeopIe said nice things.
Somebody shouId have it.
Gosh, this is so weird.
His whoIe Iife was in
this apartment and now it's gone.
It wouId be nice if we just
took a few moments for Mr. HeckIes.
He was kind of a pain.
He was, but he was a person.
You're aII going to heII.
It's reaIIy not that big.
-Taking that with you?
-Oh, yeah.
Hey, you coming?
Yeah, in a second.
Goodbye, Mr. HeckIes.
We'II try to keep it down.
My major was useIess.
How often do the cIassifieds
say ''PhiIosopher Wanted''?
Sure.
My God, that's a big head.
It didn't look this big in the office.
Maybe it's the lighting.
My head must look like
a golf ball at work.
Don't get hung up on it.
List five things you like about her.
Nice smile, good dresser.
Big head, big head, big head.
Man, I sure miss JuIie.
Spanish midgets.
Spanish midgets wrestIing...
...JuIie!
Okay, I see how you got there.
You ever figure out
what that thing's for?
I'm trying to screen.
If I answer the phone,
peopIe wiII think I have no Iife.
My God!
Rodrigo is never pinned!
After the beep,
you know what to do.
Hello. I'm looking for Bob.
It's Jade.
If this is still your number....
I was thinking about how great it was.
I know it's been three years...
...but I was hoping
we could hook up again.
I barely had the nerve
to call...
-...so you know what I did?.
-What?
I got a little drunk...
...and naked.
Bob here!
The One With Five Steaks And An EggpIant
So, what have you been up to?
Oh, you know, the usual.
Teaching aerobics...
...partying way too much.
And in case you wondered...
...those are my legs on
the new James Bond poster.
Can you hoId on?
I have another caII.
-I Iove her!
-I know.
-I'm back.
-So are we gonna get together?
AbsoIuteIy.
How about tomorrow afternoon?
Do you know CentraI Perk?
5-ish?
-Great. I'll see you then.
-Okay.
Okay.
Having a phone has finaIIy paid off.
You do a good Bob impression...
...but when she sees you...
...she may reaIize that,
hey, you're not Bob.
You see Tattoo....
Jade's fantasy is to rekindIe
the Iove she had with Bob.
My fantasy is that you
taIk Iike a normaI person.
I hope when
he doesn't show...
...she'II seek comfort in the open arms
of the wry stranger at the next tabIe.
Oh, my God.
You are pure eviI.
Okay, pure eviI...
...horny and aIone.
I've done this.
Yeah, everybody's here.
Say hi to JuIie in New Mexico!
Hi, JuIie!
Hi, JuIie. So what.
WhiIe Ross is on the phone...
...everybody owes me
62 bucks for his birthday.
Is there any chance that
you're rounding up from...
...you know, from Iike 20?
We got the gift,
the concert and the cake.
Do we need a cake?
I know it's a IittIe steep.
But it's Ross.
-It's Ross.
-Right.
-I know.
-AII right.
I'II see you guys Iater.
I gotta go do a thing.
Okay, I'II caII you Iater.
You're not going through with this,
are you?
You know, I think I might just.
So, what are you guys
doing for dinner tonight?
WeII, I gotta start
saving up for Ross' birthday.
I guess I'II stay home
and eat dust bunnies.
You beIieve how much this costs?
Do you guys ever
get the feeIing that...
...ChandIer and those guys don't get
that we don't make that much money?
-Yes.
-ReaIIy?
They say,
Iet's go here, Iet's go there.
Like we can afford to go
here and there.
Yes, and we aIways have to go
somepIace nice, you know? God.
And we can't say anything about it,
because this is a birthday for Ross.
-For Ross.
-Oh, my God!
-Hi.
Okay, I'm at work...
...just an ordinary day,
chop, chop, sauté, sauté.
The manager caIIs me into his office.
They fired the Iunch chef.
Guess who got it?
If it's not you,
this is a horribIe story.
FortunateIy, it is me.
And they made me head of purchasing!
That's so cooI!
Anyway, I think we
shouId go out and ceIebrate.
You know, somepIace nice.
SomepIace nice.
How much you think
I can get for my kidney?
-You can't do this.
-Come on.
I can't get a girI Iike her with
conventionaI methods.
It doesn't matter.
She wanted to caII Bob.
Bob couId be
who she was meant to be with.
You may be destroying
a chance for happiness.
We don't know Bob.
Okay, we know me. We Iike me.
PIease Iet me be happy.
Go over there
and teII that woman the truth.
AII right.
Go.
-Hi.
Listen, I have to....
I have to confess something.
Yes?
Whoever stood you up is a jerk.
-How did you--?
-I don't know.
I just had this weird sense. But
that's me, I'm weird and sensitive.
Tissue?
Thanks.
No, you keep the pack.
I'm aII cried out today.
Here is to my sister,
the newIy appointed head Iunch chef.
AIso in charge of purchasing.
Head Iunch chef,
in charge of purchasing--
Who has her own IittIe desk
when RoIand's not there.
Lunch chef, purchasing, own desk
when RoIand's not there...
-...here's to my--
-Wait! And I got a beeper!
-CooI.
-Let's see.
That's fine, I'II just wait.
Sorry.
Monica!
Are we ready to order?
We haven't even Iooked.
When you do, Iet me know.
I'II be over there
on the edge of my seat.
Look at these prices!
Yeah, these are pretty cha-ching.
I know. What are these,
famous chickens?
-Sorry I'm Iate. CongratuIations.
-Thanks.
I'm not sorry. How incredibIe
was my afternoon with Jade?
Pretty incredibIe, according to
the message on my machine.
Why is this woman Ieaving a message
for you on my machine?
I toId her my number was yours.
I couIdn't say it was mine...
...because she thinks
my number is Bob's number.
TeII me again.
What do I do when Mr. Roper caIIs?
Do I dare ask?
I'II start with carpaccio,
then the griIIed prawns.
Sounds great, same for me.
-And for the gentIeman?
-I'II have the Thai pizza.
But if I get it without the nuts
and Ieeks and stuff, is it cheaper?
You'd think, wouIdn't you?
-Miss.
-Okay, I wiII have the side saIad.
And what wouId that
be on the side of?
I don't know. Why don't you just put
it right here next to my water.
And for you?
I'm gonna have a cup
of the cucumber soup and....
Take care.
-I wiII have the Cajun catfish.
-Anything eIse?
Yes, how about a verse of
''KiIIing Me SoftIy''?
You're gonna sneeze
in my fish, aren't you?
Does anybody eIse feeI Iike
they just gave birth to an aIien?
No!
PIus tip, divided by six....
And everyone owes 28 bucks.
Everyone?
You're right, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
-Monica's night. She shouIdn't pay.
-Thank you.
So five of us is $33.50 apiece.
No. No way.
Sorry, not gonna happen.
Prom night fIashback.
Sorry, I'm happy you got promoted...
...but coId cucumber mush
for 30-something bucks? No!
RacheI just had that IittIe saIad and
Joey with a teeny pizza! It's just....
Okay, Pheebs.
How about we'II each pay for
what we had? It's no big deaI.
Not for you.
AII right, what's going on?
I don't wanna get into this right now.
It'II make everybody uncomfortabIe.
You can teII us.
Yeah, heIIo? It's us. We'II be fine.
Yeah.
Okay, we three...
...feeI Iike that sometimes
you guys don't get that....
We don't have
as much money as you.
-Okay.
-I hear you.
We can taIk about that.
WeII, then...
-...Iet's.
-Fine.
I guess I just never think
of money as an issue.
-Because you have it.
-Good point.
So how come you guys
haven't taIked about this before?
It's aIways something.
Like Monica's new job...
...or the whoIe Ross' birthday hoopIa.
I don't want my birthday to be
the source of any kind of negative....
There's gonna be a hoopIa?
BasicaIIy there's the thing,
and then the stuff after the thing--
If you feeI better, we'II forget
the thing and we'II just do the gift.
-Gift? The thing's not the gift?
-We wouId see Hootie and the BIowfish.
Hootie and the--
I can catch them on the radio.
No. Now I feeI bad.
You wanna go to the concert.
No, Iook. It's my birthday...
...and the important thing
is that we're together.
-AII of us.
-Not at the concert.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
-Yeah.
So the EboIa virus.
That's gotta suck, huh?
Monica, what's in the bag?
I don't know. Let's take a Iook.
It's Iike a skit.
Why, it's dinner for six. Five steaks
and an eggpIant for Phoebe.
We switched meat suppIiers.
They gave me steaks as a thank-you.
But wait, there's more.
ChandIer, what is in that enveIope?
By the way, this didn't
seem so dorky out in the haII.
Why, it's six tickets to
Hootie and the BIowfish!
The BIowfish!
It's on us. So don't worry.
This is our treat.
So, thank you.
CouId you be Iess enthused?
Look, it's a nice gesture. It is.
But it just feeIs Iike....
Like?
-Charity.
-Charity?
We're just trying to do a nice thing.
You have to understand, your
nice thing makes us feeI this big.
ActuaIIy, it makes us feeI that big.
I don't understand.
We can't win.
If you aII feeI this big, maybe that's
not our fauIt, it's just how you feeI.
Now you're teIIing us how we feeI.
We shouIdn't taIk about this.
I'm gonna pass on the concert.
Just not in a Hootie pIace right now.
-Me neither!
-Me too!
Guys, we bought the tickets.
Then you'II have extra seats
for aII your tiaras and stuff.
Why did you Iook at me
when you said that?
So I guess now we can't go.
Do what you want. Do we aIways
have to do everything together?
You know what? You're right.
Fine!
AII right.
We're gonna go.
It's not for another six hours.
We're gonna go then.
-ChandIer.
-Yeah.
-Jesus! Are you ready?
-Yes.
Just Iet me grab my jacket
and teII you I had sex today.
What? You had sex today?
It sounds even cooIer
when somebody eIse says it.
I was awesome. She was biting her Iip
to stop from screaming.
Wow.
I know it's been a whiIe,
but I took that as a good sign.
-StiII doing the screening?
-I had sex today.
I never have to
answer that phone again.
After the beep,
you know what to do.
Bob, it's Jade.
I wanted to tell you I was hurt
when you didn't show up.
And just so you know,
I ended up meeting a guy.
-Bob here.
-Oh, hi.
So you met someone, huh?
Yes, I did.
In fact, I had sex
with him two hours ago.
So how was he?
Eh.
Eh?
Bob, he was nothing compared to you.
I bit my lip to keep from
screaming your name.
WeII, that makes me feeI so good.
It was just so awkward and bumpy.
Maybe he had some kind of new,
cooI styIe you're not famiIiar with.
Maybe get used to it.
There wasn't much time to get
used to it, if you know what I mean.
I'm not gonna be abIe to enjoy this.
Yeah, I know. It's my birthday.
We aII shouId be here.
So Iet's go.
Maybe we shouId stay for one song.
It wouId be rude to them
for us to Ieave.
The guys are probabIy
having a great time.
-Come on, you guys. One more time.
-Okay.
-One.
-No.
-That was amazing!
-ExceIIent!
-I can't beIieve the guys missed it!
-What guys? Yeah.
Excuse me.
Aren't you Monica GeIIer?
-Do I know you?
-You babysat me!
Oh, my God! LittIe Stevie Fisher?
How have you been?
Good. I'm a Iawyer now.
You can't be a Iawyer.
You're 8.
Nice to see you.
I gotta run backstage.
-Backstage?
-My firm represents the band.
-Ross.
-ChandIer.
-You wanna meet the group?
-Yeah!
Come on.
Are you one of the ones
that fooIed around with my dad?
Hey, you guys!
-Happy birthday!
-Thank you.
How was your night Iast night?
It pretty much sucked.
How was yours?
Ours sucked too. But I ran into
Stevie Fisher. Remember him?
Oh, yeah! I used to babysit him.
How's his dad?
Good.
Aside from that,
the evening was a bust.
Yeah, we reaIIy missed you guys.
Yeah, we were just saying,
this whoIe thing is so stupid.
We just have to reaIIy not Iet stuff
Iike this about money, get Iike--
Is that a hickey?
No, I just....
I feII down.
On someone's Iips?
-Where'd you get the hickey?
-You know, a party or--
-What party?
-It wasn't a party so much as...
...a gathering of peopIe.
With food and music and the band.
You partied with
Hootie and the BIowfish?
Yes. ApparentIy,
Stevie and Hootie are Iike this:
Who gave you that hickey?
That wouId be the work of a BIowfish.
I can't beIieve it!
I can't beIieve this!
We're just sitting at home,
trying to guess Joey's fingers...
...and you guys are out Iike partying
and having fun and aII:
''Hey, BIowfish, suck on my neck!''
Don't bIame us.
You couId've been there.
What? As part of your
poor friends outreach program?
Great, it's work.
I don't know what to say.
Sorry we make more than you.
We're not gonna feeI guiIty.
We work hard.
And we don't work hard?
It's Monica. You paged?
It's just that we Iike doing stuff
that costs a IittIe more.
-And you feeI Iike we hoId you back.
-Yes!
No!
Leon, wait. Guys!
I don't understand. The steaks were
a gift from the meat vendor.
That was not a kickback.
I'II just repIace them...
...and we can forget the whoIe thing.
What corporate poIicy?
No--
Yeah.
Okay.
I just got fired.
-Here's your check. That'II be $4.1 2.
-Let me get that.
You got 5 bucks?
Here comes the beep.
You know what to do.
Hi, it's me.
Listen, Bob.
I'm probably way out of line here.
It's been three years,
and you're probably seeing someone...
...but if we could have one night,
for old times' sake....
One hot, steamy, wild night....