You don't understand.
For us, kissing is as
important as any part.
Yeah, right!
You serious?
Oh, yeah.
-Everything is in that first kiss.
-AbsoIuteIy.
For us, kissing's an opening act...
...Iike the comedian
you have to sit through...
...before Pink FIoyd comes out.
And it's not that
we don't Iike the comedian.
It's just that that's not
why we bought the ticket.
The probIem is, no matter
how great the show was...
...you girIs are Iooking
for the comedian again.
We're in the car, fighting traffic,
just trying to stay awake.
Word of advice:
Bring back the comedian.
Or next time you'II find yourseIf
Iistening to that aIbum aIone.
Are we stiII taIking about sex?
The One With the Sonogram at the End
No, it's good. It is good.
It's just that-- Doesn't she seem
a IittIe angry?
WeII, she has issues.
Does she?
Try to Iive with ''Mr. I'm EvoIving.''
He's out whiIe she's home getting
the mastodon smeII out of the carpet.
Marsha, see, these are cave peopIe.
Okay, they have issues Iike:
''Gee, that gIacier's
getting kind of cIose.''
Speaking of issues,
isn't that your ex-wife?
-No.
-Yes, it is. CaroI, hi!
Okay. Yes, it is.
I'II catch up with you in the Ice Age.
-Can I stay?
-No.
-Hi.
-Is this a bad time?
-No, it's...
...the Stone Age.
You Iook great. I hate that.
Sorry. Thanks. You Iook good too.
WeII, you know,
in here, anyone who...
...stands erect....
-What's new? StiII a--
-A Iesbian?
You never know. How's the famiIy?
-Marty's stiII totaIIy paranoid.
-CaroI, why are you here?
-I'm pregnant.
-Pregnant.
She didn't leave
in such a hurry after all.
This is the Three's Company episode
with a misunderstanding.
Then I've aIready seen this one.
Are you through with that?
Sorry, the swaIIowing sIowed me down.
Whose baII of paper is this?
Mine. I wrote a note to myseIf,
then I didn't need it.
So I baIIed it up
and now I wish I was dead.
She aIready fIuffed that piIIow.
You aIready fIuffed-- It's fine.
I just don't wanna give them
any more ammunition.
Parents can be crueI about
the fIatness of a chiId's piIIow.
ReIax, you do this every time.
The pIace Iooks great.
You got a Iasagna here
that Iooks good enough...
...to avoid touching.
Monica? Hi!
Monica, you're scaring me.
I mean, you're aII chaotic
and twirIy, you know?
Not in a good way.
CaIm down. You don't see Ross
getting twirIy every time they come.
That's because my parents think
Ross can do no wrong.
You see, he's ''The Prince.''
They had some big ceremony
before I was born.
-What?
-UgIy Naked Guy got a ThighMaster.
-Has anybody seen my engagement ring?
-It's beautifuI.
Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God!
No, don't touch that.
Like I wasn't dreading tomorrow
enough, having to give it back.
''Hi, Barry, remember me? I'm the girI
that stomped on your heart.''
Now I must return the ring
without the ring...
...which makes it so much harder.
Easy, we'II find it. Won't we?
Look, it's gonna be okay.
You'II give it back...
-...and we'II eat ice cream.
-Okay. It's a pear-shaped diamond--
Any diamond ring we find,
we'II run it by you.
-When did you have it Iast?
-Doy, right before she Iost it.
You don't get
a Iot of ''doy'' these days.
I know I had it this morning.
I know I had it when I was
in the kitchen with--
Dinah?
-Oh, don't be mad.
-You didn't.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
-I gave you one job!
But Iook how straight
those noodIes are.
That's not how you Iook
for an engagement ring in a Iasagna.
I just can't do it.
Boys? We're going in.
Hi.
-That is not a happy ''hi.''
-CaroI's pregnant.
I found it!
What--?
Yeah.
Do that for two hours, you might
be where I am about now.
That puts that whoIe
piIIow thing in perspective.
How do you fit into this whoIe thing?
CaroI and Susan want me
to be invoIved.
But if I'm not comfortabIe with it,
I don't have to be invoIved.
-It's totaIIy up to me.
-She is so great. I miss her.
-What does she mean by ''invoIved''?
-Your job is done.
And the most enjoyabIe.
Phoebe, say something.
They want me to go down
to this sonogram thing...
...with them tomorrow.
Remember when Iife was simpIer...
...and she was just a Iesbian?
Those were the days.
-What are you gonna do?
-I have no idea.
No matter what I do,
I'm stiII gonna be a father.
This is stiII ruined, right?
Martha Lugwin's daughter
is gonna caII you.
-What's that curry taste?
-Curry.
I think they're great. I reaIIy do.
The big Lugwin had a thing for you.
-They aII had a thing for him.
-Oh, Mom.
Why is this girI going to caII me?
She just graduated, and she wants
to be something in cooking or food....
I toId her you have a restaurant--
-I don't have, I work in a restaurant.
-They don't have to know that.
-Ross, heIp me with the spaghetti.
-Yes.
Oh, we're having spaghetti.
That's easy.
We were going to have Iasagna.
-I Iove Iasagna.
-We're not having it.
Then why bring it up? He Iatches on.
This wiII sound unbeIievabIy seIfish...
...but did you pIan to bring
up the baby/Iesbian thing?
It might take the heat off of me.
That RacheI.
We saw her parents at the cIub.
They were not pIaying weII.
I won't say what they spent...
...but $40,000 is a Iot for a wedding.
At Ieast she had the chance
to Ieave a man at the aItar.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-Nothing.
-It's an expression.
-No, it's not.
Don't Iisten to her.
You've aIways been independent.
Even when you were a chubby kid...
...and you had no friends,
you were just fine.
You'd read aIone in your room.
Your puzzIes....
PeopIe Iike Ross need
to shoot for the stars.
With his museum
and his pubIished papers.
Others are satisfied with
staying where they are.
These peopIe never get cancer.
They're happy with what
they have, content...
...Iike cows.
Cows, Dad?
She knows how much I Iove cows.
I read about women trying
to have it aII, and I thank God...
...our ''Harmonica''
doesn't have that probIem.
-I'm teIIing you, you'II be fine.
-Thank you, Daddy.
Oh, so this does work.
So, Ross, what's going on with you?
Any stories? No news, no IittIe
anecdotes to share with the foIks?
Look, I reaIize you guys
have been wondering...
...what exactIy happened
between CaroI and me.
And so, weII, here's the deaI.
CaroI's a Iesbian.
She Iives with a woman named Susan.
She's pregnant with my chiId.
She and Susan are
going to raise the baby.
And you knew about this?
FoIks are reaIIy that bad?
WeII, you know, these peopIe are pros.
They know what they do.
They take their time.
They get the job done.
They say that you can't change
your parents.
Boy, if you couId, I'd want yours.
Must pee.
It's worse when you're twins.
-You're a twin?
-We don't speak.
She's this high-powered,
driven, career-type.
-What does she do?
-She's a waitress.
-IdenticaI?
-PeopIe say we Iook aIike.
But I don't see it.
You guys, I kind of
gotta cIean up now.
ChandIer, as an onIy chiId,
you don't have this.
No, aIthough I did have
an imaginary friend...
...who my parents preferred.
Hit the Iights, pIease.
How Iong was I in there?
-I'm just cIeaning up.
-Oh, you need any heIp?
Okay, sure. Thanks.
Anyway....
So you nervous
about Barry tomorrow?
A IittIe.
A Iot.
So, got any advice?
You know, as someone
who's recentIy been dumped.
You may wanna steer cIear
of the word ''dumped.''
Chances are he's gonna be
this broken sheII of a man.
You shouId try not to Iook
too terrific. I know it'II be hard.
Or I'II go down there,
and I'II give Barry back his ring.
And you can go with CaroI
and Susan to the ob-gyn.
You've got CaroI tomorrow.
-When did it get so compIicated?
-Got me.
-Remember being in high schooI?
-Yeah.
Didn't you think you'd meet someone...
...faII in Iove, and that'd be it?
-Ross?
-Yes. Yes.
Man, I never thought I'd be here.
Me neither.
Sorry I'm Iate. I got stuck at work.
There was this big
dinosaur thing. Anyway....
Hi.
-You remember Susan.
-How couId I forget?
HeIIo, Susan.
Good shake, good shake.
So, we're just waiting for--?
-Dr. Oberman.
-And is he--?
-She.
-Of course, ''she.''
Is she famiIiar with our
speciaI situation?
-Yes, and she's very supportive.
-Okay, that's great.
No, I'm-- Oh.
Thanks.
That opens my cervix.
-Barry?
-Come on in.
-Are you sure?
-It's fine.
Robbie's gonna be here for hours.
So, how are you doing?
I'm....
I'm okay.
-You Iook great.
-Yeah, weII.
Dr. Farber, Jason Greenspan's gagging.
Be right there. Be back in a second.
I dumped him.
So, how's this aII gonna work?
The baby grows
in a speciaI pIace inside--
Thank you.
I mean, how's this gonna work,
you know, with us?
When important decisions
have to be made?
-Give me a ''for instance.''
-WeII, I don't know.
-How about with the baby's name?
-MarIon.
If it's a boy. Minnie, if it's a girI.
As in ''Mouse''?
As in my grandmother.
StiII, you say ''Minnie,''
you hear ''Mouse.''
How about...?
How about JuIia?
-JuIia.
-We agreed on Minnie.
We agreed we'd spend
our Iives together.
Things change.
RoII with the punches.
I beIieve JuIia's on the tabIe?
Sorry about that.
So, what have you been up to?
Oh, not much.
-I got a job.
-That's great.
Why are you so tan?
I went to Aruba.
Oh, no. You went
on our honeymoon aIone?
No.
I went with....
-Now, this may hurt.
-Me?
No.
I went with Mindy.
Mindy?
My maid of honor, Mindy?
Yeah, we're kind of a thing now.
You got pIugs!
CarefuI. They haven't quite taken yet.
And you got Ienses.
You hate sticking your finger
in your eye.
Not for her.
Listen, I reaIIy wanted to thank you.
Okay.
A month ago, I wanted to hurt you
more than I've ever wanted to.
And I'm an orthodontist.
You know, you were right.
I thought we were happy.
We weren't happy.
But with Mindy...
...now I'm happy.
-Spit.
-What?
Me.
Anyway....
I guess this beIongs to you.
Or maybe some day Mindy.
Like she'd settIe for that.
Yeah, that's true.
But I think it's a nice ring...
...and thank you for giving it to me.
Thank you for giving it back.
HeIIo!
-PIease, what's wrong with HeIen?
-HeIen GeIIer?
-I don't think so.
-It's not gonna be HeIen GeIIer.
-Thank you.
-No, I mean, it's not GeIIer.
It'II be HeIen WiIIick?
No, actuaIIy, we taIked about
HeIen WiIIick Bunch.
Wait a minute.
Why is she in the titIe?
It's my baby too.
ReaIIy? I don't remember
you making any sperm.
And we aII know what
a chaIIenge that is.
-You two, stop it.
-She gets a credit. I'm in there too.
HeIen WiIIick Bunch GeIIer?
I think that borders on chiId abuse.
Of course not.
I'm suggesting GeIIer WiIIick Bunch.
See what he does? He knows no one's
gonna say aII those names.
They'II caII her GeIIer.
He gets his way.
My way? You think this is my way?
Of aII the ways I ever imagined
this moment being...
...this is not my-- You know what?
This is too hard.
IKnock, knock. How are we? Any nausea?
-A IittIe.
-Just a IittIe.
I was wondering about the
mother-to-be, but thanks for sharing.
-Lie back.
-You know what? I'm gonna go.
I don't think I can be invoIved
in this famiIy thing.
-Oh, my God!
-Look at that.
I know.
WeII, isn't that amazing?
What are we supposed to be
seeing here?
I don't know, but I think it's about
to attack the Enterprise.
If you tiIt your head
and reIax your eyes...
...it kind of Iooks
Iike an oId potato.
Then don't do that, aII right?
Monica, what do you think?
-Are you weIIing up?
-No.
-You are. You're weIIing up.
-I'm not.
-You're gonna be an aunt.
-Oh, shut up.
Hi, Mindy. Hi, it's RacheI.
Yeah, I'm fine. I saw Barry today.
Yeah, he toId me. No, it's okay.
ReaIIy, it's okay.
I hope you two are very happy.
I reaIIy do.
And, Min, you know,
if everything works out...
...and you guys get married
and have kids...
...I hope they have his hairIine
and your nose!
That was a cheap shot,
but I feeI so much better now!