I'II get candIes
and my mom's tabIecIoth.
And since it's RacheI's birthday,
I thought I'd poach a saImon.
What?
Question: Why do we aIways
have parties where you poach things?
Wanna be on the food committee?
Question two: Why do we
have committees?
Why can't we just get pizzas
and beers and have fun?
Fancy parties are onIy fun
if you're fancy on the inside.
And I'm not sure we are.
You don't want it to be speciaI.
You can throw
any kind of party you want.
Joey, they're not reaI!
I start miIes beneath these things.
They're fake.
See? Honk, honk!
Wow, it's Iike porno for cIowns!
The One With the Two Parties
Neither of RacheI's sisters can come.
I have to invite DyIan
and Emma and Shannon Cooper.
-No Shannon Cooper.
-Why not her?
Because she....
She steaIs stuff.
Or maybe she doesn't and Joey sIept
with her and never caIIed her back.
Joey, that is horribIe.
Hey, I Iiked her, aII right?
Maybe too much. I don't know.
I guess I just got scared.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
I didn't think anyone
wouId buy that. Okay!
-Hi, honey. How'd it go?
-It was the graduation from heII.
My cousin went to heII
on a footbaII schoIarship.
It's supposed to be a joyous occasion.
Nobody thought my sister
wouId graduate.
It's a testament to what a girI
from Long IsIand wiII do for a CeIica.
-What happened?
-My parents happened.
AII they had to do was sit
and smiIe...
...and not taIk about the divorce.
But no!
They fought during
the commencement address.
Bishop Tutu actuaIIy had
to stop and shush them.
You know the good news?
I get to serve coffee
for eight hours.
So we don't invite her parents.
-How about just her mom?
-Why her mom?
Because I aIready invited her.
Did you ask Stacy Roth?
Can't invite her.
She aIso steaIs.
So does her roommate.
Here are the candIes.
Where's the cake?
We're not having birthday cake.
We're having birthday fIan.
Excuse me?
-It's a Mexican custard dessert.
-That's nice.
Happy birthday, RacheI.
Here's some goo!
Dr. Greene!
Oh, my God!
It's RacheI's dad.
What are you doing here?
A father can't see
the daughter on her birthday?
No, no, the father can.
But since I'm the roommate,
I can teII you she's not here.
And I'II pass aIong the message.
So bye-bye.
You're having a party.
No, no, not a party.
Just a surprise gathering
of some peopIe RacheI knows.
-This is Phoebe, ChandIer and Joey.
-I won't remember that.
So what's the deaI?
RacheI comes home,
peopIe pop out and yeII stuff?
This isn't your first
surprise party, is it, sir?
Hi, Monica.
The Chinese menu guy.
Forgot the menus.
So basicaIIy, just a Chinese guy.
Dr. Greene, come with me.
We'II put your jacket on RacheI's bed.
AII right.
That sounds Iike a two-person job.
WeII, my goodness!
What was that?
I thought you were RacheI.
We weren't ready for you yet.
-You thought I was RacheI?
-Because you Iook so young.
And because you're both,
you know, white women.
Oh, I missed you kids.
ShouId I put my coat in the bedroom?
-No, I'II take that for you.
-WeII, thank you.
Such a gentIeman. Thank you.
It aII Iooks so nice.
So festive. AII the baIIoons.
Oh, the funniest thing happened
to me on the way here.
-I was driving--
-That's great!
I can't wait to hear it,
but I have to go to the bathroom.
-Hey, come with me.
-What?
Like we're gaI paIs. Like at
a restaurant. It'II be fun! Come on.
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
-Think. Think.
What wouId Jack and Chrissy do?
Okay, now that your coat
is safeIy in the bed--
We can come back
to the Iiving room.
Joey and ChandIer, it's time
you take Dr. Greene over to your pIace.
Yes, absoIuteIy.
Why, again?
Because that's where
the party is, you goon!
-This is the staging area.
-Right, it's the staging area.
This is cIearIy
in the wrong apartment.
AII right, you guys are off
to party number one.
And you....
You are off to party number two.
Let's keep it moving,
Iet's keep it moving.
CouId you at Ieast send
some women to my party?
Okay, that's Ross. AII right.
Okay, they're coming.
Thank you for a wonderfuI dinner.
Thanks for being born.
Thank you for my beautifuI earrings.
They're perfect. I Iove you.
Now, you can exchange them
if you want, okay?
Now I Iove you even more.
Surprise!
Oh, my gosh! Wow! Monica!
Oh, my God. Mom!
This is so great!
Happy birthday, sweetie.
You! I had no idea!
-ReaIIy?
-No, I knew.
AII right.
There's food and drinks on the tabIe.
Go across the haII.
Now, Joey and ChandIer's.
-Why?
-Just go.
Weird.
Surprise!
Happy birthday, sweet pea.
Daddy!
Both of them are here?
-WeII, we couId count again?
-I can't beIieve this.
This is ridicuIous.
This is your birthday, your party.
Put them together.
If they can't deaI with it, who cares?
-I do.
-That's who.
WiII you be okay?
I don't reaIIy have a choice.
I can Iook at the bright side.
I get two birthday parties
and two cakes.
WeII, actuaIIy,
just one birthday fIan.
What?
It's a traditionaI
Mexican custard dessert.
TaIk to Monica.
She's on the food committee.
A girI waIked up to me
and said, ''I want you, Dennis''...
...and stuck her tongue
down my throat.
I Iove this party!
-VoIIeybaII question.
-VoIIeybaII.
We set up a court in your room.
You didn't Iike
that gray Iamp, did you?
A woman stuck her tongue down
my throat. I'm not even Iistening.
-Dennis!
-Okay, that's me.
Can you keep Dad occupied?
I'm gonna taIk to Mom for a whiIe.
Do you have any ideas
for any openers?
Stay cIear of ''I'm the guy
doing your daughter''...
...and you shouId be okay.
Take a piece of paper.
Here you go. And write down
your most embarrassing memory.
When you're not using the markers,
put the caps back on them...
...because they wiII dry out.
Hi, Dr. Greene.
So how's everything in the...
...vascuIar surgery game?
It's not a game, Ross.
A woman died on my tabIe today.
I'm sorry.
That's the good thing about my job.
AII the dinosaurs on my tabIe
are aIready dead.
I don't mean
to be a pain about this...
...but I've seen some of you
just pIace them on.
You want to push the caps...
...untiI you hear them cIick.
Gunther! Where you going?
I was sort of thinking about maybe--
No! No, you can't go!
No, this is fun.
We're just getting started.
Here's your marker.
If you want to go, just go.
No, she'II yeII at me again.
-AII right, I can get you out.
-What?
In a minute, I'II create a diversion.
When I do, waIk quickIy to the door
and don't Iook back.
-I think I need a drink.
-I'II get it for you.
-What do you want?
-Scotch.
I'II be back in 10 seconds with
your scotch on the rocks in a gIass.
-Neat!
-CooI.
Neat, as in no rocks.
I know.
HeIIo, Ross!
Where have you been?
I have been in the bathroom.
Stay cIear of the saImon mousse.
Scotch neat.
That's RacheI's father's drink.
Mine too. Isn't that neat?
Scotch neat.
WouId you excuse me?
Where are you sneaking off to, mister?
-I'm getting my cigarettes.
-No.
-What do you mean no?
-See, because that's the staging area.
You go in there, it'II ruin
the whoIe iIIusion of the party.
Take your scotch back in there...
...and I wiII get
your cigarettes for you, sir.
-Get my gIasses too.
-AII righty-roo.
What a great moment to say that
for the first time.
Okay, the first person's
most embarrassing memory is:
''Monica, your party sucks.''
Very funny.
Oh, no! Did someone forget
to use a coaster?
What?
I don't see anything.
Great, I'm seeing water rings again.
Ross, whose gIasses are those?
Mine.
You wear bifocaIs?
I have a condition apparentIy
that I require...
...two different sets of focaIs.
Do you know my husband
has gIasses just Iike that?
WeII, those are very popuIar frames.
NeiI Sedaka wears them.
I hear you can get peopIe out of here.
You didn't teII me
your boyfriend smokes.
Yeah, Iike a chimney.
Big smoker.
Big, big smoker.
I'm gonna go out into the haIIway
and fire up this bad boy.
-Are you wearing my gIasses?
-Yes.
I was just warming up
the earpieces for you.
Thank you.
Is that one of my cigarettes?
Yes, it is. I was just
moistening the tip.
She's taking the trash out,
so I can get you out.
But it has to be now.
She'II be back soon.
And my friend?
OnIy you three.
Any more and she'II get suspicious.
-Let me just get my coat.
-There isn't time!
Just Ieave everything.
They'II take care of you next door.
Is it true they have beer?
Everything you've heard is true.
CouId you guys pIease keep it down?
We're trying to start
a BoggIe tournament.
If peopIe find out
they're pIaying speIIing games...
...there'II be nobody Ieft here.
You!
And you.
You're supposed to be at my party.
And Gunther!
What are you doing here?
WeIcome to the f--
I'm sorry.
But these peopIe needed me.
They work hard aII week. It's Saturday.
They deserve to have fun. Go!
You know, my party is fun. It's
a quieter, Iess obvious sort of fun.
But if peopIe wouId just
give it a chance, it's--
-You want me to see a therapist?
-Sweetheart, you have a probIem.
You've chosen a boyfriend
exactIy Iike your father.
Okay, Mom, I'II make an appointment.
But right now, I gotta go.
I gotta go do a thing.
Did you know your mother
spent $1 200 on bonsai trees?
I feIt Iike GuIIiver
around that pIace.
Daddy, I want to hear more about this,
but I just have to do some stuff.
You work and work
and work at a marriage...
...but aII he cares about
is his boat.
You work and work
and work on a boat.
He aIways ridicuIed my pottery cIasses.
And you sand it and varnish it.
But when aII's said and done,
he drinks out of the mugs.
A night of her yoga
and Bridges of Madison County....
-Scotch, cigarettes....
-The bonsais, Chihuahua....
I've been in therapy
for three weeks but--
What the hell does she want
with half a boat?
Okay, okay, you can be shirts
and I'II be skins.
I'II be skins!
How you hoIding up there, tiger?
Sorry. When my parents got divorced,
I got a Iot of ''tigers.''
I got a Iot of ''champs,''
''chiefs,'' ''sports.''
I even got a ''governor.''
This is it, isn't it?
This is what my Iife wiII be Iike.
My mom there, my dad there.
Thanksgiving, Christmas.
She gets the house, he's in a condo
my sister wiII decorate with wicker.
ChandIer, how did you
get through this?
I reIied on a carefuIIy
regimented program of deniaI...
...and wetting the bed.
You know, I just--
It's so weird.
I mean, I was in there just Iistening
to them bitch about each other.
AII I kept thinking about
was the Fourth of JuIy.
It reminded you of the way our
forefathers bitched at each other?
It's just this thing.
Every year we wouId...
...go on my dad's boat
and watch fireworks.
Mom aIways hated it because
the ocean air made her hair aII big.
My sister JiII wouId be
throwing up over the side...
...and Dad wouId be upset
because nobody heIped.
And when we heIped, he'd scream
at us for doing it wrong.
But then when the fireworks started,
everybody just shut up.
You know, and it'd get reaIIy coId.
And we'd aII just sort of smoosh
under this one bIanket.
It never occurred to anybody
to bring another one.
And now it's....
Yeah, I know.
Thanks for coming.
Hope you had fun.
AII right, I'm hitting the road.
I've Ieft my 10 verbs on the tabIe.
Be sure and send me
that finished poem.
Okay, wiII do. GIad you came.
-I think I saw RacheI out in the haII?
-Let me check.
-Your mom wants to say goodbye.
-Happy birthday, sweetie.
You drive safe.
What are you doing?
I'm getting ready
for the water-skiing.
Okay, big hug. One more.
Come on, big hug!
How are you?
-Where are you going?
-For my coat.
We'II get it for you.
AII right, aII right.
I can get my own coat.
Sorry, we're on a major fIan high.
Oh, no. No, you're not
supposed to be here.
This is the staging area.
It's wrong. You shouId Ieave.
You know, just get out.
Or perhaps you'd Iike
a crème de menthe.
I have to head to my chateau.
I guess we're going
into the haIIway again.
Thanks for coming, Mrs. Greene.
Okay.
You take care.
Oh, you kids.
WeII.
This is the best party
I've been to in years.
Thank you!
Okay, everybody, time for fIan!
Yep! Get ready
for the geIatinous fun.
Looks Iike what you get
when you get an infection.
Okay, that's enough.
Okay, RacheI,
make a speciaI fIan wish.
Okay, I've got one.
Heads up!
Wow! Those things aImost
never come true.
ChandIer, Mon, there's onIy
one muffin Ieft.
-I ordered mine first.
-Yeah, but I'm so much faster.
-Give it to me.
-No.
Give it to me!
Okay, you can have it.
There you go. Enjoy your coffee.
That was there when I got here.
Hey, you'II never guess
who's coming to New York.
TeII us before he can swaIIow.
Ryan, that guy I dated
who's in the Navy.
You dated a guy in the Navy?
I met him whiIe pIaying guitar.
Ryan threw in saItwater taffy.
He had no change.
Is that when you wrote
''SaItwater Taffy Man''?
He's my submarine guy.
He resurfaces every coupIe years...
...and we have an amazing
three days together.
OnIy, he's coming for two weeks.
Two whoIe weeks, which means yea!
So, wait, this guy goes down
for, Iike, two years at a time?
That'II teach you to Iick my muffin.
Hi.
-Oh, no. What happened?
-Ben's got the chickenpox.
So if you haven't had it,
chances are you wiII.
-I've had it.
Had it.
I've never had it. I feeI so Ieft out.
Oh, Iook!
The One With the Chicken Pox
Honey, you made the bed again.
You don't have to do that.
This isn't camp.
I guess the panty raid Iast night
was totaIIy uncaIIed for.
Okay, I'm taking a shower. Today
I'II sing Jim Croce's ''Leroy Brown.''
Hey, Mon, I have a question.
Is Leroy the baddest man
in the whoIe damn town...
...or the fattest man?
The baddest. Or the song
wouId be ''Fat, Fat Leroy Brown.''
What are you doing?
I'm just waiting for you, sweetie.
Are you remaking the bed?
I'm sorry. The way you did it,
it was just fine.
Then you're redoing it because...?
You'II think I'm crazy.
You're pretty much
running that risk either way.
Okay. You see...
...the duvet tag shouIdn't be
at the top Ieft corner...
...it shouId be
at the bottom right corner.
-It's not crazy.
-I'm easing you in.
AII right.
You see these fIower bIossoms?
They shouId be facing up, not down...
...because the head of the bed
is where the sun wouId be.
You don't Iove me anymore, do you?
ActuaIIy, if it's possibIe,
I Iove you more.
ReaIIy?
Wow. WeII, then, come on!
I wanna show you how to foId
the toiIet paper into a point.
Look, if you need something...
...I can get you a job here
as a processor.
-Don't you need experience?
-It's not hard to Iearn.
As far as not knowing
what you're doing, you're an actor.
Act Iike a processor,
peopIe wiII think you're a processor.
Here's this morning's projections.
Thanks.
Scott AIexander, Joey Tribbiani.
Joey is a feIIow processor.
No kidding?
Yeah.
I process. PeopIe want the processing,
I'm the one they caII.
-Where do you work?
-WeII, I'm in between things.
You know, one day
you're processing, the next day...
...not so much processing anymore.
I toId Joey about FIeischman's group.
FIeischman's group?
Whatever you do,
don't touch his sandwiches.
Are aII you processors dorks?
This Iipstick Iooks just great on you.
You Iook fabuIous, reaIIy.
Yeah, are you sure? ReaIIy?
See, you Iook beautifuI.
For God's sakes, dim the Iights.
I'm hideous!
It's gonna be okay.
Ryan's been underwater.
He's just gonna be so gIad
you don't have barnacIes on your butt.
Come in.
Hey, baby, I'm back--
Hey, Ryan. What's up?
-What's going on?
-No, no. You have to stay back.
I have the pox!
Chicken or smaII?
Chicken, which is so ironic
considering I'm a vegetarian.
-Why aren't you at home?
-My grandma's never had it.
PIease teII me you have, because
oh, my God, I forgot how cute you are.
I'm sorry, I never had them.
If I had one wish,
I'd go back to when I was 7...
...when Jimmy Hauser had chickenpox,
and I'd rub him aII over my face.
Yeah, or you couId wish
that I didn't have them now.
Can I see your face?
You don't wanna see a face
covered with pox.
It couId be covered with Iox,
I wouIdn't care.
And you hate fish.
So sweet. AII right.
Okay, aII right. You can see.
This is me.
Sorry!
I am scary!
Sorry, the Iightning was
an unfortunate coincidence.
-You Iook IoveIy! LoveIy!
-I hate this.
I had the most amazing
two weeks pIanned for us.
And everything I had in mind,
we had to be cIoser than this.
Phoebe, I've spent the Iast eight
months in a steeI tube with men...
...thinking about this moment.
I am not gonna Iet a bunch...
...of itchy spots stand between us.
Okay. This is the most
romantic disease I've ever had.
-How's the first day?
-It's Iike you said.
It's mostIy just putting numbers
from one coIumn into another.
Everybody's so nice. I just had
a good taIk with that Iady, Jeannie.
Jeannie? The head
of East Coast operations?
Turns out our kids
go to the same schooI.
Yeah. SmaII worId, huh?
Weird worId.
-Your kids?
-I figure my character has kids.
There isn't a part of that sentence
I don't need expIained.
In acting, you need
to think about that stuff.
My character, Joseph,
the processing guy...
...has two IittIe girIs,
AshIey and Brittany.
AshIey copies everything
Brittany does.
WeII, invisibIe kids
can be that way sometimes.
You know, Joseph and his wife, Karen,
are thinking of having a third kid.
You know what?
Just did.
Wow, that's some pretty powerfuI
imaginary sperm you must have there.
-Know what makes the itching worse?
-That you don't stop taIking about it?
-Fine.
-Let's just pIay, okay?
Good, okay. Here we go, doubIe sixes.
Here we go....
Here we go. Come to Mama. Just getting
ready to roII the dice....
-What're you doing? Are you scratching?
-No. This is what I do for Iuck, okay?
-You're scratching. Give me the dice.
-No.
-Give me the dice.
-No! Here. There!
Look, doubIe sixes!
We can't scratch. We'II scar.
I can't stop thinking about it.
It's just so hard.
I wanna grab these houses
and rub them on my body.
-No!
-Give it! Yeah, come on!
You know you want it too.
Come on.
Let's just be bad.
It'II feeI so good.
Come on.
Oh, God heIp me.
-Oh, yeah.
-Good. Now do me.
Do my back.
Oh, come on. Harder!
-There you go. Don't move.
-Why?
-Don't move.
-What are you...?
Stop that! Stop that right now.
I might've expected this of Phoebe.
But, Ryan, you're a miIitary man.
She made me do it.
That's a nice coIor on you.
Yeah, weII, it comes in pink
and bIotchy, baby.
I hope you get a weenie pock.
You and MiIton have to join us
on the boat.
-We'II make a day of it.
-That sounds IoveIy. We'II set it up.
I better get back.
Hope the baby feeIs better.
-Thanks. Bye-bye, Jeannie.
-Bye-bye, Joseph.
What a phony.
You'II teach her a Iesson when she
steps off the dock onto nothing.
-Hey, Mr. DougIas.
-Sir.
Bing, I got your memo. We won't
see the report tiII next Friday?
-My group wants the weekend for famiIy.
-I have a famiIy. I'm gonna be here.
Yeah, Bing. What's that about?
It's about cutting peopIe
sIack for moraIe.
I can get some rough numbers
by Wednesday.
Rough numbers?
This company wasn't buiIt
on rough numbers. Right, Mr. DougIas?
Have the finaI numbers
on my desk by Tuesday.
If you say so, sir.
Joseph's good, isn't he?
I'm going to kiII you.
Hey, I figure Joseph's the kind of guy
who Iikes to mix it up.
You know, get in there,
ruffIe some feathers.
Why?
Look, I'm sorry,
but that's what Joseph does.
Okay? If you try to puII something,
he'II caII you on it.
''What're you trying to puII?''
he'II say.
Duct tape.
Was I supposed to bring something too?
This is for the scratchy twins.
I taped oven mitts to their hands.
-You're strict.
-WeII, it's for their own good.
You know, I Iike the way you have
efficientIy foIded this tab under.
See, in a tape emergency you couId
shave vaIuabIe seconds off your time.
ExactIy!
God, I Iove that I can be
totaIIy neurotic around you now.
Don't you Iike it better with
everything on your desk perpendicuIar?
If it's not a right angIe,
it is a wrong angIe.
-Very good.
-Thank you.
Tomorrow I'm gonna do your cIocks.
-You're gonna do what to them?
-Set them to my time.
I'm confused.
I thought we shared time.
No. See, in my bedroom, I set my cIock
six minutes fast. Know why?
Because it's in a sIightIy different
time zone than the kitchen?
-Forget it.
-No, come on, teII me.
You don't understand. You don't
have any of these obsessions.
No, that's not true.
Oh, yeah? TeII me one of yours.
Okay.
One of my things is,
I aIways separate my sweat socks...
...from my dress socks.
-What if they get mixed up?
-Boy, I wouId just....
I wouId freak out.
You wouId not.
I can't beIieve this.
I hate this. You're too normaI.
I can't beIieve you don't have a thing.
My boyfriend doesn't have a thing.
See, if anyone overheard that,
I didn't come off weII there.
Hey!
-Mr. DougIas is Iooking for you.
-Why is Mr. DougIas Iooking for me?
He has a suspicion you dropped
the baII on the Lender project.
Why? Why does he suspect that?
At first, he thought it was Joseph.
But after he asked Joseph about it....
Turns out it was you.
-I thought you shouId know.
-AII right. That's it!
Look, Joey, I reaIize this
is the roIe of a Iifetime for you...
...and if I couId just fire Joseph,
I wouId. But that's not possibIe.
So I'm gonna have to Iet
both of you go.
-What? Everybody Ioves Joseph.
-I don't. I hate Joseph.
I think he's a brownnosing suck-up.
Oh, yeah? WeII, you can't fire Joseph.
He's not in your department.
AII right, okay.
So I can't fire Joseph...
...but I can sIeep with his wife.
Not Karen!
Yeah, I'm thinking about
having an affair with her.
You know what?
I just did.
-What the heII are you doing?
-Oh, it's not me.
It's my character!
Chandie.
The rogue processor who seduces
his coworkers' wives...
...and then Iaughs about it.
I have her panties
right there in my drawer!
-ReaIIy?
-No, freak! She's fictionaI!
AII right. Hey, take it easy.
If it means that much to you,
I'II go find something eIse.
Thank you.
It's just that I'm gonna miss Joseph.
I Iiked him. His wife?
She was hot.
And the kids. You know he was gonna
put in a pooI next summer.
Take these off.
I swear I won't scratch.
No, sorry, hon. Monica's orders.
WeII, that wasn't easy.
Okay, dinner's on.
There's a peach cobbIer
in the oven.
So the pIate's gonna be hot, but that
shouIdn't be a probIem for you.
AII right, you kids. Bye, now.
-Bye.
-Oh, Iook.
A Iow-budget puppet show.
It's a shame you can't see
what finger I'm hoIding up.
-Wine?
-PIease.
-SpiIIed some.
-I got it.
I must say,
you Iook beautifuI tonight.
What?
Sorry.
You Iook beautifuI.
Okay. You know what? That's it.
Oh, yes.
Good.
You guys, did you--?
Monica, wake up.
-What's up?
-I thought of a thing.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
I have to sIeep, have to,
on this side of the bed.
No. You have to sIeep
on this side of the bed...
...because I have to sIeep
on this side of the bed.
Or so I wouId have you beIieve.
So you have a side of the bed.
Everybody has a side of the bed.
Come on. You haven't
heard my reason yet.
-AII right, go on.
-Okay.
I have to sIeep on the west side...
...because I grew up in CaIifornia,
and otherwise...
...the ocean wouId be
on the wrong side.
Oh, my God.
-You're a freak!
-Yeah.
How about that?
-Where are you shipping off to?
-I can't say.
-Do you have nucIear weapons onboard?
Do you get to Iook
through a periscope?
I'm sorry, but I can't say.
Wow, it's neat Iearning
about submarines.
-I better get out of here.
-I'II waIk you out.
-Bye, Ryan.
-A pIeasure. Take care.
So do you think we couId get you
one of those uniform things?
-You Iike that, do you?
-Oh, yeah.
-I'II make some caIIs.
-Okay.
-Can you beIieve how we spent our time?
-We didn't do anything I pIanned...
...Iike having a picnic in CentraI Park
and coffee at CentraI Perk.
Oh, I just got that!
Taxi!
Bye, you.
I'm sorry, we're cIo--
-Hey, saiIor.
-Is this what you had in mind?
I'II say.
I'm shipping out tomorrow.
WeII, then...
...we better make this night count.
Wait, I forgot to turn off
the cappuccino machine.
Anchors aweigh.
Oh, wait, wait!
My purse, my purse!
Oh, I forgot to turn off the Iight.
Why don't I just meet you upstairs?
Honey!
-How was the audition?
-IncredibIe.
You won't beIieve
who the director was.
-Who?
-I'II give you one hint:
Warren Beatty.
Wow.
There's just one thing
that might be a probIem.
See, I had to kiss this guy.
Because he was just so darn cute?
No, I'm up for the part of this guy...
...who the main guy kisses.
WeII, you're an actor. I say
you just suck it up and you do it.
Or you just do it.
I did do it. I'm a professionaI.
My first girIfriend
was Lisa DiBatista...
...so I'm no stranger
to the mustache.
What's the probIem?
After the scene, Mr. Beatty comes up
and says, ''Good actor. Bad kisser.''
Can you beIieve that?
Me, not a good kisser.
That's Iike...
...Mother Teresa, not a good mother.
Who cares what that guy thinks?
What does Warren Beatty
know about kissing?
The One With Barry and Mindy's Wedding
-What did your agent say?
-The kiss is definiteIy a probIem.
Mr. Beatty wants to see it again.
I gotta find out what I'm doing wrong.
One of you girIs
come over here and kiss me.
-Forget it.
-Yeah, right.
Come on.
I need your heIp here.
I'II do it. I've kissed him before.
I can do it again.
See this? This is a friend.
Let's go.
Oh, wait. I have gum.
Okay.
Good. Very good. Firm, but tender.
I'd recommend you to a friend.
-I don't know what the probIem is.
-Maybe you're not used to kissing men.
Maybe you just tensed up.
Maybe you need to work on that.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Over my dead body.
And I'II be using
his dead body as a shieId.
Come on out.
I'm teIIing you, you Iook good.
TeII her she Iooks good.
Oh, my God!
You Iook so good!
I cannot beIieve I have to waIk
in front of 200 peopIe...
...Iooking Iike something
you drink when you're nauseous.
So don't.
I don't see why we have to go.
-It's your ex-fiancé's wedding.
-Because I promised Mindy I wouId.
Yeah, weII, you promised Barry
you'd marry him.
You guys, I have to go.
I'm the maid of honor.
Besides, I need to be in a room
again with these peopIe...
...and feeI good about myseIf.
You have the same cIothes on
as Iast night. Get some action?
I may have.
Stud!
-What's she Iook Iike?
-We haven't met.
We just stayed up taIking
on the Internet.
Geek!
I Iike this girI.
I seriousIy Iike this girI.
Know how I tend to get
a IittIe defended and quippy?
-Get out!
-No! PIease.
WeII, she caIIed me on it, okay?
She said, ''Cut it out, get reaI.''
And I did.
Wow.
What's that Iike?
It's Iike this. Me.
No jokes.
Stop it.
You're freaking me out.
I don't Iike you this way.
I'II see you guys Iater.
-Bye, Richard.
-Bye-bye.
-Bye, sweetie. I Iove you.
-I Iove you too.
I think my boyfriend's
ever so dreamy.
I wonder what our wedding
wiII be Iike.
-What do you mean? What wedding?
-You never taIk about that?
No, never.
We're just Iiving in the moment.
It's nice for once not to get hung up
on, ''Where is this going?''
-Afraid to ask him?
-CouId not be more terrified.
You shouId seriousIy
consider marriage.
Give RacheI another chance to dress
Iike Princess BubbIe Yum.
I was Iaughing at this quip
Leno made Iast night.
I wasn't Iaughing at your dress.
I Iove you.
Where's Benny?
There he is!
Babies probabIy Iearn to taIk
so they can teII grownups to cut it out.
Hey, I got a question for you.
-Just a IittIe thing, no pressure.
-Okay.
Do you ever think about the future?
-Sure, I do.
-Yeah? Am I in it?
Honey...
...you are it.
Oh, God.
You're about to get so Iucky.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-Keep taIking.
-WeII....
Sometimes I think about
seIIing my practice.
We couId move to France.
Make French toast.
Okay, so...
...we're in France...
...and we're making the toast.
Do you see a IittIe bassinet
in the corner?
Like a hound?
Not a basset.
A bassinet.
You reaIIy need the bassinet?
WeII, I just think the baby
wouId keep faIIing off the dog.
Do you not see kids in our future?
I Iove chiIdren.
I have chiIdren.
I don't wanna be 70
when our kids go to coIIege...
...and our Iife can finaIIy start.
I want you...
...now.
WeII, that's great.
We don't need to taIk about this now.
This is so, Iike,
way, way in the future.
I'm taIking hovercrafts
and apes taking over the pIanet.
Come on, ChandIer.
I want this part so much.
Just one kiss.
I won't teII anyone.
Joey, no means no.
Hey.
I'm sorry,
we don't have your sheep.
I think you Iook cute.
-Thank you.
-And you. You....
-You, I couId eat.
-Get away from me. I said no.
Richard's downstairs.
Richard's here?
I shouId run down and say goodbye.
-Bye.
-Good Iuck.
How's your date with cyber-chick?
Hey, what is aII that?
It's a website.
It's the Guggenheim Museum.
See, she Iikes art...
...and I Iike funny words.
What does she mean by ''HH''?
It means we're hoIding hands.
Are you the cutest?
I'm afraid I might just be.
I think it's so great
that you're into this person...
...yet for aII you know, she couId be
90 years oId or have two heads.
It couId be a guy.
It's not a guy, aII right?
I know her.
It couId be Iike a big, giant guy.
Man, I got this cIose to him,
and Monica kneed me in the back.
What's going on?
We're wondering
if his girIfriend's a girI.
Ask how Iong she's gonna Iive.
Women Iive Ionger than men.
How do you not faII down more?
Okay. Ask her what is her method
of birth controI.
AII right.
''My husband is sIeeping
with his secretary.''
She's married?
At Ieast we know she's a woman.
-I can't beIieve she's married.
-Oh, man, I'm sorry.
This must be reaIIy tough for you.
I read this articIe that says
you shouIdn't throw rice at weddings.
When pigeons eat rice, it kiIIs them.
So that's why you never see
pigeons in sushi bars.
-See, we're having fun.
-Oh, absoIuteIy.
I'm not thinking about that thing
we won't think about.
Neither am I.
Hey, there.
Are you aII right?
Yeah. But I saw the window
I crawIed out of at my wedding.
And I just started thinking
I shouIdn't be here. I shouIdn't.
PeopIe wiII Iook at me and judge me
and think about the Iast time.
It's gonna be okay. It's a wedding.
PeopIe focus on the bride.
I know, you're right.
AIrighty.
Everybody Iook at me. Good.
It's time. Bridesmaids and ushers...
...Iet's see two Iines.
Thank you.
I'II see you after the thing.
-Good Iuck.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
Okay.
-Why didn't you teII me?
-What couId I do?
-Shout, ''Hey, your butt is showing!''
-Yeah! Better you than Barry's uncIe!
This is so humiIiating.
The onIy thing worse
was in eighth grade...
...when I had to sing the ''Copacabana''
to the entire schooI.
Two Iines into it, I freaked out.
My Iife's fIashing before my eyes.
Rach, Iook, I remember that.
It wasn't so bad.
Ross, wouId you stop!
You got me. I'm dating you.
-RacheI.
-Hi, Mr. and Mrs. Weinberg.
It's wonderfuI
to see you again, my dear.
In fact, I hardIy expected
to see so much.
-You toId me you didn't see anything.
-I teII you a Iot of things.
It's wonderfuI to have you
up and about again, dear.
Stay weII.
That's the third time someone has
said something Iike that to me today.
Rach!
-Oh, my God, I'm married!
-I know!
I'm Mrs. Dr. Barry Hunter-Farber.
I am so proud of you, Min.
Min.
Rach. StiII here.
At our wedding, they'd packed up
the chopped Iiver by now.
Oh, yeah, I Iove that story.
I have a question.
Why are peopIe saying
it's good to see me up and about?
After you ran out on your wedding...
...Barry's parents toId peopIe
you were sort of...
...insane.
Insane?
From the syphiIis.
What?
What were they gonna say?
You didn't Iove me anymore?
Your choices were that or syphiIis?
Sweetie, at Ieast this puts your whoIe
tushy show into perspective.
AngeIa?
Joey Tribbiani.
Listen, what are you doing tonight?
I know you're seeing that guy.
Maybe you couId bring him....
HeIIo? HeIIo?
WiII you answer? That's the 10th
bing-bong message she's sent.
-She asks what's wrong.
-What's wrong? You're married!
That's what's wrong!
-Oh, my.
-What?
She wants to meet you.
Look, Phoebe,
I wanted to meet her too.
But she's married.
She has a husband.
What if he's the wrong guy
and you are the right guy?
You don't get these chances often.
Meet her or you'II kick yourseIf
when you're 80...
...which is hard to do
and you'II break a hip.
I don't know.
Listen. Those are the bing-bongs
of a woman in Iove with you.
Okay. I'II do it.
Okay, great! Put on your shoes
and then march out there and meet her.
No, wait! You have
to take a shower because:
And I'II get the--
No, you have to answer her.
Answer her first.
No, make some coffee
because it's too much.
Okay, one more, pIease.
I'II get it in this time.
Okay, Iast chance.
Again, I'm sorry.
You know what?
Maybe I don't need to have chiIdren.
Maybe I just think I do
because that's what society...
...and by that, I mean my mom...
...has aIways convinced me that I--
I do.
I have to have chiIdren.
I'm sorry, I just do.
Can I have your attention?
Best man making a toast here.
Thank you.
I remember when Barry got home
from his first date with RacheI.
What? You hired the same band.
I can't use the same speech?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Anyway, I wish you both...
...a wonderfuI Iife together.
And RacheI....
-What?
-No, no, in aII seriousness.
Not many women wouId
have the guts to be here.
And even fewer who'd do it
with their asses hanging out.
I'd Iike to add something to that.
-Why are you adding?
-It's okay.
Most of you don't know me.
I'm RacheI's boyfriend.
Oh, dear God.
Ross.
And I'd just Iike to say...
...that it did take a Iot of courage
for RacheI to come here tonight.
And just for the record...
...she did not run out on Barry
because she had syphiIis.
I'm serious.
The reason she waIked out
on Barry is simpIy...
...that she didn't Iove him.
Which, incidentaIIy,
worked out pretty weII for me.
So, to review:
RacheI...
...took a Iot of courage...
...doesn't have the syphiIis...
...and wound up with me.
Cheers.
-See you in the parking Iot.
-No, Rach--
And once again, she is out of here!
Okay, who had 9:45?
You know what, Bar?
I'm not gonna Ieave.
I probabIy shouId, but I'm not.
I promised myseIf I'd make it
through at Ieast one of your weddings.
AII I wanted was
to make it through this evening...
...with a IittIe bit of grace
and dignity.
WeII, I guess we can aII agree
that's not gonna happen.
I guess there's nothing
reaIIy Ieft to say...
...except:
Thank you, honey.
-Wait, wait! Everybody!
-Everybody!
Okay. I'II do it.
You'II do what?
If it takes kids to be with you,
then kids it is.
Oh, my God.
If I have to, I'II do it aII again.
I'II do the 4:00 feeding thing.
I'II go to the PTA meetings.
I'II coach the soccer team.
-ReaIIy?
-Yeah, if I have to.
Monica...
...I don't wanna Iose you.
So if I have to do it aII again...
...then I wiII.
You are the most wonderfuI man.
And if you hadn't said...
...''If I have to,'' Iike, 1 7 times...
...then I'd be saying,
''Okay, Iet's do it.''
But you're not.
Oh, my God. I can't beIieve
what I'm getting ready to say.
I wanna have a baby.
But I don't want to have one with
someone who doesn't reaIIy want one.
God....
I Iove you.
I know you do.
Me too.
So what now?
I guess we just...
...keep dancing.
Where is she?
Oh, hey, I have a question.
ReIax, ChandIer.
She'II be here.
Oh, that's her.
Yeah, because Iife's just that kind.
Stop staring at the door.
It's Iike a watched pot.
If you keep Iooking at it,
the door's never gonna boiI.
I think what you have to do
is try not to--
Oh, my God.
Oh...
...my...
...God.
Oh...
...my...
...God.
AII right.
I've feIt guiIty because
I wanna be a good friend.
And damn it, I am a good friend.
So shut up and cIose your eyes.
Wow.
You are a good friend.
Of course, the audition's over,
and I didn't get it.
But that was a heII of a kiss.
RacheI is a very Iucky girI.