She's having my baby,
and she's not here yet.
-Has her water broken yet?
-I don't know.
When we taIked, she said she'd
aIready passed the mucous pIug.
Do we have to know about that?
What'II you do
when you have a baby?
I'II be in the waiting room,
handing out cigars.
Joey's made arrangements to have
his baby in a movie from the '50s.
She couId be giving birth in the cab.
ReIax. It's onIy $2
for the first contraction...
...and then 50 cents for each
additionaI contraction.
What, it's okay
when ChandIer does it?
You have to pick your moments.
Did I miss it?
-She's not here yet.
-What's with the guitar?
We might be here for a whiIe.
Things might get musicaI.
-Where have you been?
-We stopped at the gift shop.
I got this,
and Susan wanted a Chunky.
You're having a baby.
You don't stop for Chunkies.
I used to have that bumper sticker.
You see what I mean?
The One With the Birth
-''Stopped for a Chunky.''
-Let it go, Ross.
I got an extra one.
You want this?
-How's my favorite parenting team?
-Dr. FranzbIau.
I understand you're thinking
of having a baby.
I see you're nine months pregnant.
That's a good start.
-How are your contractions?
-I Iove them.
Each one's Iike a IittIe party
in my uterus.
-Every 4 minutes, Iasting 55 seconds.
-59 seconds. Quartz.
Swiss quartz.
-Am I aIIowed to drink anything?
-Ice chips.
-At the nurse's station.
-I'II get it!
-No, I'II get it.
-No, I'm getting it.
Hi. Thought you might Iike
some ice chips.
-Thanks.
-And if you need anything eIse-- I...
...do not beIieve we've met.
I'm RacheI Greene.
I'm CaroI's ex-husband's
sister's roommate.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Dr. FranzbIau.
I'm your roommate's brother's
ex-wife's obstetrician.
Oh, that's funny.
I want a baby.
Not tonight, honey.
I got an earIy day tomorrow.
-Get up. Let's get some coffee.
-Okay, because we never do that.
Shoot, shoot, shoot.
Or just faII down. That's good too.
IKnick fan?
-Oh, boy, do they suck.
-Listen, Iady--
Look. Look at your man, Ewing.
He couIdn't hit water
if he was standing on a boat.
-And who do you Iike?
-CeItics.
CeItics? They couIdn't hit a boat if--
Wait....
They suck, aII right?
Shut up.
It's a rebuiIding year--
Let me get the father.
We need a father over here.
There's no father.
-Oh, sorry.
-That's okay. I'm fine.
Okay. Right this way.
AII the other pregnant women
seem to be going in here.
They're tiny and chubby
And so sweet to touch
But soon they'll grow up
And resent you so much
Now they're yelling at you
And you don't know why
And you cry and you cry
And you cry
-Thanks, Ross.
-I'm paying you to stop.
Oh, Iook, twins.
Hi, guys. Oh, cute.
No fair.
I don't even have one.
How come they get two?
-You'II get one.
-When?
TeII you what. When we're 40,
if neither of us are married...
...what do you say we have one?
Why won't I be married
when I'm 40?
I just meant hypotheticaIIy.
HypotheticaIIy, why won't I be
married when I'm 40?
What is it? Is there something
unmarriabIe about me?
WeII?
Dear God!
This parachute is a knapsack.
Look at you, dressy-dress.
Did you go home and change?
It's an important day.
I want to Iook nice.
Has Dr. FranzbIau been by--?
I haven't seen him.
Where is he?
He is supposed to be here.
What if the baby needs him?
What's the deaI with you and doctors?
Is your father a doctor?
Yeah. Why?
No reason.
Mom, we've been through this.
No, I am not caIIing him.
I don't care if it is his kid,
the guy's a jerk.
No, I am not aIone.
Joey's here.
What do you mean ''Joey who''?
Joey who?
-Tribbiani.
-Joey Tribbiani.
Yes. Okay. HoId on.
She wants to taIk to you.
Take the phone.
Yeah, it's me.
No, we're just friends.
Yeah, I'm singIe.
Twenty-five.
An actor. HeIIo?
She's not much of a phone person.
So, what's the deaI
with this father guy?
If someone was having my baby,
I'd wanna know about it.
Hey, IKnick fan, am I interested
in your views on fatherhood? No.
-Maybe I shouId just go.
-Maybe you shouId.
Good Iuck...
...and take care.
The CeItics probIem is that
the pIayers run the team.
-That is so not true.
-Oh, it is.
-Breathe.
You're gonna kiII me.
-Fifteen more seconds. 1 4, 13, 1 2--
-Count faster.
It'II be okay. IKeep focusing on Jordy.
He'II be here soon.
-Three. Two. Who the heII is Jordy?
-Your son.
I don't have a son named Jordy.
We aII agreed on Jamie.
Jamie was the name
of Susan's first girIfriend...
...so we went back to Jordy.
What do you mean, back to Jordy?
We never Ianded on Jordy.
We just passed by it during the whoIe
Jesse-Cody-DiIIon fiasco.
Ow! Leg cramp!
-I got it.
-I got it. I'm doing it.
You get to sIeep with her.
I get the cramps.
No, you don't.
That is it.
I want both of you out.
-She started it.
-He did.
I'm trying to get
a person out of my body here...
...and you're not making it
any easier! Now go!
-Thanks.
-See what you did?
-Listen--
-Out!
Breathe. Breathe.
What is that? Something expIoded.
-That's not the baby, is it?
-Her water broke. CaIm down.
Water breaking?
What do you mean? What's that?
Breathe. Breathe.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
That's disgusting. I'm okay.
-This is so your fauIt.
-How is this my fauIt?
CaroI never threw me out
of a room before you.
There's a Iot of things
CaroI never did before me.
-Are you trying to be cIever?
-You're so threatened by me.
Hey. Okay, aII right.
That's it. Get in here.
My God, you guys.
I don't beIieve you.
There are chiIdren
coming into the worId here...
...and your fighting isn't
the first thing they shouId hear.
So stop aII the yeIIing!
Just stop it!
Don't make me do this again!
I don't Iike my voice Iike this!
Who wants to hear something ironic?
Are they here yet?
Don't worry,
we're gonna find them.
And untiI we do,
we are aII here for you. Okay?
You were teIIing me
about Paris. It sounds wonderfuI.
There was this great IittIe
pastry shop right by my hoteI--
There you go, dear.
-You find them?
-Not in the gift shop or cafeteria....
Where are Phoebe and Joey?
There's something sinister
going on here.
If you find anyone,
or parts of anyone...
...scream. And scream again.
-HeIp!
-Come on!
-I'm having a baby in there!
-HeIIo!
Okay, everyone stand back.
Ow.
AII right, good thing
we're in a hospitaI.
Come on, Lydia, you can do it.
Push him out, push him out.
Harder, harder.
Way out.
Let's get that baII and reaIIy move.
Let's get--
I was just-- Yeah, okay.
Push, push, push.
What are you gonna do,
suck the door open?
HeIp! HeIp!
And they found their bodies
The very next day
The very next--
Mom, everything's going fine.
Ross is great.
He's in a whoIe other pIace.
No, he's gone.
No, you don't have to fIy back.
ReaIIy.
What do you mean ''This might be your
onIy chance''? I'm onIy 26.
I'm not even thinking
about babies yet.
-Where have you been?
-I just had a baby.
MazeI tov.
It couId be one hour or three.
But reIax.
She's doing great.
So teII me, are you currentIy
invoIved with anyone?
Not at the moment, I'm not. Are you?
No, it's hard enough to get women
to go out with me.
Right. Yeah, I've heard that
about cute doctors.
No, reaIIy. I suppose it's because
I spend so much time, you know...
...where I do.
I try not to Iet work
affect my personaI Iife.
But it's hard when, when you do
what I do. It's, Iike....
WeII, for instance,
what do you do?
I'm a waitress.
Aren't there times when you come home
at night and you're, Iike:
''If I see one more cup of coffee....''
Gotcha.
-I'm gonna check up on your friend.
-That's fine.
-How'd you know I was here?
-Your mom caIIed me.
So is this her?
No, this is a Ioaner.
Ours is at the shop.
God, I hope she has my brains.
I'm sorry you had to do this
by yourseIf.
I wasn't by myseIf. I had a doctor,
a nurse and a heIper guy.
-So did you see who won the game?
-The IKnicks by 10. They suck.
They're not so bad.
Come on. Come on.
-You're doing it too hard.
-You have to do it hard or eIse--
Damn it. Damn it.
Damn it, damn it.
This is aII your fauIt.
This shouId be
the greatest day of my Iife.
My son is being born,
and I shouId be in there.
Instead, I'm stuck
in a cIoset with you.
I have been waiting for this
as much as you.
No one's been waiting
for this as much as I have.
You know what's funny?
You go home with the baby.
Where does that Ieave me?
You're his father.
Who am I? There's Father's Day.
There's Mother's Day.
There's no Lesbian Lover Day.
Every day is Lesbian Lover Day.
This is so great.
Do you wanna expIain that?
I mean, when I was growing up,
my dad Ieft...
...and my mother died
and my stepfather went to jaiI.
I bareIy had enough pieces
to make one whoIe parent.
And here's this baby who has
three whoIe parents...
...who fight over
who gets to Iove it the most...
...and it's not even born yet.
It's just the Iuckiest baby
in the whoIe worId.
I'm sorry. You were fighting.
Where are they?
-They'II be here.
-They wouIdn't miss this.
ReIax. You're onIy at 9 centimeters,
and the baby's at zero station.
You are reaIIy frightening me.
Somebody wanna heIp me?
Trying to rip out my heart.
That's great.
Anybody seen a nippIe?
Ten centimeters.
Here we go.
-Time to start pushing.
-But they're not here yet.
-I can't teII the baby to wait.
-Oh, God.
-Okay, got the vent open.
-Hi, I'm Ben.
I'm hospitaI worker Ben.
It's Ben to the rescue.
Ben, you ready? Give me your foot.
On three, Ben.
One, two, three.
Come on, Ben.
That's it, Ben.
What do you see?
I see what appears to be
a dark vent.
Wait.
Yes, it is, in fact, a dark vent.
Pheebs, it's open.
It's open.
Wait. You forgot your Iegs.
-Push. Push.
-We're here. We're here.
Where have you been?
Long story.
I need you to keep pushing.
I need-- Excuse me, can I have this?
There's too many peopIe here.
There's about to be one more.
So if you're not an ex-husband or
Iesbian Iife partner, out you go.
-Bye-bye.
-Good Iuck, you guys.
Do you have to be
CaroI's Iesbian Iife partner?
Out.
Here he comes.
Let me see. I've gotta see.
A head.
It's huge.
How are you doing this?
You're not heIping.
You're doing great.
-HeIIo?
-Oh, sorry.
What do you see?
We got a head. We got arms.
Oh, Iook at the IittIe fingers.
A chest and a stomach...
...and it's a boy, definiteIy a boy.
Legs, knees and feet.
He's here.
He's a person.
-Look.
-What does he Iook Iike?
IKind of Iike my UncIe Ed,
covered in JeII-O.
ReaIIy?
You guys, he's beautiful.
Thanks, Pheebs.
No shouting, but we stiII need
a name for this IittIe guy.
-How about Ben?
-I Iike Ben.
Ben.
Ben's good. How come you never
mentioned Ben before?
We just cooked it up.
That's what we were off doing.
-Can we come in?
-Yeah, come on.
I know. I know.
Everybody, there's someone
I'd Iike you to meet.
-This is Ben.
-Hi, Ben.
Ben, this is everybody.
Susan, he Iooks just Iike you.
Thanks.
I can't beIieve one of us
actuaIIy has one of these.
I know.
I stiII am one of these.
Can I?
Okay, the head. You gotta....
I'm your Aunt Monica.
Yes, I am.
I wiII aIways have gum.
Ben...
...I want you to know that
there may be some times when...
...I may not be around Iike this.
But I'II stiII aIways come back...
...Iike this.
And sometimes,
I may be away Ionger...
...Iike this.
But I'II stiII aIways come back...
And sometimes, I'II want you to steaI
third and I'II go Iike this:
He is so amazing.
Yeah, I know. Look at him.
Nothing.
I don't think that's his name.
Look, he's cIosing his eyes.
Look, he's opening his eyes.
He doesn't do much, does he?
Nope, this is pretty much it.
You guys wanna get some coffee?
I'II see you guys Iater.
He's cIosing his eyes again.