Let it go. It's not a big deaI.
Not a big deaI? It's amazing. You
reach in, there's one maneuver and bam!
A bra. Right out the sIeeve.
As far as I know, guys don't do
anything that comes cIose. Right?
Come on! You guys can pee standing up.
We can? Okay, I'm trying that.
IKnow what bIows my mind?
Women can see breasts
anytime they want.
You Iook down,
and there they are.
How you get any work done
is beyond me.
I don't get how guys can do
so many mean things...
...and not even care.
-MuItipIe orgasms!
-There you go.
The One With the
East German Laundry Detergent
Saturday night. The big night!
Date night!
Saturday night. Saturday night!
-No pIans, huh?
-Not a one!
Not even breaking up with Janice?
Right, right. Shut up.
ChandIer, nobody Iikes
breaking up with someone.
Except for IKevin MiIImore,
may he rot in heII.
-You just gotta do it.
-I know. But it's just so hard.
You're sitting there with her.
She has no idea.
You finaIIy get up
the courage to do it.
There's that awkward moment
when you've handed her the note.
You try to run out of the restaurant
before she's finished the note.
Why do you have to break up with her?
Be a man. Just stop caIIing.
If you want, I'II do it with you.
She'd feeI Iike
we're ganging up on her.
You dump Janice,
I'II dump Tony.
-You're breaking up with Tony?
-He's sweet, but it's not fun anymore.
I don't know if it's me or
his hunger strike, I don't know.
Do you want anything eIse?
You had a nutty, chocoIate-y,
kind of cake-y, pie thing that--
Nothing. I'm fine.
What's wrong? Why so scrunchie?
My father wants to give me
a Mercedes convertibIe.
That guy, he burns me up.
Yeah, it's a Mercedes
if I move back home.
It was horribIe!
He caIIed me ''young Iady.''
I hate when my father
caIIs me that.
Did he say
''You're not up to this'' again?
I got the extended version
with choruses of...
...''You'II Never Make it on Your Own.''
Hi, Joey.
Oh, my God! AngeIa!
Wow! Being dumped
by you agrees with her.
-Are you gonna go over there?
-No. Yeah. No.
Okay, but not yet.
I don't wanna seem too eager.
One Mississippi, two Mississippi...
...three Mississippi.
That seems pretty cooI.
-Hey, AngeIa.
-Joey.
You Iook good.
That's because I'm wearing a dress
that accents my boobs.
You don't say.
So, RacheI, what are you
doing tonight?
Big gIamour night.
Me and Monica at Launderama.
You wanna hear a freakish coincidence?
Guess who's doing Iaundry there too?
-Who?
-Me!
Was that not cIear?
Why don't...?
Why don't I just
join you both there?
Don't you have a Iaundry room
in your buiIding?
Yes.
I do have a Iaundry room
in my buiIding.
But there's a rat probIem.
ApparentIy, they're attracted
to dryer sheets.
They're going in fine,
but they're coming out aII fIuffy.
-Anyway, 7-ish?
-Sure.
-Forget it. I'm with Bob now.
-Bob? Who the heII's Bob?
Bob is great. He's smart,
sophisticated, and he has a reaI job.
You go on three auditions a month
and you're an actor. Bob--
Come on! We were great together.
And not just at the fun stuff,
but, Iike, taIking too.
Sorry, Joey. You said,
''Let's be friends.'' So guess what?
-What?
-We're just friends.
Fine. Fine.
Why don't the four of us have
dinner tonight? As friends.
What ''four of us''?
You and Bob,
and me and my girIfriend...
...Monica.
I'm teIIing you,
this guy's perfect for you.
Forget it! Not after your cousin
who couId beIch the aIphabet.
Come on, this guy's great.
His name's Bob. He's AngeIa's...
...brother. He's smart,
he's sophisticated...
...and he has a reaI job.
I go on three auditions a month
and say I'm an actor, but he's--
-God heIp us.
-What?
UgIy Naked Guy
is Iaying kitchen tiIe.
Look, I'm asking a favor here.
If I do this for her brother,
maybe AngeIa wiII come back to me.
What's going on?
You go out with tons of girIs.
I know, but AngeIa's different.
She's Iike one of a kind,
Iike a snowfIake or....
-Something eIse Iike a snowfIake?
-Yeah, yeah.
Look, I made a huge mistake.
I never shouId've broke up with her.
WiII you heIp me? PIease?
HoId on a sec.
You need to not touch any of those.
Okay, bye.
Monica's not coming.
It's just gonna be me and RacheI.
HoId on, camper.
You've thought this through?
It's Iaundry.
The thinking-through is minimaI.
Just you and RacheI?
Just you two?
This is a date.
You're going on a date.
-Uh-uh.
-Uh-huh.
-I haven't done that in a whiIe.
-Is it a date if she doesn't know?
Yes, absoIuteIy.
Saturday night, aII ruIes appIy.
What are you saying? I shouId
shave again? Pick up some wine?
WeII, you may wanna rethink
the dirty underwear.
It's the first time she'II see
your underwear. You want it dirty?
No.
And the fabric softener?
Okay, now what is wrong
with my SnuggIes?
What? It says I'm a sensitive,
warm kind of guy.
You know, Iike a IittIe fuzzy bear.
-I'II pick something eIse up.
-There you go.
Thank you.
What does Bob Iook Iike?
Is he taII, short?
Yep.
-Which?
-Which what?
-You've never met Bob, have you?
-No, but--
-For aII we know, he's horribIy--
-Hey, Joey!
HorribIy attractive.
I'II be shutting up now.
Where are they? Where are they?
This is nice. We never
do anything, just the two of us.
Great. Maybe tomorrow we can rent
a car, run over some puppies.
I don't wanna do that.
-Here we go.
-Have a good breakup.
-Hey, Janice.
-My God, I am so gIad you caIIed me.
I had the most supremeIy awfuI day.
That's not good.
Can I get an espresso
and a Iatte over here?
We got the proofs from the shoot
with the vegetabIes. They sucked.
I bIew off the afternoon.
I went shopping.
And I got you....
I'm Iooking. I'm Iooking.
I'm Iooking.
-I got you--
-What?
-What did you get me there?
I got you...
...these.
BuIIwinkIe socks.
-That's sweet.
-I knew you had Rockys.
You can wear BuIIwinkIe and BuIIwinkIe
or Rocky and Rocky, or you can mix.
Moose and squirreI.
Whatever you want.
I'm gonna get another espresso.
More Iatte?
No, I'm stiII working on mine.
-That's it?
-Yeah, it was reaIIy hard.
-Yeah, the hug Iooked pretty brutaI.
-You weren't there.
-Sorry.
-How are things going?
Going? Things are not going.
She got me socks.
These go with your Rockys. She reaIIy
cares about you-- I'm sorry.
Coming through. Move. Move!
Excuse me! I was kind of
using that machine.
Yeah, weII, now you're kind of not.
But I saved it.
I put my basket on top.
I'm sorry.
Is that your basket?
It's pretty.
UnfortunateIy, I don't see suds!
What?
No suds, no save, okay?
What's going on?
Nothing. This horribIe woman
just took my machine.
Was your basket on top?
-Yeah, but there were no suds.
-So?
-You know, no suds, no save.
-No suds, no-- Excuse me.
HoId on a second!
This is my friend's machine.
Hey, hey, hey!
Her stuff wasn't in it!
Hey, hey, hey! That's not
the ruIe, and you know it!
AII right. Show's over.
Nothing to see here.
Okay. Let's do Iaundry.
That was amazing!
I can't even send back soup.
WeII, that's because you're
such a sweet, gentIe....
Do you--? Do you--?
Oh, hey. You must need detergent.
-What's that?
-Überweiss.
It's new. It's German.
It's extra tough!
Rach, are you gonna separate those?
Oh, God.
Am I being a totaI Iaundry spaz?
Am I supposed to use one machine
for shirts and another for pants?
Have you never done this before?
WeII, not myseIf.
But I know other peopIe that have.
Okay. You caught me.
I'm a Iaundry virgin.
Don't worry.
I'II use the gentIe cycIe.
BasicaIIy, you wanna use
one machine for aII your whites.
A whoIe other machine
for your coIors.
And a third for your...
...deIicates.
That wouId be your bras...
...and your underpanty things.
These are white cotton panties.
WouId they go with whites
or with deIicates?
That wouId be a judgment caII.
He's so cute!
Where did you grow up?
-BrookIyn Heights.
-CIeveIand.
-How'd that happen?
-My God!
What?
I suddenIy had the feeIing
I was faIIing.
But I'm not.
So, you and AngeIa, huh?
-Yep. Pretty much.
-You're a Iucky man.
IKnow what I miss most about her?
That cute nibbIy noise
she makes when she eats.
Like a happy IittIe squirreI...
...or a weaseI.
-I never reaIIy noticed.
-Oh, yeah, yeah. Listen for it.
Monica. Monica is great.
Yeah, she is.
But it's not gonna Iast.
She's too much for me in bed.
SexuaIIy.
I've gotta teII you, Bob is terrific.
Yeah, isn't he?
It's great to meet a smart, funny guy
who's emotionaIIy oIder than 8.
You know what eIse?
He's unbeIievabIe in bed!
My brother never even toId me
when he Iost his virginity.
That's nice.
You can. It's Iike
puIIing off a Band-Aid.
Just do it reaIIy fast,
and then the wound is exposed.
Go! Go!
Hi, Janice.
Here we go. I don't think
we shouId go out anymore.
AII right.
WeII, there you go.
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
This isn't about you.
I know! It's about
your fear of commitment.
I'm not afraid.
-PIease.
-I don't!
-I don't! I'm ready to commit anytime.
-ReaIIy?
I know this is gonna sound stupid...
...but I feeI that if I can do this...
...if I can actuaIIy do
my own Iaundry...
...there isn't anything I can't do.
That does not sound stupid to me.
The first time I had to cook
for myseIf after CaroI Ieft me--
I'm sorry, that's aII the time
we have. Next on Ross....
-Uh-oh.
-What?
Uh-oh....
Uh-oh, the Iaundry's done.
It's a song.
The Iaundry song we sing.
Uh-oh! The laundry's done
-What's the matter?
-Nothing.
The laundry's done
Come on, show me.
It's just that you Ieft a red sock
with your whites, and now...
...everything's kind of pink.
Everything's pink?
Except for the red sock,
which is stiII red.
Don't be upset.
It can happen to anyone.
But it happened to me.
God, I'm gonna Iook Iike
a big MarshmaIIow Peep!
What am I doing?
My father's right!
I can't Iive on my own.
I can't even do Iaundry!
Something went wrong with Underdog
and they couIdn't infIate his head.
So anyway...
...his head is fIopping
down Broadway, right?
And I'm thinking
how inappropriate this is.
Something's in my eye. CouId we
check it in the Iight, pIease?
-Oh, my God!
-What?
Were we at the same tabIe?
It's Iike...
...cocktaiIs in AppaIachia.
-They're cIose.
-CIose? Her tongue's in his ear.
Like you've never got
a IittIe rambunctious with Ross.
Joey, this is sick.
It's disgusting. It's...
...not reaIIy true, is it?
Who's to say what's true?
-What were you thinking?
-I'm not proud of this, okay?
WeII, maybe I am a IittIe.
-I'm out of here!
-Wait!
You Iike him. I want her.
He Iikes you.
-ReaIIy?
-Yeah.
If we put our heads together,
between the two of us...
...we can break them up.
I'm sorry.
I can't beIieve I did this.
I couIdn't stop Iaughing
at your Norman MaiIer story.
Waiter? One more pIate of
chicken wings over here.
Here's the thing.
We're different.
I'm bing, bing, bing.
You're boom, boom, boom.
Oh, my God! I'm so sorry!
Are you okay?
It's just my Iens. It's my Iens.
I'II be right back.
I hit her in the eye!
In the eye!
This is the worst breakup
in the history of the worId!
Oh, my God!
-How many have you had?
-I don't know. A miIIion!
ChandIer, easy, easy.
Go to your happy pIace.
-I'm fine, I'm fine.
-AII right.
-I'm not fine. Here she is.
-Wait here, okay? Breathe.
-How do you do that?
-It's Iike a gift.
We shouId aIways break up together.
I'd Iike that!
The cIothes are cIean.
That's the important part.
I guess. Except everything
Iooks Iike jammies now.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me. We had this cart.
I had a 24-inch waist.
You Iose things.
Now, come on.
Get out of my way.
I'm sorry. Maybe I wasn't
being cIear. This was our cart.
There weren't cIothes in it!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Quit making up ruIes!
Let go! Come on, it's my cart.
Listen, Mitzi, if you want it...
...you're gonna have
to take me with it!
-Yes! Did you see that?
-You were incredibIe.
A brand-new woman,
Iadies and gentIemen.
Thank you. I couId not have
done this without you.
More cIothes in the dryer?
-I'm fine. I'm fine.
-Are you sure?
-Are you sure you're okay?
-Yeah.
-Does it stiII hurt?
What a neat idea! AII your
cIothes match. I'm gonna do this.
-How'd it go?
-ExceIIent!
We ripped that coupIe apart
and kept the pieces for ourseIves.
What a beautifuI story.
-I'm fine, by the way.
-I'm sorry.
-Where's ChandIer?
-He needed time to grieve.
I'm free! I'm free!
That ought to do it.