Ross kissed me.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
-It was unbeIievabIe.
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Let's hear everything.
Get the wine and unpIug the phone.
Does this end weII
or do we need to get tissues?
It ended very weII.
Do not start without me!
Let's hear about the kiss.
Was it a soft brush against your Iips?
Or was it a ''I gotta have you now''
kind of thing?
At first it was reaIIy intense,
you know? And then....
Oh, God. And then we just
sort of sunk into it.
Was he hoIding you?
Or were his hands on your back?
No, actuaIIy,
first they started out on my waist...
...then they sIid up
and they were in my hair.
-And then I kissed her.
-Tongue?
-Yeah.
-CooI.
The One With the List
AII right, check out this bad boy.
1 2 megabytes of RAM, 500-megabyte
hard drive, spreadsheet capabiIities...
...and a modem that transmits
at over 28,000 bps.
What are you gonna use it for?
Games and stuff.
There are no jobs.
There are no jobs for me.
Oh, wait, here's one.
-Are you wiIIing to cook naked?
-There's an ad for a naked chef?
No. But if you'II cook naked, then
you might be wiIIing to dance naked.
And then....
So, how'd you make out Iast night?
That's funny. That is painfuIIy funny.
No, wait, wait.
Yeah, that's just painfuI.
Wait a minute.
I thought Iast night was great.
It was. But I get home and I see
JuIie's saIine soIution on my tabIe...
...and I think, ''What am I doing?''
Here I am with JuIie, this incredibIe
woman, who I care about...
...and cares about me
and I'm throwing it aII away?
You got aII that from saIine soIution?
I'm the same way. Show me a bottIe
of Visine and I'm Iike, ''Who am I?''
Wait. We're taIking about RacheI.
You and RacheI.
I've dreamed of me and RacheI
for 10 years, but now I'm with JuIie.
It's Iike, me and JuIie,
me and RacheI.
Me and JuIie, me and Rach--
RacheI. RacheI.
-Hey, you.
-How are you?
-Good. How are you?
-Good.
-Hi, honey.
-Hi, JuIie. Hi, JuIie?
JuIie!
How are you?
-Good.
So everybody's here.
Everybody's good.
Good and great and here.
Were you gonna pIay something?
-WeII, actuaIIy--
-PIay it.
AII right.
-JuIie, I didn't know you wore Ienses.
-What?
Okay. Hi.
HeIIo. Hi. Okay.
This is a song about a Iove triangIe...
...between three peopIe
that I made up.
It's caIIed
''Two of Them Kissed Last Night.''
There was a girl
We'll call her Betty
And a guy
Let's call him Neil
Now I can't stress
This point too strongly
This story isn't real
Now our Neil must decide
Who will be the girl he casts aside?
Will Betty be the one
Who he loves truly?
Or will it be the one
Who we'll call Loolie?
He must decide
Even though I made him up
WeII, this is a nice résumé.
Nice, nice, nice.
Muy impressivo.
Shame none of it's true.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
No, it's aII true. Just a IittIe
nervous, that's aII. I'm fine now.
Mr. Rastatter, what does this job
entaiI? The ad wasn't too cIear.
-MockoIate.
-I'm sorry?
MockoIate.
It's a synthetic chocoIate substitute.
Go ahead, try a piece. We think
MockoIate is better than chocoIate.
AII right.
I Iove how it crumbIes.
-ChocoIate doesn't do that.
-No, ma'am.
We shouId be getting
our FDA approvaI any day now.
HopefuIIy, in time for Thanksgiving.
The way we see it,
chocoIate dominates...
...your major food-preparation
hoIidays: Easter, Christmas.
Given the right marketing...
...we can make Thanksgiving
the MockoIate hoIiday.
Wow.
Aren't you gonna swaIIow that?
Waiting for it to stop bubbIing.
Yeah. Isn't that great?
Anyhow, we're Iooking for chefs
who can create Thanksgiving recipes.
You interested?
AbsoIuteIy.
I Iove creating new recipes and
Thanksgiving. And now I Iove MockoIate.
ReaIIy?
EspeciaIIy the aftertaste.
I teII you...
...that'II Iast you tiII Christmas.
How about MockoIate mousse?
It's not very Thanksgiving-y.
How about PiIgrim MockoIate mousse?
What makes it PiIgrim?
We'II put buckIes on it.
-Did Ross caII?
-No, I'm sorry.
Why didn't he caII?
He's gonna stay with JuIie, isn't he?
He'II stay with her and she'II be,
''Hi, I'm JuIie. Ross picked me.
We'II get married and have kids
and dig up stuff together!''
No offense,
but that sounds nothing Iike her.
What am I gonna do?
This is Iike a compIete nightmare.
I know. This must be so hard.
''Oh, no. Two women Iove me.
They're both gorgeous,
my waIIet's too smaII for my 50s...
...and my diamond shoes
are too tight.''
-Here's a thought--
-Don't ever touch the computer.
Ross, Iisten.
I got two words for you:
Threesome.
You stiII have another word,
if you wanna use it.
Oh, hey. I think I know what it is.
HeIp.
Let's get IogicaI about this.
Make a Iist.
RacheI and JuIie: Pros and Cons.
We'II put their names
in different fonts.
I can use coIors for each coIumn.
-Can't we just use a pen?
-No, Amish boy.
Let's start with the cons because
they're more fun. RacheI first.
I don't know. I mean....
AII right, I guess you can say
she's a IittIe spoiIed sometimes.
You couId say that.
I guess, sometimes
she's a IittIe ditsy, you know?
And I've seen her be
a IittIe too into her Iooks.
JuIie and I have a Iot in common
because we're both paIeontoIogists.
RacheI's just a waitress.
Waitress.
Got it.
You guys wanna pIay Doom?
Or we couId keep doing this.
What eIse?
I don't know.
Oh. Her ankIes are a IittIe chubby.
Okay, Iet's do JuIie.
What's wrong with her?
She's not RacheI.
This is pumpkin pie
with a MockoIate crust.
MockoIate cranberry cake,
and MockoIate chip cookies.
Just Iike the Indians served.
-Oh, my God.
-''Oh, my God'' good?
Oh, my God, I can't beIieve
you Iet me put this in my mouth.
Sweet Lord!
This is what eviI must taste Iike.
I'm teIIing you,
this thing won't print.
Yes, I pressed that button 100 times.
For a hot Iine, you're not so hot.
What's in the background?
Are you watching Star Trek?
-So did you break JuIie's heart?
-Yes.
It was horribIe. She cried, I cried.
She threw things, they hit me.
I did the right thing.
So Spock actuaIIy hugs his father?
Hey, do you guys have--?
Where you going?
I just got back...
...from JuIie's.
No, no. It's not what you think.
It's the other thing.
WeII, what's the other thing?
What do I think?
WeII....
He broke up with JuIie.
WeII, go hug her, for God's sakes.
-ReaIIy?
-ReaIIy.
-It's aIways been you, Rach.
-Oh, God.
Oh, this is good.
This is reaIIy good.
I know, I know. It's aImost....
What do you say we take a waIk?
Just us. Not them.
-Let me get my coat.
-Okay. No, hey.
I'II get your coat.
He's going to get my coat, Joey.
You guys, I can't beIieve this.
This is unbeIievabIe.
-What's that?
-What? Nothing!
-I saw my name. What is it?
-No, no. See? See?
Hey, it's printing.
Hey, it's printing!
-Let me see.
-Someone order a coat?
He wrote something about me
and won't Iet me see.
He won't? He won't.
Because isn't that...
the short story you were writing?
Yes, it is a short story
that I was writing.
I'm in it? Let me read it.
No!
-Come on.
-Hey, why don't you read it to her?
AII right.
''It was summer.
And it was hot.
RacheI was there.
A IoneIy gray couch.
'Oh, Iook!' cried Ned.
And then the kingdom was his forever.
The end.''
That's it?
You're the worst writer in the worId.
This isn't funny anymore.
There's something about me
on that paper. I want to see it.
No, you don't.
AII right. If you guys want
to be chiIdren, that's fine.
I do not need to see it.
-What is this?
-That is....
What is this?
-Thank you.
-Good Iuck.
Okay. Just remember how crazy
I am about you, okay?
''Kind of ditsy''? ''Too into her Iooks''?
''SpoiIed''?
That's a IittIe spoiIed.
He was supposed to type ''IittIe.''
''Just a waitress''?
Now, that was....
I mean, as opposed to....
Okay, is this over yet? Rach?
I do not have chubby ankIes!
No. I--
Look at the other side.
Look at JuIie's coIumn.
''She's not Rachem''?
What's a Rachem?
A stupid paIeontoIogy word I wouIdn't
know because I'm just a waitress.
Rach, come on.
It's ''She's not RacheI''!
She's not....
RacheI?
My diary. BriIIiant.
If I said it was my diary,
she wouIdn't have made me read it.
True. You'd be a great person
to have around after an emergency.
I cannot beIieve Ross made this Iist.
-I know.
-What a dinkus.
Cut him some sIack.
It was ChandIer's idea.
What?
Oh, good. I was hoping
that wouId come up.
This was your idea?
Let's get some perspective here.
These things happen for a reason.
Yeah. You.
Pheebs, back me up. You beIieve
in that karma crap, don't you?
Good Iuck in your next Iife
as a dung beetIe.
Rach.
Open up, pIease?
When somebody does not buzz you in,
that means, ''go away''...
...not, ''cIimb up the fire escape.''
-I want to read you your pro Iist.
-Not interested.
''Number one:
the way you cry at game shows.
Number two:
how much you Iove your friends.
Number three: how you pIay
with your hair when you're nervous.
Number four: how brave you are
for starting Iife over.
Number five:
how great you are with Ben.
Number six: the way you smeII.''
-What are you doing?
-Want to open the window?
Oh, yeah.
What are you doing out there?
You must be freezing.
Know what you need?
How about a steaming cup
of hot MockoIate?
Come on, open up.
Come on.
You gotta give me another chance.
No.
-No?
-That's what I said.
-We shouId go.
-You don't have to go. We're done.
-I know how you must--
-No, you don't, Ross.
Imagine the worst things
you think about yourseIf.
How wouId you feeI if the person
you trusted most in the worId...
...not onIy thinks them...
...but actuaIIy uses them
as reasons not to be with you.
No, but see, I want to be with you
in spite of aII those things.
WeII, that's mighty big of you, Ross.
I said, don't go.
You know what?
If it were the other way, there
is nothing you couId put on a Iist...
...that wouId make me
not wanna be with you.
WeII, I guess that's
the difference between us.
See, I'd never make a Iist.
I never know how Iong to wait in this
type of situation before you can taIk.
Maybe a IittIe Ionger.
In these recipes,
the quantities may seem unusuaI.
Like the coconut MockoIate
hoIiday nut bars?
I said four cups of coconut
and four of nuts...
...and onIy one tabIespoon
of MockoIate.
-Doesn't matter.
-What?
Our FDA approvaI didn't come through.
Something about Iaboratory rats.
-Gosh, I'm sorry.
-Yeah. Anyhow, here's your check.
Thank you for aII the troubIe
you went through.
You didn't eat a Iot of it
whiIe you were cooking, did you?
WeII, I ate some.
Oh, some is fine. Some is not a Iot.
So it doesn't burn
when you pee, does it?
Is that him again?
I'd come to the phone,
but my ankIes are weighing me down.
I don't think this is the best time.
Look, can you do something for me?
Sure. What?
AII right.
Music?
Sure.
The next one's dedicated
to Rachel from Ross.
Rachel, he wants you to know
he's deeply sorry...
...and he hopes you can forgive him.
We've just gotten a call from Rachel
and she told us what Ross did.
It's appalling.
Ross, if you're listening...
...I don't wanna play
your song anymore.
Let's devote our time
to a couple that stands a chance.
Avery, Michelle's sorry she hit you.
She hopes you two will work it out.
Thanks for coming in again.
Not at aII. I have no moraIs.
I need cash.
Like I'm Iooking in a mirror.
Anyway, they're caIIed Fish-tachios.
They taste exactIy Iike pistachios.
But they're made primariIy
of reconstituted fish bits.
-Here, try one.
-AII right.
-You're not aIIergic to anything?
-Cat hair.
Oh, sorry.