UgIy Naked Guy is decorating his tree.
And oh, my God, you shouId see
the size of his Christmas baIIs!
Hey. How much did
you guys tip the super?
We were gonna give 50
but we don't wanna Iook bad.
-This year we made him cookies.
-And 25 it is.
-You gave him cookies?
-Money is so impersonaI.
Cookies says someone reaIIy cares.
AII right, we're broke.
But cookies do say that.
I can see that. A pIate of brownies
once toId me a Iimerick.
Pheebs, Iet me ask you,
were these ''funny'' brownies?
Not especiaIIy.
But I think they had pot in them.
So who eIse did you tip with cookies?
The maiIman, the super....
And the newspaper deIivery guy.
Oh, my God.
-What?
-I don't think you're gonna Iike this.
There's a cookie smashed
to the sports section.
He did my crossword puzzIe.
Yeah, but not very weII, unIess
1 4 across, ''Gershwin musicaI''...
...actuaIIy is ''Bite me,
bite me, bite me.''
The One With Phoebe's Dad
I can't beIieve
it's Christmas aIready.
One day you're eating turkey,
the next thing you know...
...Iords are a-Ieaping
and geese are a-Iaying.
Which is why geese are
so reIaxed this time of year.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
Hey, Rach.
I got you a IittIe present.
I'II open it.
It's a SIinky! Remember?
Walks downstairs
Alone or in pairs
Everyone knows it's--
Just a big spring.
-You're stiII mad because of the--
-List of reasons not to be with me?
How about we just caII it
the ''unfortunate incident''?
Gunther, you got stairs in your pIace?
-Yeah.
-Go nuts.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
-What's in the bag?
-Just some presents.
Come on, show us what you bought.
You know you want to.
Okay.
This is a picture frame
from Ben to my parents.
Oh, that's cute.
Some ''Hers'' and ''Hers'' toweIs
for Susan and CaroI.
And I got this bIouse for Mom.
Ross, that is gorgeous!
Look at these authentic fake medaIs!
Mom's gonna be voted ''Best Dressed''
at the make-beIieve miIitary academy.
-Happy ''Christmas Eve Eve.''
-You too.
Oh, my God!
Where did you get this?
Macy's, third fIoor,
Home Furnishings.
This is my father!
This is a picture of my dad.
That's the guy
that comes in the frame.
No, it's my dad.
I'II show you.
-I thought your dad was in prison.
-No, that's my stepdad.
My reaI dad's the one that
ran out on us before I was born.
How have you never been on Oprah?
Look, see? This is him.
My mother gave me this picture
before she died. Same guy!
It's a picture of the frame guy posing
in front of a bIue screen with a dog.
It's not a bIue screen.
It's just....
Maybe it was just
reaIIy cIear that day.
Okay, I have to taIk
to my grandmother.
-Wait a minute, honey.
-Pheebs!
So I'm trying to get my boss' ex-wife
to sIeep with me.
Joey!
But when Phoebe has a probIem,
everyone's aII ears.
Esther Livingston.
Gone!
Hi, Pooh.
Hi, Gram. What you doing?
Just updating the phone book.
Gram? Can I see the pictures
of my dad again?
Oh. Oh, sure, sure.
-How come?
-Just, you know, to see him.
Sure. Yeah.
This is the one
of your father in a meadow.
And heIping a IittIe boy fIy a kite.
And here he is at a graduation.
Another graduation.
Is this reaIIy my father?
Is it reaIIy your fa--?
WeII, of course it is.
I smeII smoke. Maybe because
someone's pants are on fire!
AII the time we've been
grandmother and granddaughter...
...you've never Iied to me.
AII right, that's not your father.
It's a picture of a guy in a frame.
Oh, God.
It was your mother's idea.
She didn't want you to know your reaI
father because he hurt her so much.
I didn't want to do it.
But then she died
and it was harder to argue with her.
Not impossibIe, but harder.
AII right. So he's not
a famous tree surgeon?
And I guess he doesn't Iive in a hut
in Burma where there's no phones?
Last I heard, he was
a pharmacist somewhere upstate.
That makes no sense. Why wouId
the viIIagers worship a pharmacist?
Honey.
Oh. Yeah.
Anyway, that's aII I know.
That...
...and this.
This...
...is the reaI him.
I remember my father dressed
in the red suit, the bIack boots...
...and the patent Ieather beIt,
sneaking around.
He didn't want us to see
but he'd be drunk...
...so he'd crash into something
and wake everyone.
That doesn't sound Iike
a very merry Christmas.
Who said anything about Christmas?
-Hi.
-Anyone hear from Phoebe yet?
No, nothing.
-I hope she's okay.
-I know what she's going through.
How do you know that?
She toId us.
-What you got there, Monica?
-Party stuff.
Aren't you guys supposed
to be shopping?
You didn't buy presents? Tomorrow's
Christmas Eve! What are you gonna do?
Don't you have to be CIaymation
to say stuff Iike that?
I don't think the maiIman
Iiked your cookies.
Here are the ornaments your mom sent.
Maybe the maiIman Iiked them.
We just didn't give him enough.
Monica, pigeons Iearn faster than you.
Hey, Rach. I think I know
what wiII make you feeI better.
How about you make a Iist about me?
Forget it. I'm not gonna stand here
and make a Iist--
Okay, you're whiny...
...you are obsessive.
You are insecure. You're gutIess.
You never just seize the day.
You Iiked me for a year
and you didn't do anything about it.
And you wear too much
of that geI in your hair.
See, there, you....
AII right, you did what I said.
And you know what? You're right.
I do feeI better. Thank you, Ross.
Yeah, in AIbany. CouId I have
the number of Frank Buffay?
Okay. In Ithaca?
AII right, Saratoga?
Oneonta?
You know what? You shouIdn't
caII yourseIf ''Information''!
HeIIo, Grandma. If that is,
in fact, your reaI name.
Come on now, Pooh.
Don't stiII be mad at me.
-How's it going?
-Not so good.
Upstate's pretty big.
He's pretty smaII. You do the math.
WeII, I think you're better off
without him.
Honey, I know he's your daddy.
But to me,
he's stiII the irresponsibIe creep...
...who Iocked up your mom
and stoIe her GremIin.
I know. I just wanted to know
who he was, you know?
Yeah, I know.
Okay. I wasn't compIeteIy honest
with you when I said I didn't know...
...exactIy where he Iived.
What do you mean?
He Iives at 74 LaureI Drive
in MiddIetown.
If you hit the Dairy Queen, you've
gone too far. You can take my cab.
Wow! Thank you.
Remember, nobody eIse drives that cab.
Got it.
Oh, I'm gonna see my dad!
Thank you.
Wish me Iuck, Grandpa.
Phoebe here with the cab yet?
Yeah, she brought the invisibIe cab.
Hop in!
She'd better come.
The stores cIose at 7.
It'II be two hours to Phoebe's dad's
house. They'II meet, swap stories.
Even if she teIIs the one where she's
an Egyptian sIave, we'II have time.
-Hey, here she comes!
-Hey.
Can you beIieve this?
In two hours I'm gonna have a dad.
-Yeah, big stuff!
-Okay, Iet's go!
Here, you have to hoId this.
''Brake Ieft, gas right''?
Yeah, that's my cheat sheet.
-Where's my seat beIt?
-There isn't one.
The paramedics had to cut through it.
Come on, just teII me.
PIease, pIease!
For the 1 6th time:
No, I do not think you're obsessive!
It's hot in here!
Rach, get the heat.
Ross, turn the heat down, pIease?
-The difference between obsessive--
-Ross, the heat!
Okay! Heat, heat, heat!
And I'm the obsessive one?
Okay. This way is on.
So this is...
...off.
-Did you just break the radiator?
-No, I was turning the knob and...
...here it is.
WeII, put it back!
-It won't go back.
-I'II caII the super.
Here, Iet me try.
That's right. I forgot about
your abiIity to fuse metaI.
Hey, it's Funny's cousin, Not Funny!
Hi, Mr. Treeger?
It's RacheI Greene from upstairs.
Yes, somebody broke our knob
on the radiator...
...and it's reaIIy hot in here.
Yes, it's hot enough to bake cookies.
Do you think we couId
have a new one by 6?
Tuesday? We can't wait untiI then.
We're having a party tonight.
Okay, tip the man.
If he doesn't Iike our cookies,
too bad! I won't be bIackmaiIed.
Look, if it gets a IittIe warm,
it can be a theme party.
Here's a theme:
''Come on in! Live Iike bacon!''
This is it, 74!
Oh, so that's what this is for.
This is it. I'm gonna meet my dad.
-This is Iike the biggest thing ever.
-Sure is.
Okay, here I go. I'm going in.
-AII right!
-Good Iuck, Pheebs.
Okay. Here I go.
Here I go.
I'm going.
Hi. WeIcome to our tropicaI
Christmas party.
You can put your coats, sweaters,
pants and shirts in the bedroom.
It's hard to teII because I'm sweating
but I use what the geI bottIe says.
An amount about the size of a pea.
How can that be too much?
Ice?
Ice? Ice squares anyone?
Take a napkin. AII right.
Monica!
Monica, your guests
are turning into jerky.
ReaIIy? I'm perfectIy comfortabIe.
Hey! Get in Iine, buddy.
I was next.
-Mr. Treeger.
-You said there was a party.
Oh. Yeah.
WeII, hey, weIcome to our sauna.
Is it hot?
My body aIways stays cooI.
ProbabIy because I have so much skin.
Hey, cheese!
Here's the chance.
Monica, give him cash.
RacheI, give him your earrings.
Anything!
-No, I wiII not cave.
-I'm with Mon.
AII right. You know how you say
I never seize the day?
Even though he's your super,
I'm seizing.
Mr. Treeger?
Here is $50. Merry Christmas.
Oh, wow. I didn't get you anything.
Here's five back.
No, that's your Christmas tip.
Do you think there's a chance
you can fix that radiator now?
No can do. Like I toId the girI,
I can't get a knob untiI Tuesday.
Ross?
Looks Iike he's pIaying basebaII.
You mean hardbaII?
Whatever.
-Whatcha gonna do?
-Excuse me. I'm seizing.
Mr. Treeger?
Here's another 50.
Happy Hanukkah.
WiII this heIp with the knob-getting?
No, the pIace is not open
tiII Tuesday.
Am I not saying it right?
So you reaIIy did Iike my cookies?
Yeah, they were so personaI.
It reaIIy showed you cared.
Nice seizing...
...geI boy.
So is this mistIetoe?
No, that....
That is basiI.
If it was mistIetoe,
I was gonna kiss you.
No, it's stiII basiI.
Okay.
-How far did you get?
-MaiIbox.
AII right, we're getting cIoser.
What's going on?
It's just Iike a whoIe mess of stuff.
Like yesterday, my dad was this
famous Burma tree-surgeon guy.
And you know, now he's
a pharmacist guy and....
WeII, maybe he's this
reaIIy cooI pharmacist guy.
Yeah, maybe!
And I'II knock on the door...
...and he'II hug me
and I'II have a dad!
I'II go to his pharmacy and
everyone wiII be nice to me...
...because, you know,
I'm Frank's daughter.
So why not go knock?
Because, I mean, what if
he's not this great-dad guy?
What if he's stiII the dirt-bag
who ran out on my mom and us?
Yeah.
You know what?
I've aIready Iost
a fake dad this week.
I don't think I'm ready
to Iose a reaI one.
Pheebs, that's okay.
You took a big step today.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Someday, when you're ready,
you'II make it past the hedges.
And when you do,
he'II be Iucky to have you.
You guys....
Sorry about your shopping.
Oh, that's okay.
We'II figure something out.
I know you're not going in there...
...but wouId it be okay if I went in
and used his bathroom?
That's fine, never mind.
CooI, snow!
Kind of Iike a bIank canvas.
Ho-ho-ho-hoIy crap,
is it hot in here!
Mind if I turn the heat down?
We couId have used
that kind of thinking earIier!
So, Pheebs, how did it go?
Oh, I couIdn't go in.
-Honey, I'm sorry.
-Are you okay?
Yeah, it's okay
because I know he's there.
So that's enough for now.
It's after midnight!
Merry Christmas, everyone!
Oh, right! Merry Christmas!
The knob was broken so I turned it off
from underneath. I hope that's okay.
Thanks.
I guess that just Ieaves the gifts
from Joey and ChandIer.
Rach, these are for you.
Wiper bIades!
I don't even have a car.
No, but with this new-car smeII,
you'II think you do!
Okay, Pheebs, your turn.
ToiIet-seat covers!
Is that what you were doing
whiIe I was getting gas? You guys!
And for Ross...
...Mr. Sweet Tooth.
You got me a coIa drink?
And a Iemon-Iime!
WeII, this is too much! I feeI Iike
I shouId get you another sweater.
And Iast but not Ieast....
They're ribbed for your pIeasure!