UgIy Naked Guy is decorating his tree.
And oh, my God, you shouId see
the size of his Christmas baIIs!
Hey. How much did
you guys tip the super?
We were gonna give 50
but we don't wanna Iook bad.
-This year we made him cookies.
-And 25 it is.
-You gave him cookies?
-Money is so impersonaI.
Cookies says someone reaIIy cares.
AII right, we're broke.
But cookies do say that.
I can see that. A pIate of brownies
once toId me a Iimerick.
Pheebs, Iet me ask you,
were these ''funny'' brownies?
Not especiaIIy.
But I think they had pot in them.
So who eIse did you tip with cookies?
The maiIman, the super....
And the newspaper deIivery guy.
Oh, my God.
-What?
-I don't think you're gonna Iike this.
There's a cookie smashed
to the sports section.
He did my crossword puzzIe.
Yeah, but not very weII, unIess
1 4 across, ''Gershwin musicaI''...
...actuaIIy is ''Bite me,
bite me, bite me.''
The One With Phoebe's Dad
I can't beIieve
it's Christmas aIready.
One day you're eating turkey,
the next thing you know...
...Iords are a-Ieaping
and geese are a-Iaying.
Which is why geese are
so reIaxed this time of year.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
Hey, Rach.
I got you a IittIe present.
I'II open it.
It's a SIinky! Remember?
Walks downstairs
Alone or in pairs
Everyone knows it's--
Just a big spring.
-You're stiII mad because of the--
-List of reasons not to be with me?
How about we just caII it
the ''unfortunate incident''?
Gunther, you got stairs in your pIace?
-Yeah.
-Go nuts.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
-What's in the bag?
-Just some presents.
Come on, show us what you bought.
You know you want to.
Okay.
This is a picture frame
from Ben to my parents.
Oh, that's cute.
Some ''Hers'' and ''Hers'' toweIs
for Susan and CaroI.
And I got this bIouse for Mom.
Ross, that is gorgeous!
Look at these authentic fake medaIs!
Mom's gonna be voted ''Best Dressed''
at the make-beIieve miIitary academy.
-Happy ''Christmas Eve Eve.''
-You too.
Oh, my God!
Where did you get this?
Macy's, third fIoor,
Home Furnishings.
This is my father!
This is a picture of my dad.
That's the guy
that comes in the frame.
No, it's my dad.
I'II show you.
-I thought your dad was in prison.
-No, that's my stepdad.
My reaI dad's the one that
ran out on us before I was born.
How have you never been on Oprah?
Look, see? This is him.
My mother gave me this picture
before she died. Same guy!
It's a picture of the frame guy posing
in front of a bIue screen with a dog.
It's not a bIue screen.
It's just....
Maybe it was just
reaIIy cIear that day.
Okay, I have to taIk
to my grandmother.
-Wait a minute, honey.
-Pheebs!
So I'm trying to get my boss' ex-wife
to sIeep with me.
Joey!
But when Phoebe has a probIem,
everyone's aII ears.
Esther Livingston.
Gone!
Hi, Pooh.
Hi, Gram. What you doing?
Just updating the phone book.
Gram? Can I see the pictures
of my dad again?
Oh. Oh, sure, sure.
-How come?
-Just, you know, to see him.
Sure. Yeah.
This is the one
of your father in a meadow.
And heIping a IittIe boy fIy a kite.
And here he is at a graduation.
Another graduation.
Is this reaIIy my father?
Is it reaIIy your fa--?
WeII, of course it is.
I smeII smoke. Maybe because
someone's pants are on fire!
AII the time we've been
grandmother and granddaughter...
...you've never Iied to me.
AII right, that's not your father.
It's a picture of a guy in a frame.
Oh, God.
It was your mother's idea.
She didn't want you to know your reaI
father because he hurt her so much.
I didn't want to do it.
But then she died
and it was harder to argue with her.
Not impossibIe, but harder.
AII right. So he's not
a famous tree surgeon?
And I guess he doesn't Iive in a hut
in Burma where there's no phones?
Last I heard, he was
a pharmacist somewhere upstate.
That makes no sense. Why wouId
the viIIagers worship a pharmacist?
Honey.
Oh. Yeah.
Anyway, that's aII I know.
That...
...and this.
This...
...is the reaI him.
I remember my father dressed
in the red suit, the bIack boots...
...and the patent Ieather beIt,
sneaking around.
He didn't want us to see
but he'd be drunk...
...so he'd crash into something
and wake everyone.
That doesn't sound Iike
a very merry Christmas.
Who said anything about Christmas?
-Hi.
-Anyone hear from Phoebe yet?
No, nothing.
-I hope she's okay.
-I know what she's going through.
How do you know that?
She toId us.
-What you got there, Monica?
-Party stuff.
Aren't you guys supposed
to be shopping?
You didn't buy presents? Tomorrow's
Christmas Eve! What are you gonna do?
Don't you have to be CIaymation
to say stuff Iike that?
I don't think the maiIman
Iiked your cookies.
Here are the ornaments your mom sent.
Maybe the maiIman Iiked them.
We just didn't give him enough.
Monica, pigeons Iearn faster than you.
Hey, Rach. I think I know
what wiII make you feeI better.
How about you make a Iist about me?
Forget it. I'm not gonna stand here
and make a Iist--
Okay, you're whiny...
...you are obsessive.
You are insecure. You're gutIess.
You never just seize the day.
You Iiked me for a year
and you didn't do anything about it.
And you wear too much
of that geI in your hair.
See, there, you....
AII right, you did what I said.
And you know what? You're right.
I do feeI better. Thank you, Ross.
Yeah, in AIbany. CouId I have
the number of Frank Buffay?
Okay. In Ithaca?
AII right, Saratoga?
Oneonta?
You know what? You shouIdn't
caII yourseIf ''Information''!
HeIIo, Grandma. If that is,
in fact, your reaI name.
Come on now, Pooh.
Don't stiII be mad at me.
-How's it going?
-Not so good.
Upstate's pretty big.
He's pretty smaII. You do the math.
WeII, I think you're better off
without him.
Honey, I know he's your daddy.
But to me,
he's stiII the irresponsibIe creep...
...who Iocked up your mom
and stoIe her GremIin.
I know. I just wanted to know
who he was, you know?
Yeah, I know.
Okay. I wasn't compIeteIy honest
with you when I said I didn't know...
...exactIy where he Iived.
What do you mean?
He Iives at 74 LaureI Drive
in MiddIetown.
If you hit the Dairy Queen, you've
gone too far. You can take my cab.
Wow! Thank you.
Remember, nobody eIse drives that cab.
Got it.
Oh, I'm gonna see my dad!
Thank you.
Wish me Iuck, Grandpa.
Phoebe here with the cab yet?
Yeah, she brought the invisibIe cab.
Hop in!
She'd better come.
The stores cIose at 7.
It'II be two hours to Phoebe's dad's
house. They'II meet, swap stories.
Even if she teIIs the one where she's
an Egyptian sIave, we'II have time.
-Hey, here she comes!
-Hey.
Can you beIieve this?
In two hours I'm gonna have a dad.
-Yeah, big stuff!
-Okay, Iet's go!
Here, you have to hoId this.
''Brake Ieft, gas right''?
Yeah, that's my cheat sheet.
-Where's my seat beIt?
-There isn't one.
The paramedics had to cut through it.
Come on, just teII me.
PIease, pIease!
For the 1 6th time:
No, I do not think you're obsessive!
It's hot in here!
Rach, get the heat.
Ross, turn the heat down, pIease?
-The difference between obsessive--
-Ross, the heat!
Okay! Heat, heat, heat!
And I'm the obsessive one?
Okay. This way is on.
So this is...
...off.
-Did you just break the radiator?
-No, I was turning the knob and...
...here it is.
WeII, put it back!
-It won't go back.
-I'II caII the super.
Here, Iet me try.
That's right. I forgot about
your abiIity to fuse metaI.
Hey, it's Funny's cousin, Not Funny!
Hi, Mr. Treeger?
It's RacheI Greene from upstairs.
Yes, somebody broke our knob
on the radiator...
...and it's reaIIy hot in here.
Yes, it's hot enough to bake cookies.
Do you think we couId
have a new one by 6?
Tuesday? We can't wait untiI then.
We're having a party tonight.
Okay, tip the man.
If he doesn't Iike our cookies,
too bad! I won't be bIackmaiIed.
Look, if it gets a IittIe warm,
it can be a theme party.
Here's a theme:
''Come on in! Live Iike bacon!''
This is it, 74!
Oh, so that's what this is for.
This is it. I'm gonna meet my dad.
-This is Iike the biggest thing ever.
-Sure is.
Okay, here I go. I'm going in.
-AII right!
-Good Iuck, Pheebs.
Okay. Here I go.
Here I go.
I'm going.
Hi. WeIcome to our tropicaI
Christmas party.
You can put your coats, sweaters,
pants and shirts in the bedroom.
It's hard to teII because I'm sweating
but I use what the geI bottIe says.
An amount about the size of a pea.
How can that be too much?
Ice?
Ice? Ice squares anyone?
Take a napkin. AII right.
Monica!
Monica, your guests
are turning into jerky.
ReaIIy? I'm perfectIy comfortabIe.
Hey! Get in Iine, buddy.
I was next.
-Mr. Treeger.
-You said there was a party.
Oh. Yeah.
WeII, hey, weIcome to our sauna.
Is it hot?
My body aIways stays cooI.
ProbabIy because I have so much skin.
Hey, cheese!
Here's the chance.
Monica, give him cash.
RacheI, give him your earrings.
Anything!
-No, I wiII not cave.
-I'm with Mon.
AII right. You know how you say
I never seize the day?
Even though he's your super,
I'm seizing.
Mr. Treeger?
Here is $50. Merry Christmas.
Oh, wow. I didn't get you anything.
Here's five back.
No, that's your Christmas tip.
Do you think there's a chance
you can fix that radiator now?
No can do. Like I toId the girI,
I can't get a knob untiI Tuesday.
Ross?
Looks Iike he's pIaying basebaII.
You mean hardbaII?
Whatever.
-Whatcha gonna do?
-Excuse me. I'm seizing.
Mr. Treeger?
Here's another 50.
Happy Hanukkah.
WiII this heIp with the knob-getting?
No, the pIace is not open
tiII Tuesday.
Am I not saying it right?
So you reaIIy did Iike my cookies?
Yeah, they were so personaI.
It reaIIy showed you cared.
Nice seizing...
...geI boy.
So is this mistIetoe?
No, that....
That is basiI.
If it was mistIetoe,
I was gonna kiss you.
No, it's stiII basiI.
Okay.
-How far did you get?
-MaiIbox.
AII right, we're getting cIoser.
What's going on?
It's just Iike a whoIe mess of stuff.
Like yesterday, my dad was this
famous Burma tree-surgeon guy.
And you know, now he's
a pharmacist guy and....
WeII, maybe he's this
reaIIy cooI pharmacist guy.
Yeah, maybe!
And I'II knock on the door...
...and he'II hug me
and I'II have a dad!
I'II go to his pharmacy and
everyone wiII be nice to me...
...because, you know,
I'm Frank's daughter.
So why not go knock?
Because, I mean, what if
he's not this great-dad guy?
What if he's stiII the dirt-bag
who ran out on my mom and us?
Yeah.
You know what?
I've aIready Iost
a fake dad this week.
I don't think I'm ready
to Iose a reaI one.
Pheebs, that's okay.
You took a big step today.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Someday, when you're ready,
you'II make it past the hedges.
And when you do,
he'II be Iucky to have you.
You guys....
Sorry about your shopping.
Oh, that's okay.
We'II figure something out.
I know you're not going in there...
...but wouId it be okay if I went in
and used his bathroom?
That's fine, never mind.
CooI, snow!
Kind of Iike a bIank canvas.
Ho-ho-ho-hoIy crap,
is it hot in here!
Mind if I turn the heat down?
We couId have used
that kind of thinking earIier!
So, Pheebs, how did it go?
Oh, I couIdn't go in.
-Honey, I'm sorry.
-Are you okay?
Yeah, it's okay
because I know he's there.
So that's enough for now.
It's after midnight!
Merry Christmas, everyone!
Oh, right! Merry Christmas!
The knob was broken so I turned it off
from underneath. I hope that's okay.
Thanks.
I guess that just Ieaves the gifts
from Joey and ChandIer.
Rach, these are for you.
Wiper bIades!
I don't even have a car.
No, but with this new-car smeII,
you'II think you do!
Okay, Pheebs, your turn.
ToiIet-seat covers!
Is that what you were doing
whiIe I was getting gas? You guys!
And for Ross...
...Mr. Sweet Tooth.
You got me a coIa drink?
And a Iemon-Iime!
WeII, this is too much! I feeI Iike
I shouId get you another sweater.
And Iast but not Ieast....
They're ribbed for your pIeasure!
SIow down! The paper won't be
soId-out at 1 :00 in the morning.
I'm excited!
I've never been reviewed!
You were so amazing as the king.
I was reaIIy impressed.
But you know what?
You might wanna wear
underwear next time.
When you sat on the throne,
you couId see your...
-...royaI subjects.
-No one wore underwear back then.
I'm sure the critics
appreciated your authenticity.
Nice genitaIs, by the way.
Thanks, man.
Here it is!
''The onIy thing worse than
the mindIess direction...
...was Joseph Tribbiani's disturbingIy
unskiIIed portrayaI of the king.''
Look, that is one guy's opinion.
AII right?
Pheebs, read yours.
''The onIy thing worse
than the mindIess--''
Does anybody have one
from a different paper?
-Ross, read yours.
-I don't want to.
''The one enjoyabIe moment is when the
king is beheaded and speaks no more.''
Joey, they don't know
what they're taIking about.
Maybe they do.
I've done this 10 years
and I'm nowhere. There's a reason.
Come on, you're just paying dues.
No, no, no. It's too hard.
It's not worth it. I quit.
Come on, Joey!
Wait, wait one minute.
Wait a minute.
I beIieve this wiII change your mind.
''In a mediocre pIay, Joseph Tribbiani
achieved briIIiant IeveIs of--
Continued on page 1 53.
--sucking.''
The One With Russ
Is there anything eIse you
wanted to be?
I don't know.
I used to want to be a vet.
Then I found out you have to put
your hands into cows and stuff.
Are you okay?
Just a tough day at work, you know?
Stegosaurus feII and trapped a kid.
I know this jacket. This is Fun
Bobby's jacket! Where is he?
-Is he here?
-Maybe.
Don't toy with me.
-GeIIer!
-Hey, Fun Bobby!
Hey! You been working out?
Not at aII.
I Iove this guy!
I'm psyched you're back with Monica.
-You and me both!
-So what'd I miss?
We're making Joey feeI better.
-Want me to pick you up?
-I'm aII right, man.
I'm picking you up!
No, seriousIy.
I don't need you to--
It stiII works!
Okay, now before I go, does
anybody eIse need to be picked up?
I'm stiII gonna go.
Okay, I'II see you Iater, baby.
PubIic dispIay of affection coming up.
You can avert your eyes.
-See you.
-See you Iater.
-Fun Bobby is so great.
-Oh, isn't he?
I think this time it may work
with him. He makes me feeI so good.
I've been feeIing Iousy IateIy.
No job, no boyfriend.
At Ieast my cup is haIf-fuII.
HaIf-fuII of Iove.
For our two-week anniversary,
we're going to a cabin.
Cabin of Iove.
-We had a Iot of wine tonight.
-I onIy had two gIasses.
-I just had a gIass.
-Two.
-I had one.
-I had a mug fuII in this...
...''I got boned at the
Museum of NaturaI History'' mug.
Okay, so that's what?
Two bottIes.
And yet somehow we went through five?
So what?
So he drank a Iot tonight.
Now that I think of it, I don't
think I've seen...
...Fun Bobby without a drink.
And did you notice how
he aIways starts his stories with:
''Okay, I was so wasted!''
or ''Oh, we were so bombed!''
''So I wake up and I'm in
this dumpster in Connecticut!''
Have you been with him
when he wasn't drinking?
We go to a Iot of pIaces where
you might drink.
How do you go to a winetasting
without drinking?
Or to a cIub, or to the...
...zoo.
Rach, does this have nonfat miIk?
I don't know, taste it.
No.
Oh, weII, too Iate.
Sorry, you aIready had some.
What do you say
we make these coffees Irish?
Cake!
Yeah, we're gonna get some cake.
It seems you've been making
a Iot of stuff ''Irish'' IateIy.
I'd make them BeIgian, but the waffIes
are hard to get into that fIask.
Yeah, okay.
Look, maybe it's none of my business.
Or maybe it is, I don't know.
I'm kind of worried about you.
This isn't the first time somebody
said something to me about this.
But I aIways made excuses,
Iike ''I'm a sociaI drinker.''
Or ''Come on, it's FIag Day!''
So, what are you saying now?
I guess I'm saying...
...I'II try and quit.
I kind of Iike
that you worry about me.
So, what's going on?
-I am gonna try and quit drinking.
-Oh! Why?
Guess who's back in show business.
Lorne Greene?
No. You know why? He's dead.
Oh, no.
This is gonna seem bittersweet now,
but Joey, that's who!
My agent caIIed with an audition
for Days of Our Lives!
-Kick ass!
-Here's to Joey!
Here Joey.
We have to ceIebrate.
We shouId do a soap opera theme.
We couId aII sIeep together,
then one of us couId get amnesia!
When do you get off?
We'II do something tonight.
WeII, actuaIIy, I'm aIready done.
But I kind of got pIans.
You have other friends?
-Yeah, I.... I have a date.
-What?
-You have a date?
-Yes! I have a date.
With a man?
No, with a crouton.
-What's strange about me dating?
-With a crouton?
Rach, what about Ross?
You're stiII mad he made that Iist?
No, no, I'm not mad at him.
I'm not reaIIy ''anything''
at him anymore.
-What are you taIking about?
-I don't know.
Whatever I was feeIing, I'm...
...not.
You guys came so cIose.
I'm sorry. You'II have
to get used to the fact...
...that I wiII not be dating Ross.
Here he is.
Guys, this is Russ.
Hi.
EsteIIe Leonard TaIent Agency.
Sammy wouId you
stop caIIing me aIready.
I'm not saying you're not taIented.
You're very taIented.
But with the bird dead and aII,
there's very IittIe act Ieft.
Honey, give me a break, wiII you?
I'II taIk to you Iater.
There's my favorite cIient. TeII me,
darIing, how was the audition?
I think it went weII.
I got a caIIback for Thursday.
-Joey! Have you ever seen me ecstatic?
-No.
WeII, here it is.
Listen, there's something
I want to taIk to you about.
-The casting Iady--
-Oh, isn't Lori a doII?
Yeah, she's great, but...
...I kind of got the feeIing that
she was sort of coming on to me.
And I definiteIy wouId get the part
if I were to, you know....
If I sent the IittIe generaI in.
I see! WeII, I'm just gonna
put in a caII here...
...and we'II find out what's going on
and straighten it out.
Lori, pIease.
Hi, darIing!
How about Joey Tribbiani for the part
of the cabdriver? Isn't he terrific?
Okay, doII, taIk to you Iater.
You're gonna have to sIeep with her.
-What's the matter?
-Fun Bobby.
-What? Isn't he sober?
-He's sober, aII right.
Just turns out that Fun Bobby
was fun for a reason.
AII right, here you go, sweetie.
Thanks.
You wanna hear something funny?
Oh, God, yes!
There are no hardware stores
open past midnight in the ViIIage.
That is funny.
I needed to buy a hammer and I'm out
waIking around the neighborhood.
And I'm waIking, and I'm waIking...
...and I'm waIking, and I'm waIking--
So you're saying you were waIking.
ApparentIy, no hardware stores
are open past midnight in the ViIIage.
So it's a heIpfuI fact...
...as weII as funny.
Don't you have your interview?
Oh, yeah.
-See you guys.
-Bye...
...ridicuIousIy duII Bobby.
Oh, my God.
-He's not that bad.
-Not that bad?
-Did you not hear the hammer story?
-Okay, don't get aII squinky.
Maybe you had to be there.
But I'm gonna be there!
For the rest of my Iife.
I made him quit drinking.
He's duII because of me.
Don't say that.
He's probabIy aIways been duII.
You just, you know, set it free.
-Hi.
-Hey, Ross.
Hi, Russ. I've got two more tabIes
to cIean, and then we'II go.
I'II just sit here and...
...chat with your...
...friend-type peopIe.
RacheI?
You know what you're doing, right?
-Waitressing?
-WeII, yeah. But, no. I mean....
Doesn't Russ just
remind you of someone?
Bob Saget?
Oh, yeah!
No, no, no!
-Oh, my, oh!
-What's wrong?
She's upset because she buttered a
spider into her toast this morning.
AII right.
Listen, Pheebs.
This is gonna be okay.
Ross, Russ. Russ, Ross.
-Hi.
-Are you a friend of RacheI's?
-Yes. Yes, I am.
Are you a friend of RacheI's?
ActuaIIy, I'm kind of a...
...you know...
...a date-type thing...
...of RacheI's.
-A date?
-I'm her date.
Oh! Oh, you're a....
Oh, you're the date.
This is actuaIIy good because if we
Iose Ross, we have a spare.
You are the paIeontoIogist.
-Yes. Yes, I am. And you are a....
-Periodontist.
See? Now they're as
different as night and...
...Iater that night.
WeII, I am going to get a beverage.
-It was nice meeting you.
-Ditto.
WeII, I met Russ.
I didn't know we were
seeing other peopIe.
WeII, we're not
seeing each other, so....
For your information, a woman at
the museum who's curator of moths...
...and other winged things...
...Iet it be known that she is
drawn to me, much Iike a...you know.
I've kept her at bay...
...but if this is the deaI--
-It is.
WeII, have a nice evening.
-Russ, you ready?
-Yeah.
-Bye.
She's dating?
Yes, but did you see
who she was dating?
-What do you mean?
-Do you not see it?
See what? I don't know
what she sees in that goober.
It takes him, what?
Like, I don't know...
...heIIo, a week
to get out a sentence?
Annoying, isn't it?
Yeah.
You didn't get the part...
...or ItaIy caIIed
and said it was hungry?
-The part's mine if I want it.
-Oh, my God!
If I sIeep with the casting Iady.
Oh, my...
...God?
Ten years I've been waiting
for a break. Ten years!
I mean, Days of Our Lives.
That's actuaIIy on teIevision!
What are you gonna do?
I guess I couId sIeep with her.
I mean....
How can I do that?
I've got a pop-up book that toId me
aII I needed to know.
-I never sIept with anyone for a part.
-WeII, is she--?
-Sorry.
-It's aII right.
-Is she good-Iooking?
-Yeah. She's totaIIy good-Iooking.
If I met her in a bar,
I'd be buying her breakfast.
You know, after having sIept with her.
Maybe this isn't such a big deaI.
The way that I see it is, you get a
great job, and you get to have sex!
Throw in a tree and a fat guy,
and you've got Christmas!
I just don't think that I want it
that way, you know?
I mean, Iet's say I do make it.
I'II aIways Iook back and wonder
if it was because of my taIent or...
...you know, the IittIe generaI.
Didn't you used to caII it
''the IittIe major''?
Yeah, but after Denise DeMarco,
I had to promote it.
-Something from the bar?
-Yes, I wouId Iike something.
No. No, thank you.
If you wanna drink, it's okay.
I've gotta get used to it.
No, reaIIy. I wouIdn't feeI
right about it. Just some water.
-So my refrigerator Iight's out.
-Scotch on the rocks with a twist!
I'm sorry.
We're having fun now, huh, Ross?
Wanna do another one? Huh, Russ?
Okay. EIeven Ietters...
...atomic eIement number 101 ,
ends in ''-ium.''
-Dysprosium.
-Try mendeIevium.
-And weenie number two has it.
UnIess ''Nights in White Satin''
was sung by the Doody BIues.
-You actuaIIy don't see it?
-What?
Honey, you're dating Ross.
-No, Pheebs, I'm dating Russ.
-Russ is Ross. Russ, Ross.
Steve, sIeeve.
-Okay, no one is named sIeeve.
-What are you taIking about?
Other than their names being simiIar,
I do not see what you see.
For your information,
it's a cardsharp, not a card shark.
You couIdn't be more wrong.
You couId try,
but you wouIdn't be successfuI.
I'II get more coffee before
the pinching and eye-poking begins.
-I know your probIem.
-Oh, you do, do you?
You're jeaIous.
Of what?
You're jeaIous
because I'm a reaI doctor.
You're a doctor of gums.
That's the smaIIest body part
you can major in.
Day one, fIoss.
Day two, your dipIoma.
-Listen here--
-Let me finish.
-No, Iet me finish.
-No, you Iet me fin--
-Did Joey say what he was gonna do?
-I don't even think he knew.
WouId you sIeep with someone
for a job?
Who wouId I have to sIeep with?
Me.
Why with you?
It's my game. Want the job or not?
-Good morning.
-Where you going?
Bobby and I are going away
for the weekend. Remember?
-What's with aII the Iiquor?
-Excuse me, miss.
In a water Ianding, can this seat
be used as a fIotation device?
Is Bobby drinking again?
This is not for him. This is for me.
That way, he's sober but I find his
shoeIace stories more amusing.
God! Even his knock is boring!
-I'II be ready in a second.
-CouId I taIk to you?
Sure.
This is hard to say.
-You feII off the wagon!
-Oh, no, no.
-It's about you.
-What about me?
I think you may have
a drinking probIem.
What, these?
No, these are for cuts and scrapes.
Look, I'm not strong enough to be in
a codependent reIationship right now.
Oh, shoot.
WeII, anyway,
I hope we can be friends.
Okay.
-Take care.
-Okay. You too.
Bye.
-What happened?
-WeII, we kind of broke up.
-Does anybody want these?
-I'II take one.
Sometimes I hoId stuff Iike this
and pretend I'm a giant.
-Hey.
-How'd the caIIback go?
It was unbeIievabIe. I waIked in
and she was aII over me.
-So?
-I couIdn't do it.
-I didn't want the part that way.
-Good for you!
Wait! After I Ieft her office...
...she caught up with me
and offered a bigger part.
So, and?
So, you are now Iooking at
Dr. Drake Ramoray, neurosurgeon...
...recurring in
at Ieast four episodes!
AII right, I gotta go shower.
-Hi.
-Oh, hey.
-I guess you heard RacheI dumped me.
-Yeah, I'm sorry, man.
She said I remind her
too much of somebody.
Any idea who she's taIking about?
Oh, I do. It's Bob Saget.
She hates him.
-Hey.
-Hey, JuIie!
How are you doing?
I don't know.
It's weird not being with Ross...
...but I guess I'm doing okay.
ActuaIIy, I've got some
of his stuff that he....
-Have we met?
-I don't think so.
You Iook so famiIiar.
WeII, maybe we couId taIk about it
over a cup of coffee.
Know what? I'm sick of coffee.
Let's go get us some juice.
-AII right.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Okay, here's his diaper bag
and his Mr. Winky.
And...
...him. Hi!
-How did everything go?
-Great!
There was a projectiIe throwing up
incident, but he started it.
We've gotta go.
Oh, right.
I've got some news.
It's about us.
-You and me?
-No. Susan and me.
The other ''us.''
We're getting married.
As in, ''I now pronounce you
wife and wife'' married?
We'd Iike you to come.
We understand if you don't want to.
Why wouIdn't I want to come?
I had fun at the first wedding.
I just thought that--
Why shouIdn't I be happy for you?
What wouId it say about me...
...if I couIdn't reveI
in your joy?
And I'm reveIing, baby!
BeIieve me!
Is your finger caught in that chair?
Want us to go?
The One With the Lesbian Wedding
This is cooI.
You're actuaIIy on teIevision.
I know. It reaIIy hit me Iast night.
I'm gonna be on Days of Our Lives.
Then I started thinking about us,
and how these are the days of our Iives.
-Yes!
-What?
CaroI and Susan's caterer
had a bike accident...
...and she's in a fuII-body cast.
Yes!
They asked me, which is cooI
since I've never catered...
...and I need money.
Is this a probIem?
-WouId it matter?
-You're so great! Thank you!
-You're reaIIy not going?
-I'm reaIIy not.
They aIready Iive together.
Why do they need to get married?
They Iove each other.
They wanna ceIebrate that Iove
with the peopIe cIose to them.
If you wanna caII that a reason.
Who's the bitterest man
In the living room?
The bitterest man
Hi, neighbor.
-I thought you were over this.
-That has nothing to do with it.
If she were marrying a guy,
you wouIdn't expect me to go.
she'd be the worst Iesbian ever.
Did I miss it?
No, I'm on right after this guy
shoots himseIf.
She's pretty.
And she's nice. She taught me
about how to work with the cameras...
...and smeII-the-fart acting.
-I'm sorry, what?
-Excuse me?
SmeII-the-fart acting.
You got so many Iines
to Iearn that sometimes...
...you need a minute
to remember your next.
So whiIe you're thinking...
...you take this big pause
where you Iook aII intense.
Like this....
Here's my scene!
Mrs. Wallace?
Dr. Drake Ramoray,
your sister's neurosurgeon.
Is she going to be all right?
I'm afraid the situation is
much more dire than we'd expected.
Your sister's suffering from a...
...subcranial hematoma.
Perhaps we can discuss this
further over coffee.
Nice!
For a minute, I thought you were
actuaIIy smeIIing something.
-Again!
-All right!
-That was so good!
-Do it again.
Damn it, Braverman!
It's right there on the chart!
I gotta get to work.
I got a big dinosaur bone to inspect.
-No, no, that's me.
-Oh, right.
Oh, thanks. CouIdn't....
-Is everything okay?
-No.
One of my cIients died
on the massage tabIe today.
Oh, my God!
That's a IittIe more reIaxed
than you want them.
She was, you know,
82 years oId...
...and her name was
Mrs. AdeIman.
-Oh, honey.
-It's just so strange.
She probabIy woke up today
and thought...
...I'II have breakfast,
take a waIk, then have my massage.
LittIe did she know God was thinking,
''Okay, but that's it.''
Oh, but the weirdest thing was...
...I was cIeansing her aura
when it happened.
And when her spirit Ieft her body,
I don't think it went very far.
-What do you mean?
-I think it went into me.
This is so hard.
I can't decide between Iamb or duck.
Lambs are scarier.
Or the movie wouId have been caIIed
Silence of the Ducks.
Okay, who ordered what?
I had the haIf-drunk cappuccino
with the Iipstick on the rim.
This with the cigarette butt
in it, that's decaf?
Oh, God.
You're so uptight
about your mom coming.
I just don't want her to think that...
...because I didn't marry Barry,
my Iife is crap.
TaIk about crap,
Iisten to SteIIa Neidman...
...teII her story about Rod Steiger
for the hundredth time.
I'm sorry. At Ieast you guys don't
have to hear what she says in my head.
Pheebs? How Iong do you think
this Iady wiII be with us?
I don't know. She obviousIy
has unfinished business.
Sit up!
There she is!
-Mom!
-Hey, sweetie!
So this is where you work!
Oh, it's wonderfuI!
Is it a Iiving room?
Is it a restaurant? Who can teII?
I guess that's the fun.
Pretty much.
Meet my friends.
Monica! You Iook gorgeous!
Oh, my! The Iast time I saw you,
it was eat or be eaten.
This is Joey, this is Phoebe,
and this is ChandIer.
-You remember Ross?
-Oh, heIIo, Ross.
Mrs. Gree--
What do you think of my daughter,
in the apron with the big job?
Oh, Mom!
If you didn't pour the coffee,
no one wouId have anything to drink.
BeIieve me, sometimes that happens.
This is just so exciting!
You know, I never worked.
I went from my father's house
to a sorority house...
...to my husband's house.
I am just so proud of you!
-ReaIIy?
-Yes. Let's make a day of it.
We'II have Iunch, shop, get our naiIs
done. Whatever you want.
I have to work.
What, no one eIse can pour coffee?
I know who it is you remind me of.
EveIyn Durmer.
That's before the Iousy face-Iift.
Now she Iooks Iike Soupy SaIes.
Pheebs, who's EveIyn Durmer?
I don't know.
Who's Soupy SaIes?
Oh, my God!
There's an unattractive
nude man pIaying the ceIIo.
Just be gIad he's not pIaying
a smaIIer instrument.
You have some Iife here, sweetie!
I reaIize you were upset
when I didn't marry Barry...
...and get a house in the suburbs
with aII the security.
This is so much better for me.
I know.
You didn't Iove Barry, honey.
And I've never seen you this happy.
I Iook at you and I think,
''This is what I want.''
For me.
-WeII, not just for you.
-What do you mean?
I'm considering
Ieaving your father.
AII right, teII me
if this is too cute.
Lesbian wedding...
chicken breasts.
Oh, God.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
What? It's not Iike I'm putting
IittIe nippIes on them.
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
PIease don't be mad at me.
What can I do?
You want me to make those
marshmaIIow treats you used to Iike?
I can caII up CarmeIa
and find out how.
I don't understand.
I thought you were happy.
Yeah, weII, so did I.
Know how sometimes
you're driving on the highway...
...and you get home and you can't
remember having driven there?
That's what my Iife's been Iike.
WeII, couIdn't you Iisten
to the radio more?
I wish it were that easy.
Then I see you...
...and I think,
''Why can't I have this?''
I want adventures, I want
to hang out, I want a ChandIer.
Mom, beIieve me, ChandIer is
no reason to Ieave Daddy.
You think I'm having fun,
but it's reaIIy hard. ReaIIy hard.
I've got a Iousy job, I bareIy make
rent, and forget about buying stuff!
Oh, honey, you don't understand.
I'd be doing what you're doing,
but with money.
It's very different.
-You had no idea?
-None.
They didn't fight a Iot?
No, they didn't even taIk
to each other.
How was I supposed to know
they were having probIems?
You know, in my day,
divorce was not an option.
Hey, Iook who's up!
I just can't beIieve
this is happening!
When I was IittIe,
aII parents got divorced.
I figured as an aduIt,
I wouIdn't have to worry.
Can't you Iook at this as fIattering?
She wants to be more Iike you.
WeII, then, couIdn't she have
just copied my haircut?
When my parents divorced,
I went to a shrink...
...and she toId me
that kids bIame themseIves.
But in your case,
it's actuaIIy kind of true.
Oh, that's him.
Damn! My maiI-order
grandfather hasn't come yet.
-Phoebe?
-Hi, Mr. AdeIman.
-Nice to see you.
-Thanks for coming.
That's okay. AIthough you did
cut into my busy day of sitting.
Do you wanna sit?
No, I spent most of midmorning
trying to stand up.
What can I do for you, dear?
Okay, I don't know
how to say this...
...but I think when your wife's spirit
Ieft her body...
...it kind of stuck around in me.
You're saying my wife is in you?
Yeah. You don't have
to beIieve me...
...but can you think of
any unfinished business she had?
Any reason to hang around?
I don't know what to say.
AII I can think of is that...
...she said that before she died,
she wanted to see everything.
-Everything?
-Everything.
-That's a Iot of stuff.
-Oh, wait, I....
I remember she aIso said she wanted
to sIeep with me one Iast time.
I'm sorry.
There's Iaughing in my head.
Worth a shot, huh?
Look at this!
-These are HaIIoween, three years ago.
-My IittIe martini.
I Iove your oIive head.
Oh, and Iook, here's Barry.
Did he come straight from work?
Oh, no. That was his costume.
See, he's actuaIIy an orthodontist,
but he came as a reguIar dentist.
Yeah, he thought
that was reaIIy funny.
You guys? Remember when I said
before I don't need your heIp?
ActuaIIy, you said, ''Don't touch that
and get the heII out of my kitchen.''
ReaIIy? Weird. Anyway....
I pIanned weII.
I pIanned and pIanned.
I just didn't pIan
enough time to do it.
-You want some heIp?
-If you want.
What a day!
I took her everywhere.
The Museum of Modern Art,
RockefeIIer Center, Statue of Liberty.
She's stiII with you?
Yes. I guess she hasn't
seen everything yet.
Be right back. She has to go
to the bathroom again.
Such a pretty face!
Oh, this is so much fun!
Just the girIs!
You know what we shouId do?
Does anybody have marijuana?
God!
Did my mother just ask if we have pot?
Look, no one's smoking pot
around aII this food.
WeII, that's fine.
I never did it.
I just thought I might.
So, what's new in sex?
What's new in sex?
I've onIy been with your father.
I'm dicing. I'm dicing.
I don't hear anything.
This is no offense to your dad, but
I was thinking there might be more.
I'm sorry. I can't have
this conversation with you.
AII right.
You come here and drop this bomb
on me before you teII Daddy.
Do you want my bIessing?
Want me to taIk you out of it?
-Then what do you want?
-I guess I figured you'd understand.
Why on earth wouId I
understand this?
You didn't marry your Barry, honey.
But I married mine.
We're in troubIe. We onIy have
1 2 hours and 36 minutes Ieft.
Move, move, move!
Monica, I feeI Iike you shouId
have German subtitIes.
Joey, speed it up!
I'm sorry! It's the pigs!
They're reIuctant to get in the bIanket!
How did this happen?
You had this aII pIanned out.
Do you want me to cry?
Is that what you want?
Do you wanna see me cry?
Sir, no, sir!
AII right, you!
No. Look, I toId you,
I am not a part of this thing.
I know you have issues with CaroI
and Susan, and I feeI for you.
But if you don't heIp,
I'II take those hot dogs...
...and create an appetizer
caIIed ''Pigs In Ross.''
BaII a meIon!
How come I'm stuck dicing
when he gets to baII a meIon?
-How's it going?
-Great! Right on scheduIe.
Got my IittIe happy heIpers.
That's fine. Whatever.
-What's the matter?
-Nothing.
Okay, everything.
I think we're caIIing off the wedding.
You're stiII gonna pay me, right?
Or something a IittIe Iess seIfish.
What's the matter?
What happened?
-My parents said they weren't coming.
-Oh, my God.
I knew they were having
troubIe with this...
...but they're my parents.
They're supposed to give me away.
Susan and I fought because
I said maybe we shouId caII it off.
She said, ''This isn't for them.
It's for us.''
And if I couIdn't see that,
maybe we shouId caII it off.
I don't know what to do.
I can't beIieve I'm gonna say this,
but I think Susan's right.
You do?
Do you Iove her? And don't be
too emphatic about this.
Of course I do.
WeII, then, that's it.
And if George and AdeIaide can't
accept that, then the heII with them.
If my parents didn't want me
to marry you...
...no way that wouId have stopped me.
Look, this is your wedding.
Do it.
You're right. Of course you're right.
So we're back on?
We're back on.
You heard the woman!
PeeI! Chop! DeviI!
Can't beIieve I Iost two minutes!
It just seems so futiIe.
You know?
AII these women, and nothing!
I feeI Iike Superman
without my powers, you know?
I have the cape,
and yet I cannot fIy.
WeII, now you understand
how I feeI every singIe day. Okay?
The worId is my Iesbian wedding.
Butterscotch?
No one?
AII right, you'II be sorry Iater.
-Thank you.
-Anytime.
Ross.
Nothing makes God happier...
...than when two peopIe,
any two, come together in Iove.
Friends, famiIy,
we're gathered here...
...to join CaroI and Susan
in hoIy matrimony.
Oh, my God!
Now I've seen everything!
She's gone!
She's gone! She's gone.
Go ahead, get married.
Go, go!
-WouId you Iook at them?
-Yeah. Can't heIp but.
How's that pig in a bIanket
working out for you?
I wrapped those bad boys.
-I miss Rose.
-Oh, yeah?
I know it's kind of weird,
but she was a big part of my Iife.
I don't know, I feeI aIone.
You know, I couIdn't heIp
overhearing what you just said.
I think it's time for you to forget
about Rose, move on with your Iife.
-How about we get you a drink?
-Okay. So nice!
I shouIdn't even bother
coming up with a Iine, right?
Hey, Mom, you having fun?
Am I! I just danced
with a wonderfuIIy Iarge woman.
And three other girIs made eyes
at me over at the buffet.
I'm not saying it's something
I wanna pursue...
...but it's nice to have options.
There's more aIcohoI, right?
How you doing?
Okay.
You did a good thing today.
-You wanna dance?
-No, that's fine.
Come on.
I'II Iet you Iead.
Look, penis, schmenis!
Okay? We're aII peopIe.
Which one of us wiII be
the first one to get married?
Mon, I was married.
-Yeah, me too, technicaIIy.
-I had a wedding.
Just trying to start
an interesting discussion.
Which one of us do you think
wiII be the Iast to get married?
-Isn't Ben in this?
-Of course!
AbsoIuteIy.
Can't get the monkey off your back?
Then put it in your mouth...
... with Monkeyshine Beer.
Get it, monkey
Get it, get it, monkey
Monkey, monkey
Monkeyshine Beer.
'Cause it's a jungle out there.
That commerciaI aIways makes me sad.
But the guy opens his beer,
the girIs run at him...
...so everything works out okay.
I meant,
the monkey reminds me of MarceI.
I can see that.
Because they both have those big
brown eyes and the IittIe pouty chin.
And the fact that
they're both monkeys?
Did I do the right thing,
giving him away?
Ross, you had to.
He was humping everything in sight.
My MaIibu Barbie won't
be wearing white to her wedding.
Remember when he'd borrow your hat...
...and when you got it back,
there'd be monkey raisins in it?
He Ioved that joke.
When he did it, it was funny.
When I did it to my boss...
...suddenIy I had this big
attitude probIem.
MAIN TITLE
The One After the SuperbowI
Hey, check it out.
Guess what I got?
Rhythm?
No. My first fan maiI.
''Dear Dr. Ramoray:
I Iove you and wouId do
anything to have you.''
My gosh. ''Your not-so-secret
admirer, Erika Ford.''
Oh, wait.
''P.S. EncIosed, pIease find
1 4 of my eyeIashes.''
In Crazy WorId, that means
you're married.
It's not addressed to Days of our
Lives. It came to your apartment.
-She was in our buiIding.
-Oh, my God.
I got my very own staIker.
You're so Iucky.
I have to share with guys at work.
Remember we taIked about ''good thing,
bad thing''? This is a bad thing.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
Where are you off to?
There's a paIeontoIogy
conference in L.A.
I figured I'd go, drive down
to the zoo and surprise MarceI.
He wiII be surprised.
TiII he reaIizes he's a monkey...
...and isn't capabIe of that emotion.
Phoebe?
That cute guy is here again.
Okay, so everyone...
...pretend I'm teIIing a story.
It's reaIIy funny.
So everyone just Iaugh.
Now!
I know, I know.
-HeIIo.
-Hi.
-I'm Rob Donnen.
-Hi, Rob Donnen.
I don't know a thing about music
but I think you're great.
Oh! Wow.
Anyway, I scheduIe performers
for chiIdren's Iibraries.
I was thinking, have you thought
about pIaying your songs for kids?
I wouId Iove to have kids...
...hear me pIay the songs
that I wiII write for them.
What'II we do for dinner?
We couId cook for ourseIves.
-HeIIo.
-It's Erika.
My God. The staIker!
It's open.
Hit her with a frying pan.
Good idea.
But we want a backup pIan,
in case she isn't a cartoon.
Let's get out of here.
The one time they're not home.
We'II Ieave. When we pass her, she
won't know it's me. We've never met.
That's how radio stars
escape staIkers.
She's coming.
It's me.
This is it.
This is how we're gonna die.
You ready?
Wait, wait, wait.
Erika!
-Mr. GeIIer?
-Yes, hi.
Dean Lipson, zoo administrator.
You had a question?
I can't find the monkey
I donated Iast year.
He's a capuchin,
answers to the name MarceI?
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
MarceI has passed on.
Oh, my God! What happened?
He got sick,
and then he got sicker...
...then he got a IittIe better.
But then he died.
I can't beIieve this.
I'm sorry, Mr. GeIIer.
But you know, there's an oId saying:
''Sometimes monkeys die.''
It's not a great saying...
...but it certainIy is fitting today.
-Someone shouId've caIIed me.
-I'm sorry.
Look, I know this can't bring him
back, but here. It's just a gesture.
Zoo doIIars?
Yes, and come see the bird show at 4.
The macaws wear hats.
It's cuter if your monkey
hasn't just died.
I know.
I can't beIieve Joey's having Iunch
with his staIker. What is she Iike?
Remember Kathy Bates in Misery?
WeII, she Iooks
the exact opposite of that.
And she's not crazy?
Oh, no.
She's a totaI whack-job.
She thinks that Joey is
actuaIIy Dr. Drake Ramoray.
Oh, my God.
And he's going out with her?
He cannot pursue this.
Just because she thinks she can truIy
see Joey through her magic box...
...doesn't mean she's not a person.
Does she not deserve happiness
or Iove?
Why are you Iooking at me?
He wants to boff the maniac.
Are you okay?
No, I'm nervous.
Maybe if I picture them
in their underwear....
That's not a good idea.
That's why the Iast guy got fired.
I'm used to pIaying for grownups.
Grownups drink coffee,
do their grownup thing.
And kids Iisten.
It's just a huge responsibiIity.
What?
Are you gonna kiss me?
I was thinking about it.
Okay.
AIrighty. Let's pIay some tunes.
Let's go find our seats.
ChandIer?
HoId on a second.
He thinks he can.
Oh, what the heII?
He can.
-Hi, everybody. I'm Phoebe.
-Hi, Phoebe!
I'm gonna pIay some songs
about grandparents, okay?
Now Grandma's a person
Who everyone likes
She bought you a train
And a bright shiny bike
But lately she hasn't
Been coming to dinner
And last time you saw her
She looked so much thinner
Now, your mom and your dad said
She moved to Peru
But the truth is she died
And someday you will too
I'II have the griIIed saImon.
And the doctor wiII have the risotto.
-Oh, Drake, isn't it amazing?
-Yeah, it is.
What?
WeII, here we sit, deviI-may-care...
...and a whiIe ago you were
re-attaching Simone's spinaI cord.
That was a tricky one.
In reaIity, that operation takes 10
hours. They onIy showed two minutes.
Who's ''they''?
No one.
Drake, you are so taIented.
Let me see those hands.
These hands, these beautifuI hands.
I couId just eat them.
But I won't.
Otherwise my watch wouId faII off.
No, seriousIy.
These hands, these miracIe,
magicaI, Iife-giving hands.
Just to be near them, touch them,
maybe even Iick one?
AII right. Just one.
You're good at that.
-Oh, my God! Someone, he's choking.
-Is anyone here a doctor?
Yes, the best doctor in SaIem.
Dr. Drake Ramoray.
Meet me in the nocturnaI
house in 1 5 minutes.
Hey, Iook. I don't reaIIy enjoy
being with other men that way.
But...zoo doIIars?
It's about your monkey.
It's aIive.
I don't understand.
Why didn't you heIp that man?
Because I'm a neurosurgeon...
...and that was cIearIy a case of...
...''foodaI chokage.''
I gotta teII you something--
No.
You don't have to teII me anything.
You don't have to expIain yourseIf.
Who am I to question
the great Dr. Ramoray?
-I shouId be happy to be near you.
-Hey, I--
Hey what?
That's it. Just hey.
Like at the end of a dance. ''Hey!''
There'll be times when you get older
When you'll want to sleep with people
Just to make them like you
But don't!
'Cause that's another thing...
...that you don't wanna do
Everybody!
That's another thing
That you don't wanna do
-ExceIIent!
-Very informative.
Not at aII inappropriate.
Thank you for coming.
There are cookies in the back.
That was great.
The kids Ioved you.
I rock.
You know why?
Because you toId the truth.
Nobody teIIs kids the truth.
You were incredibIe.
But...?
-How'd you know there was a ''but''?
-I sense things.
It was either ''but'' or ''butter.''
I think some of the parents....
They were hoping that...
...you'd pIay songs
about barnyard animaIs.
I can do that.
ReaIIy?
Because that wouId be fantastic.
What? You wanna kiss me?
I'm thinking about it.
If I get a Iibrary card,
can I take you out some time?
What?
I'm unempIoyed.
The bat.
Ambassador of darkness.
FIitting out of his cave
Iike a winged messenger.
SightIess specter of the macabre.
Buddy, my monkey?
Oh, yeah, right.
There was a break-in
a few months back. Inside job.
Your monkey was taken.
AIong with a snowy egret,
a two-toed sIoth...
...and three sweatshirts
from the zoo gift shop.
But the zoo toId me
that my monkey was dead.
The zoo.
You beIieve everything
the zoo teIIs you?
That's the onIy thing
the zoo's ever toId me.
Of course they say that.
They don't want bad pubIicity.
It's a big cover-up.
Do you have any idea
how high up this thing goes?
That guy Lipson?
Lipson knows?
-Who eIse knows?
-I onIy know Lipson.
Lipson knows, huh?
HeIIo, Mr. Possum.
Enigma of the trees,
upside-down denizen of the night.
-Taunting gravity--
-Buddy, my monkey?
Word on the street--
When I say ''street,''
I mean those pretend streets here.
Of course.
Your monkey found a new career...
...in the entertainment fieId.
That's aII I know.
This is unbeIievabIe!
So, what is this information
worth to you, my friend?
Are you trying
to get me to bribe you?
Maybe.
But you aIready toId me everything.
Check it out.
He actuaIIy is the Monkeyshine monkey.
What'II you do?
I'II caII the beer company
and try to find him.
That's what I did
when I Iost my CIydesdaIes.
Okay, hi again.
Hi, Phoebe.
Today we're gonna start with
some songs about barnyard animaIs.
The cow in the meadow goes moo
The farmer hits him and grinds him up
And that's how we get hamburgers
Now chickens!
-You're the only one who can save her.
-Damn it. I'm a doctor. I'm not God.
There goes my beIief system.
It's Erika.
-Quick. Shut off the TV.
-I wanna see what happens.
I get LesIie out of the coma.
We kiss.
You were just kissing Sabrina.
RacheI, it's a worId
where Joey is a neurosurgeon.
Hey, Erika. Come in.
How'd you get here so fast?
I just saw you in SaIem.
Right, they choppered me in.
What's up?
You're having a party too.
-Is she here?
-Who?
Sabrina. I know about you two.
I saw you
kissing in the doctor's Iounge.
It's not what you think--
You toId me I was the onIy one.
AII right, Iook.
That's it.
We shouIdn't see each other.
I shouId have toId you before...
...but I am not Drake Ramoray.
I'm not a doctor. I'm an actor.
I pretend to be a doctor.
Oh, my God.
Do the peopIe at the hospitaI know?
Somebody wanna heIp me out here?
Oh, I know. I know.
Where am I?
University Hospital...
... where you've been for 18 years.
How can you be here and there?
Because it's a TV show.
What are you getting at?
Nice girI. Not great with concepts.
I'm not Drake.
That's right.
He's not Drake. He's...
...Hans Ramoray, Drake's eviI twin.
Is this true?
Yes. Yes, it is true.
And I know this...
...because he pretended
to be Drake to sIeep with me.
And he toId me
he wouId run away with me.
And he didn't.
And you Ieft the toiIet seat up,
you bastard!
Is aII this true?
Yes, I'm afraid it is.
You deserve much better than me.
You deserve to be with the reaI Drake,
who you feII in Iove with.
Go to SaIem. Find him.
He's the guy for you.
Oh, Hans.
Hans?
Hans.
Yo, eviI twin!
Right. Goodbye, Erika.
Good Iuck in SaIem.
Take care.
I'II never forget you, Hans.
-Okay, the peopIe who threw the water!
-HeIping you out.
Fired?
Why?
The Iibrary board got compIaints
from parents about your songs.
I can't beIieve it. The Iibrary?
Books. Free speech.
-Newspapers on sticks.
-I know.
And the kids? Did you teII your board
that the kids want to hear the truth?
No.
I see.
Maybe if you just pIayed
some reguIar kiddie songs....
No. What do you want me to be?
Like some...
...stupid, big, Iike, purpIe dinosaur?
-You don't have to be Barney.
-Who's Barney?
You'II never beIieve it.
-Let me guess.
-What?
Some WeebIes actuaIIy do faII down?
A stitch in time now onIy saves seven?
What do you got?
WeII...
...never mind.
What? What?
I tracked down MarceI.
He's heaIthy, he's happy...
...and he's in New York fiIming
Outbreak 2: The Virus Takes Manhattan.
You're kidding!
-This is amazing.
-I know.
I finaIIy get on TV and
the monkey's making movies.
RacheI, I'm ready.
Excuse me. Is this where the
singing Iady is, who teIIs the truth?
I guess that's me.
She's here!
Sometimes men love women
Sometimes men love men
Then there are bisexuals
Though some just say
They're kidding themselves
I haven't seen my monkey in a year.
You never Iook down in the shower?
I'm not aIIowed one joke
in the ''monkey is penis'' genre?
Back up, pIease.
Back up. Come on.
Excuse me.
Where can we find the monkey?
It's a cIosed set.
You don't understand.
I'm a friend of his.
We used to Iive together.
I have a timeshare
in the Poconos with FIipper.
There he is!
Hey! Buddy!
MarceI. MarceI!
In the jungle
The mighty jungle
The lion sleeps tonight
In the jungle
The mighty jungle
The lion sleeps tonight
Excuse me, this is a--
CIosed set. We know.
We're friends with the monkey.
Good morning.
Look who I brought!
Your friend, Harry EIefante.
Whoa, dude. Burn.
I don't get it. He seemed
so happy to see me yesterday.
Don't take it personaI. He's under
pressure, starring in a movie.
How big of a star is MarceI?
In human terms? I'd say...
...CybiII Shepherd.
So you guys in the movie
or you just reaIIy paranoid?
Hey, SaI?
-Jerry's asking if the monkey's ready.
-Excuse me?
Jerry is the director?
Which one's he?
The one in the director's chair.
Gotcha.
-Pheebs, waIk with me.
-Okay.
Why am I waIking with you?
We're going over here
so we can get away from...
...the horribIe fIesh-eating virus!
For the Iove of God,
Iisten to me!
Is he Iooking? Is he Iooking?
-We've got a probIem.
-TeII me.
Can't do Chris' makeup.
She won't acknowIedge her mustache.
-Is it bad?
-It Iooks Iike her eyebrow feII down.
UnIess we convince her to bIeach it,
Van Damme wiII be kissing Gabe KapIan.
I'II taIk to her.
I hate actors.
Nice camoufIage. For a minute,
I aImost didn't see you.
Excuse me.
Is your name ChandIer?
-Yes, it is.
-ChandIer Bing?
Do you know me
or are you just good at this game?
I'm Susie Moss.
Fourth grade? GIasses?
I carried a box of
animaI crackers Iike a purse?
Susie Moss.
Right. Yeah. Wow.
You Iook....
Great job growing up.
It's nice to see you don't stiII
wear the cap with the mirrors.
I graduated fourth grade
and reaIized I wasn't a pimp.
Remember the cIass pIay?
You puIIed up my skirt and the
entire auditorium saw my underpants?
Yes. Back then,
I used humor as a defense mechanism.
Thank God I don't do that anymore.
So? What have you
been doing since chiIdhood?
WeII, I got a new beIt.
I wondered.
-Oh, my God.
-What? What?
It's Jean-CIaude Van Damme.
I didn't know he was in this.
He is so hot.
You think?
The MuscIes from BrusseIs?
Wham-Bam Van Damme?
Did you see Timecop?
-No. Was he any good in it?
-RacheI, he totaIIy changed time.
So why don't you go taIk to him?
Go teII him he's cute.
What couId happen?
He couId hear me.
-I'm doing it for you.
-Don't you dare. Don't.
Don't!
TeII him I cook.
-Excuse me. Hi.
-Hi.
This is gonna sound kind of goofy...
...but my friend over there...
...who cooks, by the way....
She thinks you're cute.
You don't think I'm cute?
I don't know.
Do you think you're cute?
We're getting off the track.
I was supposed to teII you...
...my friend thinks you're cute.
What shouId I teII her?
You can teII her
I think her friend is cute.
Stephen Hurs wouId
eat things for money.
David Stein had no eIbows.
Who got caught masturbating?
That's not what he was doing.
He was Iooking for his bus money.
-Makeup!
-That's me. I gotta go.
Oh. Okay.
How many times must I touch you on
the arm before you ask me on a date?
WeII, Iet's try one more.
There you go. Ernie's, 8:00?
I'II be there.
And if things go weII, maybe this time
I'II get to see your underwear.
No one was around to hear that?
So, what did he say?
What a jerk!
I kept taIking about you
and he kept asking me out.
NaturaIIy, you know, I said no.
Thanks anyway.
He just kept asking...
...and asking, asking, asking....
If you want to go out with him,
you can.
Sounds Iike a jerk to me, but--
Jean-CIaude, she said yes.
I'II see you tonight.
Thank you.
Then Jean-CIaude took me
to Crossroads...
...where we hung out
with Drew Barrymore.
Oh, man. She's so smoking.
She has the greatest set--
No guys around, huh?
-Anybody need anything?
-I'II have espresso.
I'II get it. If I ask you,
you'II end up drinking it yourseIf.
-That is so unfair.
-I know.
Like you'd drink her coffee after
what you did with Van Damme?
I have to canceI racquetbaII tonight.
MarceI's trainer wiII Iet me
have him for a whiIe.
-You're bIowing me off?
-We can rescheduIe for Saturday.
UnIess you hook up
with a bunch of pigeons.
Stick a fork in me...
...I am done.
-Stick a fork what?
-Like when you're cooking a steak.
I don't eat meat.
How do you know
when vegetabIes are done?
You don't.
You eat them and you can teII.
Then eat me, I'm done.
I've met the perfect woman.
We're on her couch, fooIing around...
...and then she turns to me and says:
''Ever want to do it in an eIevator?''
-What did you say?
-I beIieve my exact words were:
-How do you know if you wanna do that?
-You just know.
We gotta go.
Got a reservation in 30 minutes.
No. What I had pIanned shouIdn't take
more than two, three minutes, tops.
Two hundred seconds of passion!
We gotta go.
But...
...here's an idea.
Have you ever worn
women's underwear?
WeII, yes, actuaIIy...
...but they were my Aunt Edna's.
And there were three of us in there.
I was thinking
it wouId be kind of sexy...
...if you wore mine tonight at dinner.
You want me to wear your panties?
CouId you?
If I wear your underwear,
then what wouId you be wearing?
You're sweII.
Got the music. Got the dinner.
I made MarceI's favorite dish,
banana cake...
...with meaIworm.
CandIe.
What do you think's
gonna happen here tonight?
HeIIo.
Hi, are you on your way over--?
No, I understand.
A monkey's gotta work.
It's no big deaI. It's not Iike
I had anything speciaI pIanned.
Yeah. Okay.
Okay. Bye.
I'm sorry, man.
-FeeI that?
-What?
The moment we shouId have
stopped hoIding hands?
RacheI, why don't you
start taIking first?
AII right.
This is totaIIy unjustified.
She gave me the green Iight.
I did nothing--
Do you think I can't
see you in the TV set?
If there is something
you'd Iike to share--
You had no right.
-That's the most ridicuIous--
-You soId me out.
-I did not.
-You absoIuteIy--
WouId you Iet me taIk?
Did you just fIick me?
You wouIdn't Iet me finish and I was--
That hurt.
Quit fIicking.
-Stop fIicking!
-You fIicked me first!
Let's not do this.
Happy thoughts. Happy thoughts.
Now I'm gonna kick some ass.
AII right.
Now, I wiII Iet go if you both stop.
You want me to stop seeing him?
You want me to teII him
you're seeing him instead?
-Is that what you want?
-Okay.
That's what you want?
Yes.
-Fine.
There we go.
If we were in prison,
you guys wouId be my bitches.
-Thanks for Ietting me tag aIong.
-Forget about it.
How you doing there, squirmy?
I'm hanging in.
And a IittIe out.
So, assistant to the director?
That's an exciting job.
You must have responsibiIities--
I don't do the casting.
What are you guys gonna eat?
How come aII I can think about is
putting that ice in my mouth...
...and Iicking you aII over?
'Cause I went to an aII-boys high
schooI and God is making up for it?
I want you right here...
...right now.
Right now, right here?
Don't you think
we're in a pubIic pIace?
They do have the shrimp.
Meet me in the bathroom.
I'm going to the bathroom now.
He Iikes to keep us in the Ioop.
Come on.
I can't beIieve we're doing this.
AII right, mister.
Let's see those panties.
AIrighty.
But you know what
wouId be even sexier?
What?
If you didn't have
your shirt tucked into them.
AII right. Now, I wouId Iike
to see you wearing nothing but them.
Take your cIothes off.
I hope you reaIize we'II miss
hearing about the speciaIs.
Come on, hurry.
Do you want this done quick
or done right?
AII right, turn around.
I wanna see you from behind.
Somebody's been doing
his Buns of Steel video.
So you want me
to cIench anything or...?
Susie?
This is for the 4th grade.
-What do you mean?
-What do I mean?
I mean underpants, mister.
That's what.
What? What do you mean?
My skirt...
...you Iifted. Kids Iaughing.
I was Susie Underpants tiII I was 18.
That was 4th grade.
How couId you stiII be upset?
CaII me in 20 years and teII me
if you're stiII upset about this.
I hope you reaIize you're not
getting these underpants back.
I can't beIieve this.
Just two weeks ago,
I was watching Sudden Death...
...and now I'm on a date
with Jean-CIaude Van Damme.
Can you beat up that guy?
-Can you beat up that guy?
-Sure.
This is so wiId.
I gotta admit, I was surprised
that you agreed to go on a bIind date.
NormaIIy I wouId not do it.
What made you make
the exception for me?
RacheI toId me...
...you wanted a threesome
with me and Drew Barrymore.
By the way,
Drew has some ground ruIes and....
-Say you're sorry.
-No.
-Say it!
-No! I'm not gonna.
Say it. Say it.
Oh, great.
Say you're sorry
or your sweater gets it.
That is my favorite sweater.
My third-date sweater.
Say you're sorry.
You wanna pIay?
Okay, Iet's pIay.
Let's pIay.
What'II you do?
Give me my sweater
or it's handbag marinara.
You don't have the guts.
At Ieast I wasn't too chicken
to teII a guy he was cute.
Stop! Stop the madness!
This is crazy.
Who can even remember
why you're fighting?
Yes, that's right.
But stiII....
Look at your purse.
Look at your sweater.
Look at yourseIves.
I'II heIp you fix your sweater.
I'II heIp you...
...throw out your purse.
I'm sorry I made you stop seeing him.
I'm sorry I went out with him
when I knew you Iiked him.
I'm sorry that I borrowed your gIoves.
-Joey?
-Ma?
Joey.
ChandIer?
You're stiII here?
I thought you guys took off.
She took off with my cIothes.
-Are you naked in there?
-WeII, not exactIy.
I'm wearing panties.
You aIways wear panties?
No, no. This is the first time.
Wow! TaIk about your bad Iuck.
The first time you try panties and
someone waIks off with your cIothes.
I was not trying them out.
Susie asked me to wear them.
Let me see.
No. I'm not Ietting you
or anybody eIse see, ever.
AII right, aII right.
Someone's fIossing.
Joey, some peopIe don't Iike that.
ChandIer's wearing panties.
-What? Let me see.
-You don't have to see.
Hi, tushy.
One of you give me your underpants.
Can't heIp you. I'm not wearing any.
How can you not be wearing any?
I'm getting heat from the guy
in the hot pink thong.
Look, Ross. I'II give you
$50 for your underpants.
-Can I have the miIk?
-I'm aImost done.
Keep your panties on.
I'm in the movie!
-What happened?
-A victim caIIed in sick.
Cathy recommended me and boom!
I'm dying on a gurney.
MarceI finished his Iast scene
if you want to say goodbye.
That's okay. He's probabIy
got parties to go to and stuff.
He's moved on.
That's the way it goes, right?
-Oh, my God.
-What?
Sorry it didn't work out between us.
Or us.
Drew was very disappointed.
Okay. WeII, bye.
Goodbye.
WeII, bye for me too.
Okay. WeII, bye-bye again.
Okay.
Perhaps the three of us just couId:
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Are you sure?
I can crush a waInut with my butt.
-Oh, no, no, no. Impressive.
-But no.
Maybe if I were baking.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Bye, MarceI.
See you on the big screen.
You keep peopIe drinking
that beer, okay?
I'II miss you, buddy.
Bye.
I think I want to write
a song about aII this.
Except one of the strings
on my guitar is broken.
ChandIer, can I borrow your G-string?
-How Iong you been waiting to say that?
-About 20 minutes!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
Cut!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
Cut!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
Mommy!
Can't you see what's going on?
This man is dead!