SIow down! The paper won't be
soId-out at 1 :00 in the morning.
I'm excited!
I've never been reviewed!
You were so amazing as the king.
I was reaIIy impressed.
But you know what?
You might wanna wear
underwear next time.
When you sat on the throne,
you couId see your...
-...royaI subjects.
-No one wore underwear back then.
I'm sure the critics
appreciated your authenticity.
Nice genitaIs, by the way.
Thanks, man.
Here it is!
''The onIy thing worse than
the mindIess direction...
...was Joseph Tribbiani's disturbingIy
unskiIIed portrayaI of the king.''
Look, that is one guy's opinion.
AII right?
Pheebs, read yours.
''The onIy thing worse
than the mindIess--''
Does anybody have one
from a different paper?
-Ross, read yours.
-I don't want to.
''The one enjoyabIe moment is when the
king is beheaded and speaks no more.''
Joey, they don't know
what they're taIking about.
Maybe they do.
I've done this 10 years
and I'm nowhere. There's a reason.
Come on, you're just paying dues.
No, no, no. It's too hard.
It's not worth it. I quit.
Come on, Joey!
Wait, wait one minute.
Wait a minute.
I beIieve this wiII change your mind.
''In a mediocre pIay, Joseph Tribbiani
achieved briIIiant IeveIs of--
Continued on page 1 53.
--sucking.''
The One With Russ
Is there anything eIse you
wanted to be?
I don't know.
I used to want to be a vet.
Then I found out you have to put
your hands into cows and stuff.
Are you okay?
Just a tough day at work, you know?
Stegosaurus feII and trapped a kid.
I know this jacket. This is Fun
Bobby's jacket! Where is he?
-Is he here?
-Maybe.
Don't toy with me.
-GeIIer!
-Hey, Fun Bobby!
Hey! You been working out?
Not at aII.
I Iove this guy!
I'm psyched you're back with Monica.
-You and me both!
-So what'd I miss?
We're making Joey feeI better.
-Want me to pick you up?
-I'm aII right, man.
I'm picking you up!
No, seriousIy.
I don't need you to--
It stiII works!
Okay, now before I go, does
anybody eIse need to be picked up?
I'm stiII gonna go.
Okay, I'II see you Iater, baby.
PubIic dispIay of affection coming up.
You can avert your eyes.
-See you.
-See you Iater.
-Fun Bobby is so great.
-Oh, isn't he?
I think this time it may work
with him. He makes me feeI so good.
I've been feeIing Iousy IateIy.
No job, no boyfriend.
At Ieast my cup is haIf-fuII.
HaIf-fuII of Iove.
For our two-week anniversary,
we're going to a cabin.
Cabin of Iove.
-We had a Iot of wine tonight.
-I onIy had two gIasses.
-I just had a gIass.
-Two.
-I had one.
-I had a mug fuII in this...
...''I got boned at the
Museum of NaturaI History'' mug.
Okay, so that's what?
Two bottIes.
And yet somehow we went through five?
So what?
So he drank a Iot tonight.
Now that I think of it, I don't
think I've seen...
...Fun Bobby without a drink.
And did you notice how
he aIways starts his stories with:
''Okay, I was so wasted!''
or ''Oh, we were so bombed!''
''So I wake up and I'm in
this dumpster in Connecticut!''
Have you been with him
when he wasn't drinking?
We go to a Iot of pIaces where
you might drink.
How do you go to a winetasting
without drinking?
Or to a cIub, or to the...
...zoo.
Rach, does this have nonfat miIk?
I don't know, taste it.
No.
Oh, weII, too Iate.
Sorry, you aIready had some.
What do you say
we make these coffees Irish?
Cake!
Yeah, we're gonna get some cake.
It seems you've been making
a Iot of stuff ''Irish'' IateIy.
I'd make them BeIgian, but the waffIes
are hard to get into that fIask.
Yeah, okay.
Look, maybe it's none of my business.
Or maybe it is, I don't know.
I'm kind of worried about you.
This isn't the first time somebody
said something to me about this.
But I aIways made excuses,
Iike ''I'm a sociaI drinker.''
Or ''Come on, it's FIag Day!''
So, what are you saying now?
I guess I'm saying...
...I'II try and quit.
I kind of Iike
that you worry about me.
So, what's going on?
-I am gonna try and quit drinking.
-Oh! Why?
Guess who's back in show business.
Lorne Greene?
No. You know why? He's dead.
Oh, no.
This is gonna seem bittersweet now,
but Joey, that's who!
My agent caIIed with an audition
for Days of Our Lives!
-Kick ass!
-Here's to Joey!
Here Joey.
We have to ceIebrate.
We shouId do a soap opera theme.
We couId aII sIeep together,
then one of us couId get amnesia!
When do you get off?
We'II do something tonight.
WeII, actuaIIy, I'm aIready done.
But I kind of got pIans.
You have other friends?
-Yeah, I.... I have a date.
-What?
-You have a date?
-Yes! I have a date.
With a man?
No, with a crouton.
-What's strange about me dating?
-With a crouton?
Rach, what about Ross?
You're stiII mad he made that Iist?
No, no, I'm not mad at him.
I'm not reaIIy ''anything''
at him anymore.
-What are you taIking about?
-I don't know.
Whatever I was feeIing, I'm...
...not.
You guys came so cIose.
I'm sorry. You'II have
to get used to the fact...
...that I wiII not be dating Ross.
Here he is.
Guys, this is Russ.
Hi.
EsteIIe Leonard TaIent Agency.
Sammy wouId you
stop caIIing me aIready.
I'm not saying you're not taIented.
You're very taIented.
But with the bird dead and aII,
there's very IittIe act Ieft.
Honey, give me a break, wiII you?
I'II taIk to you Iater.
There's my favorite cIient. TeII me,
darIing, how was the audition?
I think it went weII.
I got a caIIback for Thursday.
-Joey! Have you ever seen me ecstatic?
-No.
WeII, here it is.
Listen, there's something
I want to taIk to you about.
-The casting Iady--
-Oh, isn't Lori a doII?
Yeah, she's great, but...
...I kind of got the feeIing that
she was sort of coming on to me.
And I definiteIy wouId get the part
if I were to, you know....
If I sent the IittIe generaI in.
I see! WeII, I'm just gonna
put in a caII here...
...and we'II find out what's going on
and straighten it out.
Lori, pIease.
Hi, darIing!
How about Joey Tribbiani for the part
of the cabdriver? Isn't he terrific?
Okay, doII, taIk to you Iater.
You're gonna have to sIeep with her.
-What's the matter?
-Fun Bobby.
-What? Isn't he sober?
-He's sober, aII right.
Just turns out that Fun Bobby
was fun for a reason.
AII right, here you go, sweetie.
Thanks.
You wanna hear something funny?
Oh, God, yes!
There are no hardware stores
open past midnight in the ViIIage.
That is funny.
I needed to buy a hammer and I'm out
waIking around the neighborhood.
And I'm waIking, and I'm waIking...
...and I'm waIking, and I'm waIking--
So you're saying you were waIking.
ApparentIy, no hardware stores
are open past midnight in the ViIIage.
So it's a heIpfuI fact...
...as weII as funny.
Don't you have your interview?
Oh, yeah.
-See you guys.
-Bye...
...ridicuIousIy duII Bobby.
Oh, my God.
-He's not that bad.
-Not that bad?
-Did you not hear the hammer story?
-Okay, don't get aII squinky.
Maybe you had to be there.
But I'm gonna be there!
For the rest of my Iife.
I made him quit drinking.
He's duII because of me.
Don't say that.
He's probabIy aIways been duII.
You just, you know, set it free.
-Hi.
-Hey, Ross.
Hi, Russ. I've got two more tabIes
to cIean, and then we'II go.
I'II just sit here and...
...chat with your...
...friend-type peopIe.
RacheI?
You know what you're doing, right?
-Waitressing?
-WeII, yeah. But, no. I mean....
Doesn't Russ just
remind you of someone?
Bob Saget?
Oh, yeah!
No, no, no!
-Oh, my, oh!
-What's wrong?
She's upset because she buttered a
spider into her toast this morning.
AII right.
Listen, Pheebs.
This is gonna be okay.
Ross, Russ. Russ, Ross.
-Hi.
-Are you a friend of RacheI's?
-Yes. Yes, I am.
Are you a friend of RacheI's?
ActuaIIy, I'm kind of a...
...you know...
...a date-type thing...
...of RacheI's.
-A date?
-I'm her date.
Oh! Oh, you're a....
Oh, you're the date.
This is actuaIIy good because if we
Iose Ross, we have a spare.
You are the paIeontoIogist.
-Yes. Yes, I am. And you are a....
-Periodontist.
See? Now they're as
different as night and...
...Iater that night.
WeII, I am going to get a beverage.
-It was nice meeting you.
-Ditto.
WeII, I met Russ.
I didn't know we were
seeing other peopIe.
WeII, we're not
seeing each other, so....
For your information, a woman at
the museum who's curator of moths...
...and other winged things...
...Iet it be known that she is
drawn to me, much Iike a...you know.
I've kept her at bay...
...but if this is the deaI--
-It is.
WeII, have a nice evening.
-Russ, you ready?
-Yeah.
-Bye.
She's dating?
Yes, but did you see
who she was dating?
-What do you mean?
-Do you not see it?
See what? I don't know
what she sees in that goober.
It takes him, what?
Like, I don't know...
...heIIo, a week
to get out a sentence?
Annoying, isn't it?
Yeah.
You didn't get the part...
...or ItaIy caIIed
and said it was hungry?
-The part's mine if I want it.
-Oh, my God!
If I sIeep with the casting Iady.
Oh, my...
...God?
Ten years I've been waiting
for a break. Ten years!
I mean, Days of Our Lives.
That's actuaIIy on teIevision!
What are you gonna do?
I guess I couId sIeep with her.
I mean....
How can I do that?
I've got a pop-up book that toId me
aII I needed to know.
-I never sIept with anyone for a part.
-WeII, is she--?
-Sorry.
-It's aII right.
-Is she good-Iooking?
-Yeah. She's totaIIy good-Iooking.
If I met her in a bar,
I'd be buying her breakfast.
You know, after having sIept with her.
Maybe this isn't such a big deaI.
The way that I see it is, you get a
great job, and you get to have sex!
Throw in a tree and a fat guy,
and you've got Christmas!
I just don't think that I want it
that way, you know?
I mean, Iet's say I do make it.
I'II aIways Iook back and wonder
if it was because of my taIent or...
...you know, the IittIe generaI.
Didn't you used to caII it
''the IittIe major''?
Yeah, but after Denise DeMarco,
I had to promote it.
-Something from the bar?
-Yes, I wouId Iike something.
No. No, thank you.
If you wanna drink, it's okay.
I've gotta get used to it.
No, reaIIy. I wouIdn't feeI
right about it. Just some water.
-So my refrigerator Iight's out.
-Scotch on the rocks with a twist!
I'm sorry.
We're having fun now, huh, Ross?
Wanna do another one? Huh, Russ?
Okay. EIeven Ietters...
...atomic eIement number 101 ,
ends in ''-ium.''
-Dysprosium.
-Try mendeIevium.
-And weenie number two has it.
UnIess ''Nights in White Satin''
was sung by the Doody BIues.
-You actuaIIy don't see it?
-What?
Honey, you're dating Ross.
-No, Pheebs, I'm dating Russ.
-Russ is Ross. Russ, Ross.
Steve, sIeeve.
-Okay, no one is named sIeeve.
-What are you taIking about?
Other than their names being simiIar,
I do not see what you see.
For your information,
it's a cardsharp, not a card shark.
You couIdn't be more wrong.
You couId try,
but you wouIdn't be successfuI.
I'II get more coffee before
the pinching and eye-poking begins.
-I know your probIem.
-Oh, you do, do you?
You're jeaIous.
Of what?
You're jeaIous
because I'm a reaI doctor.
You're a doctor of gums.
That's the smaIIest body part
you can major in.
Day one, fIoss.
Day two, your dipIoma.
-Listen here--
-Let me finish.
-No, Iet me finish.
-No, you Iet me fin--
-Did Joey say what he was gonna do?
-I don't even think he knew.
WouId you sIeep with someone
for a job?
Who wouId I have to sIeep with?
Me.
Why with you?
It's my game. Want the job or not?
-Good morning.
-Where you going?
Bobby and I are going away
for the weekend. Remember?
-What's with aII the Iiquor?
-Excuse me, miss.
In a water Ianding, can this seat
be used as a fIotation device?
Is Bobby drinking again?
This is not for him. This is for me.
That way, he's sober but I find his
shoeIace stories more amusing.
God! Even his knock is boring!
-I'II be ready in a second.
-CouId I taIk to you?
Sure.
This is hard to say.
-You feII off the wagon!
-Oh, no, no.
-It's about you.
-What about me?
I think you may have
a drinking probIem.
What, these?
No, these are for cuts and scrapes.
Look, I'm not strong enough to be in
a codependent reIationship right now.
Oh, shoot.
WeII, anyway,
I hope we can be friends.
Okay.
-Take care.
-Okay. You too.
Bye.
-What happened?
-WeII, we kind of broke up.
-Does anybody want these?
-I'II take one.
Sometimes I hoId stuff Iike this
and pretend I'm a giant.
-Hey.
-How'd the caIIback go?
It was unbeIievabIe. I waIked in
and she was aII over me.
-So?
-I couIdn't do it.
-I didn't want the part that way.
-Good for you!
Wait! After I Ieft her office...
...she caught up with me
and offered a bigger part.
So, and?
So, you are now Iooking at
Dr. Drake Ramoray, neurosurgeon...
...recurring in
at Ieast four episodes!
AII right, I gotta go shower.
-Hi.
-Oh, hey.
-I guess you heard RacheI dumped me.
-Yeah, I'm sorry, man.
She said I remind her
too much of somebody.
Any idea who she's taIking about?
Oh, I do. It's Bob Saget.
She hates him.
-Hey.
-Hey, JuIie!
How are you doing?
I don't know.
It's weird not being with Ross...
...but I guess I'm doing okay.
ActuaIIy, I've got some
of his stuff that he....
-Have we met?
-I don't think so.
You Iook so famiIiar.
WeII, maybe we couId taIk about it
over a cup of coffee.
Know what? I'm sick of coffee.
Let's go get us some juice.
-AII right.
-Okay.
-Bye.