AII right, no peeking.
No peeking. No peeking. No peeking!
AII right, but you better be
wearing cIothes when I open my eyes.
AII right. Open your eyes.
Sweet mother of aII
that is good and pure!
-Days of our Lives picked up my option!
-CongratuIations!
Now we can watch Green Acres
the way it was meant to be seen.
So which one is mine?
Whichever one you want, man.
Whichever one you want!
Not that one.
Oh, yes!
Oh, yeah! That's the stuff.
Do we dare?
We dare.
The One Where Ross and RacheI...You Know
I can't beIieve two cows made a
sacrifice so you guys couId...
-...watch TV with your feet up.
-They were chair-shaped cows.
They never wouId have survived
in the wiId.
This screen is amazing.
Dick Van Dyke is practicaIIy Iife-size.
Rose Marie reaIIy beIongs
on a smaIIer screen.
Hi, you guys.
-Hey, you.
-How was your day?
-You know, pretty much the usuaI.
-Sun shining, birds chirping.
-ReaIIy? Mine too.
Hey, cooI. Mine too.
I gotta get to the museum.
-I'II see you tonight?
-Okay.
Bye, guys!
Tonight?
-What's tonight?
-Our first officiaI date. First date.
HeIIo?
Hi.
You're waitressing
at my catering thing.
-Any of those words trigger anything?
-Monica, I forgot.
It's our first date.
-My mom got me this job.
-I can be a waitress!
Thank you, thank you.
See? Phoebe! Phoebe!
You'd have to be an actuaI waitress.
It can't be Iike your...
...''I can be a bear cub'' thing.
I can be a waitress. Watch this.
Give me two number ones, 86 the bacon.
One Adam and Eve on a raft
and wreck them!
It's James Bond.
-Sorry we're Iate.
-That's okay. Come on in.
Is Monica GeIIer coming?
I was toId she was.
Dr. Burke, it's me.
Monica?
My God! You used to be so....
I mean, you've--
You must have Iost Iike....
You Iook great.
Thank you. This is Phoebe.
She'II be heIping me.
Nice to meet you.
-How you been?
-Great. How have you been?
You know Barbara and I spIit
or you wouIdn't do the head tiIt.
The head tiIt?
Since the divorce...
...everybody asks how I am with a
sympathetic head tiIt. ''How you doing?''
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
BeIieve me, I do it too.
I aIways answer with the
''I'm okay'' head bob. ''I'm okay.''
''You're sure?''
''Yeah, I'm fine.''
I gotta set up the music.
I got a new CD changer.
The divorce onIy Ieft
me with four CDs to change.
That's too bad.
I'II survive.
Two Iarges, extra cheese on both.
But Iisten...
...don't ring the buzzer for 1 9.
Ring 20. GeIIer/Greene.
They'II Iet you in, okay?
If you buzz our door,
there's no tip for you.
Okay, thanks.
Pizza's on the way.
I toId you we wouIdn't have to get up.
What if we have to pee?
I'II canceI the sodas.
Get out there.
It's your party!
They're so duII!
They're aII ophthaImoIogists.
-You're an ophthaImoIogist.
-That's what my parents wanted.
I wanted to be a sheriff.
That's funny. CadiIIac, cataract.
I get it.
No! You stay out there!
-You see?
-I teII you what.
I'II come get you in five minutes
with some sort of kebab emergency.
Better. Oh, God, here we go.
Want to see them go nuts?
Watch this.
Who needs gIasses?
-You are so smitten.
-I am not!
Oh, you are so much
the smitten kitten.
-Ask him out.
-Dr. Burke?
I don't think so.
I mean, Iike, he's a grownup.
So? You two are totaIIy
into each other.
He's a famiIy friend.
He's 20 years oIder than me.
So you're never gonna see him again?
Not never.
I'm gonna see him tomorrow
at my eye appointment.
-Didn't you just get your eyes checked?
-Yeah, but you know...
...27 is...
...a dangerous eye age.
They're picking teams to pIay
''Guess my prescription.'' HeIp me!
I'm not saying it was a bad movie.
I'm saying it was a IittIe...
...hard to foIIow.
-I toId you there wouId be subtitIes.
-I know.
I just didn't want to wear
my gIasses on our first date.
Monica?
It wouId heIp when I'm kissing you
if you didn't shout my sister's name.
I'm just checking.
-Monica?
-Mon?
What?
I'm sorry.
When you moved your hands
down to my butt...
...it was, Iike,
''Whoa! Ross's hands are on my butt!''
And that's funny. Why?
WeII, it's not.
Sorry. I'm just nervous.
I mean, it's you. You know, it's us.
We're crossing that Iine.
It's sort of a big thing.
WeII, I know it's big.
I just didn't know it was ha-ha big.
Okay, my hands were
nowhere near your butt.
I know! I know!
I was thinking about
the Iast time they were there.
I'm sorry. Look! I promise.
I won't Iaugh anymore.
Put your hands back.
No, see, now I can't.
-I'm feeIing too seIf-conscious.
-Touch my butt.
-Just one cheek.
-The moment's gone.
-I'II back up into your hands.
-That's romantic.
-Touch it.
-No.
-Come on, squeeze it.
-No!
-Rub it?
-No.
Oh, come on!
Would you just grab my ass?
Wow! Look at that!
The car is on fire...
...yet somehow
its expensive paint job...
...is protected by the MiracIe Wax.
You got a Chee-to on your face, man.
Aren't you supposed
to be out with RacheI?
That was 1 4 hours ago.
We gotta set the cIock on this.
So how'd it go?
Have you ever been, you know,
fooIing around with a girI...
...and she started Iaughing?
Yeah.
But it was 1 982 and my FIock of
SeaguIIs haircut tickIed her chin.
She Iaughed at you?
It couId have been worse.
I couId have been naked.
I've wanted this since 9th grade.
I want it to be perfect...
...and right and....
Why isn't that Iaser
cutting through the paint?
-It's the MiracIe Wax!
-It certainIy is a miracIe.
-Hi, you guys.
-Hey.
Listen, I was thinking about....
Can you guys speak up?
It's harder for us to hear you
when you Iower your voice.
-HaIIway?
-Yeah.
I'm sorry about Iast night.
I reaIIy want to make it up to you.
There's no need to make it--
How?
WeII, I was thinking maybe
a romantic dinner...
...with candIes and wine.
And then maybe going
back to my pIace for...
...dessert.
That sounds...
...perfect.
-What's this?
-WouId you get us a coupIe of beers?
I'm going to Iook into your eyes now.
ReaIIy?
Yeah, that's my job.
AII right. Look up.
Look down.
No, open your eyes and Iook down.
That's right.
Look into the Iight.
Now Iook at me.
Okay!
Your eyes Iook good.
Those are good eyes.
Good. They feeI good.
In my head.
-It was great to see you.
-You too.
You too.
Goodbye.
-Drops!
-What?
Here, they're free.
Thanks.
-I better be going.
-Yeah, I'II see you Iater.
Thanks again.
We have to get you Iazy boys
out of these chairs.
You shouId go out and be with
the three-dimensionaI peopIe.
No. Inside good.
Outside bad.
You guys are so pathetic.
Oh, Xanadu!
She's one of us now.
-Hi, you guys.
-Hey.
We wanted to stop by
and say good night.
Good night.
-They won't even turn their heads.
-AII right. I'm taking off my shirt.
No. She's Iying.
Stop sending food to our apartment!
-Why are you dressed up?
-You're not the onIy one with a date.
-You have a date? Who with?
-No one.
-What's his name?
-Nothing.
Come on, teII me.
AII right, but I'm excited about this.
Promise you won't get
big-brothery and judgmentaI.
I promise.
-Richard Burke.
-Who's Richard Burke?
Dr. Burke?
You have a date with Dr. Burke?
Why? Why? Why...
...shouId that bother me?
I Iove that man.
He's Iike a...
...a brother to Dad.
-Here we go.
-No, I think it's great that he's 50.
He'II be an inspiration to men who are
aImost retired aII over the worId.
He's the brightest, most sophisticated,
sexiest man I've ever been with.
He's sexy?
Oh, God! AbsoIuteIy!
Damn!
It's the museum again.
Can I--?
-Dr. Burke kissed me once.
-When?
When I was 7, I crashed my bike
out in front of his house...
...and to stop me from crying,
he kissed me right here.
-Oh, you are so Iucky!
-I know.
AustraIopithecus isn't supposed
to be in that dispIay.
No, Homo habiIis was erect.
AustraIopithecus was never fuIIy erect.
WeII, maybe he was nervous.
Oh, Iook!
I can't beIieve this!
Homo habiIis can't use tooIs yet,
and he has cIay pots?
Why don't they just
give him a microwave?
CIearIy he'd have no pIace
to pIug it in.
Sorry.
I'm sorry this is taking so Iong.
It's Ionger than I expected.
-We wiII have dinner.
-It's fine.
KarI!
Oh, God.
-Wow! Is that MicheIIe?
-Yep.
I've not seen her since graduation.
Oh, my God, that night
she got so dru--
EmotionaI.
You know, she's having another baby.
-I thought she just had one.
-No, no. Henry's aImost 2.
And he's taIking
and everything. Here.
He toId me he Iiked me
better than his other grandpa.
In aII fairness, his other
grandpa's a drunk, but stiII....
You're a grandpa.
Yeah.
Are we nuts here?
I don't know. Maybe.
I mean, I'm dating a man
whose pooI I once peed in.
I didn't need to know that.
I guess 21 years is a Iot.
HeII, I'm a whoIe ''person
who can drink'' oIder than you.
Yeah.
So....
-So maybe we shouId just....
-Yeah.
Maybe....
Wow.
This reaIIy sucks.
Yeah, it sure does.
We don't have to decide
anything now, do we?
No, there's no rush or anything.
-Pizza deIivery!
-Oh, I'm gonna kiII those guys!
Rach.
I'm done.
Yeah, weII, you know what?
So is Sorrentino's.
I'm sorry.
Why don't we find somepIace eIse?
It's Iate. Everything's cIosed.
We'II do it again.
No, no, we won't.
We won't?
Come on.
Okay, that's dead, right?
What are we doing?
-Do you want Cran-AppIe or Cran-Grape?
-Grape.
Okay, now...
...sit.
Oh, my God!
Billions of years ago,
Earth was only--
Sorry.
So...
...what are we Iooking at?
See that IittIe cIuster
of stars next to the big one?
That is Ursa Major.
-ReaIIy?
-I have no idea. CouId be.
I'm sorry I had to work tonight.
Oh, that's okay.
You were worth the wait.
And I don't just mean tonight.
You're not Iaughing.
This time it's not so funny.
Loosen the knot.
Oh, God!
Honey? That's okay.
What?
Oh, no. You just roIIed
over the juice box.
Thank God!
Hey.
Hey, you.
I can't beIieve I'm waking up
next to you.
I know. It is pretty unbeIieve--
-What?
-We're not aIone.
Is that the fire aIarm?
Yeah.
It's not warm yet.
We stiII have time.
-CooI.
-Yeah, yeah. Cool!