-Hey, Dad. What are you doing here?
-I just stopped by your boyfriend's.
-And?
-I was gonna punch him in the nose.
But he had the game on,
so we started watching.
At haIftime,
I was gonna give him what for.
-But he offered me a beer. Know what?
-What?
He's got it on tap!
In his apartment. The thing is buiIt
into his bar. It's unbeIievabIe!
Dad, did you taIk about me?
Oh, right. WeII, actuaIIy,
we never got to you.
Look, you're a big girI. I just hope
you know what you're doing.
I do.
-You're wearing the tie I got you!
-Yeah.
So where did you get the hat?
I don't know.
So, what do you think?
Casa de Joey.
-I decorated it myseIf.
-Get out!
Wow, Joey, this is....
-Art.
-Art it is.
Check this out.
Is it a coffee tabIe?
Is it a panther?
There's no need to decide.
Hey, nice piIIow.
So now teII me,
is this genuine Muppet skin?
Hey, exceIIent water tabIe thing.
Thanks. I Iove this. But you
know what? It makes me want to pee.
Yeah, me too.
I think that's the chaIIenge.
How come ChandIer didn't come?
It's because he had
a thing with the thing.
Right. I got it.
So why don't you show us
the rest of your casa?
The best part! Come on.
Nice toiIet.
No. Behind it.
-You have a phone in here?
-That's right. I have a phone...
...in here.
-Promise me something.
-Yeah?
Never caII me from that phone.
The One Where Eddie Moves In
Okay, here we go.
Sorry, they were aII out of appIe pie.
Someone just got the Iast piece.
Oh, my God!
You won't beIieve this!
I have just been discovered.
Now wait a minute. I cIaimed you
in the name of France four years ago.
Anyway.
Don't freak out and say how
great this is untiI I'm done.
I met this producer
of this record company...
...who said I have
a fresh, offbeat sound...
...and she wants to do
a demo of ''SmeIIy Cat.''
I toId you not to do that yet.
And she wants to do a video.
I'm not done yet, okay?
God!
If that goes weII, they may
even want to make an aIbum.
I'm done now.
If you care for me,
get the pie out of the man's hood.
-Get the what?
-There's a pie in the hood. Go!
-What are you doing?
-I'm sorry. My pie was in your hood.
I have to get the coffee...
...out of that guy's pants and I'II
be back in the hospitaI by 7.
Damn it, Ross!
Get your butt out of the bathroom!
CaIm down. I'm bIow-drying.
BIow-drying what?
You have no hair.
-What's going on?
-He's been in there for an hour.
It's Iike I Iive with him again.
He's here when I sIeep, wake up
and when I want to shower.
It's Iike I'm 1 6 again.
WeII, you're not 1 6.
You're both aduIts now.
Get out, you doofus!
Or, you know,
he's rubber and you're gIue.
AII yours.
I hope you cIeaned your hair
out of the drain.
-Shut up!
-Shut up.
Cut it out!
I've never wanted you more.
Hello?
-Louie? Where's Howard?
-He went home.
He said he might stop up.
He said to tell you
he wasn't feeling so good.
Hey, what time do you get off?
I'm not feeling too good either.
So, what do you say, boys?
ShouId I caII him?
You know what they say:
Ask your sIippers a question...
...you're going crazy.
Freaking art!
-HeIIo.
-Hey.
Hey!
Sorry I didn't make it over there.
That's okay.
You had a thing.
-I hear the pIace Iooks great.
-Forget about it. I'm having a baII!
-How's the apartment doing?
-It's terrific.
I mean, it's a reguIar space...
...fest!
WeII, great.
Yeah, I just wanted
to caII and say hey.
WeII, okay.
-Was that the oven timer?
-That's right, my friend.
-It's time for....
-Baywatch!
-You beIieve Stephanie has skin cancer?
-I can't beIieve she's Iieutenant!
That's because you Iove
Yasmine BIeeth.
How couId anyone not Iove
Yasmine BIeeth?
They're running!
See, this is the briIIiance
of the show.
I say aIways keep them running.
AII the time running!
Run!
Run, Yasmine! Run Iike the wind!
-But you wanted to Iive by yourseIf.
-I did. I thought it'd be great.
I figured I'd have time aIone
with my thoughts.
It turns out I don't have
as many thoughts as you'd think.
Why don't you taIk to ChandIer
and move back?
You reaIIy think he'd take me?
We had a good taIk Iast night...
-...but when I moved, I hurt him bad.
-He wouId definiteIy want you back.
I'm teIIing you,
no way he's moving back.
But we had one of the greatest
taIks we ever had Iast night.
I mean, it was--
It was Iike when we first
Iived together.
I know you don't want
to hear this now...
...but we've seen him
in his new pIace. And he's happy.
He's decorated.
ChandIer, he has moved on, okay?
You have to, too.
You have to accept the fact
that you're just friends now.
You're not...
...roommates anymore.
Okay, you ready to try one?
Okay.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
Smelly, smelly
Really bad smelling smelly cat
Whoa! Oh, my God!
I mean, Iike, who was that?
They're your backup singers.
Behind you, hon.
I thought they were just watching me.
Like at an aquarium, you know?
-They're so good. You're so good!
-AIrighty!
Okay, now that everyone knows
everyone, Iet's try it again.
From the top.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
Smelly, smelly, smelly, really bad
Smelling smelly cat. It's not your--
Okay, sorry.
I'm just not getting...
...that everyone gets how smeIIy
this cat actuaIIy is.
If we couId taIk about this. I need
to feeI that you care about the cat.
We can taIk, but this costs
$100 a minute to be in here.
Okay, so the cat stinks,
but you Iove it. Let's go.
No, there is no way
he was a veIociraptor.
Look at the craniaI ridge.
If Dino was a veIociraptor,
he wouId have eaten the FIintstones.
-Were you taking a nap?
-I was.
Can you hoId on?
That's the other Iine.
HeIIo?
Yeah, she's here,
but can she caII you back?
Okay, thanks.
-CaII Joanna.
-She Ieave a number?
Did you see me write one down?
I don't have her number, butt-munch.
-She'II caII back. Don't be a baby.
-You're the baby.
-Off my back.
-Get out of my face.
Wait, hoId on, Tony. HoId on.
HeIIo?
Hi.
Yeah, No. she's right here. HoId on.
Tony, can I caII you back?
That's my sister's boyfriend.
-Give me that.
-Okay.
Sweetie, before I forget, did I
Ieave my diaphragm at your pIace?
Hi, Mom.
So how's the paIace?
Funny you shouId mention that,
because I was thinking--
What's with the boxes?
ActuaIIy, I have some news.
Is Joey gonna pick up
his moose hat or shouId I toss it?
Why don't you ask him yourseIf?
This is my roommate, Eddie.
-Nice to meet you.
-Likewise.
I'II take that.
It's what I came for.
So this is new.
Where did you two meet?
At the supermarket
in the ethnic food section.
I heIped him pick a chorizo.
We got to taIking. He needed
a pIace and I had a spare room.
Oh, now it's a spare room?
WeII, yeah.
In that it's not being used...
...and I have it to spare.
WeII, I got what I came for.
I'II see you guys.
Hey, Joe.
When'd you start using
moose in your hair?
Is this guy great or what?
Yeah, yeah, he is.
-He has a new roommate? Who is he?
-Eddie. He just met him.
It'II never Iast.
He's just a rebound roommate.
Check it out! Check it out!
It's ''SmeIIy Cat,'' the video!
Now, I haven't seen it yet,
so if you don't Iike it...
...so what?
None of you ever made a video.
Get out of here, cat! You stink!
-Smoking!
-Look at me!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
It's not your fault
Smelly, smelly, really bad smelling
Smelly cat, it's not your fault
Smelly cat, smelly cat
-Oh, my God!
-I know.
I sound amazing!
They won't take you to the vet
You're obviously not their favorite pet
Smelly cat, smelly cat
It's not your fault
Oh, no
I've never heard myseIf sing before.
I mean, except in my own head.
This is so cooI!
Now I can hear what you hear!
Pretty different, huh?
I am sorry,
but I'm incredibIy taIented!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
It's not your fault
-Joey, what's going on, man?
-Eddie.
-Morning.
I just came by to pick up my maiI.
-Where's the maiI?
-Over on the tabIe.
It's not on this tabIe anymore?
No. Eddie Iikes to keep it over there.
AII right, here you go, my friend.
Eggs à Ia Eddie.
That's great.
What?
I thought you Iiked eggs with bread
with the hoIe in the middIe à Ia me!
I do, but Eddie makes them this way.
They're darn good.
-Wanna try some?
-No, thanks.
AII right. WeII, you guys,
I'm out of here.
-See you, paIs.
-See you.
-How are you two getting aIong?
-I couIdn't be happier.
Great. I'm happy for you.
AII right, that's it!
He just comes in here,
Mr. Johnny New Eggs, with his--
His moving the maiI
and his, ''See you, paIs.''
There's no juice!
There's no juice for the peopIe
who need the juice. I need the juice!
There's another carton
right over there.
This isn't about juice anymore,
aII right?
-AII right. What's it about?
-Eggs!
Whose eggs do you Iike better,
his or mine?
-I Iike both eggs equaIIy!
-Come on!
Nobody Iikes two eggs equaIIy!
Which one do you Iike better?
What's the difference?
Your eggs aren't here anymore!
You took your eggs and you Ieft!
Did you expect me
to never find new eggs?
Maybe this isn't about the eggs.
Maybe this is about
the chicken that Iaid them.
What chicken?
There's no chicken.
I can't taIk to you!
-I want Entertainment Tonight.
-We're watching...
...Predators of the Serengeti.
-WouId you guys stop?!
-It's my TV!
-Quit it!
-Bite me!
Oh, my God!
Monica keeps changing the channeI.
Great. Why don't you teII Mommy on me?
Now I'm Mommy in this IittIe pIay?
Look, I refuse to get sucked into this
weird IittIe GeIIer dimension thing!
I'm gonna take a nice Iong,
hot bubbIe bath...
...because you kids
are driving me crazy!
-What do we do about this?
-Tape Entertainment Tonight.
Not that! This! Us!
Oh, my God, Ross....
You're just....
Since you've been here,
you drive....
Mon, you've gone uItrasonic
again, aII right?
I just can't stand you being here...
...aII the time!
Why? Why can't you stand me
being here? We're just having fun.
Fun? You think this is fun?
We were fooIing around,
Iike when we were kids.
I hated you when we were kids!
-You hated me when we were kids?
-I hated you. I Ioved you...
...in a you're-my-brother-so-I-have-to
way, but basicaIIy I hated your guts.
-Why did you hate me?
-Because you were mean to me...
...and you teased me
and you aIways got your way.
And that wasn't fun for you?
I can't beIieve you hated me.
But now I Iove you.
-And not just because I have to.
-ReaIIy?
Yeah.
You're just gonna have to stop
pissing me off.
I can do that.
Then I won't have to kiII you.
So you wanna watch
Entertainment Tonight?
Thanks.
Tonight, America's sport's
magazine moves to--
-You know what?
-What?
If you reaIIy wanna watch
that Serengeti thing, we can.
Okay.
Listen, you are not going
to beIieve this...
...but that is not me
singing on the video.
How did you find out?
The record company sent a paper
for me to sign saying it's okay...
...for someone eIse to sing for me.
That was a cIue.
What wiII you do?
-I can't work with peopIe who do this.
-Sure.
-I mean, this poor woman.
-What woman?
The voice woman.
She has a great voice,
but she doesn't have a video.
-Okay, Pheebs, what about you?
-I have a video. Pay attention.
This voice woman, she's so taIented.
But according to the producer peopIe,
she doesn't have the right Iook.
She's Iike one of those
animaIs at the pound...
...who nobody wants
because they're not pretty enough.
Or some oId dog
who's kind of stinky and--
Oh, my God! She's ''SmeIIy Cat''!
That song has so many IeveIs.
Hey, Eddie.
You wanna pIay some foosbaII?
No, thanks, man.
I'm not reaIIy into sports.
Yeah, okay. AII right.
Doesn't matter.
Time for Baywatch!
You Iike that show?
You don't Iike that show?
It's just pretty peopIe
running around on the beach.
That's the briIIiance of it.
The pretty peopIe.
And the running.
I'm gonna go read in my room
for a IittIe whiIe.
Okay, man.
I'm gonna start off with a IittIe
song caIIed ''SmeIIy Cat.''
Oh, for those of you who are
wondering, this is my reaI voice.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
Everybody!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
It's not your fault
-Monica!
-They won't take you to the vet
ChandIer!
You're obviously not
their favorite pet
-Joey!
-You may not be a bed of roses
-RacheI!
-You're no friend to those with noses
Ross, those are
the onIy Iines we have. Sorry.
Back to the chorus everybody!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you
It's not your fault
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you
It's not your fault