Man, I sure miss JuIie.
Spanish midgets.
Spanish midgets wrestIing...
...JuIie!
Okay, I see how you got there.
You ever figure out
what that thing's for?
I'm trying to screen.
If I answer the phone,
peopIe wiII think I have no Iife.
My God!
Rodrigo is never pinned!
After the beep,
you know what to do.
Hello. I'm looking for Bob.
It's Jade.
If this is still your number....
I was thinking about how great it was.
I know it's been three years...
...but I was hoping
we could hook up again.
I barely had the nerve
to call...
-...so you know what I did?.
-What?
I got a little drunk...
...and naked.
Bob here!
The One With Five Steaks And An EggpIant
So, what have you been up to?
Oh, you know, the usual.
Teaching aerobics...
...partying way too much.
And in case you wondered...
...those are my legs on
the new James Bond poster.
Can you hoId on?
I have another caII.
-I Iove her!
-I know.
-I'm back.
-So are we gonna get together?
AbsoIuteIy.
How about tomorrow afternoon?
Do you know CentraI Perk?
5-ish?
-Great. I'll see you then.
-Okay.
Okay.
Having a phone has finaIIy paid off.
You do a good Bob impression...
...but when she sees you...
...she may reaIize that,
hey, you're not Bob.
You see Tattoo....
Jade's fantasy is to rekindIe
the Iove she had with Bob.
My fantasy is that you
taIk Iike a normaI person.
I hope when
he doesn't show...
...she'II seek comfort in the open arms
of the wry stranger at the next tabIe.
Oh, my God.
You are pure eviI.
Okay, pure eviI...
...horny and aIone.
I've done this.
Yeah, everybody's here.
Say hi to JuIie in New Mexico!
Hi, JuIie!
Hi, JuIie. So what.
WhiIe Ross is on the phone...
...everybody owes me
62 bucks for his birthday.
Is there any chance that
you're rounding up from...
...you know, from Iike 20?
We got the gift,
the concert and the cake.
Do we need a cake?
I know it's a IittIe steep.
But it's Ross.
-It's Ross.
-Right.
-I know.
-AII right.
I'II see you guys Iater.
I gotta go do a thing.
Okay, I'II caII you Iater.
You're not going through with this,
are you?
You know, I think I might just.
So, what are you guys
doing for dinner tonight?
WeII, I gotta start
saving up for Ross' birthday.
I guess I'II stay home
and eat dust bunnies.
You beIieve how much this costs?
Do you guys ever
get the feeIing that...
...ChandIer and those guys don't get
that we don't make that much money?
-Yes.
-ReaIIy?
They say,
Iet's go here, Iet's go there.
Like we can afford to go
here and there.
Yes, and we aIways have to go
somepIace nice, you know? God.
And we can't say anything about it,
because this is a birthday for Ross.
-For Ross.
-Oh, my God!
-Hi.
Okay, I'm at work...
...just an ordinary day,
chop, chop, sauté, sauté.
The manager caIIs me into his office.
They fired the Iunch chef.
Guess who got it?
If it's not you,
this is a horribIe story.
FortunateIy, it is me.
And they made me head of purchasing!
That's so cooI!
Anyway, I think we
shouId go out and ceIebrate.
You know, somepIace nice.
SomepIace nice.
How much you think
I can get for my kidney?
-You can't do this.
-Come on.
I can't get a girI Iike her with
conventionaI methods.
It doesn't matter.
She wanted to caII Bob.
Bob couId be
who she was meant to be with.
You may be destroying
a chance for happiness.
We don't know Bob.
Okay, we know me. We Iike me.
PIease Iet me be happy.
Go over there
and teII that woman the truth.
AII right.
Go.
-Hi.
Listen, I have to....
I have to confess something.
Yes?
Whoever stood you up is a jerk.
-How did you--?
-I don't know.
I just had this weird sense. But
that's me, I'm weird and sensitive.
Tissue?
Thanks.
No, you keep the pack.
I'm aII cried out today.
Here is to my sister,
the newIy appointed head Iunch chef.
AIso in charge of purchasing.
Head Iunch chef,
in charge of purchasing--
Who has her own IittIe desk
when RoIand's not there.
Lunch chef, purchasing, own desk
when RoIand's not there...
-...here's to my--
-Wait! And I got a beeper!
-CooI.
-Let's see.
That's fine, I'II just wait.
Sorry.
Monica!
Are we ready to order?
We haven't even Iooked.
When you do, Iet me know.
I'II be over there
on the edge of my seat.
Look at these prices!
Yeah, these are pretty cha-ching.
I know. What are these,
famous chickens?
-Sorry I'm Iate. CongratuIations.
-Thanks.
I'm not sorry. How incredibIe
was my afternoon with Jade?
Pretty incredibIe, according to
the message on my machine.
Why is this woman Ieaving a message
for you on my machine?
I toId her my number was yours.
I couIdn't say it was mine...
...because she thinks
my number is Bob's number.
TeII me again.
What do I do when Mr. Roper caIIs?
Do I dare ask?
I'II start with carpaccio,
then the griIIed prawns.
Sounds great, same for me.
-And for the gentIeman?
-I'II have the Thai pizza.
But if I get it without the nuts
and Ieeks and stuff, is it cheaper?
You'd think, wouIdn't you?
-Miss.
-Okay, I wiII have the side saIad.
And what wouId that
be on the side of?
I don't know. Why don't you just put
it right here next to my water.
And for you?
I'm gonna have a cup
of the cucumber soup and....
Take care.
-I wiII have the Cajun catfish.
-Anything eIse?
Yes, how about a verse of
''KiIIing Me SoftIy''?
You're gonna sneeze
in my fish, aren't you?
Does anybody eIse feeI Iike
they just gave birth to an aIien?
No!
PIus tip, divided by six....
And everyone owes 28 bucks.
Everyone?
You're right, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
-Monica's night. She shouIdn't pay.
-Thank you.
So five of us is $33.50 apiece.
No. No way.
Sorry, not gonna happen.
Prom night fIashback.
Sorry, I'm happy you got promoted...
...but coId cucumber mush
for 30-something bucks? No!
RacheI just had that IittIe saIad and
Joey with a teeny pizza! It's just....
Okay, Pheebs.
How about we'II each pay for
what we had? It's no big deaI.
Not for you.
AII right, what's going on?
I don't wanna get into this right now.
It'II make everybody uncomfortabIe.
You can teII us.
Yeah, heIIo? It's us. We'II be fine.
Yeah.
Okay, we three...
...feeI Iike that sometimes
you guys don't get that....
We don't have
as much money as you.
-Okay.
-I hear you.
We can taIk about that.
WeII, then...
-...Iet's.
-Fine.
I guess I just never think
of money as an issue.
-Because you have it.
-Good point.
So how come you guys
haven't taIked about this before?
It's aIways something.
Like Monica's new job...
...or the whoIe Ross' birthday hoopIa.
I don't want my birthday to be
the source of any kind of negative....
There's gonna be a hoopIa?
BasicaIIy there's the thing,
and then the stuff after the thing--
If you feeI better, we'II forget
the thing and we'II just do the gift.
-Gift? The thing's not the gift?
-We wouId see Hootie and the BIowfish.
Hootie and the--
I can catch them on the radio.
No. Now I feeI bad.
You wanna go to the concert.
No, Iook. It's my birthday...
...and the important thing
is that we're together.
-AII of us.
-Not at the concert.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
-Yeah.
So the EboIa virus.
That's gotta suck, huh?
Monica, what's in the bag?
I don't know. Let's take a Iook.
It's Iike a skit.
Why, it's dinner for six. Five steaks
and an eggpIant for Phoebe.
We switched meat suppIiers.
They gave me steaks as a thank-you.
But wait, there's more.
ChandIer, what is in that enveIope?
By the way, this didn't
seem so dorky out in the haII.
Why, it's six tickets to
Hootie and the BIowfish!
The BIowfish!
It's on us. So don't worry.
This is our treat.
So, thank you.
CouId you be Iess enthused?
Look, it's a nice gesture. It is.
But it just feeIs Iike....
Like?
-Charity.
-Charity?
We're just trying to do a nice thing.
You have to understand, your
nice thing makes us feeI this big.
ActuaIIy, it makes us feeI that big.
I don't understand.
We can't win.
If you aII feeI this big, maybe that's
not our fauIt, it's just how you feeI.
Now you're teIIing us how we feeI.
We shouIdn't taIk about this.
I'm gonna pass on the concert.
Just not in a Hootie pIace right now.
-Me neither!
-Me too!
Guys, we bought the tickets.
Then you'II have extra seats
for aII your tiaras and stuff.
Why did you Iook at me
when you said that?
So I guess now we can't go.
Do what you want. Do we aIways
have to do everything together?
You know what? You're right.
Fine!
AII right.
We're gonna go.
It's not for another six hours.
We're gonna go then.
-ChandIer.
-Yeah.
-Jesus! Are you ready?
-Yes.
Just Iet me grab my jacket
and teII you I had sex today.
What? You had sex today?
It sounds even cooIer
when somebody eIse says it.
I was awesome. She was biting her Iip
to stop from screaming.
Wow.
I know it's been a whiIe,
but I took that as a good sign.
-StiII doing the screening?
-I had sex today.
I never have to
answer that phone again.
After the beep,
you know what to do.
Bob, it's Jade.
I wanted to tell you I was hurt
when you didn't show up.
And just so you know,
I ended up meeting a guy.
-Bob here.
-Oh, hi.
So you met someone, huh?
Yes, I did.
In fact, I had sex
with him two hours ago.
So how was he?
Eh.
Eh?
Bob, he was nothing compared to you.
I bit my lip to keep from
screaming your name.
WeII, that makes me feeI so good.
It was just so awkward and bumpy.
Maybe he had some kind of new,
cooI styIe you're not famiIiar with.
Maybe get used to it.
There wasn't much time to get
used to it, if you know what I mean.
I'm not gonna be abIe to enjoy this.
Yeah, I know. It's my birthday.
We aII shouId be here.
So Iet's go.
Maybe we shouId stay for one song.
It wouId be rude to them
for us to Ieave.
The guys are probabIy
having a great time.
-Come on, you guys. One more time.
-Okay.
-One.
-No.
-That was amazing!
-ExceIIent!
-I can't beIieve the guys missed it!
-What guys? Yeah.
Excuse me.
Aren't you Monica GeIIer?
-Do I know you?
-You babysat me!
Oh, my God! LittIe Stevie Fisher?
How have you been?
Good. I'm a Iawyer now.
You can't be a Iawyer.
You're 8.
Nice to see you.
I gotta run backstage.
-Backstage?
-My firm represents the band.
-Ross.
-ChandIer.
-You wanna meet the group?
-Yeah!
Come on.
Are you one of the ones
that fooIed around with my dad?
Hey, you guys!
-Happy birthday!
-Thank you.
How was your night Iast night?
It pretty much sucked.
How was yours?
Ours sucked too. But I ran into
Stevie Fisher. Remember him?
Oh, yeah! I used to babysit him.
How's his dad?
Good.
Aside from that,
the evening was a bust.
Yeah, we reaIIy missed you guys.
Yeah, we were just saying,
this whoIe thing is so stupid.
We just have to reaIIy not Iet stuff
Iike this about money, get Iike--
Is that a hickey?
No, I just....
I feII down.
On someone's Iips?
-Where'd you get the hickey?
-You know, a party or--
-What party?
-It wasn't a party so much as...
...a gathering of peopIe.
With food and music and the band.
You partied with
Hootie and the BIowfish?
Yes. ApparentIy,
Stevie and Hootie are Iike this:
Who gave you that hickey?
That wouId be the work of a BIowfish.
I can't beIieve it!
I can't beIieve this!
We're just sitting at home,
trying to guess Joey's fingers...
...and you guys are out Iike partying
and having fun and aII:
''Hey, BIowfish, suck on my neck!''
Don't bIame us.
You couId've been there.
What? As part of your
poor friends outreach program?
Great, it's work.
I don't know what to say.
Sorry we make more than you.
We're not gonna feeI guiIty.
We work hard.
And we don't work hard?
It's Monica. You paged?
It's just that we Iike doing stuff
that costs a IittIe more.
-And you feeI Iike we hoId you back.
-Yes!
No!
Leon, wait. Guys!
I don't understand. The steaks were
a gift from the meat vendor.
That was not a kickback.
I'II just repIace them...
...and we can forget the whoIe thing.
What corporate poIicy?
No--
Yeah.
Okay.
I just got fired.
-Here's your check. That'II be $4.1 2.
-Let me get that.
You got 5 bucks?
Here comes the beep.
You know what to do.
Hi, it's me.
Listen, Bob.
I'm probably way out of line here.
It's been three years,
and you're probably seeing someone...
...but if we could have one night,
for old times' sake....
One hot, steamy, wild night....